<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network/</link><description>Recent content in Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:09:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kodak Alaris unveils new wireless scanners with network connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</guid><description>Kodak Alaris&amp;rsquo; latest desktop scanners, the Kodak ScanMate i1150WN and Kodak i1190WN, offer wireless and network connectivity and are compatible with mobile apps. These features support bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policies and workplace mobility.
Source: Kodak Alaris. The Kodak ScanMate i1150WN.
The i1150WN and i1190WN scanners can connect through an office network or Wi-Fi, making them adaptable to various office settings. Standard drivers (TWAIN, ISIS) allow integration with new and existing business applications, streamlining the capture process and simplifying software installation.</description></item><item><title>HPE has reduced the entry threshold for its storage portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</guid><description>Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) recently improved its entry storage products to help budget-conscious customers leverage their data and speed up applications. These new HPE MSA Storage options deliver the most budget-friendly dual-controller hybrid flash array from a major vendor while the new HPE StoreEasy 1650 Expanded makes storing large amounts of information more economical.
Being able to quickly and effectively use information is crucial for success. &amp;ldquo;Agility and speed are critical for staying competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s economy, no matter the business size,&amp;rdquo; said Manish Goel, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Storage at HPE.</description></item><item><title>Tips from Akamai for optimizing app engagement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</guid><description>A report from Akamai highlights that 95% of gamers quit playing a game within the first month. The company states that slow loading times are a major factor, causing 40% of players to abandon games. Additionally, 20% of gamers expect instant page loads.
To enhance user retention, Akamai suggests strategies applicable to any app:
Anticipate Large-Scale Success: Be prepared for a global player base. Utilize a robust content delivery network to handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region.</description></item><item><title>I Want Fiber But Not Construction Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has become the top choice for business private lines and internet connections. It offers a practically unlimited capacity with minimal latency, packet loss, and jitter. Prices are now more competitive than before, provided you don&amp;rsquo;t encounter high construction costs.
Why Fiber Can Involve Construction Expenses
Businesses accustomed to T1 lines, Ethernet over Copper, or business cable might be surprised by quotes that include substantial construction costs for installing a fiber line.</description></item><item><title>Telecom and Network Domain Names For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong domain name is crucial for any online business. The best names reflect your business, are easy to remember for offline use, and are pronounceable. Owning your own domain provides a much stronger online identity compared to generic alternatives. This ownership gives you full control over your website, email, and branding.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in business telecom for almost 15 years and acquired many domain names related to that industry.</description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable.</description></item><item><title>The first router is introduced by Synology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</guid><description>Source: Synology. The Synology Router RT1900ac.
Synology has introduced its first router, the Synology Router RT1900ac. This router allows users to connect an external storage device, effectively creating a personal cloud storage solution.
The router boasts combined transfer speeds of up to 1,900 Mbps and utilizes beamforming technology to optimize Wi-Fi signals for individual devices. A mobile app provides users with control over the router&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time.</description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds.</description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>Where Have All The IPs Gone?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-have-all-the-ips-gone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-have-all-the-ips-gone/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Where have all the IPs gone? Gone to users every one.&amp;rdquo;
- apologies to Pete Seeger
Have you heard? The internet is full. It&amp;rsquo;s expected to reach its limit in the next few years. This means no new users, websites, or online services. It&amp;rsquo;s like a club that&amp;rsquo;s reached capacity; they&amp;rsquo;ll have to turn people away at the door. &amp;ldquo;Here, take a pager, and we&amp;rsquo;ll call you when it&amp;rsquo;s your turn.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth Gets Incrementally Finer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet service has been very beneficial for businesses of all sizes. It not only keeps LAN-WAN-LAN connections using the Ethernet protocol, but lease prices are also typically much lower per Mbps than older services like T-Carrier and SONET. But wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have the ideal line speed without settling for a service that&amp;rsquo;s too small or paying too much for unnecessary bandwidth?
Fortunately, XO Communications, a leading Metro Ethernet WAN service provider, now offers a wide range of bandwidth options for businesses with on-net fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future.</description></item><item><title>StarHub, offering the quickest 3G and 4G network in Singapore, introduces the World's Fastest Band</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</guid><description>StarHub, a telecommunications company, has unveiled the &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Fastest Band&amp;rdquo; to celebrate its recognition in OpenSignal&amp;rsquo;s Speed Awards 2018 for having Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fastest 4G and 3G speeds. OpenSignal, a global wireless coverage mapping specialist, awarded StarHub based on network quality. StarHub&amp;rsquo;s VP of Segment &amp;amp; Marketing, Donovan Kik, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to network quality and customer satisfaction. He stated their dedication to meeting customer needs and expectations despite achieving this recognition.</description></item><item><title>CA Technologies reports that CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has been successful in its first 100 days</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:46:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</guid><description>CA Technologies, a provider of IT management solutions for securing and managing complex IT environments, has released a new version of its freemium product, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap. This solution helps businesses support agile business services.
Since its release 100 days ago, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has seen 5,000 downloads from SMBs, Fortune 1000 companies, and IT service providers across 147 countries. The full-featured version of CA Nimsoft Monitor shares the same codebase and proactively monitors servers, networks, storage, databases, and applications.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs SONET Throw Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SONET and Carrier Ethernet, two contenders for the top spot in high-speed business bandwidth.
SONET, or Synchronous Optical NETwork, is a fiber optic transmission system using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). Primarily used by telephone companies to boost their digital trunk capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s known for its redundant data rings over fiber optic cables, which create an automatic failover mechanism in case of a network disruption. While perfect for carrier-grade digitized phone calls, SONET can also handle packetized data including voice, video, and standard T1 or T3 lines.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Fiber Optic WAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</guid><description>As your company grows, you might find that your internet connection, cloud services, and connections between offices are slowing down. It might be time to upgrade your bandwidth before things get sluggish. But what should you get? More of what you already have or something new?
Outdated Connections Are Holding You Back When your business was starting out, networking was mostly about connecting computers and printers in the same office, with a basic connection to the outside world.</description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations.</description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date.</description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location.</description></item><item><title>Instagram outperformed Facebook during the Rio 2016 Olympics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</guid><description>Source: ComScore. Social network interactions between Facebook and Instagram for July 2016 around the Olympic games, which ran from 5 to 21 August.
ComScore, a media measurement company, found that Instagram was the top platform for engagement during the 2016 Rio Olympics, even though Facebook, its parent company, was primarily used for pre-event official content sharing.
In June, the UK ranked third globally in unique visitors to the official Rio Olympics website (RIO2016.</description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U.</description></item></channel></rss>