<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>3G Cellular on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3g-cellular/</link><description>Recent content in 3G Cellular on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3g-cellular/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both.</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks.</description></item></channel></rss>