<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Colocation Centers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation-centers/</link><description>Recent content in Colocation Centers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation-centers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Service Providers Colocate With Customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</guid><description>A new trend is emerging, and it&amp;rsquo;s not just about companies moving their data to the cloud. Now, cloud service providers are moving into the same facilities as their customers.
Why is this happening? Companies are realizing that running applications on distant servers can&amp;rsquo;t match the speed of having them on-site. While this can be addressed by investing in high-bandwidth, low-latency connections, it&amp;rsquo;s often more cost-effective to simply be in the same location as your provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telx Minimizes Latency WIth Colocation Near Carriers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</guid><description>For applications sensitive to delays, proximity to service providers is crucial. Regardless of your equipment&amp;rsquo;s speed, signal propagation sets the minimum latency. This speed is about a millisecond per 186 miles in a vacuum and increases with copper or fiber cables, further compounded by routers and switches. Being directly connected to your provider minimizes this distance. Telx offers a solution.
Telx specializes in colocation, connecting customers and providers physically. With 15 strategically located centers in 9 states, they offer proximity to media hubs, cable landings, fiber paths, and exchanges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Burstable Bandwidth Offers Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</guid><description>Most businesses purchase dedicated WAN bandwidth to support their voice and data services. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a more cost-effective option called burstable bandwidth.
Take business broadband service as an example. A dedicated DS3 connection provides a constant 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads. This full capacity is always available, whether you&amp;rsquo;re sending a large file or backing up data. When not fully utilized, the line remains idle.
The recent drop in DS3 prices has made it a common choice for medium to large businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>