<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Handset on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/handset/</link><description>Recent content in Handset on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/handset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces the 'Butterfly' smartphone in specific Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 to the Japanese market through KDDI. This phone, also known as the HTC Butterfly 2, will be available from various carriers, including Chunghwa Telecom in Taiwan, CSL in Hong Kong, and others in South Asia.
Source: HTC.
The new HTC Butterfly 2 simplifies daily tasks with features like HTC Sense 6, an HTC Duo Camera, and the Motion Launch sensor.
Using au carrier aggregation*, the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 offers download speeds up to 150Mbps and supports WiMAX2+.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 210, an entry-level dual SIM phone, is priced at less than S$160</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</guid><description>HTC will launch its budget-friendly smartphone, the HTC Desire 210, in Singapore on Wednesday, September 3, 2014. The phone will be sold through various retailers in two colors: Stealth Black and Polar White. A notable feature of the Desire 210 is its dual SIM card support, allowing users to manage personal and work profiles easily from a single device.
Source: HTC.
“The HTC Desire 210 brings impressive technology and design to the entry-level smartphone market,” stated Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia.</description></item><item><title>Phones become unresponsive due to Android vulnerability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</guid><description>Trend Micro has identified a weakness in the Android operating system that can cause a phone to seem non-functional. Affected phones exhibit symptoms like no ringing or notification sounds, an inability to make calls, and an unresponsive screen. Additionally, locked phones cannot be unlocked.
This vulnerability affects Android versions from 4.3 (Jelly Bean) to 5.1.1 (Lollipop), encompassing over half of all Android devices currently in use. Despite being reported to the Android Engineering Team in late May, no official fix has been released through the Android Open Source Project (AOSP).</description></item><item><title>A new budget-friendly Lumia is about to be released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The Lumia 430.
Microsoft has released the Lumia 430 Dual SIM, its most budget-friendly Lumia smartphone that can be upgraded to Windows 10*. Priced at approximately S$119, the Lumia 430 joins Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s affordable smartphone lineup alongside the Lumia 435, which features Lumia Camera.
Equipped with Windows Phone 8.1, a Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a 1.2GHz dual-core CPU, and pre-installed Microsoft Office, Skype, and OneDrive, the Lumia 430 Dual SIM enables users to be productive at work, enjoy entertainment, and stay connected while on the move.</description></item><item><title>The HTC One E9+ dual sim will be available in Singapore starting August 29th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-one-e9-dual-sim-will-be-available-in-singapore-starting-august-29th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:40:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-one-e9-dual-sim-will-be-available-in-singapore-starting-august-29th/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The HTC One E9+ dual sim in rose gold.
HTC has introduced the HTC One E9+ dual sim in Singapore. This lightweight smartphone boasts a sizable 2K display and injects vibrant colors into the signature flagship design.
&amp;ldquo;This latest addition to our HTC One E series capitalizes on the success of our flagship phones, offering both sophistication and style,&amp;rdquo; stated Faisal Siddiqui, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;The HTC One E9+ dual sim represents a continuation of HTC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and design, showcasing a large 5.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 510 provides budget-friendly LTE capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 22:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</guid><description>HTC&amp;rsquo;s most budget-friendly LTE smartphone is hitting the shelves just days after the company launched the Desire 210 in Singapore. Starting September 6, 2014, you can find the HTC Desire 510 at mobile carriers and major retailers across Singapore. This device boasts a quad-core LTE processor, a 4.7” display, and runs on Android 4.4.
Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;While the industry has been buzzing about the impact of 4G, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook that only a handful of high-end devices truly utilize this technology,&amp;rdquo; says HTC CEO, Peter Chou.</description></item><item><title>HTC has launched the HTC Desire 826 dual sim, promising an exceptional mobile audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The Blue Lagoon version.
HTC is enhancing the mobile audio experience with its Desire 826 dual sim phone, featuring HTC BoomSound and Dolby Audio surround sound. This makes HTC the first smartphone manufacturer to integrate dual front-facing stereo speakers, a precisely adjusted sound profile, and Dolby&amp;rsquo;s decoding technology for a comprehensive multi-channel audio solution.
This combination provides listeners with a level of audio depth and range not typically found in mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Huawei has launched the HUAWEI nova 3i</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 06:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</guid><description>Singapore is among the first countries globally to introduce the HUAWEI nova 3i, a midrange smartphone equipped with AI-powered front-facing dual cameras.
Huawei aims to make high-end technology and value accessible to budget-conscious consumers, according to Cheng Jiangfei, Managing Director of Huawei Singapore Consumer Business Group. He emphasized that the HUAWEI nova 3i combines stylish design with advanced AI features, offering exceptional quality and functionality at an affordable price.
Notable features of the HUAWEI nova 3i include:</description></item></channel></rss>