<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Report Models on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/report-models/</link><description>Recent content in Report Models on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/report-models/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SQL Reporting Services, Dynamics GP, and Report Models can be frustrating.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-reporting-services-dynamics-gp-and-report-models-can-be-frustrating/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-reporting-services-dynamics-gp-and-report-models-can-be-frustrating/</guid><description>I really enjoy using SQL Reporting Services and Dynamics GP, especially the standard reports included with Dynamics GP. However, I feel a slight dread when asked to modify one, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even a developer!
Why the apprehension? I might be revealing my non-technical side, but reports based on report models make me particularly nervous. Sometimes, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky and the necessary field is already there, requiring just minor adjustments. However, a recent request wasn&amp;rsquo;t so straightforward.</description></item><item><title>Things that I adore about SQL Reporting Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/things-that-i-adore-about-sql-reporting-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/things-that-i-adore-about-sql-reporting-services/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;ve been rather quiet online lately, I can assure you it&amp;rsquo;s not due to a lack of things to share! My recent travels and the beautiful spring weather have lured me away from my computer.
However, SQL Reporting Services has been on my mind, particularly with recent client projects and an upcoming training session I&amp;rsquo;m delivering on using it with Microsoft Dynamics GP 10.0. Revisiting the material has reminded me of some useful features I tend to overlook.</description></item></channel></rss>