<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Connections on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is 5G Bandwidth Slicing The New Private Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet is great for connecting, but it&amp;rsquo;s not always reliable. While it provides widespread access, low costs, and supports most applications, it can fall short when high performance and reliability are crucial. Issues like latency, packet loss, and congestion can hinder or even prevent interactive applications from working correctly. The solution? Private networks.
What is a Private Network?
The internet is a public network, accessible to almost anyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Can You Cope With Big Data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 22:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/</guid><description>The sheer size of &amp;ldquo;Big Data&amp;rdquo; is a popular topic, but what does it really mean?
Does the thought of managing massive amounts of data feel overwhelming, or do you see it as an opportunity? Ensuring you have the right infrastructure and connectivity is essential. Discover the cloud and connection services tailored for your business&amp;rsquo;s location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Gigabit Prices On Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 05:45:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</guid><description>Modern businesses are increasing their reliance on bandwidth-intensive applications like video and cloud-based solutions, putting a strain on their Wide Area Networks (WANs). While evaluating bandwidth needs and exploring the best deals seems logical, it can often feel complicated. However, new tools are emerging to simplify this process.
Traditionally, obtaining competitive telecom prices meant identifying local carriers, navigating through voicemail systems, enduring endless phone tag, and deciphering complex quotes to ensure accurate comparisons...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantage of Dedicated Cloud Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</guid><description>Companies of all sizes are increasingly adopting cloud services due to their cost-effectiveness. However, the assumption that a basic internet connection is sufficient for accessing these services is proving to be inaccurate in many situations.
While the internet&amp;rsquo;s widespread availability and affordability make it appealing for WAN services, its security concerns led to the development of VPNs. These secure tunnels encrypt data, allowing remote workers and branch offices to connect securely to corporate networks and transfer sensitive information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>