<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Production on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-production/</link><description>Recent content in Video Production on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-production/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gig E WAN Comes To The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</guid><description>It may seem surprising, but businesses can now access 10 Gigabit Ethernet connections for their wide area networks. What&amp;rsquo;s even more surprising is how many businesses can actually utilize this bandwidth.
Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular among large corporations and tech companies that need to manage and deliver massive amounts of data quickly. What kinds of companies are we talking about?
For those involved in video production or editing, Gigabit per second connections are essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Lit Buildings and Near Net Fiber Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic internet service is becoming increasingly essential for modern businesses, but not everyone has access to it. Some businesses don&amp;rsquo;t need the high speeds fiber offers and are content with slower options. Others might have outdated perceptions of fiber&amp;rsquo;s affordability. Many are unaware that fiber might already be available in their building or nearby.
Fiber optic internet isn&amp;rsquo;t the niche product it once was. Even consumers are demanding fiber to their homes for streaming and entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Video-Film Production Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 18:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</guid><description>The shift to digital video and film production has made it possible to work with collaborators across the globe. While physical delivery of tapes and disks is an option, tight production timelines often necessitate electronic file transfer. This, however, raises questions about how to carry out the process and the associated costs.
Bandwidth is the defining feature of digital transfer services, representing the transmission speed in bits per second. It&amp;rsquo;s typically measured in Mbps or Gbps, and generally speaking, a higher bandwidth comes with a higher price tag...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Can GigE Bandwidth Do For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly common in local area networks, with network cards and backbones now supporting these higher speeds. Companies that rely heavily on digital processes and high bandwidth data transfers are likely already using Gigabit Ethernet. However, they need a way to extend these high-speed transfers beyond their local networks.
Companies with large numbers of employees, extensive customer bases, or applications that generate significant amounts of data can benefit from Gigabit Ethernet WAN connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>