<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General Court on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-court/</link><description>Recent content in General Court on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:14:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-court/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A missed chance to enhance access to justice in environmental issues: the CJEU's ruling on the applicability of the Aarhus Convention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</guid><description>**
**
Dr. Apolline J. C. Roger, Senior Teaching Fellow in EU environmental law, University of Edinburgh Law School.
The right to access justice is a crucial safeguard for environmental NGOs and citizens, allowing them to contest public authorities&amp;rsquo; decisions that impact the environment and public health. By joining the Aarhus Convention in 2005, the EU acknowledged this right as a pillar of good governance and a key element of the human right to a healthy environment.</description></item><item><title>Reforming the EU's Court System: The path to progress lies in creating a more accountable court, not simply a larger one.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</guid><description>Alberto Alemanno, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Law &amp;amp; Risk Regulation, HEC Paris
Laurent Pech, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Public Law, Middlesex University London
1. Setting the Stage
Recent media attention on the EU Court of Justice highlights a departure from its previous low profile. Surprisingly, this attention is not focused on a specific court decision but rather on internal disputes regarding a proposal to address the court&amp;rsquo;s efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Politicians 1, Architects 0: Constructing the EU Judicial System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently suggested that the EU should double the number of judges on the General Court and eliminate the EU Civil Service Tribunal. This piece examines the reasons behind this significant proposition for restructuring the EU judicial system and evaluates its merits.
Background
The EU judicial system has consistently expanded to accommodate a growing caseload. The Single European Act of 1987 allowed for the establishment of the Court of First Instance (renamed the General Court by the Lisbon Treaty) to support the Court of Justice.</description></item><item><title>Farewell Address to the CJEU by EU Judge Dehousse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-address-to-the-cjeu-by-eu-judge-dehousse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-address-to-the-cjeu-by-eu-judge-dehousse/</guid><description>Introduction by Professors Alemanno &amp;amp; Pech
This blog post presents the English translation of a farewell address by Judge Franklin Dehousse, who served on the EU General Court from 2003 to 2016.
Unusually, no public ceremony was held for the departing EU judges, including Judge Dehousse. This is likely due to Dehousse&amp;rsquo;s vocal criticism of the EU court system reform, a reform he extensively analyzed in several research papers.</description></item></channel></rss>