<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>M-Commerce on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/m-commerce/</link><description>Recent content in M-Commerce on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:53:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/m-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shopee Malaysia's MyCyberSale provides discounts of up to 90%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:53:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</guid><description>Source: Shopee. Part of a banner for MyCyberSale.
During Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;MyCyberSale,&amp;rdquo; which ends September 30th, shoppers on Shopee have a chance to win an iPhone 7 and other prizes. Free shipping is also offered during this period.
Featured sale items include:
Jabra SPORT CORDED Stereo Headset This black, waterproof headset is designed for athletic individuals. Offered by Jabra Malaysia, this headset comes with a two-year warranty. Shopee is offering a 69% discount on this product...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is launching the 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day in September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</guid><description>Source: Shopee website. The countdown begins 1 September.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace owned by Garena Interactive Holding, is launching its first-ever 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day. This one-day event will take place on September 9th and offer shoppers a mobile shopping experience.
The event is anticipated to be the largest mobile shopping sale in the region. Shoppers in Singapore can expect 24 hours of continuous deals and promotions. These include discounts of up to 90%, a selection of items under S$0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia honors female entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, marked International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day on March 8, 2017, by recognizing the achievements of women.
This year&amp;rsquo;s International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day centers around empowering women globally and inspiring them to make bold moves. Shopee Malaysia honored this theme by highlighting the stories of women entrepreneurs who took a leap of faith to launch their own ventures. The platform&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly design, free nationwide shipping, and zero-commission fees are designed to encourage more women to tap into their potential as leaders and business owners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is encouraging subscribers to use their phones for payment at the supermarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</guid><description>A picture of a Dash payment reader at a FairPrice checkout.
Starting November 17th, shoppers can use Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash mobile payment app at over 200 NTUC FairPrice locations, including their supermarkets, Xtra hypermarkets, and standalone Cheers stores.
Gan Siok Hoon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of mCommerce, Consumer Singapore, stated that as a major fintech provider, they were excited to partner with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer, FairPrice, to offer this fast and secure payment option to their over half a million daily shoppers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Marco, it's Polo on Your Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</guid><description>Fashion giant Ralph Lauren is taking shopping to the next level by moving beyond online stores and embracing mobile shopping via cell phones. This shift, known as mobile or m-commerce, is poised to become as significant as e-commerce has been in recent times. Its success relies on internet-enabled smartphones and mobile-friendly websites designed for smaller screens, along with advancements like barcode scanning software and web-connected vending machines.
Why the focus on cell phone shopping?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash is running a flash campaign offering mystery cashback for purchases made on Lazada.SG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment app, Dash, is holding a short promotional campaign with online store Lazada.SG. From October 2nd to 9th, 2015, shoppers can receive a surprise cashback reward of 15% to 50%*.
Each day of the campaign features a &amp;ldquo;Dash Happy Hour.&amp;rdquo; During this limited time frame, which lasts up to two hours, customers using Dash to pay for purchases on Lazada.SG can earn cashback. The specific cashback amount won&amp;rsquo;t be disclosed until the end of each day and will be added to customer accounts within three business days...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo measures the passion for travel among Singaporeans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</guid><description>Mobile travel purchases saw a 35% surge between 2011 and 2016, a trend predicted to continue its upward trajectory. Accessibility (74%) and convenience (69%) are the primary motivators for respondents&amp;rsquo; preference to browse travel products online. A significant 78% choose smartphones over desktops/laptops for browsing due to their on-the-go functionality.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology firm, highlights the continuous growth of mobile travel sales, emphasizing it as a prime growth avenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>