<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Northern Ireland on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/northern-ireland/</link><description>Recent content in Northern Ireland on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/northern-ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Examining the Reunification of Ireland from an EU Legal Viewpoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</guid><description>Nikos Skoutaris, Lecturer in EU law at the University of East Anglia; website on Secessions, Constitutions and EU law.
When the UK voted to leave the EU on June 23, 2016, Northern Ireland voted to remain. This result has led Sinn Féin to call for a referendum on Irish unification, which would allow Northern Ireland to stay in the EU. This discussion has gained momentum following the most recent Northern Ireland Assembly election, which saw a significant decrease in the Unionist vote.</description></item><item><title>The Day the Unicorns Cried: Understanding Phase 1 of the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
The recent joint report on the progress of Brexit negotiations, along with a related paper from the Commission, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of negotiations. Based on this report, the EU27 have agreed that &amp;ldquo;sufficient progress&amp;rdquo; has been made to move forward. This next phase will focus on a transition period and, potentially starting in March 2018, the framework for the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU.</description></item><item><title>The Good Friday Agreement: A Personal Reflection on the Value of Peace over Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-good-friday-agreement-a-personal-reflection-on-the-value-of-peace-over-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 11:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-good-friday-agreement-a-personal-reflection-on-the-value-of-peace-over-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah Kay, human rights lawyer
As a teenager in the spring of 1998, I felt frustrated and stuck. I lived in a small house in West Belfast with my grandmother and a rotating group of cousins. My grandfather, an active member of the Republican movement, had died a few years earlier. I was lucky to spend summers traveling with my parents, who had custody of me, experiencing a world beyond our limited opportunities and ongoing conflict.</description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement: Analysis 1 Overview</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</guid><description>Analysis of the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement - October 2019 Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction While the approval of the Brexit withdrawal agreement is uncertain at present, the UK Parliament&amp;rsquo;s upcoming vote necessitates an updated analysis of the revised agreement. This updated version includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship.
This post aims to provide a simplified explanation of the agreement for non-lawyers, outlining its structure and key content.</description></item><item><title>The Windsor Framework Relaunch receives general acclaim with little said.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: en:User:Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
The opportunity to finalize the Windsor Framework and ensure its acceptance was limited. The challenging task of establishing trade rules for goods moving between Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK had been largely settled almost a year prior. The objective was to minimize trade friction within the UK while upholding the EU Single Market.</description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU.</description></item><item><title>The Dillon Judgment, Exemption of Laws, and Article 2 of the Northern Ireland Protocol/Windsor Framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD researcher, Queens University Belfast, and Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Aaronward, via Wikicommons media
In a landmark decision, a UK court has disapplied portions of a UK Act of Parliament for the first time since Brexit due to conflicts with the Withdrawal Agreement, specifically highlighting the ongoing connection between UK and EU legal systems. This unexpected development, though previously argued for, underscores the UK government&amp;rsquo;s consistent underestimation of Article 2&amp;rsquo;s impact on rights-related cases.</description></item><item><title>Simply Refuse? The latest 'Stormont Brake' within the Windsor Framework (part 2 of the framework analysis)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</guid><description>The Stormont Brake: A Closer Look at its Potential Impact Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons Introduction
This analysis delves into the &amp;lsquo;Stormont Brake&amp;rsquo;, a new mechanism within the Windsor Framework designed to address concerns about how EU law applies to Northern Ireland. This analysis explores the text and interpretation of this &amp;lsquo;brake&amp;rsquo; on changes to EU law under the protocol. While it might never be used, understanding the mechanics of the Stormont Brake is crucial to grasp its potential implications.</description></item><item><title>Allister Round 2: Exploring the depths of UK constitutional law in the Mariana Trench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD student, Queen’s University Belfast School of Law
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikicommons
Introduction
It&amp;rsquo;s a common observation in UK constitutional law that complex issues rarely have simple solutions. Instead, they often result in multiple, overlapping interpretations. This is certainly the case with the recent Allister and others v Prime Minister and others [2022] NICA 15 ruling from the Northern Ireland Court of Appeal (NICA). It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this case is headed to the UK Supreme Court on appeal, ensuring further analysis and discussion.</description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the Northern Ireland Protocol in question? Examination of the High Court ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</guid><description>Sarah Kay, human rights lawyer
Brexit has negatively impacted Northern Ireland, as was anticipated. Five years after the Brexit referendum, the High Court in Belfast issued a significant political decision regarding a legal challenge to the Northern Ireland Protocol. This challenge mirrors the Miller 1 case concerning Brexit&amp;rsquo;s constitutionality. Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s fragile political landscape, exacerbated by Brexit, has exposed existing systemic issues.
The legal challenge was brought forward by two main parties: Clifford Peeples, who opposed the Irish Sea border, and unionist members, including former First Minister Arlene Foster, who argued that the Protocol weakens Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s ties with Great Britain.</description></item><item><title>An Unassuming Suggestion: Preventing a Standstill on the Irish Border in the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Brexit withdrawal agreement negotiations are in danger of collapsing due to disagreements on managing the Irish border. The UK government&amp;rsquo;s lack of concrete proposals for customs away from the border is concerning. Additionally, the UK Foreign Secretary&amp;rsquo;s inability to differentiate between a simple congestion charge and the complexities of border control is disappointing.
In anticipation of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s upcoming proposals, I have drafted a text (Annex 1) addressing the Irish border in the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice.</description></item><item><title>Can devolved powers help mitigate the negative effects of Brexit on Scotland?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 07:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The UK&amp;rsquo;s devolution process, implemented with the understanding of continued EU membership, granted legislative and executive autonomy to Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland through specific Acts of Parliament. These Acts, while establishing varying degrees of autonomy, shared a common thread: devolved powers must not contradict UK&amp;rsquo;s international obligations, particularly EU law.</description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures.</description></item></channel></rss>