<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Live on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/live/</link><description>Recent content in Live on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/live/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The TomTom City portal offers real-time traffic and travel updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</guid><description>TomTom (TOM2) introduces TomTom City, a digital platform providing real-time traffic data and travel details to both individuals and traffic management professionals.
This new service showcases the wide array of traffic information available for specific cities and acts as a hub for connecting traffic authorities, businesses, and citizens to collaborate on sustainable and efficient mobility solutions. Building on the traffic information already available through TomTom navigation devices and partners in automotive, consumer, and government sectors, TomTom City expands upon the historical congestion data provided in reports like the TomTom Traffic Index...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACCA will be hosting a virtual conference called Accounting for the Future from September 15 to 18</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</guid><description>Source: ACCA website.
The sixth annual Accounting for the Future virtual conference, hosted by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), will focus on important topics impacting the future of accounting. These topics include corporate culture, sustainability, and global business service models.
The conference, taking place from September 15th to 18th, 2014, will feature four days of live and on-demand video and audio webcasts covering various subjects related to the accounting profession...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces complimentary live services for 2017 Garmin Drive models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</guid><description>Garmin International has refreshed its Garmin Drive portable navigation device (PND) lineup with free live services* for the most up-to-date content and driver alerts to improve safety. These upgrades to the Garmin Drive, Garmin DriveSmart, Garmin DriveAssist, and Garmin DriveLuxe models show the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving PNDs.
The base model Garmin Drive 51/61 includes helpful driver alerts. The Garmin DriveSmart 51/61 adds smart features. The camera-equipped Garmin DriveAssist 51 is for recording drives, while the premium Garmin DriveLuxe 51 has an elegant metal design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The bank in Beirut provides live video conferencing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</guid><description>Bank Audi has established a new flagship branch called &amp;ldquo;Novo&amp;rdquo; in Beirut Central District&amp;rsquo;s Palladium Building. This branch is open every day of the year from 10 am to 10 pm and provides customers with interactive banking services.
In addition to smart ATMs offering services like cash withdrawals, cash and check deposits, and credit card payments, the branch introduces a first-of-its-kind feature in Lebanon: Interactive Teller Machines (ITMs). These ITMs enable customers to connect with personal tellers through live video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>