<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Personal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/personal/</link><description>Recent content in Personal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IndianMoney.com is creating additional financial education content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</guid><description>IndianMoney.com, a leading financial education company in India, partnered with Kannada news channel Suddi TV to create Money Maathu (Money Talk), an educational series about personal finance. The series features short episodes, typically eight to ten minutes long, that cover a wide range of financial topics. With 35 episodes already released, the goal is to empower viewers with the knowledge to make informed financial choices.
CS Sudheer, founder and CEO of IndianMoney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bioactive ingredients will drive growth in the personal care industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</guid><description>A global shift from synthetic to natural active ingredients in personal care products is driving significant investments in the market, according to research firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. This trend is fueled by a growing consumer belief that natural ingredients are safer for human health and the environment.
Source: Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. Generic personal care dispensers.
Currently, natural active ingredients represent 25% to 30% of the total market share. However, this is predicted to double by 2023, leading to increased innovation in addressing the challenges of incorporating these often delicate ingredients...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adapt your beauty routine to the changing weather conditions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</guid><description>Mintel Beauty &amp;amp; Personal Care (BPC) has recognized a new global beauty trend: seasonality. This trend reflects how different weather conditions influence beauty routines.
Source: Mintel website.
According to Mintel BPC, product launches related to this trend significantly increased from 9.8% in 2011 to 11.1% in 2014. This is particularly noticeable in facial skincare, where seasonal product launches grew from a mere 0.5% in 2009 to 1.2% in 2014.
Jane Henderson, Global President of Mintel’s Beauty and Personal Care Division, notes a growing consumer awareness of how environmental changes impact their skin and hair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco has launched new personal hardware to improve collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</guid><description>At Cisco Live! 2014 in the US, Cisco unveiled new personal collaboration tools. The company recognizes that teamwork often spans continents, demanding tools that enable seamless and immediate collaboration, regardless of location.
Source: Cisco. The Cisco DX80 in action.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution comes in the form of the DX70 and DX80 desktop collaboration devices. These Android-based devices act as hubs for collaboration tools and applications. Featuring large touch screens, the DX70 and DX80 combine Cisco&amp;rsquo;s expertise in HD video, high-quality audio, and web conferencing with integrated business applications and web browsing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Science Park 1 will be testing a program for sharing personal mobility devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</guid><description>Ascendas-Singbridge Group, a leading provider of sustainable urban and business space solutions in Asia, has partnered with Neuron Mobility, a smart transportation solutions provider, to pilot a personal mobility device (PMD) sharing program at Singapore Science Park 1. This six-month trial reflects the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing accessibility and convenience for tenants, employees, and visitors within the park.
Starting June 14, 2017, fifty GPS-equipped e-scooters and twenty bicycles will be available for rent at six designated parking zones throughout Singapore Science Park 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>