<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Macao on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/macao/</link><description>Recent content in Macao on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/macao/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr.</description></item><item><title>SJM Resorts will be hosting the inaugural MICHELIN Star Table event in mid-September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</guid><description>Source: SJM resorts. Palace Garden Head Chef Ken Chong will introduce the authentic elegance of fine Cantonese cuisine with his signature dish, crystal king tiger prawn.
SJM Resorts, an official MICHELIN Guide partner in Macao, has introduced its inaugural MICHELIN Star Table experience.
The debut event will be held at the Palace Garden within the Grand Lisboa Palace Resort Macau on September 15th and 16th. It will showcase a six-course menu representing the best of Chinese cuisine through a collaborative effort between two renowned chefs.</description></item></channel></rss>