<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Managed MPLS Networking Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</guid><description>Imagine your company with offices across the country, each operating its own independent local network for computers, phones, and video calls. While efficient individually, they lack integration. To unify your company, connecting these separate networks is key. This will boost efficiency by centralizing functions, improving collaboration among employees nationwide, and enabling specialized support centers.
Integrating your phone system with your network can lead to substantial savings on long-distance calls. Instead of relying on traditional phone lines, internal communication happens within your network, cutting toll charges.</description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost.</description></item></channel></rss>