<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disability Discrimination on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disability-discrimination/</link><description>Recent content in Disability Discrimination on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 19:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disability-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can obesity be considered a disability?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</guid><description>By Katharina Ó Cathaoir, PhD Fellow, University of Copenhagen
==============================================================================================
Does being obese qualify as a disability? This complex issue was the focus of Advocate General Jääskinen&amp;rsquo;s opinion on July 17, 2014, in the case of Kaltoft v. Municipality of Billund. The case has drawn significant interest, particularly regarding potential impacts on employment and healthcare. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to note that the Advocate General&amp;rsquo;s opinion is not legally binding and the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will issue its own judgment in the coming months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Commission's reflections on the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities focus more on praise than introspection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:44:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</guid><description>Dr. Charlotte O’Brien, Lecturer in Law, York Law School, University of York
Over seven years after signing the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities (UNCRPD) and over three years after its conclusion, how effectively is the EU safeguarding the disability rights outlined within it? The European Commission claims it is doing very well. In fact, it suggests the UNCRPD was hardly necessary, as the EU was already on the right track...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contemplating EU Gender Equality Law on Surrogate Mothers' Day in Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:57:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The desire to have children has always been deeply understood, especially for women facing medical obstacles to childbirth. Adoption was the traditional solution, but recent decades have introduced alternatives like IVF and surrogacy.
While the EU doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly regulate these practices, it does address maternity leave through the Pregnant Workers&amp;rsquo; Directive. The Directive on Sex Discrimination in Employment further tackles the employment aspects of pregnancy. This directive prohibits discrimination against women undergoing IVF treatment even before pregnancy, as established by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Mayr case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ clarifies EU's authority over copyright law in the Marrakesh Treaty ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 02:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</guid><description>Gesa Kübek, PhD candidate at the law faculty of the University of Passau.
In its February 14, 2017 Opinion 3/15, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) determined that the European Union (EU) possesses exclusive competence to enter into the Marrakesh Treaty to Facilitate Access to Published Works for Persons Who Are Blind, Visually Impaired, or Otherwise Print Disabled (hereafter: Marrakesh Treaty). This decision aligns with Advocate General (AG) Wahl’s prior Opinion, which similarly argued for exclusive EU competence in this domain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should there be increased use of majority voting in EU social policy decisions? Evaluating the Commission's suggestion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, PhD Candidate, University of Antwerp
In April 2019, the European Commission initiated a discussion on streamlining the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making in social policy. The goal was to enhance efficiency by utilizing &amp;ldquo;passerelle&amp;rdquo; clauses, which permit a shift from unanimous voting to qualified majority voting (QMV) and from special to ordinary legislative procedures. This change, while requiring unanimous approval from Member States, aims to bypass the complexities of Treaty revisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions on cases involving obesity and discrimination laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 03:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</guid><description>Katharina O Cathaoir
The European Court of Justice, in its decision on Kaltoft, determined that obesity itself is not a protected characteristic under EU employment law, nor is it automatically a disability. However, the Court acknowledged that the EU Directive prohibiting workplace discrimination based on disability might apply in certain situations. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this ruling specifically pertains to employment disputes, as EU law does not address disability discrimination outside of the workplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>