<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Transit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-transit/</link><description>Recent content in IP Transit on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-transit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Communications Nears Tbps National Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 01:23:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</guid><description>Any lingering doubts about the supposed overabundance of bandwidth in the late &amp;rsquo;90s telecom boom should be dispelled by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; recent announcement. Despite upgrading their national backbone just last year, XO is increasing its capacity again. This upgrade will boost major coast-to-coast network routes from 400 Gbps to a staggering 800 Gbps, putting them within reach of terabit-per-second speeds.
This massive capacity increase is driven by a fivefold surge in demand for high-capacity inter-city network services over the past year, according to XO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>40 Gbps Bandwidth Available For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</guid><description>XO Communications has increased business bandwidth options by offering two 40 Gbps network services across its nationwide fiber optic network. Randy Nicklas, XO Communications&amp;rsquo; CTO, highlights the advantages of these new 40 Gbps services:
You can listen to the interview directly on this page:
Clearly, we&amp;rsquo;re entering a new era of high-bandwidth applications for businesses and service providers like cable companies. High-speed financial trading needs the fastest speeds, with even milliseconds of delay impacting outcomes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>