<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Employment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employment/</link><description>Recent content in Employment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2017 Budget is on handling uncertainty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Budget website. View of Singapore.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2017 aimed to prepare the nation for the future amidst significant global economic shifts, presenting both obstacles and prospects. Finance Minister Heng Swee Keat stressed the need for companies and workers to develop robust adaptability to navigate these changing economic structures and technologies. He highlighted that digitalization, innovation, and a highly skilled workforce are key for cities and regions to thrive while maintaining global openness and connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowdsourcing In Lieu of Outsourcing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</guid><description>Over recent years, outsourcing has become increasingly popular as a way to meet business needs. However, since the Great Recession, crowdsourcing has emerged as a new and growing trend. This approach leverages the collective talent of a group to find solutions for specific tasks.
Crowdsourcing provides a decentralized approach to problem-solving, unlike traditional methods of assigning tasks to employees or contractors. Imagine needing a building sold – you&amp;rsquo;d hire a real estate agent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contract positions are the perfect solution for companies in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</guid><description>A recent survey by Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, indicates a rise in contract employment in Singapore. The Singapore Contracting Survey reveals that hiring managers are increasingly turning to skilled contract workers due to difficulties in obtaining approval for permanent positions. Many companies are implementing hiring freezes, often mandated by their headquarters, leading managers in Singapore to seek adaptable, temporary staffing solutions.
The survey, which polled over 300 professionals in Singapore with contracting experience, explored the advantages and disadvantages of contract work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Jobs Come Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</guid><description>Although the Great Recession continues, the impact varies across industries. In fact, the technology sector is performing quite well in terms of employment. From November to December of last year, while 85,000 jobs were lost overall, the tech industry actually added 5,200 new positions. This suggests that technology might be a promising field.
However, having technological skills doesn&amp;rsquo;t guarantee employment. Many factory workers, for instance, would likely agree. The manufacturing sector was already moving overseas even before the recession...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CIER Employment Index indicates a decrease in employment rates in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</guid><description>The Chinese job platform Zhaopin and the China Institute for Employment Research (CIER) at Renmin University have published their CIER Employment Index Report for July to September 2015.
The report&amp;rsquo;s index, which measures the ease of finding a job, rose consistently from 2011 to 2014. However, mirroring the economic slowdown, the job market has weakened, leading to a decline in the CIER Index for the past two quarters. The index dropped from its peak of 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>