<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Celcom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/celcom/</link><description>Recent content in Celcom on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:26:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/celcom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Celcom users now have the option to subscribe to iflix</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</guid><description>iflix, a Southeast Asian internet TV provider, has teamed up with Malaysian mobile network operator Celcom Axiata to offer TV series, movies, and other content to Celcom&amp;rsquo;s over 12 million subscribers in Malaysia.
Starting March 15, 2016, all Celcom subscribers will get two free months of iflix, allowing them to stream content seamlessly on Celcom&amp;rsquo;s 4G network (a value of RM20). After the two-month promotional period, customers can continue enjoying iflix for a discounted rate of RM9 per month.</description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music.</description></item></channel></rss>