<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transfer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transfer/</link><description>Recent content in Transfer on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transfer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Western Union has extended its contract to provide its services at Hong Leong Bank branches in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Western Union, a company specializing in money transfers, has extended its partnership with Hong Leong Bank (HLBB) for another three years. This agreement allows Western Union to continue providing its services across all 283 HLBB branches in Malaysia.
Chew Mei Ling, Western Union&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, highlighted the increasing demand for both inbound and outbound remittances in the country. She emphasized that the renewed partnership with HLBB will support this growth by offering customers fast, reliable, and convenient money transfer services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transfer files from your phone without using up your mobile data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</guid><description>Xender, a Chinese app, simplifies phone-based file sharing without incurring mobile data costs using peer-to-peer technology.
For device-to-device transfers, Xender creates a local Wi-Fi hotspot that nearby users can join. This allows for the seamless sharing of photos, music, files, and apps between phones, proving particularly useful when upgrading to a new device. Xender boasts unlimited file sizes, cross-platform compatibility, and transfer speeds up to 50 times faster than Bluetooth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xpress Money introduces a daily raffle for customers sending money in 11 countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</guid><description>Xpress Money, a money transfer company, has introduced a 49-day promotion called &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday.&amp;rdquo; This program is open to customers sending money from Malaysia and ten other countries, including several in the Middle East.
Source: Xpress Money website.
The World Bank reported that in 2012, individuals sent $2.3 billion from Malaysia to other countries. Xpress Money anticipates a 15% increase in money transfers during Ramadan. Sudhesh Giriyan, Xpress Money&amp;rsquo;s Vice President and Business Head, stated that the &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday&amp;rdquo; program is a gesture of goodwill towards customers during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>