<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ambassador on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ambassador/</link><description>Recent content in Ambassador on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ambassador/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Coral Beirut Al Hamra now offers two additional Ambassador Suites as part of its room options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</guid><description>The Coral Beirut Al Hamra Hotel recently introduced a new suite category featuring expansive rooftop terraces with outdoor seating areas. Situated on the 11th floor, the 87 square meter Ambassador Suites offer fully equipped kitchens, large living rooms, and luxurious bathrooms, complete with high-end amenities.
Hartmut Grauel, General Manager of the hotel, stated that these new suites cater to the preferences of discerning travelers. He noted a consistent demand for spacious accommodations akin to full-size apartments, complete with kitchens and living rooms.</description></item></channel></rss>