<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Public Health on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/public-health/</link><description>Recent content in Public Health on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/public-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The alignment of Ireland's Public Health (Alcohol) Bill with EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Ollie Bartlett, Maynooth University
After nearly three years of discussion, the Irish Public Health (Alcohol) Bill has been passed by the Irish Parliament. The Bill aims to address Ireland&amp;rsquo;s significant alcohol-related harm through five key measures: minimum alcohol pricing; stricter labeling; advertising restrictions; separating alcohol from other retail products; and limitations on alcohol sales and supply.
While lauded as &amp;ldquo;groundbreaking&amp;rdquo; by Health Minister Simon Harris, some argue that elements of the Bill, particularly those related to the free trade of alcohol within the European Union, might not be legal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU’s Patients’ Rights Directive in practice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</guid><description>Tamara Hervey, Professor of Law and Head of Law School, University of Sheffield
As Europe focuses on the immense refugee crisis, discussing other migration matters can seem trivial. However, this week also saw the release of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s report on the &amp;ldquo;Patients&amp;rsquo; Rights Directive.&amp;rdquo; This report reveals that the directive&amp;rsquo;s name is misleading, as its primary goal appears to be safeguarding national health systems instead of patients&amp;rsquo; rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Compliance of Alcohol Health Warning Labelling in Member States with EU Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Nikhil Gokani, a lecturer specializing in consumer protection and public health law at the University of Essex, holds key positions in several organizations: Chair of the Alcohol Labelling and Health Warning International Expert Group at the European Alcohol Policy Alliance, Vice President of the Law Section at the European Public Health Association, and a member of the Technical Advisory Group on Alcohol Labelling at the World Health Organization (WHO)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit must ensure that health is not negatively impacted, which includes ensuring that there are adequate rules in place for medical professional qualifications.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield argues that a Leave.EU tweet claiming EU regulations unnecessarily extend doctor training is misleading.
Hervey presents four key arguments: Firstly, the UK, as a long-standing EU member, significantly shaped EU medical training standards. While these standards do influence UK medical qualifications, their impact is limited, and the UK has the authority to propose changes. The current system, including the duration of training, reflects the UK&amp;rsquo;s active participation in shaping these regulations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization has declared the Ebola outbreak a global public health emergency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) declared the West African Ebola outbreak a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) on August 8th.
As of August 4, 2014, there were 1,711 cases (1,070 confirmed, 436 probable, and 205 suspected) of Ebola virus disease (EVD), resulting in 932 deaths. Between August 5th and 6th, 2014, 68 new EVD cases (including confirmed, probable, and suspected) and 29 deaths were reported across Guinea, Liberia, Nigeria, and Sierra Leone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disappointing CJEU ruling upholds ban on blood donation by gay and bisexual men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice in Case C-528/13 Léger determined that permanent bans on blood donation by gay and bisexual men solely based on their sexual history with other men might be justified in certain situations to ensure high health protection standards. This piece argues that this ruling is disappointing and could lead to accusations of inadequate LGB rights protection or even ingrained homophobia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>