<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pollution on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pollution/</link><description>Recent content in Pollution on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 16:20:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pollution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The labeling of the European Union in the International Maritime Organization is more of a focus than the EU's actual competence.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</guid><description>Cathleen Berg, doctoral student, University of Bayreuth
Advocate General (‘AG’) Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s November 25, 2021, opinion regarding a legal challenge from the European Commission against the European Council (Case C-161/20) highlights the contrasting interests between the European Union (‘EU’) and its Member States. This disagreement centers around how they exercise their authority within the International Maritime Organization (‘IMO’), an organization where the EU currently holds neither membership nor observer status. If the Court of Justice sides with AG Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s analysis, this case could significantly impact how the EU interest is represented within IMO committees, potentially shifting power from the Commission to the Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>YouGov is tracking the impact of the haze</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</guid><description>Southeast Asia faced significant haze this year, mainly due to regional forest fires. A YouGov survey reveals a high level of awareness about this issue within the region.
Nearly 80% of Asian respondents are aware of the haze originating from Indonesian landscape fires. This awareness is lower in Hong Kong (48%) and Mainland China (44%). However, in Indonesia, Malaysia, and Singapore, the three countries most affected, only 2% of respondents in each country reported being unaware of the haze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Berkeley Earth raises concerns about air pollution in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</guid><description>Source: Berkeley Earth website.
A recent study published in PLOS ONE by Berkeley Earth reveals that air pollution causes approximately 4,000 deaths per day in China, representing 17% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total deaths. This non-profit organization, established to investigate concerns raised by global warming skeptics, determined that the air quality for 38% of China&amp;rsquo;s population would be deemed &amp;ldquo;unhealthy&amp;rdquo; by United States standards.
Berkeley Earth&amp;rsquo;s analysis of hourly measurements from 1,500 ground stations over a four-month period indicated coal as the most likely source of PM2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Alternative Energy Makes Sense for Technology Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 10:04:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</guid><description>The digital world&amp;rsquo;s dependence on energy is deeply intertwined and may be its downfall, just as energy production&amp;rsquo;s side effects threaten our physical world. Climate change, for instance, directly impacts the sustainability of Business 2.0.
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume that dirty, resource-intensive energy is a relic of the industrial age, replaced by a cleaner information age, especially online. However, the online world can create a false sense of detachment from the physical resources it relies on...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Paid To Celebrate National Cell Phone Recycling Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s National Cell Phone Recycling Week, and there&amp;rsquo;s a way to make some money while participating! This initiative, spearheaded by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), highlights the importance of recycling valuable and potentially harmful materials found in cell phones.
Wireless carriers and various retailers are accepting old cell phones to ensure these devices are properly processed and their components are reused in new products. By taking part, you contribute to environmental protection by preventing hazardous materials from ending up in landfills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>