<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Durian on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/durian/</link><description>Recent content in Durian on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:43:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/durian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting October 14, the Coffee Lounge at Goodwood Park Hotel will be offering an expanded menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Goodwood Park Hotel, home to the Coffee Lounge known for its Taiwan porridge and local dishes, is launching a limited-time menu enhancement. From October 14th, guests can enjoy new additions to the &amp;ldquo;Design Your Own Local Degustation Set Menu&amp;rdquo; and a special dessert buffet featuring Mao Shan Wang durian.
This year, from October 14th to November 17th, Coffee Lounge&amp;rsquo;s popular dessert buffet will showcase Mao Shan Wang durian pastries alongside its regular offerings during lunch and dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new snowskin flavors at Goodwood Park are ideal combinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 13:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with new snowskin mooncake flavors that perfectly pair two complementary ingredients. This year, the hotel is even introducing its first-ever chocolate mooncake.
One of the new additions is the Yuzu Lychee Snowskin Mooncake, featuring the bright citrus flavor of yuzu combined with sweet lychee pieces. Another highlight is the limited-edition Dark Chocolate Crunchy Hazelnut Snowskin Mooncake. This decadent treat consists of a crunchy hazelnut chocolate center surrounded by rich dark chocolate mousse, all encased in a snowskin made with crushed vanilla beans and caramel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>