<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Clarke Quay on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/clarke-quay/</link><description>Recent content in Clarke Quay on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/clarke-quay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Join us at Smile Singapore in Clarke Quay Central and share your beautiful smile with us!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</guid><description>The installation of the Smile project at Clarke Quay Central is currently underway.
Clarke Quay Central mall is promoting a happier Singapore with its Smile Singapore campaign. Launched as part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Jubilee celebrations, this project gives companies a platform to share their happy moments in the nation.
Caine Teo, head of Ape Works, the Creative Partner of the Smile Singapore Campaign, believes happiness is infectious. By showcasing pictures of smiling faces, they hope to remind Singaporeans of the many reasons to smile in their country.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is invited to a new year countdown at Clarke Quay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay.
Clarke Quay invites everyone in Singapore to celebrate the end of the year with exciting festivities. Popular radio DJs Glenn Ong from Class95FM and Sonia Chew from 987FM will host the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve countdown. The event will feature live music by the band Goodfellas, a vibrant street parade with a glow theme, and roving percussionists.
The entire event at Clarke Quay will be broadcasted live on 987FM.</description></item><item><title>The Butchers Club Burger offers National Day dishes in celebration of Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>The Butchers Club Burger in Singapore is launching a special menu item for National Day: The Little Red Dot Burger.
Starting July 29th and lasting for two weekends, The Little Red Dot Burger will be featured as part of a National Day Set Menu at The Butchers Club Burger Singapore. This marks the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s first National Day celebration in Singapore, and the burger itself is a tribute to a beloved local dish: satay ayam (chicken satay).</description></item><item><title>Clarke Quay Restaurant Week offers exclusive meals at discounted prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-restaurant-week-offers-exclusive-meals-at-discounted-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:56:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-restaurant-week-offers-exclusive-meals-at-discounted-prices/</guid><description>Clarke Quay&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Restaurant Week kicks off on Monday, April 20th, and continues until Sunday, May 3rd. This extended &amp;ldquo;week&amp;rdquo; offers diners the chance to savor exclusive set lunches priced at S$35++ or S$45++ by booking directly with participating Clarke Quay restaurants.
Source: Clarke Quay.
For instance, RAS The Essence of India presents a five-course set lunch featuring dishes like banajara kebab, lamb rogan gosht, boondhi raita, and rasmalai for S$35++.</description></item><item><title>Clarke Quay is shimmering with holiday spirit this Christmas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-is-shimmering-with-holiday-spirit-this-christmas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:44:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-is-shimmering-with-holiday-spirit-this-christmas/</guid><description>This Christmas season at Clarke Quay is all about celebrating and enjoying the festivities. Visitors can delight in the luminous displays along the river or snap photos with Christmas characters every Friday and Saturday from 8 pm to 10 pm until December 30th around Clarke Quay and Read Bridge.
From December 5th to 7th, between 5 pm and 11 pm, shoppers can explore a wide selection of handcrafted goods at the Artisan Pop Up Christmas Market located in Central Fountain Square.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay for the Once Upon a Nightmare free street party to celebrate Halloween</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-for-the-once-upon-a-nightmare-free-street-party-to-celebrate-halloween/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-for-the-once-upon-a-nightmare-free-street-party-to-celebrate-halloween/</guid><description>Clarke Quay is hosting &amp;ldquo;Once Upon A Nightmare,&amp;rdquo; a street party they&amp;rsquo;re calling the most frightening Halloween event of the year. The event, which is free to attend, will be hosted by popular radio DJs Justin Ang and Vernon A from 98.7FM’s Muttons On The Move.
Source: Clarke Quay.
Attendees can enjoy live music from local band Enigma and participate in themed games for a chance to win prizes. Guests are encouraged to dress up in their most twisted and imaginative interpretations of fairytale characters.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay to celebrate F1 with special meal promotions and parties at Attica</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 18:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay website.
Clarke Quay is celebrating the Singapore Grand Prix season with special offers and events for both racing fans and those just looking to enjoy the festivities.
Everyone can take advantage of dining deals like buy-one-get-one-free offers at District 10, special Grand Prix menu items at Hooters, and a free meal for every four diners at Peony Jade.
Those with Grand Prix tickets can also enjoy discounts of 10% to 20% at participating restaurants.</description></item></channel></rss>