<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>International Business on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-business/</link><description>Recent content in International Business on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:52:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GTT Expands Ethernet Footprint With PacketExchange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</guid><description>GTT, a global telecommunications company, is expanding its Ethernet services globally by acquiring PacketExchange, an Ethernet provider. PacketExchange, based in London, boasts a substantial 10 Gigabit fiber optic IP network spanning Europe, the United States, and Asia, largely acquired through its acquisition of MZIMA Networks in 2010. This combined infrastructure offers private line services, MPLS, VPLS networking, and peering capabilities.
This acquisition highlights the growing dominance of Carrier Ethernet in telecommunications.</description></item><item><title>Your Cell Phone Is A Tool For International Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-a-tool-for-international-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-a-tool-for-international-business/</guid><description>If you do business internationally, your cell phone can be a valuable tool for staying connected with clients abroad.
While your current cell phone plan might cover local and domestic long-distance calls, it could be expensive or even impossible to make international calls. You might find yourself waiting to use your landline or VoIP service, which can be inconvenient and even cause you to lose business. A better solution is to use a low-cost international dial-around service.</description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Routes To Europe and Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-routes-to-europe-and-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 08:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-routes-to-europe-and-asia/</guid><description>Numerous American companies establish branches in the UK and Europe, while multinational corporations operate globally. A prevalent solution for connecting these international offices, including cloud services, is low-latency fiber optic routes. The term &amp;ldquo;low latency,&amp;rdquo; once obscure, gained prominence with the shift from traditional phone lines to VoIP. Previously, it primarily described delays in satellite communication.
The question arises: why the emphasis on low-latency fiber routes now? Aren&amp;rsquo;t fiber connections inherently low latency?</description></item><item><title>Better Network Connectivity Into France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</guid><description>Globalization is increasingly common, and even companies without a multinational presence often conduct business internationally. The European Union, with its vast pool of consumers and producers, is a significant market, and France stands out as a key destination within the EU.
Level 3 Communications, a major telecommunications provider, recently enhanced its resources, infrastructure, and services for French enterprise customers. The company expanded its network reach with additional Points of Presence (POPs) in Paris and its surrounding areas, along with core network extensions in Lille, Lyon, and Toulouse.</description></item></channel></rss>