<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sex Discrimination on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sex-discrimination/</link><description>Recent content in Sex Discrimination on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sex-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU's decision on the importance of parenthood in EU law slips away from us.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Most EU laws and court decisions on sex discrimination focus on improving women&amp;rsquo;s job opportunities and ensuring equal treatment in the workplace. A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Maistrellis case tackles these issues from a different perspective: a father&amp;rsquo;s access to parental leave when the mother isn&amp;rsquo;t employed or looking for work. This judgment brings up important questions about how EU employment and discrimination laws affect family life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contemplating EU Gender Equality Law on Surrogate Mothers' Day in Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:57:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The desire to have children has always been deeply understood, especially for women facing medical obstacles to childbirth. Adoption was the traditional solution, but recent decades have introduced alternatives like IVF and surrogacy.
While the EU doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly regulate these practices, it does address maternity leave through the Pregnant Workers&amp;rsquo; Directive. The Directive on Sex Discrimination in Employment further tackles the employment aspects of pregnancy. This directive prohibits discrimination against women undergoing IVF treatment even before pregnancy, as established by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Mayr case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The rights of pregnant workers and the free movement rights of EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Jessy Saint Prix, a young woman from France, relocated to Britain in 2006 to pursue a teaching career. Her experience led her to learn much more about EU law and the English legal system than she expected.
After working in the UK as a teaching assistant for a year, she began a teacher training program (PGCE). During the program, she became pregnant and decided to pause her studies to register with a teaching agency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Expanding the margin of appreciation: France's prohibition on public face-veiling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 05:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</guid><description>The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) has ruled on a highly anticipated case, SAS v France, concerning France&amp;rsquo;s 2010 law prohibiting face coverings in public. The case was brought by a French woman, represented by British lawyers, who argued that the law violated several articles of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), including the right to freedom of religion, expression, and association, as well as protection from discrimination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New mothers who are self-employed and the EU free movement law: the CJEU reaches the expected decision.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
* For further information on EU free movement law issues, refer to the upcoming second edition of the commentary on the EU Citizenship Directive, authored by Elspeth Guild, Steve Peers, and Jonathan Tomkin – available soon
A pertinent question arises when an EU citizen relocates to another Member State and gives birth: do new mothers risk losing their rights under EU free movement law?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU truly dedicated to addressing violence against women, or is it just empty words?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre of the University of Oxford - @CateBriddick
Background
The European Union (EU) has a core legal commitment to fight discrimination, including sex-based discrimination, and to promote gender equality. However, it has faced ongoing and valid criticism for not upholding these commitments, especially regarding its treatment of female migrants and refugees. Therefore, the Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2016 announcement that the EU would sign and ratify the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women (the Istanbul Convention) was welcomed by activists and academics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it against EU law to tolerate discrimination against women who are breastfeeding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, leader of the UK Independence Party, recently expressed that while he personally had no issue with public breastfeeding, businesses should set their own rules. He suggested businesses could ask breastfeeding women to move to a less conspicuous area, implying a discreet approach would be preferable.
His statement was prompted by incidents where a restaurant asked a woman to cover her baby while breastfeeding and another establishment suggested using the disabled restroom for this purpose...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Referendum Briefing 6: The Impact on EU Employment and Equality Law Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers suggests that while some claim there would be a &amp;ldquo;bonfire of rights&amp;rdquo; if the UK left the EU, particularly in employment and equality, others argue that the EU has no bearing on these laws in the UK. This post will demonstrate that EU law has significantly improved employment and equality rights in the UK, especially for women in the workplace.
A study of all UK cases reaching the EU court concerning these issues reveals that 60% of cases involving equal treatment for women resulted in findings that UK law was inadequate, leading to improved workplace protections for women...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Commission's Proposal on gender quotas in corporate boards suggests a 40% representation of Venus and 60% representation of Mars.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-proposal-on-gender-quotas-in-corporate-boards-suggests-a-40-representation-of-venus-and-60-representation-of-mars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 13:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-proposal-on-gender-quotas-in-corporate-boards-suggests-a-40-representation-of-venus-and-60-representation-of-mars/</guid><description>Juan Carlos Benito Sánchez, LL.M. Candidate at KU Leuven — Twitter @jcbensan
The European Union faces a significant gender diversity challenge in its top corporate leadership positions. Although more than half of European university graduates are women, they remain underrepresented on company boards. Men outnumber women nearly four to one in these positions, with significant disparities among member states, ranging from under five percent female representation to over thirty percent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-proposal-on-gender-quotas-in-corporate-boards-suggests-a-40-representation-of-venus-and-60-representation-of-mars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-proposal-on-gender-quotas-in-corporate-boards-suggests-a-40-representation-of-venus-and-60-representation-of-mars/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>