<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experience on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/experience/</link><description>Recent content in Experience on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has identified Tokyo, Singapore, and Dubai as some of the top choices in its Cities Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</guid><description>Singapore at night.
The travel website TripAdvisor recently published its second annual Cities Survey, which collected data from over 54,000 user reviews. The survey evaluated cities worldwide based on traveler feedback.
Tokyo received the highest ranking for providing the best overall travel experience. It also earned top scores for its helpful residents, taxi services, public transportation, and clean streets. Tokyo ranked among the top ten cities in 13 out of 16 survey categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Drone Experience Program by JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp; Resorts is launching in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. View from a DJI drone.
JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and drone manufacturer DJI have partnered to introduce the brand&amp;rsquo;s first Drone Experience Program.
This program will allow guests to try out DJI&amp;rsquo;s drone technology and experience JW Marriott properties from a fresh perspective. They can also capture and share these unique moments with loved ones.
Launching on November 12, 2016, at JW Marriott Zhejiang Anji, the program will feature on-site sessions hosted by DJI experts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>