<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lit Building on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lit-building/</link><description>Recent content in Lit Building on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lit-building/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>I Want Fiber But Not Construction Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has become the top choice for business private lines and internet connections. It offers a practically unlimited capacity with minimal latency, packet loss, and jitter. Prices are now more competitive than before, provided you don&amp;rsquo;t encounter high construction costs.
Why Fiber Can Involve Construction Expenses
Businesses accustomed to T1 lines, Ethernet over Copper, or business cable might be surprised by quotes that include substantial construction costs for installing a fiber line.</description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands.</description></item><item><title>Looking For A Lit Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</guid><description>When seeking high-speed internet for your business, you need more than just a building with lights on at night. You need a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; – one connected to a fiber optic network.
Fiber optic connectivity is crucial for high bandwidth. While most buildings have copper wiring for traditional phone lines and T1 connections, these offer limited bandwidth (1.5 Mbps per line). Fiber optics, on the other hand, provide significantly faster speeds (10 Gbps or more per fiber) using light to transmit data.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward.</description></item></channel></rss>