<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bluetooth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bluetooth/</link><description>Recent content in Bluetooth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bluetooth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bose's Bluetooth speakers and headphones simplify the process of making connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</guid><description>Bose has expanded its SoundLink mobile audio lineup with two new products: the SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker, their most budget-friendly SoundLink speaker yet, and the SoundLink Bluetooth on-ear headphones, Bose&amp;rsquo;s first foray into on-ear Bluetooth headphones.
The SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker features a brand new design. Weighing in at 1.25 pounds (567g), it measures 5 inches wide, 2.1 inches deep, and 5.3 inches high. Bose has engineered the speaker with dual-opposing passive radiators and two high-efficiency transducers to deliver powerful, full-range sound, including impressive bass performance.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit WiFi For Video Streaming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</guid><description>WiFi has become the standard wireless connection due to its widespread availability, outpacing technologies like Bluetooth and WiMax. While cellular data is useful in the absence of WiFi, its limited bandwidth and potential for overage charges make it a secondary choice. In fact, data shows that most tablet users don&amp;rsquo;t even utilize their device&amp;rsquo;s cellular capabilities. WiFi&amp;rsquo;s strength is evident in its ability to not only replace cellular broadband but also wired connections.</description></item><item><title>The Altec Lansing Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds come with noise isolation and GPS tracking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>Source: Altec Lansing. The Freedom True Wireless
Bluetooth Earbuds have rechargeable lithium
ion batteries.
Altec Lansing&amp;rsquo;s new Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds offer a truly wireless experience, featuring rechargeable lithium-ion batteries integrated into the earbud housings.
These innovative earbuds boast a six-hour battery life, IPX7-rated waterproof construction for sweat resistance, and Bluetooth-based GPS tracking to easily locate misplaced earbuds.
Expected to launch in the second quarter of 2016 with a manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s suggested retail price of US$149.</description></item><item><title>Tile's tiles bring the Internet of Things to life, even without an internet connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tile-s-tiles-bring-the-internet-of-things-to-life-even-without-an-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tile-s-tiles-bring-the-internet-of-things-to-life-even-without-an-internet-connection/</guid><description>You may have heard of the Internet of Things, but dismissed it as irrelevant to you. However, consider the startup Tile, which aims to become a global &amp;ldquo;lost and found&amp;rdquo; system.
Tile isn&amp;rsquo;t about internet-connected refrigerators spamming people. Instead, it involves small, attachable devices that can be placed on keychains and other items to prevent them from getting lost.
[Image of Tile device]
Source: Tile website.
Technically, Tile devices don&amp;rsquo;t directly connect to the internet.</description></item><item><title>HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 Bluetooth earphones are now available in Singapore through Huawei's official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</guid><description>Huawei Singapore has introduced the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3, stereo Bluetooth earphones with a groundbreaking open-fit design that incorporates active noise cancellation.
Source: Huawei. Eager customers queue at SITEX to buy the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 on November 30, 2019.
As the new year approaches, Huawei is focused on creating a comprehensive product ecosystem in Singapore, allowing customers to experience seamless connectivity between their smartphones and other devices such as the new Huawei Watch GT 2 and Gentle Monster – Huawei Eyewear.</description></item><item><title>Is Twitter Really 75 Years Old?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</guid><description>You might be amazed to discover that the core concept of Twitter predates you, your parents, and possibly even your grandparents.
While Twitter itself wasn&amp;rsquo;t around back then, a similar idea existed. In 1935, London had the &amp;ldquo;Notificator,&amp;rdquo; a robot messenger described by BoingBoing. This public vending machine allowed people to leave notes for friends. Users could write messages on a continuous paper strip, insert a coin, and their message would move up, making room for the next one.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the fast Phone Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</guid><description>The Phone Finder helps locate lost smartphones, even if they&amp;rsquo;re on silent mode, for up to three years. When the Phone Finder device is clicked within 15 meters of the missing phone, the phone will ring, vibrate, and flash, making it easier to find. If the phone is out of range, the Phone Finder website displays its location on a map.
Source: Kickstarter
Creator Gabsow Tom selected Bluetooth 2.1 for its forward and backward compatibility, allowing the Phone Finder to work with any smartphone, regardless of its iOS or Android version.</description></item><item><title>Jabra introduces the Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company known for creating intelligent audio devices, has introduced the Jabra Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset. This new headset is a unified communication (UC) upgrade from their original Jabra Stealth and is designed specifically for professionals who are often on the go.
Weighing in at a mere 0.24 ounces (approximately 6.8 grams), the Jabra Stealth UC is remarkably lightweight, making it both inconspicuous and incredibly easy to carry around.</description></item><item><title>The main focus of Kickstarter is iFind, which is powered by ambient electromagnetic radiation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</guid><description>WeTag&amp;rsquo;s iFind tags use Bluetooth to connect with iOS or Android devices and don&amp;rsquo;t require charging. Like similar tracking devices, the tag is attached to an item and located using a smartphone.
If the item goes out of range, the &amp;lsquo;Rope&amp;rsquo; feature notifies the owner. The &amp;lsquo;UHelp&amp;rsquo; feature leverages nearby phones to help find the lost object through Bluetooth. WeTag highlights a unique feature: shaking the iFind tag will cause the paired phone to vibrate.</description></item></channel></rss>