<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>100 Gbps on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/100-gbps/</link><description>Recent content in 100 Gbps on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/100-gbps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comcast’s 100 Gbps Core Network Supports Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</guid><description>Over the past year, major telecom companies have been upgrading their core networks from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. Comcast recently joined this trend by incorporating Ciena&amp;rsquo;s Wave Logic 3 interfaces into their existing Ciena 6500 packet optical platforms. This begs the question: why would a cable company make this change, and how can it benefit your business?
Comcast is widely recognized as a Cable TV provider, or MSO (Multi-System Operator).</description></item><item><title>Qwest Brings 100 Gbps to Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</guid><description>Qwest is increasing its long haul network bandwidth from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. The implementation of this upgrade is underway and will continue throughout the following year.
What implications does this have for your company? Qwest provided examples of the speed of 100 Gbps point-to-point network traffic. Imagine downloading 138 DVDs (4.7 Gigabytes each) in just 60 seconds. A 2-hour HD movie or presentation could be transferred in a mere 9 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>Ciena Takes New Bandwidth Technologies On The Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</guid><description>Today, June 29th, those in Waltham, MA can experience cutting-edge carrier bandwidth technology firsthand. Visit the Ciena Innovation Lab to see live demonstrations of their latest optical, Ethernet, and software solutions. The lab will move to its next location in White Marsh, MD on July 15th.
What exactly is the Ciena Innovation Lab? It&amp;rsquo;s a mobile showcase housed in a semi-trailer, packed with the most recent advancements in telecom and networking.</description></item><item><title>Juniper Has Routers For The 100 Gbps WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</guid><description>Verizon and Juniper are partnering on a large-scale project to implement 100 Gbps fiber optic connections to meet the increasing demand for faster internet speeds.
While carriers have experimented with 100 Gbps transmission, which is significantly faster than the typical 10 Gbps long-haul networks, it seems that widespread adoption is on the horizon. Juniper has developed an interface capable of handling this bandwidth directly, eliminating the need for carriers to combine multiple links.</description></item></channel></rss>