<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SAP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sap/</link><description>Recent content in SAP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Southeast Asia is leading the way in digital transformation and digital leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</guid><description>Source: SAP. Agree or disagree? Management and staff in Southeast Asia and globally share their thoughts in the Leaders 2020 study.
Almost 25% of Southeast Asian companies are considered digital leaders, according to a recent study by SAP and Oxford Economics. This figure surpasses the global average of 16% reported in the Leaders 2020 study.
This new category of high-achieving companies reports greater profit increases, improved employee engagement, and more inclusive workplace environments.</description></item><item><title>Find joy through organizing your business travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</guid><description>Source: SAP Concur. View from a plane window.
SAP Concur draws parallels between decluttering and business travel, suggesting innovative ways to improve efficiency for travelers.
Andy Watson, SVP and GM for Asia Pacific Japan and Greater China at SAP Concur, believes that just as a messy home can be transformed into a joyful space, technology can turn the often-dreaded experience of business travel into something enjoyable.
Traditionally, business travelers face several time-consuming tasks: manually searching and booking flights and accommodations, organizing multiple bookings, obtaining internal trip approvals, managing paper receipts, and manually filing expense claims upon return.</description></item><item><title>SAP reported that small and medium-sized enterprises in the Asia-Pacific region have adopted remote work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</guid><description>A recent study titled &amp;ldquo;Digital, Resilient, and Experience-driven: How Small and Midsize Organisations Can Prepare for the New Economy,&amp;rdquo; conducted by SAP in conjunction with Oxford Economics, reveals that small and mid-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the Asia-Pacific region are well-situated to flourish in the evolving business landscape following the COVID-19 pandemic.
The study, which surveyed 2,000 senior executives globally, including 832 from APAC countries like Singapore, Australia, and Japan, examined the priorities and digital readiness of SMEs.</description></item></channel></rss>