<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data/</link><description>Recent content in Data on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Caution: Superman is poisonous</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</guid><description>According to a McAfee blog post, Superman poses a significant online threat. The company argues that the widespread presence of superheroes beyond comic books allows hackers and scammers to exploit them for cybercrime.
McAfee&amp;rsquo;s survey, which used their SiteAdvisor site ratings, revealed that Superman is the &amp;ldquo;Most Toxic Superhero.&amp;rdquo; The study found that searches combining &amp;ldquo;Superman&amp;rdquo; with terms like &amp;ldquo;free torrent download,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;watch,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;free app,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; have a 16.5% chance of leading to websites containing threats like spyware, adware, spam, phishing, viruses, and other malware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel will be providing the option to share up to 50GB of mobile data at the PC Show 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</guid><description>Singtel is increasing its mobile data offerings with the launch of &amp;ldquo;DataMore,&amp;rdquo; a new plan featuring larger data bundles. This launch comes less than a month after Circles.Life entered the market with a focus on data options. DataMore is designed for users who need a lot of data and is shareable with multiple users, making it perfect for families.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Mobile Marketing, highlights that this plan caters to customer demand for larger data packages at affordable prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Be cautious of insiders when it comes to protecting data privacy: Infowatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</guid><description>The most significant danger to data privacy in Southeast Asia comes from internal actors. Cybersecurity firm InfoWatch Group&amp;rsquo;s recent study reveals that careless top executives and employees with access to sensitive data are the primary cause of data leaks in ASEAN nations.
The company states that executives, employees, IT administrators, and other authorized personnel caused slightly more than 56% of compromised data incidents in Southeast Asia. External attacks and former employees were responsible for the remaining 44%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Today is World Backup Day. Have you ensured the safety of your data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</guid><description>A recent worldwide study funded by Acronis, a prominent name in hybrid cloud data protection, highlights a rising awareness of the importance of safeguarding personal data on computers, mobile phones, and tablets.
Almost half of the surveyed individuals possess more than four devices per household requiring protection, and 45% are most afraid of misplacing photos and videos. Security and privacy were identified as crucial factors in data backup.
Evolving Concerns in Personal Data Security The traditional worries of hardware malfunctions and accidental deletions are no longer the sole reasons for data loss apprehension...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2017 is compatible with Facebook, wireless backups, and remote backups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:47:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</guid><description>Source: Acronis. Acronis True Image 2017.
Acronis, a major provider of hybrid cloud data protection, released Acronis True Image 2017, its newest personal backup software.
This iteration combines the existing full image local and cloud backup with new features such as wireless backup for mobile devices to either local Windows computers or the Acronis Cloud. It also allows for an unlimited number of mobile devices and provides complete Facebook account data backups...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circles.Life introduces a range of new services centered around unlimited usage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</guid><description>For S$3, enjoy unlimited on-demand data at 4G+ speeds.
For the first time, get unlimited WhatsApp roaming in 18 countries for S$1 per day.
Source: Circles.Life. Poster for Unlimited
Data on Demand. Circles.Life, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fourth mobile operator, argues that the current unlimited data plans are actually quite restrictive. They believe that these plans should not be limited to weekends, slowed down after a small data limit, or tied to yearly contracts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Box Zones provides customers with increased flexibility in choosing the locations for storing their data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</guid><description>The enterprise content management platform Box has introduced Box Zones, enabling companies to store their data regionally in Europe and Asia. Utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) and IBM Cloud, Box Zones will allow content to be stored in Germany, Ireland, Singapore, and Japan, based on customer requirements.
Box CEO and co-founder Aaron Levie highlighted that businesses are increasingly interconnected, collaborative, and global due to cloud technology. However, local regulations often compel companies to make technological compromises that hinder their growth and reduce employee productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub is offering a deal of 3GB for S$3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</guid><description>StarHub is offering a new &amp;ldquo;3GB-for-$3&amp;rdquo; data upsize option for its mobile postpaid customers. For a limited time, customers who sign up for or renew their StarHub 4G plans can get an extra 3GB of data for S$3 per month. This promotional price will increase to S$6 per month for customers who sign up on or after April 1, 2016.
Here are the details for StarHub&amp;rsquo;s two-year mobile postpaid plans:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces music services that do not use data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</guid><description>Singtel debuted its Singtel Music service, a first-of-its-kind offering in Singapore. For a fixed monthly price, subscribers gain access to music from Spotify, KKBOX, AMPed, and MeRadio without incurring data charges.
Representatives from Singtel Music at the launch event.
Singtel Music provides premium accounts from Spotify, KKBOX, or AMPed, enabling users to stream an extensive library of songs without data usage concerns. Additionally, they can enjoy 13 MeRadio stations without impacting their data allowance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get double the mobile data for just a small increase with Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Coinciding with the start of IT Show 2016, Singtel is introducing DataX2, a new service that doubles customers&amp;rsquo; monthly mobile data for a fixed price of S$5.90. This new option reflects Singtel&amp;rsquo;s focus on data-driven services, building on the success of last year&amp;rsquo;s SIM Only Plan.
DataX2 lets customers double their data when they sign up for or renew a Combo Mobile Plan (Combo 2 or higher)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell has launched backup appliances for midmarket businesses, along with complimentary Windows data recovery software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</guid><description>Dell has introduced new data protection solutions tailored for small and medium-sized businesses to enhance the protection of their crucial systems, applications, and data, both on-site and in cloud environments. These solutions include data deduplication appliance models and the new Dell Data Protection | Endpoint Recovery – Free Edition.
Back up more and store less The latest additions to the Dell DR series of deduplication appliances are the Dell DR4300e, DR4300, and DR6300...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transfer files from your phone without using up your mobile data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</guid><description>Xender, a Chinese app, simplifies phone-based file sharing without incurring mobile data costs using peer-to-peer technology.
For device-to-device transfers, Xender creates a local Wi-Fi hotspot that nearby users can join. This allows for the seamless sharing of photos, music, files, and apps between phones, proving particularly useful when upgrading to a new device. Xender boasts unlimited file sizes, cross-platform compatibility, and transfer speeds up to 50 times faster than Bluetooth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub reintroduces 12GB mobile data bundles and additional features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced a new, budget-friendly package called SurfHub, combining mobile and home internet services.
For a starting price of S$96.56 per month on a 24-month contract, SurfHub customers receive a 4G mobile plan with a minimum of 12GB of data and a 1Gbps fiber broadband connection for their homes. This combined offer costs roughly half the price of a standalone 12GB mobile plan. SurfHub also includes generous benefits like up to 700 minutes of local calls, 1,500 local SMS/MMS messages, and a subsidy for a new mobile phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your Pipes Fat Enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</guid><description>Higher resolution data demands more bandwidth, and WAN connections can become bottlenecks. Imagine a kink in a garden hose - the data is the water, and bandwidth is the pressure. Just as a kink restricts water flow, limited bandwidth slows data transfer, even with efficient network engineering. A larger pipe is needed for faster flow, just as a fatter data pipe is necessary for faster data transfer.
The increasing size and resolution of electronic business data necessitate these &amp;ldquo;fatter pipes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eliminating uncertainty in analytics with BeyondCore Apps for Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</guid><description>Source: BeyondCore website.
BeyondCore has introduced BeyondCore Apps for Office, a solution that provides automated analysis for the Microsoft Office suite with a single click. The company recognized the need for accessible and efficient analytics tools for business users who require data-driven insights to make informed decisions and improve their operations.
Arijit Sengupta, CEO and Founder of BeyondCore, highlighted the challenges of traditional analytics, describing it as a manual and time-consuming process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Learn about data science quickly with CEG Digital's online course</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</guid><description>CEG Digital, the flexible learning branch of global education provider Cambridge Education Group (CEG), has teamed up with the Web Science Institute at the University of Southampton (WSI), a top-100 university, to offer short online courses.
Dr. Elena Simperl, WSI Associate Professor and Scientific Director of the European Data Science Academy, emphasized the importance of data science skills, stating, &amp;ldquo;Data science is crucial for our economy. Our new series of short professional courses complement our postgraduate degrees and target decision-makers, business analysts, IT developers, and others interested in cutting-edge data science technologies and applications in fields like digital marketing, finance, and healthcare...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Router Included With Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</guid><description>Considering upgrading your voice or data bandwidth? DS3 service offers 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads, suitable for demanding tasks like video transfer, medical imaging, or call centers. But finding the right DS3 router for your network can feel like an added burden.
Rest assured, DS3 is a well-established technology with readily available equipment and decreasing prices. As more companies switch from T1 lines to DS3 bandwidth, implementation is becoming increasingly straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces an improved True Image family and guarantees regular updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</guid><description>Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, recently launched its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 products in Singapore.
During the launch event, Acronis Co-Founder and CEO, Serguei Beloussov, emphasized the increasing importance of data protection, stating that it will soon be as essential as basic necessities. He believes that data represents a comprehensive record of our lives and preserving it should be a top priority, with the goal of eventually retaining all data indefinitely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel now offers budget-friendly roaming options for Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
Singtel is introducing a new &amp;ldquo;Roam Like Home&amp;rdquo; DataRoam Saver plan for customers traveling to Australia. The DataRoam Saver Australia (Monthly) 1 GB plan is currently offered at a promotional price of S$10 for the first gigabyte of data. After exceeding this limit, users will be charged S$0.10 per megabyte.
Singtel claims this plan is the most budget-friendly option available and builds upon the success of the DataRoam Saver Malaysia (Monthly) 1 GB plan launched last October...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tableau Public undergoes a makeover as participation increases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</guid><description>Source: Tableau Public gallery. This Tableau Public visualization displays the world&amp;rsquo;s largest stadiums. Interact with the visualization here.
Tableau reported that 36,000 users joined Tableau Public in 2014, publishing a record number of data stories on the free platform. Tableau Public allows users to create, share, and discover data stories on the web. It comprises a downloadable authoring tool for exploring and visualizing data, a cloud platform for hosting, sharing, and embedding interactive visualizations, and a learning program offering support and training to a global community of data enthusiasts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Veeam introduces a new free backup tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 06:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</guid><description>Source: Veeam video.
Veeam has introduced a cost-free solution for creating backups of Windows desktops and laptops that doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessitate any extra software or costs.
Users have the flexibility to select their backup locations, including options such as external hard drives, shared folders on the network, and more. This free software from Veeam also offers the capability to generate bootable recovery media, proving useful when addressing computer issues that hinder the operating system from starting properly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub simplifies mobile customers' ability to browse and travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile postpaid customers can now subscribe to a Mobile DataTravel plan for S$15. This plan offers 2GB of data valid for 30 days, usable in a single country or across multiple destinations.
DataTravel eliminates the need to manually select or lock phones to specific mobile networks, unlike traditional roaming plans. StarHub highlights this as a unique advantage among Singaporean telcos and plans to expand its list of supported destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides triple the mobile data for a low price, along with Wi-Fi calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</guid><description>Singtel launched a new mobile data add-on called DataX3 at their iPhone 7 event held at Marina Bay Sands Convention Centre. For S$9.90 per month, DataX3 allows customers to triple their mobile data limit. This add-on is available to Singtel Combo Plan customers (Combo 2 and above). It follows the successful launch of the DataX2 add-on earlier this year.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, highlighted the importance of affordable mobile data for communication, shopping, banking, and entertainment in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circles.Life offers 20GB for just S$20 per month</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-offers-20gb-for-just-s-20-per-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-offers-20gb-for-just-s-20-per-month/</guid><description>Circles.Life subscribers can now enjoy a nearly unlimited data plan. For an extra S$20 each month, users can receive 20GB of data on top of their existing plan and bonus data.
Circles.Life, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fourth postpaid carrier and sole digital telco, now offers a plan with almost unlimited data for S$20 per month.
Circles.Life Co-Founder and Director Rameez Ansar stated, &amp;ldquo;Our mission is providing an exceptional customer experience to customers and giving them control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-offers-20gb-for-just-s-20-per-month/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-offers-20gb-for-just-s-20-per-month/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>