<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economic Policy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic-policy/</link><description>Recent content in Economic Policy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:42:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Preserving the euro: Gauweiler's challenge to the legality of the OMT program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
On June 16th, the Court of Justice ruled in the Gauweiler case, declaring the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program legal under EU law. This decision has significant implications for the ECB&amp;rsquo;s authority, the EU Economic and Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s constitutional structure, and the relationship between the Court of Justice and the referring court, the German Federal Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the ECB's OMT program in question? The Advocate-General's opinion in Gauweiler suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 01:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective (OUP)
On January 14th, Advocate General Cruz Villalon presented his legal opinion on the Gauweiler case (C-62/14), which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. He believes the OMT program generally complies with EU treaties, provided certain conditions are met if it&amp;rsquo;s activated in the future. This case has significant implications for the European Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s (EMU) constitutional framework, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s role, and the relationship between the German Constitutional Court (Bundesverfassungsgericht) and the Court of Justice of the EU.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Europe: A Preview of the Five Presidents' Report on EMU Completion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-europe-a-preview-of-the-five-presidents-report-on-emu-completion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 14:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-europe-a-preview-of-the-five-presidents-report-on-emu-completion/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis, DPhil student at University of Oxford, Academy of Athens scholar
In June 2015, the leaders of the EU and Euro area institutions released a report outlining a plan for strengthening and finalizing the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU). This report, based on crisis-combatting measures, offers numerous suggestions for improving the EMU&amp;rsquo;s governance and deepening economic integration within the Euro area. The EU Presidents suggest advancing towards a unified economic, financial, fiscal, and political system.</description></item></channel></rss>