<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Relationship on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/relationship/</link><description>Recent content in Relationship on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:19:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/relationship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Chinese New Year promotion by Digi highlights the importance of family and tradition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</guid><description>Source: Digi website.
For many Chinese individuals, the Chinese New Year signifies the only opportunity to reconnect with distant family members. Malaysian telecommunications company Digi is capitalizing on this tradition with a new promotional campaign designed for a global audience.
Recognizing that in today&amp;rsquo;s world, many individuals simply use titles like &amp;lsquo;aunt,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;uncle,&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cousin&amp;rsquo; for relatives beyond their immediate family, Digi&amp;rsquo;s campaign encourages the use of more precise family titles within Chinese families.</description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features.</description></item></channel></rss>