<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it/</link><description>Recent content in IT on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:57:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singaporean IT leaders are concerned that a shortage of skills could impede the progress of the Smart Nation initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</guid><description>93% of Singaporean Chief Information Officers (CIOs) are worried that Singapore lacks the IT talent pool needed to successfully implement Smart Nation initiatives.
Six out of 10 CIOs believe Smart Nation initiatives will lead to more IT jobs, and 53% believe these initiatives will boost average IT salaries.
New independent research* commissioned by specialized recruiter Robert Half reveals that over 9 in 10 (93%) Singaporean IT leaders are concerned about the lack of readily available IT talent in Singapore to build a Smart Nation-ready workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IT Departments are Wearin' the Green</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</guid><description>Maintaining IT budgets requires more than just good fortune these days. Many companies are discovering that environmentally friendly practices can save them money. These eco-conscious choices benefit both the planet and their bottom line.
One of the first areas to examine is electricity consumption. Power usage can be deceptive because it often occurs in small, unnoticeable increments. Every desktop computer, even when idle, contributes to the overall energy use, measured in watt-hours and kilowatt-hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The World Economic Forum introduces its inaugural online leadership module for professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</guid><description>Professionals can now register for the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s first online leadership program, Global Information Technology Outlook. This six-week module, created for senior executives and fast-track leadership programs, offers a comprehensive overview of important new technologies transforming industries and society.
Professor Klaus Schwab, Founder and Executive Chairman of the World Economic Forum, highlighted the challenges leaders face understanding the increasingly complex and unpredictable world, largely due to rapid technological advancements. He stated that the Forum Academy module addresses this by giving leaders a better grasp of ongoing information technology transformations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For the initial six months, HP Touchpoint Manager is being offered at a discounted rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Touchpoint Manager, a cloud-based IT management solution specifically designed for small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs).
Managing IT systems has become more challenging due to the increasing variety of devices and operating systems used in business, from company-provided equipment to personal devices.
HP Touchpoint Manager simplifies IT management for SMBs, helping them ensure device functionality, data security, and IT staff effectiveness. Its adaptability allows it to manage a wide array of devices and operating systems, including iOS, Android, and Windows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Solarwinds is advocating for the recognition of IT personnel on September 15th as IT Professionals Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</guid><description>SolarWinds, a company that provides software for managing hybrid IT infrastructures, has declared the third Tuesday of September (starting on September 15, 2015) as IT Professionals Day. This day is meant to show appreciation for IT professionals, recognizing their often-unsung contributions to modern businesses.
To mark IT Professionals Day, SolarWinds published the findings of their IT Pro Value Survey. This research highlights the significant contributions of Singaporean IT professionals. It examines how much end-users value IT departments and explores how valued IT professionals feel within their organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Workaholic and Proud of IT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 22:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re deeply involved in technology, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you might identify as a workaholic. Did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a day specifically for acknowledging workaholics? It&amp;rsquo;s not an official holiday, of course, as that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t align with the workaholic spirit. Workaholics Day falls on July 5th, the day after most people are recovering from their Fourth of July festivities.
While others are recovering from fireworks or tending to minor burns, you might find yourself busy with crucial hardware upgrades in a server room...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>