<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IOS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ios/</link><description>Recent content in IOS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars.</description></item><item><title>Tile's tiles bring the Internet of Things to life, even without an internet connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tile-s-tiles-bring-the-internet-of-things-to-life-even-without-an-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tile-s-tiles-bring-the-internet-of-things-to-life-even-without-an-internet-connection/</guid><description>You may have heard of the Internet of Things, but dismissed it as irrelevant to you. However, consider the startup Tile, which aims to become a global &amp;ldquo;lost and found&amp;rdquo; system.
Tile isn&amp;rsquo;t about internet-connected refrigerators spamming people. Instead, it involves small, attachable devices that can be placed on keychains and other items to prevent them from getting lost.
[Image of Tile device]
Source: Tile website.
Technically, Tile devices don&amp;rsquo;t directly connect to the internet.</description></item><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer.</description></item><item><title>The HandySpeech app, which converts handwriting to speech, is now available on Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</guid><description>iSpeak4U, a company known for developing mobile apps for individuals with speech and hearing impairments, has launched an Android version of their app HandySpeech. This app offers a simple and efficient communication tool for those with speech difficulties.
Source: iSpeak4U. HandySpeech running on various devices.
With HandySpeech, users can input text on a device screen using their finger or a stylus, and the device will then vocalize the written words. The app is designed to store frequently used phrases and adapt to the user&amp;rsquo;s handwriting style.</description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security.</description></item><item><title>iOS 9 has been released by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple has announced that its latest mobile operating system, iOS 9, will launch on September 16th. This free update for iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch users boasts enhanced search capabilities and improved Siri functionality.
One of the standout features of iOS 9 is its new multitasking capabilities for iPad. Users can now work with two apps concurrently, viewing them side-by-side. A Picture-in-Picture feature also allows for video playback while using other apps.</description></item><item><title>Singtel announces pricing for iPhone SE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Singtel has revealed its plans to offer Apple&amp;rsquo;s 4-inch iPhone SE starting March 31, 2016. Customers can pre-order the device now. A 16 GB model with the most affordable plan, costing S$27.90 per month for two years, is priced at S$350.
The telecom provider recently conducted a crowdsourced study, highlighting its superior 4G network speed and coverage in Singapore. The study, based on data from IDA&amp;rsquo;s MyConnection SG crowdsourced survey and 4G Mobile Service Coverage results, positioned Singtel as a frontrunner.</description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings.</description></item><item><title>Access PC or Mac applications from iOS and Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</guid><description>Source: Parallels website.
Parallels has launched an updated version of its Parallels Access app for iOS and Android. The app allows for remote access to both PCs and Macs, letting users access files and run applications while on the move.
With Parallels Access, mobile devices can remotely utilize applications, edit documents, and search through files on a connected computer. Users can connect to any computer through a web browser without needing additional plugins or extensions.</description></item><item><title>Fishbat provides commentary on the latest developments in iOS8 and the introduction of Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple, the tech giant, recently launched the first beta version of iOS 8.1. This upgrade comes shortly after the release of iOS 8.0.2, which was itself a fix for a bug found in the recently launched iOS 8.0.1.
This new beta version offers several new features:
A redesigned icon for iBooks. An option to enable dictation within the keyboard settings. Updated application permission settings. Larger application icons specifically designed for the new widgets in the notification center.</description></item><item><title>The new version of Flickr is now available for iOS 9</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 02:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s Flickr app for iOS 9 now includes features designed for the updated operating system.
Source: Yahoo.
The app utilizes 3D Touch on the latest iPhones. This allows users to preview content by pressing lightly on the screen. For example, in the Camera Roll, lightly pressing a photo shows a preview, while a harder press expands it to full screen.
Another 3D Touch feature, &amp;ldquo;Quick Actions,&amp;rdquo; lets users perform certain tasks directly from the app icon.</description></item><item><title>The language learning app HelloTalk has reached 1 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</guid><description>Source: HelloTalk app page at the Play Store.
The mobile language learning app HelloTalk has reached over one million registered users globally, according to its developer, HelloTalk.
The HelloTalk app allows users to teach each other their native languages using their mobile devices. Users can communicate in real-time with native speakers through various features, helping them practice their target language.
Over one million HelloTalk users, representing over 200 countries, use the app to learn various languages.</description></item></channel></rss>