<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Euromonitor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/euromonitor/</link><description>Recent content in Euromonitor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/euromonitor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry.</description></item><item><title>The demand for milk and yogurt-based beverages is increasing in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Increased advertising in mass media, along with more television shows and magazine content focused on health topics, have made Indonesian consumers more aware of the advantages of drinking milk from 2011 to 2016, according to Euromonitor.
Ultrajaya Milk Industry &amp;amp; Trading Company leads the drinking milk market, holding a 23% value share in 2016. Its most recognized brand is Ultra. Euromonitor attributes the company&amp;rsquo;s success in flavored milk to its strong marketing and enhanced distribution.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor outlines four key pillars for a successful expansion into emerging markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, has published an e-book titled &amp;ldquo;Succeed in Emerging Markets: Selection, Strategy and First Steps&amp;rdquo;. This e-book presents a four-pillar model designed to guide businesses entering emerging markets.
The first pillar, &amp;ldquo;market,&amp;rdquo; examines macroeconomic stability, consumer market size, growth, and openness.
The second pillar, &amp;ldquo;population,&amp;rdquo; delves into demographics to help businesses assess how their products or services align with the competitive landscape.
The third pillar, &amp;ldquo;access,&amp;rdquo; evaluates the ease of market entry.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate is considered the most popular indulgence product in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesians are increasingly understanding the advantages of moderate chocolate consumption, leading to consistent purchases for snacking and special occasions. This trend fueled growth in chocolate confectionery sales in 2016, according to research firm Euromonitor. The company predicts chocolate confectionery will remain the preferred treat for Indonesian consumers of all ages.
Ceres PT, a major player in the Indonesian chocolate market, held a commanding 52% market share in 2016. Euromonitor attributes this success to the company&amp;rsquo;s strong brand reputation, diverse product range, and competitive pricing.</description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Economic Community has the potential to be a goldmine for B2C businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, has published a white paper outlining a strategic framework for marketing to ASEAN consumers.
The establishment of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in December 2015 will unify the ten ASEAN member states into a single market and production hub. This development is anticipated to draw significant attention from multinational corporations that have traditionally focused on China and India. Euromonitor suggests that the AEC is on track to become a global economic powerhouse due to its projected robust economic growth.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor has discovered that India and China have lower-than-average per capita calorie purchases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</guid><description>A new study by Euromonitor International reveals how many nutrients people consume daily from packaged foods and beverages. This data, found in their Passport: Nutrition database, tracks the consumption of calories, fats, saturated fats, carbohydrates, sugars, salt, protein, and fiber across 54 countries.
Globally, we buy enough packaged food and soft drinks to consume 1.5 trillion calories per day, averaging 765 calories per person. While a healthy daily intake is around 2,000 calories, North America and Western Europe exceed 1,500 calories, contrasting with India&amp;rsquo;s 150 and China&amp;rsquo;s 510.</description></item><item><title>Casual dining is becoming more popular globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</guid><description>A global market research firm, Euromonitor International, determined that consumer food service sales increased by 5.7% worldwide in 2015, a rise from the previous year&amp;rsquo;s growth rate of 5.3%. Fast casual dining experienced the most significant growth within the industry at 10.4%, generating an extra US$3.4 billion in revenue between 2014 and 2015.
Elizabeth Friend, a Consumer Foodservice Strategy Analyst at Euromonitor International, observed, &amp;ldquo;Consumers are changing their dining habits, especially in developed countries.</description></item><item><title>Limited edition experiences are a popular trend in the food service industry in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</guid><description>In 2015, Australian diners increasingly embraced their inner foodies, craving novel culinary experiences. Food service operators responded with innovation, experimenting with formats, menus, and dining concepts, according to a Euromonitor blog post.
One example highlighted by the research firm is Hotel Marriott in Melbourne&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Table for 12&amp;rdquo; concept, launched in October 2015. This exclusive dining experience offered a four-course degustation menu for a limited group of twelve guests, available only one night a week.</description></item><item><title>The ideal location for candy in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT is a dominant player in the Indonesian confectionery market, particularly recognized for its Mentos brand.
According to a report on the Indonesian confectionery sector by market research firm Euromonitor, the wide array of inexpensive sugary treats, combined with robust marketing campaigns from prominent manufacturers, has propelled sales in this category within Indonesia.
Holding a commanding 23% market share in 2016, Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT remains the leader in the sugar confectionery sector.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor categorizes audiences into seven different consumer types</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-categorizes-audiences-into-seven-different-consumer-types/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 17:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-categorizes-audiences-into-seven-different-consumer-types/</guid><description>Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Survey team has identified seven distinct global consumer types based on their Global Consumer Trends survey: the Undaunted Striver, Impulsive Spender, Balanced Optimist, Aspiring Struggler, Conservative Homebody, Independent Skeptic and Secure Traditionalist.
Source: Euromonitor
website.
Each consumer type exhibits unique preferences and habits, even when sharing similar demographics. For instance, the relatively young Impulsive Spender views life as busy but exciting, characterized by a social, indulgent, and friend-oriented nature. Conversely, Independent Skeptics, also categorized as young consumers, define themselves by living life on their own terms, embracing unconventionality, skepticism, and indifference.</description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031.</description></item><item><title>The premium image of cheese is advantageous in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesian families, especially those residing in major urban areas, are anticipated to increasingly incorporate cheese as a staple ingredient in their meals. This trend is linked to a growing consumer preference for preparing Western dishes, such as pizzas, pastas, cakes, pastries, and toast, which often feature cheese, within their own homes, as indicated by research conducted by Euromonitor. A notable shift in preference is the rising popularity of cheese paired with white bread, replacing traditional spreads like chocolate sprinkles, jam, or honey.</description></item><item><title>The top 10 global consumer trends for 2015 focus on multitasking and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor.
Market research firm Euromonitor International recently published their findings on the top 10 global consumer trends for 2015.
Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Global Consumer Trends 2015 report states that consumers, pressed for time, are seeking convenience, diverse options, global product availability, and instant satisfaction. They aim to get the most out of their time and money, looking for products and services that meet multiple needs. As an illustration, a Swedish taxi service provides in-car therapists for their stressed and busy clients at a rate of US$165 per hour.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports a decrease in luxury demand in China and an increase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, predicts the global luxury goods industry will experience a 19% growth, reaching $405 billion by 2019.
Fflur Roberts, the Head of Luxury Goods Research at Euromonitor, pointed out China&amp;rsquo;s significant luxury market growth of $9.6 billion over the past five years. She noted that this growth, while impressive, slowed at the end of 2013, prompting luxury brands to reassess their strategies in China and other emerging markets.</description></item><item><title>A recent Euromonitor survey reveals sugar as a new culprit in the food industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has observed a growing global trend of consumers turning against sugar. This shift in attitude stems from heightened awareness of its health implications.
Consumers are actively trying to decrease or eliminate sugar from their diets, with a significant 42% actively looking for food labels indicating low or no added sugar, according to Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Global Consumer Trends Survey.
&amp;ldquo;Sugar is now widely perceived as a health risk, with some even equating it to tobacco in terms of toxicity,&amp;rdquo; says Gina Westbrook, Director of Strategy Briefings at Euromonitor International.</description></item><item><title>There is a growing trend of adults purchasing toys and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</guid><description>In 2016, games and puzzles experienced an 8% surge in the global market, surpassing construction toys as the fastest-growing toy category, according to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm. This impressive growth also marks the highest for the category since 2002.
Although construction toys saw a growth of 7.8% in 2016, a dip compared to the double-digit growth of 2015, they still dominated the traditional toys and games market with a value of US$10 billion.</description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports that skincare is a popular trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has reported that the global beauty industry is experiencing growth, particularly in emerging markets, as consumers increasingly adopt more comprehensive beauty routines and upgrade to premium products.
Skincare stands out as the dominant segment in most markets, with global sales projected to exceed US$130 billion by 2019. &amp;ldquo;Consumers are allocating a significant portion of their beauty spending on skincare, averaging US$15 per person annually,&amp;rdquo; notes Irina Barbalova, Head of Beauty and Personal Care at Euromonitor International.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor examines consumer opportunities for individuals aged 60 and above</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 12:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Market research firm Euromonitor International has published a new report on the growing market of older consumers. Though businesses have often overlooked this demographic— individuals aged 60 and above— due to perceptions of low spending, limited income, and resistance to marketing, this group is expanding rapidly.
In 2014, the global population aged 60 and over reached 912 million, accounting for 12.6% of the total. By 2030, this segment is projected to increase to 1.</description></item></channel></rss>