<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Relocation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/relocation/</link><description>Recent content in Relocation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:30:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/relocation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The ECJ has upheld the EU law on relocating asylum-seekers, but some question if it is a Pyrrhic victory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</guid><description>The EU Court Rules on Refugee Relocation: A Pyrrhic Victory? Professor Steve Peers examines the European Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s (ECJ) decision regarding the mandatory relocation of asylum-seekers, highlighting the complex interplay between legal effectiveness and political realities.
In 2015, facing a significant influx of asylum-seekers, the EU implemented a measure requiring member states to relocate 160,000 individuals from overburdened Italy and Greece. This decision faced resistance, particularly a legal challenge from Slovakia and Hungary, questioning its legal basis and practicality.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft EU/Turkey agreement on migration and refugees legally sound?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent legal debates have arisen concerning the proposed EU/Turkey agreement on refugees. While general points were discussed last month, a leaked draft of the final deal necessitates a closer examination before the finalizing summit.
The agreement, framed as an EU-Turkey statement, builds upon the March 7, 2016, statement with added elements. It is crucial to note that as a statement, it won&amp;rsquo;t be legally binding, requiring no formal EU or national approval beyond the summit&amp;rsquo;s endorsement.</description></item><item><title>EU Law and Policy on the Relocation of Asylum-Seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers recently discussed the legal aspects of the refugee crisis, focusing on international law. This post will examine the relocation of asylum-seekers within the EU, a topic that has sparked considerable debate. The EU recently passed a second decision on this matter, facing opposition from several member states. This decision follows an earlier one from September. Both are temporary measures, effective for two years, but there is a proposal for a permanent system.</description></item><item><title>Making The Move For Higher Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 18:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</guid><description>Are you experiencing bandwidth limitations in your organization? With the rapid advancement of online technology, many organizations are facing a shortage of bandwidth. While contacting your service provider to increase your line speed might seem like the solution, they might inform you that you already have the maximum speed available. So, what are your options?
Have you thought about relocating? Bandwidth availability and cost vary significantly by location. Some places have many choices and reasonable prices, while others might not be able to meet your basic needs regardless of your budget.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries.</description></item><item><title>Preserving the Formal Rule of Law in the EU's Asylum Policy: The CJEU's Ruling on the Asylum Relocation Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, Ph.D. Researcher in European Union Law at the School of Law and Government of Dublin City University*
*Reblogged from the Bridge Network blog
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling found Poland, Hungary, and the Czech Republic to be in violation of European Union (EU) law. The violation stems from their failure to implement two Council Decisions outlining the relocation of asylum seekers.</description></item><item><title>Best investment migration programmes for wealthy individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</guid><description>The increased global demand for residence and citizenship-by-investment programs, particularly among wealthy investors, highlights the desire to overcome limitations posed by single jurisdictions in the wake of COVID-19. Recognizing this, Deep Knowledge Analytics and Henley &amp;amp; Partners have collaborated to create the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
Source: Henley &amp;amp; Partners website. Illustration for the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
This digital publication provides a detailed analysis, interactive tools, and unique perspectives on the efficiency of countries offering these programs during the pandemic, and their potential as future havens for longevity.</description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly.</description></item></channel></rss>