<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet/</link><description>Recent content in Internet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hasso Plattner Institute is offering a free six-week MOOC on the Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</guid><description>The Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) is offering a free, six-week online course in English about the fundamentals of the Internet. Starting on March 31st, HPI&amp;rsquo;s director, Professor Christoph Meinel, will teach participants about the technical basis of the Internet through a massive open online course (MOOC) titled &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Internetworking with TCP/IP.&amp;rdquo; The course is available to anyone and can be accessed through free registration.
Professor Meinel believes that anyone who uses the Internet for daily tasks like online shopping, reading news articles, or sending emails should understand the technologies that make these actions possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I Know Where You Took Your Pictures Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</guid><description>Eye-Fi, the WiFi-enabled memory card, has introduced a new feature: location tagging. Their latest product, Eye-Fi Explore, automatically adds geotags to photos as you take them.
You might be surprised to learn that they haven&amp;rsquo;t actually included a GPS receiver in the small SD card. Instead, it uses a system that determines location based on known WiFi hotspots. This method covers a significant portion of the U.S. population and major metropolitan areas in Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom and Network Domain Names For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong domain name is crucial for any online business. The best names reflect your business, are easy to remember for offline use, and are pronounceable. Owning your own domain provides a much stronger online identity compared to generic alternatives. This ownership gives you full control over your website, email, and branding.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in business telecom for almost 15 years and acquired many domain names related to that industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Internet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, businesses depend heavily on infrastructure like electricity, telephone lines, and internet connectivity, often delivered through copper cables. While electricity and landline phones are widely accessible due to national initiatives, internet availability, particularly broadband via copper or fiber optic cables, diminishes as you move away from city centers. Rural areas often lack wired internet infrastructure entirely, leaving businesses with limited choices.
One option for these areas is wireless internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get double the mobile data for just a small increase with Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Coinciding with the start of IT Show 2016, Singtel is introducing DataX2, a new service that doubles customers&amp;rsquo; monthly mobile data for a fixed price of S$5.90. This new option reflects Singtel&amp;rsquo;s focus on data-driven services, building on the success of last year&amp;rsquo;s SIM Only Plan.
DataX2 lets customers double their data when they sign up for or renew a Combo Mobile Plan (Combo 2 or higher)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet to Soothe the Savage Flyer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</guid><description>Is there anything more frustrating than squeezing into the last seat on a long flight, stuck between grumpy passengers with hours to kill? You yearn for the distraction of emails or online games, but alas, internet access in the air seems like a distant dream.
Fear not, weary traveler! The wait for in-flight WiFi is almost over. Major airlines are preparing to offer internet access on their planes, but it comes at a price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regulation of Audiovisual Media Services and the "Exception for Newspapers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 01:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Case C-347/14 New Media Online GmbH v. Bundeskommunikationssenat, 21 October 2015
Traditionally, broadcasting and newspapers have been regulated differently. Newspapers have enjoyed more lenient, often self-regulatory, oversight. EU law harmonized television broadcasting through the Television without Frontiers Directive. Newspapers, if subject to EU law, fell under general free movement and competition rules. As technology evolved and online information services emerged, the Television without Frontiers Directive underwent revisions, becoming the Audiovisual Media Services Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless for Point of Sale Authorizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</guid><description>Credit card processing is essential for modern businesses, so having a fast and reliable authorization terminal is crucial. While dial-up terminals might have been sufficient in the past, their slow speed can frustrate customers and reflect poorly on your business. Upgrading to a broadband connection is a worthwhile investment.
T1 lines have become more affordable, making them a popular choice for businesses. However, they can still be expensive for smaller companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New EU Regulatory Guidelines for Net Neutrality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
New EU regulations designed to ensure equal treatment of internet traffic were enacted in the fall of 2015 and implemented in April 2016. These net neutrality rules were intended to prevent discrimination by internet service providers and promote innovation, but their effectiveness was debated.
The regulations stipulate that internet providers should treat all traffic the same, regardless of the source, content, or device. However, the vague language and exceptions within the regulations led to uncertainty regarding the level of protection for users and permitted provider activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smart Grids Picking the Bones of BPL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</guid><description>Were you eagerly anticipating the day when your electrical outlets would provide both electricity and high-speed internet? That dream might not materialize. Broadband over Power Line (BPL), as a consumer internet option, appears to be fading. However, despite complaints from amateur radio operators about interference, BPL is not disappearing entirely. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s transforming into a utility-focused communication system, potentially offering a solution that benefits everyone.
The turning point for BPL may have been the recent news that Current Communications is ending its BPL service in Dallas, initially intended for 2 million homes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dude, Where's My Site?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 04:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</guid><description>Ever feel like the internet is taking a break, but you&amp;rsquo;re not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s just you? Sometimes, websites refuse to load, leaving you wondering if the problem is on your end. A new tool called DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com provides a simple solution. Just enter the website address, and it will tell you if the site is truly down or if it&amp;rsquo;s just your connection.
Created by a Twitter engineer, DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com addresses the common question of whether a website is offline or if it&amp;rsquo;s a personal issue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pi1M Training Programme offered by Digi provides benefits to small business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Participants of the Pi1M Training Programme gathered for a group photo.
Digi Telecommunications recently conducted a training program for community members residing near the company-managed Pusat Internet 1 Malaysia (Pi1M) centers. This tailored program reflects Digi&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering online entrepreneurship within its Pi1M communities. Currently, Digi manages 34 Pi1Ms across Pahang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Johor, Melaka, and Sarawak, with plans to establish 70 more centers by year&amp;rsquo;s end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chumby Kicks the Clock Radio to the Curb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</guid><description>Are traditional alarm clocks and radios truly effective ways to wake up? Imagine a more modern approach: starting your day with your favorite internet radio station, a quick weather and market update, and a glimpse at your online auctions. You could even catch up on news and sports or play a game. All of this is possible with the Chumby.
What exactly is a Chumby? It&amp;rsquo;s a wireless internet device featuring speakers, a touchscreen, and motion sensors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New ECHR ruling on freedom of expression and internet comment liability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 13:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) raises the question of whether internet site providers should be held accountable for comments made by users. This issue gained significance following the court&amp;rsquo;s ruling in MTE v. Hungary.
Considering the importance of intermediaries in the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth, there are arguments for not treating them like traditional publishers. Instead, they could be granted some immunity regarding content posted by others...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Routes to Virtual Private Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</guid><description>VPNs have become the go-to solution for connecting multiple business locations due to their cost-effectiveness and ease of maintenance. Managed service providers allow businesses to enjoy secure multipoint communication without the burden of extensive staffing or high monthly line lease fees.
Virtual private networking is now cloud-based, but the choice of cloud type remains. You can opt for a VPN solution using the public internet or choose a completely private network for enhanced performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fishbat provides commentary on the latest developments in iOS8 and the introduction of Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple, the tech giant, recently launched the first beta version of iOS 8.1. This upgrade comes shortly after the release of iOS 8.0.2, which was itself a fix for a bug found in the recently launched iOS 8.0.1.
This new beta version offers several new features:
A redesigned icon for iBooks. An option to enable dictation within the keyboard settings. Updated application permission settings. Larger application icons specifically designed for the new widgets in the notification center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Helping Your Business Achieve Hyperconnectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It took a whole generation to connect the entire world to the internet. Now, get ready for an even bigger change: we&amp;rsquo;re moving towards hyperconnectivity, and it&amp;rsquo;s happening fast.
Everything, Everywhere, All at Once
Hyperconnectivity means that anything and anyone who can be connected will be connected all the time. We&amp;rsquo;ve already shifted from logging in to having always-on internet for our computers and phones. The next step is to let our devices communicate with each other without us...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Holy Guacamole, It's Green Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</guid><description>The internet&amp;rsquo;s days of excessive energy consumption might be ending. Websites and online businesses contribute to environmental issues, but we can&amp;rsquo;t just abandon the technology we rely on. We need a more sustainable solution: eco-friendly hosting.
The demand for electricity is increasing while clean energy sources are limited. Traditional power sources like coal are harmful, and even with reduced emissions, they still contribute to climate change. Renewable energy is becoming a viable solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are you still using Windows XP? Norton and Qihoo 360 are here to assist you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</guid><description>The AV-Test Institute, located in Germany, tested ten antivirus programs for Windows XP. Out of these, Qihoo 360 Internet Security 9 and Norton Internet Security 2014 proved most effective.
Source: Qihoo 360. AV-TEST Report: Exploit Protection on Windows XP
The institute designed 54 attack simulations using various methods and vulnerabilities to thoroughly test each program. The tested antivirus solutions included products from Qihoo 360, Avast, AVG, Avira, Bitdefender, Eset, Kaspersky, and Norton...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cracking down on online terrorism - a threat to freedom of speech? The EU Regulation on online terrorist content under scrutiny.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
On September 12th, 2018, the European Commission presented a proposal for a regulation aimed at combating terrorist content online. This regulation would mandate that EU Member States require internet platforms to proactively remove such content and ensure that authorities possess the capabilities to address this illegal material. This proposal builds upon existing voluntary partnerships like the EU Internet Forum and previous non-binding recommendations from the Commission on tackling illegal content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copyright and the Internet: Poland vs. Parliament and Council (Case C-401/19), Advocate General's Opinion, July 15, 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
The rise of &amp;ldquo;Web 2.0&amp;rdquo; and social media has enabled widespread content sharing, but also raised questions about managing user rights and the role of online platforms in addressing challenges that their services might facilitate. One issue is the use of filtering technologies, particularly their impact on users&amp;rsquo; freedom of expression. Courts have previously voiced concerns about these techniques in copyright cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Video is Moving to H.264</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</guid><description>Digital video is gaining immense popularity and rapidly consuming internet bandwidth. It&amp;rsquo;s revolutionizing television, expanding its presence on the internet, and being adopted by businesses for cost reduction, productivity gains, and environmental benefits. However, its major drawback is its heavy bandwidth consumption.
H.264, a video coding standard, addresses this issue by offering high-quality video at lower bandwidths through compression. While uncompressed high-quality video demands significant bandwidth, unsuitable for most businesses and consumers, H...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Are A WiFi Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-a-wifi-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 03:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-a-wifi-finder/</guid><description>ThinkGeek is offering the ultimate in internet geekiness: a t-shirt that lights up to show the strength of nearby WiFi signals. This shirt will make internet addicts follow you everywhere. You could even become a hotspot yourself and have people at your beck and call – or at least within range of your signal.
The Wi-Fi Detector Shirt from ThinkGeek is a black cotton t-shirt featuring a removable decal of a tower emitting signal lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-a-wifi-finder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-a-wifi-finder/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>