<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Multimedia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multimedia/</link><description>Recent content in Multimedia on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 10:17:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multimedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We Welcome a New iMac to the Family</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-welcome-a-new-imac-to-the-family/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 10:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-welcome-a-new-imac-to-the-family/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday afternoon, and I&amp;rsquo;m eagerly waiting for a delivery that seems to be taking forever. Finally, after hours of waiting, the FedEx truck arrives, carrying the item I&amp;rsquo;ve been anticipating for a week: a brand new, customized 24-inch Apple iMac.
You might wonder why I&amp;rsquo;m so excited, considering it took me a year after deciding to buy a new computer to finally order it. After all, I was a dedicated Mac user for over a decade before switching to PCs ten years ago...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-welcome-a-new-imac-to-the-family/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-welcome-a-new-imac-to-the-family/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC HD2 Smartphone With Movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</guid><description>Have you ever been offered a cell phone with two full-length movies already on it? That&amp;rsquo;s only the beginning of what the HTC HD2 smartphone for T-Mobile offers. This phone doesn&amp;rsquo;t just offer entertainment, it delivers it in spades!
The massive touchscreen display immediately suggests this phone is designed for multimedia. It boasts a 4.3-inch screen with 800 x 480 pixel resolution. Those specs sound more like a small computer than a phone, and that&amp;rsquo;s a good thing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV Envy Touch Phone Messaging Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</guid><description>Do you find yourself desiring a modern touchscreen phone but also require a physical QWERTY keyboard? The new LG enV Touch eliminates this dilemma by offering both!
When closed, the &amp;ldquo;enV Touch&amp;rdquo; resembles a typical touchscreen smartphone. The exterior features a 3-inch, 800x480 pixel color TFT touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable shortcuts. However, a hidden surprise awaits inside: a second 3-inch, 800x400 pixel color display. This internal screen, paired with a spacious QWERTY keyboard, prioritizes efficient typing over touch input...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV2 Sparks Envy Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</guid><description>The LG enV, nicknamed the &amp;ldquo;envy phone,&amp;rdquo; certainly attracted attention. Its successor, the enV2 VX9100, takes it up a notch, especially for those who love texting, gaming, and enjoying media on their phone.
The standout feature of the enV2 is its hidden full QWERTY keyboard. No need to fumble with a virtual keyboard on this phone! It boasts a real keyboard with comfortably sized keys. Keep your enV2 closed for calls, just like any other standard phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>From Here to Samsung Eternity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-here-to-samsung-eternity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-here-to-samsung-eternity/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a frigid winter day with howling winds and accumulating snow outside. However, right here before me, I&amp;rsquo;m captivated by a Hawaiian beach scene playing on a screen. A young couple enjoys the crashing waves. It&amp;rsquo;s so realistic that I&amp;rsquo;m tempted to step into the picture and join them on the warm sand. Despite knowing it&amp;rsquo;s just a TV screen, I feel a noticeable warmth. This captivating scene effectively blocks out the dreary winter weather outside my window, showcasing the impressive power of visual suggestion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-here-to-samsung-eternity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-here-to-samsung-eternity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Laptop Too Big? Try a Tablet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/laptop-too-big-try-a-tablet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:33:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/laptop-too-big-try-a-tablet/</guid><description>Carrying a laptop everywhere would be great if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t so heavy and cumbersome. While internet-enabled phones address the size issue, their small buttons and screens can be limiting. Ideally, there&amp;rsquo;s a middle ground—something portable yet equipped for easy internet browsing. This is where internet media tablets come in.
The Archos 7, for example, is a top-tier ultra-mobile computer resembling a larger iPhone, with a 7-inch touchscreen offering an 800x480 pixel resolution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/laptop-too-big-try-a-tablet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/laptop-too-big-try-a-tablet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>