<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scotland on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scotland/</link><description>Recent content in Scotland on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:03:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scotland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Putting an end to Brexit? Explaining the Wightman case on reversing the Article 50 notification independently.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
As the deadline for Brexit approaches and Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s conflicting negotiating goals become clearer, there are increasing demands for transparency regarding the Brexit process.
In late 2017, seven Scottish politicians from different parties and legislative bodies in Scotland (the Scottish Parliament, the UK Parliament, and the European Parliament) initiated a legal case in the Scottish Court of Session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit: You have the option to change your mind. The CJEU ruling in Wightman allows for a U-turn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The recent definitive ruling by the Full Court concerning the Wightman case reaffirms the UK&amp;rsquo;s ability to independently revoke its withdrawal notification from the EU under the most flexible terms. This judgment aligns with the non-binding opinion given the previous week by an Advocate-General.
The judgment
The Court dismissed the UK government&amp;rsquo;s claim of the case being hypothetical, emphasizing the imminent involvement of some litigants (who are MPs) in voting on the proposed withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Paying tribute to Catalonia: The impact of EU law on movements for independence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:39:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent surge in support for pro-independence parties in Catalonia has revived discussions about the connection between EU law and independence movements within member states. This issue was previously discussed in the context of the Scottish independence referendum, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth revisiting now. There are three interconnected questions: Firstly, what happens if a region within a member state declares independence unilaterally, a potential scenario in Catalonia? Secondly, if a newly independent state, formerly part of an EU member, seeks continued EU membership, what are the implications?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The case of Scotch Whisky Association v Lord Advocate [2017] UKSC 76 demonstrates the appropriateness and necessity of implementing minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-scotch-whisky-association-v-lord-advocate-2017-uksc-76-demonstrates-the-appropriateness-and-necessity-of-implementing-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-scotch-whisky-association-v-lord-advocate-2017-uksc-76-demonstrates-the-appropriateness-and-necessity-of-implementing-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Law School, Lancaster University (@AngusMacCulloch)
The UK Supreme Court, in a long-awaited decision on SWA v Lord Advocate, dismissed the Scotch Whisky Association&amp;rsquo;s (SWA) appeal, allowing the Scottish Government to proceed with its Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) policy on alcohol sales. This policy, setting a minimum price of £0.50 per unit of alcohol under the 2012 Alcohol (Minimum Pricing)(Scotland) Act, faced a five-year delay due to legal challenges arguing its conflict with EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-scotch-whisky-association-v-lord-advocate-2017-uksc-76-demonstrates-the-appropriateness-and-necessity-of-implementing-minimum-alcohol-pricing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-scotch-whisky-association-v-lord-advocate-2017-uksc-76-demonstrates-the-appropriateness-and-necessity-of-implementing-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Potential Reconstruction of Hadrian's Wall: How Scottish Independence Could Impact British Border Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 11:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Hadrian&amp;rsquo;s Wall is often thought to have been built by the Romans to defend civilized Britannia from invading Picts, who are considered the ancestors of modern-day Scots. This idea is echoed in Game of Thrones, where the Wall serves to keep out wild and dangerous beings from the North.
Theresa May, the British Home Secretary, recently invoked this imagery when she suggested that if Scotland were to become independent, border control would need to be reinstated between Scotland and the remaining United Kingdom...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What would be the effect on the UK's relations with the EU if Scotland gained independence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:31:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the Scottish independence referendum approaches, with the &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; campaign gaining momentum and even leading some polls, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to analyze the potential impact of Scottish independence on the European Union (EU). This analysis will focus on the EU membership of both an independent Scotland and the remaining UK (rUK).
Scottish independence would trigger four significant, near-simultaneous events: negotiations between Scotland and rUK about their future relationship; negotiations for Scotland to rejoin the EU; renegotiation of the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership; and a UK general election...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the notice to withdraw from the EU being revoked? Wightman's opinion suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
Is initiating the Article 50 withdrawal process from the EU irreversible, like jumping off a cliff? Or is it more like going shopping, where you can change your mind along the way, in the parking lot, or even inside the store? Perhaps this change of heart might be due to discovering the promised sale doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, the management is under investigation, and the supposed extensive international food section is just a couple of dusty packages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing Health and Trade: The Scotch Whisky Association ruling on finding the right equilibrium.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School The Court of Justice has issued its judgment regarding the legality of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s minimum alcohol pricing (MUP) measure in Case C-333/14. Both the Scottish Government and the Scotch Whisky Association (SWA), which initiated the legal challenge, have expressed satisfaction with the ruling, although the SWA might be more content as the case now returns to Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Inner House of the Court of Session, which had referred it to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Scotland and Brexit: Courageous Heart or Fearful Creature?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</guid><description>Steve Peers
During the Scottish National Party (SNP) conference, Scotland&amp;rsquo;s First Minister, Nicola Sturgeon, revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to present a draft bill for a second independence referendum. She also announced their intention to introduce an alternate plan ensuring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the EU single market, even if the rest of the UK chooses to leave. This proposal would involve granting the Scottish Parliament substantial new powers, encompassing all current EU-related powers held by Scotland and additional authority to negotiate international treaties and manage immigration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can devolved powers help mitigate the negative effects of Brexit on Scotland?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 07:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The UK&amp;rsquo;s devolution process, implemented with the understanding of continued EU membership, granted legislative and executive autonomy to Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland through specific Acts of Parliament. These Acts, while establishing varying degrees of autonomy, shared a common thread: devolved powers must not contradict UK&amp;rsquo;s international obligations, particularly EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Issues Surrounding Scotland, the EU, and 'Indyref2'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 08:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Scottish First Minister Nicola Sturgeon recently revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s desire to pursue a second independence referendum. This announcement follows the UK government&amp;rsquo;s dismissal of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s proposed Brexit alternatives. The timing of this potential referendum, contingent on the UK&amp;rsquo;s final Brexit arrangements, brings Scotland&amp;rsquo;s EU membership into focus. While a second referendum would encompass issues beyond EU relations, this analysis will primarily address the legal complexities surrounding Scotland&amp;rsquo;s potential EU membership, particularly the misconception of budget deficits as a barrier to entry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Attorney General considers the intersection of public health, trade, and competition in setting minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School Background to the Opinion Advocate General (AG) Bot provided his opinion on September 3rd, 2015, regarding Case C-333/14, which involved the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to establish a minimum price per unit (£0.50) on alcohol sales. This Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) faced legal challenges from the Scotch Whisky Association, leading to the case reaching the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The CJEU was asked to determine whether the MUP aligned with the single Common Market Organisation (CMO) and the free movement principles of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions on Scotland's Position in Europe: Analysis of the Scottish Government's latest suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The Scottish government recently released its anticipated paper exploring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s position within Europe. While acknowledging the government&amp;rsquo;s support for both EU membership and Scottish independence, the paper concentrates on potential outcomes should Brexit occur while Scotland remains part of the UK. Accusations that the paper dismisses referendum results, regarding either Brexit or Scottish independence, or simply rehashes arguments for independence are unfounded.
The paper essentially presents two main options: a UK-wide approach to Brexit that considers the concerns of Scottish voters, or, if that fails, a separate approach specifically for Scotland...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>