<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OC3 Fiber Optic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc3-fiber-optic/</link><description>Recent content in OC3 Fiber Optic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc3-fiber-optic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>