<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lunch on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lunch/</link><description>Recent content in Lunch on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lunch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home.</description></item><item><title>Clarke Quay Restaurant Week offers exclusive meals at discounted prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-restaurant-week-offers-exclusive-meals-at-discounted-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:56:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-restaurant-week-offers-exclusive-meals-at-discounted-prices/</guid><description>Clarke Quay&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Restaurant Week kicks off on Monday, April 20th, and continues until Sunday, May 3rd. This extended &amp;ldquo;week&amp;rdquo; offers diners the chance to savor exclusive set lunches priced at S$35++ or S$45++ by booking directly with participating Clarke Quay restaurants.
Source: Clarke Quay.
For instance, RAS The Essence of India presents a five-course set lunch featuring dishes like banajara kebab, lamb rogan gosht, boondhi raita, and rasmalai for S$35++.</description></item><item><title>Rajah revitalizes themed buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 19:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</guid><description>Starting April 4th, the all-day restaurant 21 On Rajah will introduce new lunch and dinner buffets inspired by Mediterranean and Asian cuisine.
Rijsttafel Weekday Lunch Buffet
Source: 21 on Rajah. A selection of dishes from the Rijsttafel weekday lunch buffet.
Inspired by the Dutch &amp;ldquo;rijsttafel&amp;rdquo; – meaning &amp;ldquo;rice table&amp;rdquo; – this lunch buffet presents a diverse array of side dishes served with rice, similar to the local nasi Padang. Chef de Cuisine Faustino Jr and his team have crafted a menu designed to energize diners for the rest of the day.</description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive Mie menus featured at Japan Food Town this December</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</guid><description>Japan Food Town is celebrating a &amp;ldquo;Mie Prefecture Fair&amp;rdquo; from December 1st to 7th, 2016, showcasing special menus from over 13 restaurants using ingredients from Mie Prefecture, such as Matsusaka wagyu beef, Ise-ebi lobster, and fresh oysters.
During this limited-time event, visitors can enjoy dishes made with top-grade A4 Matsusaka beef. This highly prized beef, exclusive to Japan Food Town in Singapore, comes from Special Grade Matsusaka Cattle raised in Mie Prefecture under the strict standards of the Matsusaka Cattle Council.</description></item></channel></rss>