<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtual Private Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-private-network/</link><description>Recent content in Virtual Private Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 04:59:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-private-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Different Types of VPN Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 04:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</guid><description>You prioritize the privacy of your network, but what happens when you need to connect to the outside world? Do you let anyone and everyone in, or do you secure your network across the distance using a private or virtually private network?
Before Virtual Private Networks (VPNs), there were private networks, and they still exist. Some situations demand such high security that the only way to guarantee control and prevent intrusions is through dedicated, point-to-point private lines.</description></item><item><title>Secure Any Public WiFi Hotspot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: you&amp;rsquo;re away from your secure office network or home WiFi, relying on public WiFi that makes you uneasy. While convenient, unsecured WiFi hotspots present a security risk. How can you be sure someone isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring your activity with malicious software when you send private emails or sensitive data?
](http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-1726600-11129503)
It&amp;rsquo;s a valid concern. Cybercrime is rampant, and tools for intercepting data on public WiFi are readily available.</description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1.</description></item><item><title>Advantage of Dedicated Cloud Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</guid><description>Companies of all sizes are increasingly adopting cloud services due to their cost-effectiveness. However, the assumption that a basic internet connection is sufficient for accessing these services is proving to be inaccurate in many situations.
While the internet&amp;rsquo;s widespread availability and affordability make it appealing for WAN services, its security concerns led to the development of VPNs. These secure tunnels encrypt data, allowing remote workers and branch offices to connect securely to corporate networks and transfer sensitive information.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes.</description></item><item><title>Two Routes to Virtual Private Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</guid><description>VPNs have become the go-to solution for connecting multiple business locations due to their cost-effectiveness and ease of maintenance. Managed service providers allow businesses to enjoy secure multipoint communication without the burden of extensive staffing or high monthly line lease fees.
Virtual private networking is now cloud-based, but the choice of cloud type remains. You can opt for a VPN solution using the public internet or choose a completely private network for enhanced performance.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Private Network Definition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</guid><description>While everyone understands the concept of a network, the meaning of a virtual private network (VPN) can be a bit unclear. Essentially, a VPN is a real network that utilizes technology to make its privacy seem virtual. For instance, the internet is inherently public, but methods exist to enhance the privacy of online communications, making them &amp;ldquo;virtually&amp;rdquo; private.
A genuinely private network necessitates stringent access control. Only authorized individuals and devices should be granted access.</description></item><item><title>Transparent LAN Service for WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transparent-lan-service-for-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transparent-lan-service-for-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>With the increasing trend of businesses expanding beyond a single location, the demand for reliable wide-area connectivity is on the rise. This is particularly relevant for companies with branches across the country and medical facilities spread over large regions. While traditional telecommunications services have connected multiple locations, newer solutions now allow your local area network (LAN) to cover an entire metropolitan area or even span multiple states.
One such solution is known as transparent LAN service, which effectively combines multiple separate LANs into a single, unified network.</description></item></channel></rss>