<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Centre on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/centre/</link><description>Recent content in Centre on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/centre/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ICSC's Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards honor D-Cube City, Jem, and Siam Center with gold awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</guid><description>The International Council of Shopping Centers (ICSC) Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards recently celebrated excellence in the region&amp;rsquo;s shopping center industry. Awards recognized outstanding achievements in marketing, retail property design and development, and retail store design.
The Design &amp;amp; Development category acknowledges retail properties for their overall design quality and development creativity, whether through renovation or expansion of an existing property or the innovative design of a new retail project. This category includes both new developments and renovations &amp;amp; expansions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre now offers complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Guests at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) can enjoy free Wi-Fi access through the &amp;lsquo;ADNEC Free Wi-Fi&amp;rsquo; network.
Humaid Matar Al Dhaheri, Acting Group CEO of Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company, stated that providing complimentary Wi-Fi highlights ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s focus on using technology to improve visitor experiences. This service eliminates the need for visitors to seek out basic internet access, aligning with ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing its technological infrastructure and enhancing service offerings to meet the changing needs of its stakeholders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collective Works and CapitaLand are teaming up to launch a new coworking space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</guid><description>Artist&amp;rsquo;s impression of the new coworking space at Capital Tower, Singapore.
A new high-end coworking space will be launched on the 12th floor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Capital Tower. This joint venture between two companies will occupy 22,000 square feet and support 250 businesses. The space is adaptable and caters to a variety of businesses, from new startups to large corporations. Technological features include secure server hosting, video conferencing, internet phone services, and fiber optic broadband internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GuocoLand will be responsible for overseeing the management of both Sofitel Singapore City Centre and Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Tanjong Pagar
Centre.
GuocoLand will oversee the operation of two new AccorHotels establishments: the Sofitel Singapore City Centre at Tanjong Pagar Centre in Singapore and the Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara in Damansara City, Kuala Lumpur. These additions contribute a total of 534 rooms to AccorHotel’s luxury brand.
Raymond Choong, President and CEO of GuocoLand Group, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership with AccorHotels, highlighting the shared vision for creating modern, convenient spaces within bustling business districts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Suzhou is gaining more recognition in the MICE industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</guid><description>The Suzhou Culture and Expo Centre Company (SCECC), which manages the Suzhou Culture and Arts Centre and the Suzhou International Expo Centre, claims that Suzhou is arguably the top Meetings, Incentives, Conferences and Exhibitions (MICE) destination in China.
SCECC highlights Suzhou&amp;rsquo;s success in hosting significant events, such as the 53rd World Table Tennis Championships earlier this year and Armani&amp;rsquo;s selection of the city&amp;rsquo;s Humble Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Garden as the venue for the global debut of its Pivoine Suzhou perfume...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>