<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>April on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/april/</link><description>Recent content in April on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/april/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates NBD observes improvement in Dubai's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</guid><description>Source: Emirates NBD. Emirates NBD Dubai Economy Tracker Index: Sector
summary. Seasonally adjusted, 50 = no-change.
Data from April shows a continuing upswing in private sector output. Compared to March, all three major sub-sectors reported greater new business growth. Employment figures are increasing again, but at a slower rate than the survey average. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s private sector companies reported continued recovery and growth momentum since the survey&amp;rsquo;s record low in February...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Optimize marketing tactics with native mobile strategies tailored for the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 15:56:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Sinead Woodley, Managing Director UK at April Six, a digital marketing agency, emphasizes that the right marketing approach can significantly enhance early buyer engagement for tech companies. Speaking at the Asia Pacific launch of April Six in Singapore, she highlighted how technology can be leveraged to achieve this.
Woodley cited EMEA-wide campaigns for VMware as a prime example, where April Six successfully reached IT professionals who are typically averse to marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>