<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Football on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/football/</link><description>Recent content in Football on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 05:07:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Don't waste a valuable opportunity: the importance and methods of reforming the governance of European football following the collapse of the 'SuperLeague'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 05:07:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</guid><description>Professor Stephen Weatherill, Faculty of Law and Somerville College, University of Oxford, analyzes the attempted formation of a European SuperLeague and what it reveals about the weaknesses in European football governance and legal frameworks. He argues that while the SuperLeague ultimately failed, the desire for such a league persists and requires proactive legal and structural reforms to safeguard the European model of sport.
A Persistent Threat
The proposed SuperLeague, driven by wealthy and commercially successful clubs, posed a significant challenge to UEFA, the governing body of European football...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself for the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</guid><description>Get ready for football fever this July as Arsenal, Atlético de Madrid, and Paris Saint-Germain head to Singapore for the 2018 International Champions Cup. This renowned annual tournament showcases top European football clubs competing across North America, Europe, and Asia.
Source: Sports Hub website. Three football clubs will be playing against each other at the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore on July 26, 28 and 30.
Beyond the three matches at the National Stadium on July 26th, 28th, and 30th, fans can immerse themselves in the excitement at the House of Football pop-up in Clarke Quay, Singapore’s vibrant nightlife and dining hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing a football package that includes both Copa America and UEFA Euro 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Singtel will broadcast the Copa America Centenario USA 2016. This competition is the oldest international tournament for nations in the Americas and features top players like Alexis Sanchez, Lionel Messi, and Luis Suárez. This year, for the first time, the tournament will be hosted outside of South America.
Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director, Home, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, stated that combining Copa America 2016 and UEFA Euro 2016 broadcasts allows Singtel to provide fans with two of the most exciting football events globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Before you decide to check out Ronaldo, reconsider your decision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</guid><description>A study by McAfee, a part of Intel Security, reveals that cybercriminals often use popular figures like Cristiano Ronaldo to lure unsuspecting users to malicious websites. These websites, designed to look like legitimate fan pages, can infect devices with malware capable of stealing personal information. McAfee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Red Card Club&amp;rdquo; list highlights the top eleven footballers whose names are most frequently used in these scams, with Ronaldo topping the list, followed by Lionel Messi and Iker Cassillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How do the Court's rulings on December 21, 2023 impact UEFA's position as a 'gatekeeper' in the Football Revolution?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</guid><description>Steve Weatherill, Somerville College and Faculty of Law, University of Oxford
Photo credit: Werner100359, via Wikimedia Commons
Summary
Recent Court of Justice rulings on December 21, 2023, determined that practices requiring prior approval for new sporting competitions created by external entities clash with EU law. This decision primarily stemmed from the lack of clear, unbiased, and transparent criteria and procedures. While governing bodies, particularly in football, are obligated to adjust their practices, the extent of their authority as gatekeepers remains unclear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>