<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Euro on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/euro/</link><description>Recent content in Euro on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/euro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Battle of the Legal Giants: Can the Euro endure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The German Federal Constitutional Court (BVerfG) has finally submitted a legal question to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on a critically important issue: the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) policy. This policy is widely credited with saving the EU&amp;rsquo;s single currency. If either court finds the policy unlawful, the euro&amp;rsquo;s continued existence could be in jeopardy.
In simple terms, the OMT is a 2012 commitment by the ECB to buy government bonds from struggling eurozone countries on secondary markets (from banks and financial institutions)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Greece to be expelled from the eurozone? How will the ECB's actions in limiting funding options for Greece impact Target2?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</guid><description>Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster https://iglinavos.wordpress.com/
The European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) actions regarding Greece, particularly since Syriza&amp;rsquo;s political victory, have drawn considerable criticism. This piece examines the gradual tightening of Greece&amp;rsquo;s financial situation within the framework of ECB regulations and considers potential outcomes if a resolution for Greece&amp;rsquo;s urgent funding requirements isn&amp;rsquo;t reached by June 2015.
ECB Halts Greek Government Bonds as Collateral
Since accepting its initial bailout in 2010, Greece has largely been unable to secure funding from markets except through domestic T-Bill issuances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>