<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ericsson on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ericsson/</link><description>Recent content in Ericsson on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ericsson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Copper WAN Bandwidth Headed to 500 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</guid><description>Ericsson has developed a new technology that could significantly boost data transmission speeds over existing copper wire infrastructure. This innovation allows for WAN connections over copper, achieving speeds up to 500 Mbps.
While Gigabit Ethernet is achievable with Cat-6 wiring for LAN connections, this technology focuses on connecting businesses to broadband providers using existing copper infrastructure. This is significant because many businesses require increased bandwidth for various purposes, including server farms, internet access, data transfer between locations, and the growing need for electronic medical record transfers.</description></item><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson.</description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson has unveiled its 10 top consumer trends for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson website. Infographic summarizing the 10 hot consumer trends for 2019.
· Consumers anticipate that smart speakers will participate in family disagreements, much like human family members do.
· Users of virtual assistants believe that devices capable of understanding human emotions will be commonplace within the next three years.
· Users of augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) express a desire for interactive, virtual assistance with practical tasks such as cooking or completing repairs.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson reveals insights on video consumption habits of consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Looking for effective ways to invest your marketing budget? The recent Ericsson ConsumerLab TV &amp;amp; Media Report might offer some valuable insights.
Now in its fifth year, the study surveyed 1,000 individuals in Singapore for the first time. The results reveal that 80% of Singaporeans engage in streaming TV or video content at least once a week, while 72% continue to watch traditional broadcast programs. Globally, 75% of consumers stream content multiple times weekly, compared to 77% who watch scheduled broadcast TV programs.</description></item></channel></rss>