<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contact Center on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contact-center/</link><description>Recent content in Contact Center on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:11:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contact-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud vs Premises Contact Center Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</guid><description>Lots of small businesses can get by with just a local or toll-free number for customer calls. But as companies grow, they usually dedicate staff and resources to handle customer interactions, creating a dedicated department known as a contact center. While contact centers are important, they can be expensive to run. Is there a way to reduce the cost?
Until recently, outsourcing to different locations was an option, but that often led to issues with language barriers and inconsistent service quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How AI is Helping to Improve Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Customer service calls are increasingly frustrating due to rising costs and labor shortages, negatively impacting both customers and companies. Tech expert David Pogue, in a CBS News report, suggests a blend of human agents and AI as a solution.
One such AI, called Grace, can handle customer interactions independently. However, AI like Grace can falter in complex situations, necessitating a transfer to human agents. While some of the best agents are located internationally and may have accents, this can be a hurdle for some US customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Centers Move To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems are gaining popularity as a replacement for traditional phone systems. Businesses are recognizing the benefits of moving their phone systems to the cloud. So why aren&amp;rsquo;t call centers embracing this technology?
Actually, some call centers are already using cloud-based systems. Smaller and geographically dispersed call centers are more likely to transition from physical to cloud-based phone systems. Larger call centers face more challenges in adopting this technology because their needs extend beyond basic phone functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>