<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Store on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/store/</link><description>Recent content in Store on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/store/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero.</description></item><item><title>The KOGEI Future Forward exhibition at Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store showcases the work of 15 artists</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</guid><description>The Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a contemporary art exhibition, KOGEI Future Forward, from February 15 to 20, 2017. The exhibition showcases the work of 15 Japanese artists, highlighting kogei as a unique form of Japanese fine art.
Kogei, meaning &amp;ldquo;craft,&amp;rdquo; emerged during the Meiji Period (1868-1912) and has evolved over time to gain recognition as fine art. This exhibition offers a fresh perspective on kogei, curated by Yuji Akimoto, a renowned art professor and museum director.</description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils new flagship store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-new-flagship-store/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 07:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-new-flagship-store/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. From left: Anna Yip, Deputy CEO, Singtel Singapore; Yuen Kuan Moon, Group CEO, Singtel; Ng Tian Chong, CEO, Singtel Singapore; and Lionel Chng, MD, Customer Success, Singtel Singapore.
Singtel just launched its latest flagship store, Singtel Shop 313@Somerset, in the middle of Orchard Road. This 4,900 square foot space showcases cutting-edge retail technology to create an enhanced customer experience for shopping, creating, and entertainment. This new store represents Singtel Singapore&amp;rsquo;s renewed dedication to improving the customer experience.</description></item></channel></rss>