<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Woman on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/woman/</link><description>Recent content in Woman on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/woman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to Accenture, gaining digital skills could help reduce the gender gap by up to 40 years faster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</guid><description>Source: Accenture. Closing the gender gap at work.
According to Accenture research, digital skills and technologies are empowering women in Singapore to secure and progress in their careers. However, a wage disparity persists, with men earning more. Ranked 5th out of 31 countries in Accenture&amp;rsquo;s research, Singaporean women demonstrate significant progress in digital fluency, reflecting their adoption and utilization of digital tools for knowledge acquisition, networking, and enhanced efficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JWT has identified 100 trends for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Source: JWT website.
The renowned marketing communications company, JWT, has unveiled &amp;ldquo;The Future 100,&amp;rdquo; a report that offers unique perspectives and analyses of 100 significant trends and cultural shifts to monitor in the coming year.
Lucie Greene, JWTIntelligence&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Director, emphasizes the importance of understanding the direction and implications of change for brands today. She points out that the rapid evolution of the digital world, readily available information, globalization, and social media have significantly accelerated the pace of trends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dove encourages women to push boundaries and redefine beauty and success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</guid><description>Women are rejecting the idea that their appearance should limit their potential, sharing empowering stories in Dove&amp;rsquo;s new film, #MyBeautyMySay. The film aims to motivate women to defy stereotypes and societal expectations.
Dove&amp;rsquo;s Global Beauty Confidence Report reveals that women desire the freedom to express themselves authentically but feel restricted by judgments about their appearance. For example, 70% of women receive more compliments on their looks than their work achievements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UOB creates profiles of the contemporary Singaporean woman and customizes card privileges to suit her needs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 08:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first profiles of the modern Singaporean woman, categorized by their behaviors and spending habits. The UOB Leading Ladies report identifies these women as digital natives, young professionals, and cosmopolitan leaders.
Jacquelyn Tan, UOB&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director and Regional Head of Cards and Payments, highlighted the report&amp;rsquo;s focus on the entrepreneurial spirit and spending trends of contemporary Singaporean women. She emphasized the significant contribution of women to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s GDP, exceeding 40%, and their dedication to both work and family...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>