<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gigabit Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Gigabit Connections on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand.</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>As companies increasingly adopt cloud services and engage in data-heavy activities like video streaming and big data analysis, the demand for greater WAN bandwidth is on the rise. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming commonplace to see requests for 1,000 Mbps connections, often fulfilled by a 1 Gbps Ethernet or GigE point-to-point connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the details and available choices for Gigabit Ethernet service.
Ethernet, the standard protocol for LANs, commonly operates at speeds of 10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1,000 Mbps, or 10 Gbps.</description></item></channel></rss>