<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flash on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flash/</link><description>Recent content in Flash on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HPE has reduced the entry threshold for its storage portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</guid><description>Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) recently improved its entry storage products to help budget-conscious customers leverage their data and speed up applications. These new HPE MSA Storage options deliver the most budget-friendly dual-controller hybrid flash array from a major vendor while the new HPE StoreEasy 1650 Expanded makes storing large amounts of information more economical.
Being able to quickly and effectively use information is crucial for success. &amp;ldquo;Agility and speed are critical for staying competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s economy, no matter the business size,&amp;rdquo; said Manish Goel, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Storage at HPE.</description></item><item><title>HP has improved MSA Storage for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP is introducing new features for its MSA Storage solutions to benefit startups, SMBs, and customers with small sites. These enhancements aim to increase competitiveness.
The improved MSA 2040 Storage offers significantly faster application performance, up to 45% faster, without extra costs through firmware updates. Additionally, new MSA 2040 bundles provide cost savings of up to 45% for hybrid flash deployments. Furthermore, the introduction of Serial Attached SCSI (SAS) connectivity to the MSA 1040 Storage positions it as the most budget-friendly shared storage option from a major vendor.</description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers.</description></item><item><title>DEAL.com.sg is celebrating its upcoming birthday by giving away S$5 million to customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</guid><description>The flash sale website, DEAL.com.sg, is thanking its loyal customers by offering them millions of dollars in discounts. This initiative, launched after the company&amp;rsquo;s start in May 2010, also aims to draw in new customers.
Patrick Linden, the CEO of DEAL.com.sg&amp;rsquo;s parent company, iBuy Group, expressed his gratitude, stating that the company is giving back $5 million to thank customers for their support over the past three and a half years.</description></item></channel></rss>