<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Muslim on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/muslim/</link><description>Recent content in Muslim on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 12:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/muslim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Yokohama Convention &amp; Visitors Bureau extends a warm welcome to Muslim travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 12:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</guid><description>Source: Yokohama Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau
The Yokohama Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau (YCVB) reports that its specialized Muslim Tourist Information microsite, part of the official Yokohama Visitors&amp;rsquo; Guide website, is gaining traction with Muslims in Southeast Asia.
Launched in December 2013, the Muslim Tourist Information website highlights tourist attractions, dining, halal shops, and mosques, all recommended by Yokohama&amp;rsquo;s Muslim residents. A survey of Southeast Asian Muslims revealed that over 90% found the information on restaurants, mosques, and recommended itineraries helpful.</description></item><item><title>JWT has identified 100 trends for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Source: JWT website.
The renowned marketing communications company, JWT, has unveiled &amp;ldquo;The Future 100,&amp;rdquo; a report that offers unique perspectives and analyses of 100 significant trends and cultural shifts to monitor in the coming year.
Lucie Greene, JWTIntelligence&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Director, emphasizes the importance of understanding the direction and implications of change for brands today. She points out that the rapid evolution of the digital world, readily available information, globalization, and social media have significantly accelerated the pace of trends.</description></item></channel></rss>