<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>M1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/m1/</link><description>Recent content in M1 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/m1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds.</description></item><item><title>Singtel customers enjoy the top roaming experience in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Opensignal. 4G download speed experience in Mbps for Singapore roamers in Malaysia compared to the experience for Malaysian mobile users.
A 2019 Opensignal study on Singaporean 4G users roaming in Malaysia revealed that Singtel subscribers had the best download speeds, upload speeds, and latency.
M1 and StarHub users experienced comparable download and upload speeds while in Malaysia. However, StarHub users enjoyed better latency compared to M1. Although both StarHub and M1 users faced significantly slower latency than Malaysian domestic users, indicating a poorer experience, Singtel users only lagged behind domestic Maxis users by 2.</description></item></channel></rss>