<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recording on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recording/</link><description>Recent content in Recording on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 04:43:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recording/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Test Drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-test-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 04:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-test-drive/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day! My second Beocord 5000 (specifically models 4715/4716) is functional again and playing in sync with the rest of my setup: the Beomaster 6000 4-Channel and the Beogram 4002. To mark this occasion, I chose Sonny Rollins&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Alfie&amp;rdquo; for the first recording.
The movie &amp;ldquo;Alfie,&amp;rdquo; starring Michael Caine, is a personal favorite, and its soundtrack is incredible. Here are some snapshots from the listening session:</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Fader Fixed and Putting it Back Together</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-fader-fixed-and-putting-it-back-together/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-fader-fixed-and-putting-it-back-together/</guid><description>I examined the fader on my Beocord 5000 (4715) tape deck and discovered significant corrosion on the Fade In and Fade Out button contacts, preventing them from making a connection. Using DeoxIT D100 applied to a strip of paper, I cleaned the contact pads while pressing the buttons. This successfully removed the corrosion, evidenced by black streaks on the paper. I repeated this process on the remaining buttons, restoring the deck&amp;rsquo;s responsiveness to a like-new condition.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): First Recordings!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-first-recordings-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-first-recordings-/</guid><description>I connected my Beocord 5000 tape deck to my Beomaster 6000 receiver for testing. Using a Beogram 4004 turntable, I recorded a track from a 1970s Miles Davis record onto a TDK SA 90 cassette. Everything worked perfectly! The Beocord performed flawlessly, recording and playing back the track with excellent quality. The sound was almost identical to the source material, with just a touch more background noise (even with Dolby noise reduction enabled).</description></item></channel></rss>