<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LED on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/led/</link><description>Recent content in LED on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/led/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration and Test Drive with Cal Tjader and Claus Ogerman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable for an Australian customer who purchased it on eBay. The turntable arrived in poor condition.
My initial evaluation is documented here.
This post details the unit&amp;rsquo;s restoration, excluding the dust cover, which will be covered separately.
I began with the DC platter motor, as is customary, since the bearing lubrication process requires a few days. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable. Initial assessment of the unit can be found on a separate blog post.
The restoration began with the platter motor, as its bearings require a lengthy oil treatment. The motor was extracted, disassembled, and its bearings were submerged in oil under a vacuum to allow for optimal oil diffusion.
Concurrently, the carriage assembly was cleaned. All &amp;ldquo;motion critical&amp;rdquo; parts, including the arm and its associated mechanisms, were removed, ultrasonically cleaned, and reassembled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration Including a Refurbished Keypad and Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This unit is currently for sale. Please, see here.
This post details the complete restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) from Arizona, which I first inspected as shown here. The unit&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is pictured below:
My first step, as always, was to initiate oil infusion for the platter motor bearings. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:
I took it apart to extract the bearings (two small rings on the black pad):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This blog post details the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a client in Florida. A previous post documented the initial assessment of the unit.
Upon beginning the restoration, the turntable was in relatively original condition. However, the platter motor showed signs of prior work, evidenced by an incorrectly installed pulley.
To address this, the motor was removed and disassembled to extract and lubricate the bearings. This involved immersing them in motor oil under vacuum until air bubbles ceased to appear, indicating the bearings were properly saturated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Upgrade of the Tracking System with a LED Based Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</guid><description>With the DC motor operating correctly, the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) continued with the arm lowering mechanism and tracking feedback system.
The arm lowering mechanism, consisting of a solenoid and damper, was disassembled, cleaned, and lubricated. This process involved removing the damper, linkages, retaining washer, and spring. Detailed videos illustrating the rebuilding process are available. After reassembly, the arms were meticulously aligned parallel to each other and the keypad edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The potential marketing opportunities presented by a customizable wearable device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</guid><description>Source: Broadcast Wear website. Control the shirt&amp;rsquo;s display with an app.
Broadcast Wear, an innovative company from Hyderabad, has introduced a programmable t-shirt with touch-sensitive technology, opening up exciting possibilities for marketing.
Their invention incorporates a flexible, washable LED screen directly into the fabric. Users can pair the shirt with the Broadcast Wear smartphone app to instantly show any text or image. A simple tap turns the screen on and another tap switches it off...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (I)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m waiting for a part for a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, I&amp;rsquo;ve started restoring another one with faulty displays. It seems cassettes are making a comeback! I&amp;rsquo;m even hoping for new tapes and maybe even a revival of the Sony Walkman II.
This particular Beocord 9000 has a very dim display:
[Image of dim display]
The &amp;ldquo;Time Cal&amp;rdquo; bulb is also weak, a common issue. I began with the VU meter (or Peak Program Meter), as I haven&amp;rsquo;t refurbished this type before...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacement of End Groove Detection Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 23:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5501) RPM trimmer panel, the focus shifted to the malfunctioning end groove detection mechanism. This ingenious mechanism utilizes a light bulb, a photoresistor, and an encoder wheel acting as a pulley to detect when the carriage accelerates after the record&amp;rsquo;s final track. By identifying this movement, the mechanism reduces the return time to the home position for records with extended end grooves, such as 12&amp;quot; singles or certain LPs with shorter playtimes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (III)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</guid><description>This article, the third in a series about restoring a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s peak program meters (PPM), focuses on installing and calibrating the rebuilt PPM.
The initial step involved switching the original current limiting resistors with values suitable for modern SMD LEDs. These LEDs are more efficient and brighter, requiring significantly larger resistors to match the original brightness. Testing showed that 470 Ohm and 330 Ohm resistors for red and green LEDs, respectively, produced slightly brighter output compared to the original 180 Ohm and 120 Ohm resistors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the Incandescent Indicator Light Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, two indicator lights presented problems. One had a typical issue with a broken lead, while the other had become dim due to a deteriorating filament.
To address this, I opted to use SMD LEDs as replacements, similar to a method I&amp;rsquo;ve used for Beomaster 8000 units, documented on my blog. This provides lasting stability and safeguards against potential shipping damage. However, the Beocord 9000 has more compact reflector housings compared to the Beomaster 8000, necessitating a redesign of the PCBs for the LEDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoring the Peak Program Meters with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s Peak Program Meter (PPM), even though it was fully functional. This decision stemmed from my success in restoring a different Beocord&amp;rsquo;s PPM that had several broken segments.
Since the technology behind these PPMs is similar to that of a 7-segment display, I realized that the segments in this unit were also susceptible to future breakage. Therefore, I chose to preemptively address the issue while I had the opportunity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Tracking Sensor Incandescent Bulb with a Drop-In SMD LED Assembly and a Peek at the Opto-Resistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</guid><description>The tracking sensor bulb in my Beogram 4000 recently burned out. This was the fourth bulb to fail. I decided to use this opportunity to install my new SMD LED replacement assembly. This assembly uses efficient white LEDs at low power for longevity, likely exceeding 50 years. It also reduces the unit&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption by a few watts, lessening the load on the aging transformer. Details about the assembly and adjustments can be found in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>Some time ago, a customer in Texas purchased a Beogram 4000 turntable on eBay from a seller in New York. The turntable was in fair condition, as detailed on the blog (see hyperlink). To address a cracked corner on the dust cover, the decision was made to acquire a second Beogram 4000, allowing the creation of one flawless unit from the two. With the arrival of the second turntable, the restoration began...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Display Restoration with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:28:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 being restored has a common issue: a faulty 7-segment display. While only one segment was out, these large, early LED displays are a key design element, making repair essential.
This display resembles the Beomaster 8000&amp;rsquo;s frequency display, but they are not interchangeable. The repair process, however, is the same as documented in previous posts.
To begin, PCB #11 and the bezel are removed to access the display for desoldering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustment of the Tonearm Height and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and with the major tasks complete, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the finer points. One detail that caught my eye was the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s resting position, which was noticeably higher than the sensor arm when lifted.
[Image]
Although this doesn&amp;rsquo;t impact sound quality, it was aesthetically displeasing. After consulting the manual, which recommended aligning the tonearm height with the sensor arm, I made the adjustment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Redesigned Drop-In Tracking Sensor Light Bulb Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I decided to upgrade the tracking sensor light bulb with a new SMD LED design I had created. My previous design lacked stability with the intensity adjustment trimmer, so I redesigned it to be more secure and visually appealing.
The new design incorporates the trimmer directly onto the circuit board and houses it within the light shield. This required modifications to the 3D printed housing to accommodate the trimmer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Full Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 22:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable originating from California. The restoration process commenced with the reconstruction of the carriage and arm lowering mechanisms, encompassing meticulous cleaning and lubrication of components like the solenoid and damper.
Following the mechanism restoration, focus shifted to the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm. This involved addressing a common issue: a detached copper pad on the sensor arm assembly. The pad was reattached using epoxy to ensure smooth operation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This article details the refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5504) turntable. An initial assessment of the unit is documented in a previous post here.
The turntable, stripped of its panels and platter, appeared relatively untouched. However, evidence of previous work emerged later.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly, which was quite dirty. After disassembling and cleaning the parts, the platter motor and capacitors were removed for thorough cleaning. The motor housing, including the bearings, underwent an oil infusion process under vacuum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor and Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently obtained a main PCB and DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002. I began with the motor refurbishment, a process that often requires several days for the bearings to become saturated with oil.
The motor is depicted here:
Disassembly was necessary to access the bearings, visible as two small rings on the black component in the front:
The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was noticeably oily, suggesting prior tampering. This was supported by a damaged commutator brush that was bent out of its intended form:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Unusual Keypad PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</guid><description>This article highlights a unique Beogram 4000 keyboard PCB. Typically, the two bulbs illuminating the position scale are wired in series, using two 12V bulbs connected between the 24V power source and ground. This setup is illustrated in the first image and diagram. Notably, this series configuration results in the bulbs having opposite polarity.
This polarity difference is ideal for the author&amp;rsquo;s polarized LED replacement boards. The second image showcases these boards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5501 from Sweden: Full Technical Restoration and Some Interesting Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 turntable (Type 5501 with optical carriage position detection) for a complete technical restoration. The unit arrived without a dust cover. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the Beogram right after unpacking:
Besides a number of loose parts that fell out when I opened the box, I was surprised to see that the cartridge was still mounted on the tonearm:
Fortunately, the MMC4000 cartridge had a small plexiglass guard in place, preventing any damage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED and Improvement of the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>Replacing the sensor arm LED is typically the final step in converting a Beogram 4002 to use all LEDs. After restoring the DC motor, the next task was to install a recently designed flex-PCB-based LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb. The image below shows the sensor arm with the detector assembly removed:
Upon zooming in on the full-resolution image, a small black spot is visible on the glass bulb. This spot indicates significant tungsten evaporation from the filament, suggesting the bulb is nearing the end of its life and could soon fail, rendering the Beogram inoperable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>This article details the comprehensive restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The initial evaluation of this unit is detailed in a separate post.
The turntable was first disassembled, revealing the need for bearing lubrication in the platter motor, a common issue in these models. This process typically takes a few days.
While the bearings were being re-lubricated, the intricate carriage mechanism, responsible for raising and lowering the tonearm, was addressed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with Stanley Turrentine and Milt Jackson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Kentucky. The unit, pictured below, was in excellent condition, making it ideal for a complete refurbishment.
As is typical with DC motor Beograms, the platter motor was the starting point. These motors commonly suffer from dried-out bearings, leading to speed instability. The extracted motor is shown here:
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings:
The bearings, visible as two small rings on the black pad, were then submerged in motor oil under a vacuum:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Complete Functional Restoration and a Spin with the Cal Tjader Quartet!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The restoration began with addressing the motor, a common procedure for these models. After removing and disassembling the motor, the Oilite bearings were submerged in oil and placed under a vacuum for several days to replenish lubrication.
Next, the carriage and arm mechanisms were disassembled, cleaned, and re-lubricated. This included taking apart and servicing the damper. The main PCB was removed, and both power transistors were replaced...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Grounding Switch That Allows to Connect System and Signal Grounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</guid><description>During my latest restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I encountered a loud hum when playing records through my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s 4-channel phono input. The issue was resolved by connecting the signal and system grounds. Although the root cause of the hum remains unclear, I decided to install a switch to allow for easy toggling between the original separate grounding configuration and a direct connection between signal and system grounds at the turntable&amp;rsquo;s output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 551x: Exciting!! Replica DC Motor Bearing Prototypes from Beoparts Successfully Tested</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</guid><description>I received another set of Beogram 4002 platter motor components and an RPM panel from a customer in the Netherlands to restore. My work started with the motor, as it usually does.
I disassembled the motor to get to the bearings.
Typically, I would show a picture of the bearings being oiled in a vacuum chamber, but I received new Oilite bearings from www.beoparts-shop.com specifically for these DC motors, which I am testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</guid><description>During the ongoing restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the incandescent bulbs illuminating the RPM trimmer scales were replaced with LEDs for enhanced longevity. Custom-designed circuit boards housing SMD LEDs were crafted to seamlessly replace the original bulbs, ensuring a direct fit.
These LED assemblies are offered to fellow enthusiasts, with an instructional video demonstrating their installation available online.
The following images detail the RPM trimmer panel, initially showcasing the rear view with original bulbs in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (II)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s rebuilt Peak Program Meters (PPM) display passed a 24-hour test, confirming its functionality.
To reattach the red-green covers, I secured the display to ensure a tight seal, preventing light leakage. Using a soldering iron, I melted the plastic posts of the covers, replicating the original attachment method.
During cleaning, the glue holding the light guide dissolved, indicating it was likely polyvinyl ester-based. I used &amp;lsquo;Aleene&amp;rsquo;s Original Tacky Glue&amp;rsquo; as a substitute, providing a clear and durable bond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor, Main PCB and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 18:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, experiencing RPM fluctuations, recently arrived from a customer for repair. The restoration process involved addressing issues with the DC platter motor, the main PCB, and the RPM adjustment panel.
The platter motor was disassembled to lubricate the bearings. After immersing them in oil and applying a vacuum, the bearings were left undisturbed for two days to ensure proper saturation. Once the bubbling ceased, indicating full replenishment, the bearings were extracted and the motor was reassembled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Control Panel - LEDs and Gold Plating of Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the enhancement of the carriage position switches, the control panel restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable commenced. The project involved a typical upgrade of incandescent bulbs to LED assemblies and gold plating of switch terminals for enhanced longevity and performance.
The initial stage revealed significantly oxidized keypad switch terminals:
The terminals were carefully removed:
Following oxidation removal using a fiberglass pen, the terminals were gold-coated:
An oversight led to one terminal being missed initially:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Completing the Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 10:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</guid><description>During the summer of 2019, I had the opportunity to work on a Beogram 4002 turntable from Virginia, specifically restoring its DC platter motor. I recently received the entire unit for a complete overhaul. The arm lowering mechanism had been previously restored and was in excellent condition. My attention turned to the remaining areas needing restoration.
To begin, I tackled the main PCB. The first photo illustrates its original condition:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination with a Red/Green LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, the light bulb illuminating the peak program meter&amp;rsquo;s dB scale malfunctioned. This common issue stems from the age of the bulbs, as their leads tend to oxidize and break under pressure.
The initial state of the display, lacking illumination for the numbers on the dB scale, is shown below:
The bulb is inserted into a waveguide that distributes light across the scale, with a textured surface behind the numbers for diffusion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulb of the Tracking Sensor with a Drop-In LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 11:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 400x turntable, it&amp;rsquo;s common to replace the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s incandescent bulb with a more durable LED assembly. A drop-in replacement for the Beogram 4002 and 4004 models has been created and documented, while the Beogram 4000 version incorporates a Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen-specified intensity trimmer for fine-tuning the tracking feedback system&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to recalibrate the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s position after any light source replacement to maintain accurate tracking sensitivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Keypad Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with LEDs. This enhances the unit&amp;rsquo;s lifespan and prevents issues that incandescent bulbs, susceptible to vibration, can experience during shipping.
The top two bulbs illuminate the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s unique position indicator, while the vertical bulbs light the RPM trimmers. I recently designed SMD LED-based PCB replacements for the position indicator bulbs (available via email).
Standard red LEDs with current-limiting resistors can replace the RPM trimmer bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with an SMD LED Light Source and Adjustment of the Feedback Sensisitivy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 turntable had a damaged part (the tracking sensor aperture) that was bent and obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. This issue prevented the tracking system from working correctly. The initial setup used an incandescent light bulb:
Upon removing the bulb housing, it was evident that the aperture was bent and rubbing against the optical sensor housing:
The aperture was carefully straightened, and the bulb assembly was replaced with a new SMD LED light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asus introduces a portable LED projector with a 4K display</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</guid><description>The PB287Q is a 28-inch monitor with 4K ultra high definition.
At CES last week, Asus, known for its consumer notebooks and motherboards, introduced new products designed for content creators and mobile professionals seeking enhanced performance and affordability. The company emphasized delivering bigger, better, and faster solutions. Among their offerings is the PB287Q, a 28-inch display with 4K ultra high definition (UHD) resolution. This slim-profile monitor features a full range of adjustments including swivel, tilt, pivot, and height, along with Splendid Plus video intelligence technology for optimal viewing comfort...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Restoration and a Test Spin with Oscar Peterson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable from Sweden in very corroded condition. To address the extensive corrosion, I chose to use another 4000 unit as a donor for parts. The donor unit, while missing some components, was free of corrosion.
My restoration process started with the carriage. I disassembled and cleaned the arm lowering system, damper, carriage rods, and spindle in an ultrasonic bath. Additionally, the sensor arm assembly was removed to lubricate the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Rebuilding the Pinch (Rubber) Roller</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 22:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/</guid><description>The last step in restoring my Beocord 9000 is fixing the worn-out pinch roller, a common problem in these decks given their age. These decks are over 30 years old, surpassing the lifespan of most rubber components. For optimal performance, a pinch roller rebuild is essential.
Fortunately, Terry Witt of Terry&amp;rsquo;s Rubber Rollers &amp;amp; Wheels is an expert in restoring tape rollers. He is highly regarded in the field, as evidenced by his reputation on online forums...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Incandescent Light Bulbs in Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, all four incandescent bulbs in the control panel were found to be non-functional. This highlighted the fragility of these bulbs and emphasized the need for a more durable solution. To address this, the original bulbs were replaced with custom-designed LED replacements.
Specifically, the two position indicator bulbs were replaced with surface-mounted LED (SMD LED) units. The two bulbs responsible for illuminating the RPM trimmers were replaced with high-intensity red LEDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with the Bill Evans Trio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable from a Massachusetts customer. The initial evaluation can be found here.
The restoration began by addressing the carriage system. This involved cleaning hardened lubricants from various parts like the arm lowering mechanism, rods, spindle, linkages, and damper, and applying modern synthetic lubricants.
A key aspect of the Beogram 4000 is its solenoid-activated switches, which frequently experience oxidation and require attention. The contact terminals were removed and re-plated with nickel and gold-cobalt alloy for optimal performance and corrosion resistance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>