<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter 2 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chapter-2/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter 2 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 11:13:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chapter-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Potential Reconstruction of Hadrian's Wall: How Scottish Independence Could Impact British Border Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 11:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Hadrian&amp;rsquo;s Wall is often thought to have been built by the Romans to defend civilized Britannia from invading Picts, who are considered the ancestors of modern-day Scots. This idea is echoed in Game of Thrones, where the Wall serves to keep out wild and dangerous beings from the North.
Theresa May, the British Home Secretary, recently invoked this imagery when she suggested that if Scotland were to become independent, border control would need to be reinstated between Scotland and the remaining United Kingdom...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>