<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1973AMBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1973ambg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 1973AMBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1973ambg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This article details the installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control Module into a Beogram 4002 (Type 5504) turntable. This particular unit was restored for a customer in Australia and also features an internal Beolover RIAA phono pre-amplifier.
The Commander Module, seen here before installation, allows for remote control of the turntable:
The module includes an IR receiver (black wire at the bottom), an adapter board (narrow board on the right), a wiring harness (white wires), and an auto-repeat indicator (red wire at the top).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Newly Adapted Beolover RIAA Pre-Amp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</guid><description>Following the recent redesign of the Beolover internal RIAA pre-amplifier for DC-motor Beogram 4002/4 turntables and its adaptation for the Beogram 4000, the final stage of the design process involved adjusting the circuit for the AC-motor Beogram 4002. The owner of a recently restored 4002 (5504) requested the RIAA installation, making his Beogram the first AC-motor 4002 to feature a Beolover RIAA.
The new board features an input jack that connects to a replicated Beogram-style plug through a multi-lead wiring harness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This article details the refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5504) turntable. An initial assessment of the unit is documented in a previous post here.
The turntable, stripped of its panels and platter, appeared relatively untouched. However, evidence of previous work emerged later.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly, which was quite dirty. After disassembling and cleaning the parts, the platter motor and capacitors were removed for thorough cleaning. The motor housing, including the bearings, underwent an oil infusion process under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): A New Arrival from Australia with a Very Creative Way to Send the Cartridge Along!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-a-new-arrival-from-australia-with-a-very-creative-way-to-send-the-cartridge-along-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:51:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-a-new-arrival-from-australia-with-a-very-creative-way-to-send-the-cartridge-along-/</guid><description>The same Australian who owned the Beogram 4000 I recently restored also sent me a Beogram 4002 (a Type 5504) for refurbishment. Like the first turntable, it arrived safely in good condition thanks to its double boxing.
This unit came equipped with an MMC20E cartridge, secured in a uniquely inventive manner. Upon inspection at my workbench, I was greeted with this:
Removing the styrofoam revealed the following:
This novel approach, while unusual, seemed surprisingly effective for transporting a cartridge in the absence of a proper container.</description></item></channel></rss>