<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Small on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small/</link><description>Recent content in Small on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:15:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ma from Alibaba emphasizes the importance of providing additional support for young entrepreneurs and small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ma-from-alibaba-emphasizes-the-importance-of-providing-additional-support-for-young-entrepreneurs-and-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ma-from-alibaba-emphasizes-the-importance-of-providing-additional-support-for-young-entrepreneurs-and-small-businesses/</guid><description>Alibaba Group&amp;rsquo;s Executive Chairman, Jack Ma, addressed the 34 member states of the Asian Cooperation Dialogue (ACD). He urged them to implement policies and infrastructure that would empower individuals under 30 and businesses with under 30 employees. Ma believes these groups will be the driving force behind future global economic success.
Speaking as both Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Executive Chairman and the UNCTAD Special Adviser on youth entrepreneurship and small business, Ma emphasized the significance of small entities, stating that &amp;ldquo;small is beautiful&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;small is powerful...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ma-from-alibaba-emphasizes-the-importance-of-providing-additional-support-for-young-entrepreneurs-and-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ma-from-alibaba-emphasizes-the-importance-of-providing-additional-support-for-young-entrepreneurs-and-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Canon has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Canon Singapore has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution providing businesses with real-time delivery tracking and automated scheduling. Designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) that rely on scheduling, delivery, and documentation for their core operations, FleetnexG offers a way to optimize resources and boost efficiency.
Vincent Low, Director &amp;amp; General Manager of Business Imaging Solutions at Canon Singapore, highlights the need for SMEs to go beyond timely order fulfillment. He emphasizes that optimizing resources for greater efficiency and productivity is crucial for success in today&amp;rsquo;s business landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in Singapore are increasingly transitioning to cloud services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</guid><description>Parallels, a company specializing in hosting and cloud services, has released an updated report on the Singaporean cloud market for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), called Parallels SMB Cloud Insights. This 2014 report predicts significant growth for the SMB cloud services market in Singapore, projecting it to reach S$916 million by 2017. This represents a strong three-year compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 21%.
Source: Parallels. Zanni.
John Zanni, Chief Marketing Officer for Service Providers at Parallels, observed that the Asia Pacific region is poised to outpace the rest of the world in cloud adoption due to its later start...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India will receive the India Inclusive Innovation Fund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</guid><description>The Indian Cabinet has approved a proposal from the Ministry of Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSME) to establish a dedicated fund. This fund will focus on promoting grassroots innovations that generate social benefits alongside reasonable economic returns. Union Minister Shri Kalraj Mishra shared this information in a written response to a question in Lok Sabha.
The fund, named &amp;ldquo;India Inclusive Innovation Fund,&amp;rdquo; aims to support businesses developing solutions for citizens at the lower end of India&amp;rsquo;s economic spectrum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protect your Office 365 emails with the latest Dropsuite cloud solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</guid><description>Smaller businesses can access Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s email backup and archiving tool for Microsoft Office 365 through intermediary companies like Ozhosting in Australia and ICONZ-Webvisions in Singapore.
Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Charif Elansari, emphasized their commitment to developing user-friendly solutions that are easy for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to buy and use.
Ozhosting CEO, Doug Endersbee, expressed satisfaction in offering Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive email archiving service, which meets legal requirements for retaining records, to their customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa introduces Visa Business Hub to assist small and medium-sized businesses with technology and strategic planning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</guid><description>Visa has launched the Visa Business Hub, a platform designed to assist small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in navigating technology and improving their management practices. The hub, initially launched in Singapore and Malaysia, offers software-as-a-service (SaaS) solutions that can potentially reduce IT costs by up to 25% through a pay-as-you-use model. This approach minimizes upfront expenses and implementation time.
Research indicates that a significant number of businesses in Singapore (80%) view SaaS/cloud adoption as a strategic move rather than a passing trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropmysite has undergone a rebranding and is now known as Dropsuite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</guid><description>Dropmysite, a cloud-based backup provider for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), has been renamed Dropsuite. This rebranding reflects a new global vision, business strategy, and ambition focused on business continuity, data recovery, and protection.
Dropsuite now offers a comprehensive suite of backup, recovery, and archiving solutions, consolidating its previous standalone brands: Dropmysite (website and database backup), Dropmyemail (email backup), and Dropmymobile (mobile data backup).
Furthermore, Dropsuite has introduced DSE Server Backup, a new file-based server backup solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SMBs can access Office 365 through GoDaddy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a technology company that supports small businesses, has partnered with Microsoft to offer Microsoft Office 365 to small businesses in Asian markets. This collaboration is part of GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s ongoing effort to provide top-tier business management solutions worldwide.
By offering Office 365, GoDaddy allows its customers to easily access professional email linked to a domain name, secure cloud storage, and a wide range of productivity and collaboration tools.
&amp;ldquo;GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s understanding of small businesses combined with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s email and productivity suite gives small business owners in Asia the tools they need to simplify their operations,&amp;rdquo; said Roger Chen, Vice President of Asia, GoDaddy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy is dedicated to creating impressive and impactful business identities for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>GoDaddy: Expanding Beyond Domains to Empower Small Businesses While GoDaddy is known for domain names, it has evolved into much more. CEO Blake Irving emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s focus on supporting small businesses, a demographic often overlooked despite representing a significant portion of most economies.
Irving highlights that small businesses, even those with a single employee, present a vast untapped market. Traditional solutions often cater to either large enterprises or individual consumers, leaving small businesses underserved...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The enhanced Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB from ALE simplifies collaboration and boosts productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</guid><description>Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise, operating under the Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise brand, helps small and medium businesses provide a streamlined user experience and enhanced onsite mobility for their employees, while ensuring business continuity. This is achieved through the latest update of their product, Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB.
The latest improvements to OpenTouch Suite for SMB focus on increasing productivity and efficiency. This is achieved through expanded communication and collaborative tools, as well as enabling employees to access the company environment from any location, at any time, using mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean financial technology company is striving to provide improved lending terms for business-to-business transactions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</guid><description>A Singapore-based fintech startup, Cash-IN-Asia, has introduced a new business-to-business (B2B) lending platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s fully digital approach lets business owners secure financing directly from their mobile devices.
Cash-IN-Asia aims to support micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in Singapore. The company offers products designed to meet current needs and help these businesses thrive even after the current economic challenges.
Their ISO27001-certified platform leverages artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics to deliver a comprehensive solution for MSMEs seeking transparent and flexible financing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kaspersky provides solutions to combat ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</guid><description>Ransomware is increasingly targeting businesses, encrypting files and demanding payment for decryption keys.
A Kaspersky Lab report reveals a six-fold increase in ransomware attacks against businesses from 2015 to 2016, affecting one in ten business users.
Cybercriminals are focusing on businesses, particularly small and medium-sized companies. A Kaspersky Lab and B2B International study found that 42% of respondents from these businesses considered ransomware a major threat.
Even brief data unavailability can severely impact small businesses, potentially halting operations entirely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>