<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plastic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plastic/</link><description>Recent content in Plastic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:40:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plastic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anyone can begin eliminating plastic from their lives at any time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</guid><description>Douglas Yeo, pictured second from the right, is the Course Director at DIWA and a dedicated environmental advocate. Although widely recognized for his role as a diver in the 2018 Thai cave rescue and his nomination for Singaporean of the Year, Yeo is also the driving force behind a growing movement to eliminate plastic use.
Known as the PlasticFREE initiative, this DIWA-supported campaign encourages individuals to minimize plastic waste. Participants are invited to start with small changes in their own lives and then spread the message to friends and family...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Sub-Chassis and the Platter, and RPM Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 04:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</guid><description>Today was dedicated to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis on a Beogram 4002 (5513) that I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I aimed to align the platter&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface with the surrounding panels, center the sub-chassis within the transport locks&amp;rsquo; limits, and ensure the arms were parallel to the aluminum surfaces. It&amp;rsquo;s intricate work involving aligning numerous components. After gaining experience with this process, I achieved a satisfactory result, aligning the Beogram to specifications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BPA-free may not necessarily be better for you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bpa-free-may-not-necessarily-be-better-for-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 06:02:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bpa-free-may-not-necessarily-be-better-for-you/</guid><description>Many plastic water bottles, especially those marketed for sports or children, highlight being &amp;ldquo;BPA free.&amp;rdquo; Public concern regarding bisphenol A (BPA) grew in 2008, leading many companies to adopt BPA replacements, particularly for products aimed at children and athletes.
While the shift away from BPA in certain products might seem reassuring, issues remain. BPA is still commonly used in thermal receipt paper, can linings, and even water pipes, often without public disclosure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bpa-free-may-not-necessarily-be-better-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bpa-free-may-not-necessarily-be-better-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Broken SO ('Shut Off') Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 05:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about a malfunctioning &amp;ldquo;Shut Off&amp;rdquo; (SO) switch, which was missing a crucial plastic part, causing issues with the deck&amp;rsquo;s shutdown process. To address this, a 3D printed replacement part was designed and created. The &amp;ldquo;End Switch&amp;rdquo; (ES), still equipped with its plastic component, is pictured alongside the SO switch, highlighting the missing element.
Creating a functional replacement part was challenging due to its small size and the limitations of the 3D printer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>