<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT Infrastructure on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-infrastructure/</link><description>Recent content in IT Infrastructure on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-infrastructure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers.</description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points.</description></item><item><title>A Graphical Introduction to Big Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</guid><description>Confused about the hype surrounding Big Data? This infographic might help clear things up&amp;hellip;
Feeling limited by your current internet connection when dealing with large amounts of data, cloud services, backups, or file transfers? Upgrading might be more affordable than you expect. Get immediate pricing on cost-effective copper and fiber internet options for your business.
Credit to Wikibon Infographics for this infographic on Big Data.</description></item><item><title>Take a Bow For The SIP Revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</guid><description>A significant change is happening in businesses of all sizes. It&amp;rsquo;s not related to politics, social issues, or processes. It&amp;rsquo;s a subtle change that most employees aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of, a change that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily noticeable and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require anyone to alter their work methods. It simply provides enhanced capabilities and cost savings. This is the SIP revolution.
What is SIP, and why is it so transformative? Watch this brief introduction to find out&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Concentric Cloud Solutions Virtualizes Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been bombarded with information about virtualization, unsure if it can help control unpredictable business expenses. You might feel overwhelmed about the process of deploying virtualization. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry, Concentric can guide you through it.
Initially confined to local data centers, virtualization has migrated to the cloud. The fundamental concept is maximizing hardware performance. This is achieved by making a single server function as multiple servers, or transforming a cluster of smaller servers into a powerful computing unit.</description></item><item><title>Your Desk Just Moved To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 10:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The 20th century saw a significant shift in employment, moving from farm work to factory jobs and finally to office positions. Now, the 21st century is experiencing another major change as workplaces transition from offices to the cloud.
The Cloud is Here and Now
Contrary to the idea of the cloud being a distant concept, it has become an integral part of our present reality. Nearly everything we do has or will soon have a cloud connection.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Manufacturing Driving Faster WANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</guid><description>The recent &amp;ldquo;Great Recession&amp;rdquo; stands out not just for its severity, but also for the uneven recovery that followed. While businesses have bounced back, job growth has lagged. This unusual trend has been attributed to unexpected gains in productivity, where output increases without a proportional rise in employment. But is this sustainable or merely a blip in the current economic climate?
The saying &amp;ldquo;everything old is new again&amp;rdquo; rings true. While new applications and technologies emerge, they often echo past advancements driven by innovation.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth on Demand Complements Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:50:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
One of the biggest advantages of cloud services over traditional IT infrastructure is their flexibility. With a vast pool of virtual servers and storage, businesses can adjust resources on demand, significantly improving productivity and resource usage.
However, connectivity hasn&amp;rsquo;t quite caught up with this shift. Connecting to the cloud often relies on fixed-capacity connections. Upgrading these connections is typically a complex and time-consuming process, creating a bottleneck in an otherwise agile system.</description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network.</description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate.</description></item></channel></rss>