<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Damaged on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/damaged/</link><description>Recent content in Damaged on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/damaged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Awesome Refurbished Keypads in the House!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</guid><description>I received two refurbished Beogram 4002 keypads from Denmark today. My friend, who did the repainting, said the weather conditions were perfect for the job, and he was right! The picture shows how fantastic they look.
He&amp;rsquo;s incredibly talented! The keypads look brand new, as if they were just made in 1975. He did a phenomenal job. I had sent him a worn-out keypad from a Beogram 4002 I recently restored, and he even found another one!</description></item><item><title>Kérastase Résistance Thérapiste offers amazing results for hair that has been over-processed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oréal.
The Résistance line was launched by Kérastase in 1995 to provide women with superior hair care and repair solutions. Two decades later, the brand expanded with Résistance Thérapiste, specifically addressing the needs of over-processed hair.
Kérastase claims that this innovation, driven by a breakthrough discovery in hair structure, harnesses the power of an ancient plant and incorporates a novel sensory experience, allowing women to achieve complete renewal of damaged hair in just one use.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Some Final Touches - Replacing Plinth and Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</guid><description>Following the installation of the BeoloverRIAA internal preamplifier and the Commander remote control, this Beogram 4002 (5523) needed a few finishing touches.
The original plinth of the Beogram was damaged. A replacement plinth was sourced, but it also had minor damage, particularly to the corners. Inspired by a previous veneer repair on a Beomaster 8000, a similar approach was taken to address the plinth&amp;rsquo;s corners. Veneer was added and color-matched to the existing finish, significantly improving the appearance, although not completely perfect.</description></item></channel></rss>