<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asiana on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asiana/</link><description>Recent content in Asiana on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asiana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asiana discontinues codeshare agreement with US Airways, impacting flights to Japan and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Asiana Airlines will end its codeshare agreement with US Airways on March 30, 2014. Passengers are advised to review their flight reservations. The affected routes are listed below:
Asiana Airlines flights
Japan
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Fukuoka, Osaka, Nagoya, Okinawa, and Shizuoka
America
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Chicago, New York, and Honolulu
US Airways flights
America
Los Angeles to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia San Francisco to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Seattle to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Chicago to/from Atlanta, Orlando, Indianapolis, Columbus, Cleveland, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines expands its presence in the United States with a new codeshare agreement with Asiana Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines has broadened its codeshare partnership with Asiana Airlines, expanding its network beyond Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon International Airport to include Honolulu, Seattle, and Los Angeles.
These Star Alliance members have been codesharing on flights between Singapore and Seoul-Incheon since September 2005. Singapore Airlines currently offers four daily flights on this route, with one continuing to San Francisco, while Asiana operates daily flights.
Asiana also places its code on Singapore Airlines-operated flights extending beyond Singapore to Jakarta, Indonesia; Perth, Australia; Auckland, New Zealand; and Cape Town, South Africa.</description></item></channel></rss>