<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Refugees on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/refugees/</link><description>Recent content in Refugees on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/refugees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reconsidering Gender-Based Asylum: Examining the Advocate General's Perspective on Female Refugees Escaping the Taliban</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand (Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law) and Salvo Nicolosi (Senior Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law)
Photo credit: USAIDAfghanistan, via Wikimedia Commons
A central question in international refugee law is whether women can qualify for refugee status based solely on their gender. This debate recently reached the Court of Justice through two connected cases, AH and FN, concerning women seeking asylum. Advocate General Richard de la Tour issued his opinion on these cases on November 9, 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advancing Gender-Sensitive EU Asylum Law: Examining the Situation of 'Westernised Women'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand, Assistant Professor, and Salvo Nicolosi, Senior Assistant Professor, University of Utrecht
Photo credit: Mystslav Chernov, via Wikimedia Commons
Recent developments in EU law show a growing recognition of gender-based asylum claims. A notable example is the June 11, 2024, judgment by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of K, L v Staatssecretaris van Justitie en Veiligheid. This case, concerning two Iraqi sisters seeking asylum in the Netherlands, centers around interpreting &amp;ldquo;membership of a particular social group&amp;rdquo; within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, specifically regarding &amp;ldquo;westernized women&amp;rdquo; who fear persecution upon returning to their home countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mixed messages are being sent by the CJEU regarding LGBTI asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many nations have severe punishments for individuals identifying as LGBTI, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recognizes persecution based on sexual orientation as grounds for asylum in the EU. This protection falls under the &amp;lsquo;particular social group&amp;rsquo; category within the EU&amp;rsquo;s qualification Directive.
The CJEU has previously clarified that individuals seeking asylum on the basis of sexual orientation are not required to conceal their sexual orientation in their home country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Strategy on immigration policy in the EU by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</guid><description>This is an unofficial preview of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s communication on the EU migration agenda, scheduled for release on May 13th. Please be aware that the content may change before publication and may be incomplete.
I. Introduction
Migration has been a constant throughout human history, driven by a range of factors such as political oppression, war, poverty, opportunity, and family reunification. Each migrant&amp;rsquo;s story is unique, and their movement has diverse impacts on society, necessitating a variety of responses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating Discontent: Questions and Answers about the legal concerns of asylum-seekers crossing the Channel.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 23:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Supported by an ESRC Priority Brexit Grant on &amp;lsquo;Brexit and UK and EU Immigration Policy&amp;rsquo;.
Some politicians are trying to create unnecessary fear and outrage over a relatively small number of people crossing the English Channel. This situation does bring up important legal questions. While the legal aspects have been discussed elsewhere, such as in the Free Movement blog, this post aims to clarify some of these legal issues in a straightforward question-and-answer format...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dublin system: Balancing Mutual Trust and Human Rights Protection in the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated to the Centre of Interdisciplinary Research in Constitutional Law of Saint-Louis University (USL-B) and the Centre of European Law of the Free University Brussels (ULB). The author wishes to thank the Professors E. Bribosia and S. Van Drooghenbroeck for their valuable advice.
Introduction
On February 16th, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) issued a significant judgment in the case of C...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion of AG de la Tour in C-621/21: Is it a helpful clarification or an unnecessary hindrance to women seeking international protection from gender-based violence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Grundler, a Lecturer in Law at the Department of Law and Criminology, Royal Holloway, University of London, examines a recent legal opinion concerning refugee and subsidiary protection eligibility for women at risk of violence within their families.
Advocate General (AG) de la Tour&amp;rsquo;s Opinion in case C-621/21 tackles the scope of the refugee definition within Article 2(d) of the Qualification Directive and the definition of subsidiary protection beneficiaries in Article 2(g) concerning women facing potential violence within a family setting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What potential issues could arise with the EU, Turkey, and the Refugee Crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers* and Emanuela Roman, University of Palermo and Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam**
*Emanuela Roman wrote the sections on ‘safe third country’, ‘super-safe third country’ and ‘first country of asylum’. Steve Peers wrote the rest of the main text and the annexes.
Turkey plays a pivotal role in the EU&amp;rsquo;s current refugee crisis, hosting over two million Syrian refugees and serving as a transit point for many asylum seekers. A growing number of these individuals travel from Turkey to the Greek islands, contributing to a notable increase in asylum seekers within the EU in recent times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 6 of the new EU asylum laws: The updated Dublin regulations regarding the accountability for asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway, University of London
Photo credit: Ggia, via Wikimedia Commons
(last updated 10 June 2024: changed text marked by an asterisk)
Shortly before Christmas 2023, the European Parliament and the Council finalized an agreement on five crucial components of EU asylum law. These components address asylum procedures, the &amp;lsquo;Dublin&amp;rsquo; system for determining responsibility for asylum applications, the supporting &amp;lsquo;Eurodac&amp;rsquo; database, migrant/asylum seeker screening, and crisis derogations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three main points about the EU's New Pact on Migration and Asylum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</guid><description>Lilian Tsourdi, Assistant Professor, University of Maastricht
*Photo credit: Délmagyarország/Schmidt Andrea
The EU&amp;rsquo;s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, along with its accompanying legislative proposals, represents the latest policy framework for asylum, migration, and border management. Its stated goal is to create streamlined migration procedures and stronger governance. Since September 2020, negotiations on the Pact&amp;rsquo;s legislative components have been underway.
Recently, both the European Parliament (April 2023) and the Council of the European Union (June 2023) have adopted negotiating positions on two significant instruments: the Asylum Procedures Regulation (APR), which updates regulations on determining asylum and related rights, and the Asylum and Migration Management Regulation (AMMR), which reforms the EU&amp;rsquo;s system for allocating responsibility for processing asylum requests and establishing a solidarity framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Law and Policy on the Relocation of Asylum-Seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers recently discussed the legal aspects of the refugee crisis, focusing on international law. This post will examine the relocation of asylum-seekers within the EU, a topic that has sparked considerable debate. The EU recently passed a second decision on this matter, facing opposition from several member states. This decision follows an earlier one from September. Both are temporary measures, effective for two years, but there is a proposal for a permanent system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Childhood Coming to an End? The Court of Justice Affirms the Right of Unaccompanied Child Refugees to Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Reaching the age of 18 is a major milestone, signifying a transition to adulthood. While it may not bring immediate changes to family dynamics, it holds significant legal implications.
However, in immigration and asylum law, turning 18 can mean reduced legal rights, especially for vulnerable unaccompanied minors. Given lengthy legal processes, a key question arises: When an applicant starts as a minor but turns 18 before the process concludes, do they keep the protections afforded to children?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU leaders are avoiding taking significant action to address the migrant crisis.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU leaders convened yesterday and agreed on a policy to handle the escalating migrant death toll in the Mediterranean Sea. This new policy expands on the recently implemented 10-point plan established by ministers. Notably, some significant last-minute revisions to the initial draft highlight the leaders&amp;rsquo; priorities.
Detailed comments
The leaders&amp;rsquo; statement appears to demonstrate more empathy than the prior 10-point plan. It acknowledges the immense loss of life as a tragedy and prioritizes the prevention of further deaths at sea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>People without nationality and refugees escaping Ukraine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</guid><description>Chris Nash, Director of the European Network on Statelessness*
*Reblogged from the Network website
As the number of people seeking refuge from the conflict in Ukraine approaches two million, our organization and our members working in the region are working to understand the specific needs of stateless individuals displaced by this crisis.
Based on previous experiences, including our research from the Stateless Journeys initiative, we know that stateless people fleeing from conflict encounter additional obstacles when crossing borders and seeking asylum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it permissible for Member States to confiscate the assets of asylum-seekers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk (Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen) and Steve Peers
Recently, several countries within and outside the EU have made headlines for seizing assets from asylum-seekers upon entry. This raises the question of whether this practice aligns with EU law. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine national practices, the development of relevant EU regulations, and finally, draw our conclusions.
Denmark
In November 2015, the Danish government put forward 34 measures aimed at deterring asylum seekers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's reaction to migrant fatalities focused on safeguarding and stopping them, or is it merely a way to disguise policy laundering?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU foreign and interior ministers recently agreed on a ten-point plan to address the tragic loss of migrant lives in the Mediterranean. While a summit and a new strategy are forthcoming, this initial plan is disappointing. It lacks crucial specifics and prioritizes border control and restrictive measures over aiding migrants facing perilous journeys and seeking safety.
This analysis will examine each of the plan&amp;rsquo;s ten points, followed by a look at the suggested &amp;ldquo;Australian solution&amp;rdquo; and the controversial &amp;ldquo;Christians only&amp;rdquo; approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Could a third phase of the Common European Asylum System bring wisdom and goodness to those who are considered vile?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 05:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
The EU is looking to overhaul its Common European Asylum Policy, and the Commission has laid out its suggestions in a new discussion paper. These proposals, which are expected to lead to further legislation, aim to address the flaws in the current system. This blog post will break down these proposals and analyze their potential impact.
The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum policy has been developed in phases, with the initial legislation implemented between 2003 and 2005 and the second phase between 2011 and 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Just like the sun, hope shines bright: Court of Justice decision expands refugee minors' right to family reunification.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 21:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani (PhD) is a linguist agent working for the European Commission and a member of Amnesty International Belgique francophone’s Sexual Orientation and Gender Identity (OSIG) coordination group. The opinions and perspectives presented in this article are solely those of the author and do not necessarily represent the views, policies, or opinions of the European Commission or Amnesty International.
Photo credit: Enno Lenze, via Wikimedia Commons
As of this writing, the European Parliament recently voted to approve the EU’s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, despite concerns raised by over 50 civil society organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examine what you observe and I will determine if you are homosexual: Evaluating the Advocate General's viewpoint in Case C-473/16, F v Bevándorlási és Állampolgársági Hivatal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/</guid><description>By Nuno Ferreira (Professor of Law, University of Sussex) and Denise Venturi (PhD student, Scuola Sant Anna, Pisa)*
Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Actions Raise Concerns Again
Hungary has been under scrutiny for controversial actions. Viktor Orban&amp;rsquo;s right-wing government has faced criticism from parts of Hungarian society and European institutions for policies targeting specific universities, constructing border barriers to deter refugees, and implementing other contentious measures. A recent source of alarm is Hungary&amp;rsquo;s treatment of asylum seekers, particularly those claiming persecution based on sexual orientation, an area already subject to criticism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Summary of a new report: Is Restoring the Borderless Schengen Area an Impossible Mission?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: BlueMars, via Wikimedia Commons
A new report I wrote for the Swedish Institute of European Policy Studies (SIEPS) analyzes the potential effects of the recently approved changes to the Schengen Borders Code. This blog post summarizes the key findings of the report.
The report addresses concerns regarding the increasing trend of Schengen countries reinstating border checks within the zone for extended periods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's responses to the Iraq war and EU asylum law are uncertain.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Almost twelve years after it began, the Iraq war remains a point of contention, with many believing Tony Blair and George W. Bush initiated an unlawful conflict. These critics believe only a trial for war crimes for both Bush and Blair would be a satisfactory outcome. While I believe this may happen someday, it would require a jury of highly improbable individuals. (Perhaps those individuals disappeared alongside the supposed weapons of mass destruction)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Nigel Farage's claim that the EU's asylum policies will allow in half a million terrorists accurate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, the UK Independence Party leader, recently asserted that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s response to the migrant crisis could unintentionally allow a large number of terrorists into the EU. He bases this on the threat by ISIS to use smuggling routes to infiltrate the EU and urges David Cameron to block the EU&amp;rsquo;s plans.
These claims lack merit. The EU&amp;rsquo;s approach essentially maintains the existing situation. The current maritime surveillance efforts, while being expanded, may not become full-scale rescue missions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evaluating the new proposal on "Safe countries of origin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission recently introduced several new immigration and asylum initiatives. Three proposals, in particular, suggest binding measures: a temporary relocation measure for asylum-seekers, a permanent relocation system for asylum-seekers, and a regulation establishing a common list of &amp;ldquo;safe countries of origin.&amp;rdquo; This list would include Western Balkan countries and Turkey. This article will focus on the &amp;ldquo;safe country of origin&amp;rdquo; rules.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the UK, Ireland, and Denmark are not subject to these measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>