<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>International Criminal Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-criminal-law/</link><description>Recent content in International Criminal Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-criminal-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas.</description></item></channel></rss>