<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microsoft Windows on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microsoft-windows/</link><description>Recent content in Microsoft Windows on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microsoft-windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud On The Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</guid><description>Big corporations are shifting their data centers to the cloud for financial and logistical benefits, enabling work from anywhere. But what about smaller businesses? Can they enjoy similar advantages?
One cloud solution often overlooked due to its existence before the cloud trend is GoToMyPC. Although not typically associated with the cloud, it embodies the concept.
GoToMyPC enables remote login to your computer. But isn&amp;rsquo;t accessing your desktop from a restaurant, running office applications, conceptually similar to using a private cloud?</description></item><item><title>Google's Plan To Chew Up Microsoft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</guid><description>A recent Wall Street Journal article hints at Google&amp;rsquo;s next target: Microsoft.
Google&amp;rsquo;s goals might extend beyond replacing Microsoft as the dominant force in PC operating systems. Their ambition could be complete control over all devices with embedded computers, essentially every electronic device.
This theory stems from reports that PC manufacturers like Hewlett-Packard are experimenting with Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system in netbooks. Android, primarily a mobile phone operating system, might seem harmless to established PC operating systems, but that might be a miscalculation.</description></item></channel></rss>