<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Hosted VoIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-hosted-voip/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Hosted VoIP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-hosted-voip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</a></p></description></item><item><title>End of the Premises Contact Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business telephone systems have evolved significantly. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from single-line phones to switchboards, automated systems, and sophisticated call center PBXs. However, one thing remained constant: these systems were all located on-site.
What’s Wrong With Premises Equipment?
Keeping everything in-house seems appealing because it gives you control over functionality, access, and services. You might even believe that in-house systems are more reliable than off-site solutions.
On-premises systems offer visibility and control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>