<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Singapore on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/singapore/</link><description>Recent content in Singapore on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/singapore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LASALLE Show will begin in April 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</guid><description>From the beginning of April to the end of May, the public and industry professionals are invited to view almost 900 graduating student projects at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s LASALLE College of the Arts yearly graduation showcase.
The projects featured at The LASALLE Show are developed throughout the students&amp;rsquo; final year and embody the culmination of their artistic growth and the realization of their aspirations. The LASALLE Show also provides insights into current trends in contemporary arts and design and highlights the emerging work of young artists.</description></item><item><title>In 2021, digitalization will be the driving force behind recruitment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Randstad Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 2021 Market Outlook Report examines the economic and hiring trends anticipated for 2021.
Jaya Dass, Managing Director for Randstad Malaysia and Singapore, emphasizes that digital transformation will be a key driver of talent demand in 2021. She predicts a surge in demand for tech professionals and digitally skilled individuals across various sectors. While acknowledging the cautious optimism of businesses in the wake of the pandemic, Dass highlights the need for agility and innovation to adapt to the evolving landscape.</description></item><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides leasing options for high-end smartphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first mobile phone leasing program to make high-end devices more accessible.
Subscribers with SIM Only plans can choose to pay a low monthly fee to use premium Apple and Samsung handsets instead of buying them outright. They can lease the newest Apple iPhone and Samsung Galaxy models for two years and have the option to upgrade in the twelfth month for a S$200 fee.
With prices starting at S$35 per month for a Samsung Galaxy S9 (64 GB), customers can save up to S$578 off the regular retail price if they lease the phone for a year or S$358 if they keep it for two years.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Smile Singapore in Clarke Quay Central and share your beautiful smile with us!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</guid><description>The installation of the Smile project at Clarke Quay Central is currently underway.
Clarke Quay Central mall is promoting a happier Singapore with its Smile Singapore campaign. Launched as part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Jubilee celebrations, this project gives companies a platform to share their happy moments in the nation.
Caine Teo, head of Ape Works, the Creative Partner of the Smile Singapore Campaign, believes happiness is infectious. By showcasing pictures of smiling faces, they hope to remind Singaporeans of the many reasons to smile in their country.</description></item><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport Group announces the closure of Terminal 2 for a period of 18 months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Changi Airport.
Due to a significant decrease in air travel and the low likelihood of a return to pre-pandemic levels soon, Changi Airport Group (CAG) has decided to consolidate operations at Changi Airport. This move aims to reduce operating costs like utilities and cleaning for CAG and its partners while optimizing resource allocation across the airport&amp;rsquo;s terminals.
Starting May 1, 2020, Terminal 2 (T2) will halt operations for 18 months, relocating airlines to other terminals*.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean IT leaders are concerned that a shortage of skills could impede the progress of the Smart Nation initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</guid><description>93% of Singaporean Chief Information Officers (CIOs) are worried that Singapore lacks the IT talent pool needed to successfully implement Smart Nation initiatives.
Six out of 10 CIOs believe Smart Nation initiatives will lead to more IT jobs, and 53% believe these initiatives will boost average IT salaries.
New independent research* commissioned by specialized recruiter Robert Half reveals that over 9 in 10 (93%) Singaporean IT leaders are concerned about the lack of readily available IT talent in Singapore to build a Smart Nation-ready workforce.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp.</description></item><item><title>In 2017, a settlement network powered by blockchain announced that it would waive fees for transfers to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</guid><description>OKLink, a global settlement platform, has introduced the first entirely free remittance corridor. The company stated that transfers up to US$100,000 each month to Singapore will be free throughout 2017.
Previously, OKLink applied a 0.1% fee on cross-border payments to Singapore, while other companies might charge up to US$5 per transaction.
&amp;ldquo;As the world&amp;rsquo;s largest blockchain-powered global settlement network, we can process cross-border payments faster and more affordably as more partners join,&amp;rdquo; explained Jack Liu, Chief Strategy Officer at OKLink.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>Orchard Road in Singapore is adorned with Christmas lights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road is aglow with Disney magic this holiday season. The &amp;ldquo;Disney Magical Moments — Christmas on A Great Street!&amp;rdquo; celebration features illuminated displays of beloved characters. The lights were officially switched on the evening of November 10.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the Toy Story-themed lights outside Plaza Singapura from the opening night.
The lights are arranged in four color-themed zones:
- Orange: Pixar’s Toy Story characters, including Woody, Buzz Lightyear, and their friends.</description></item><item><title>Tea Forté Singapore presents three mooncake collections as part of the Autumn in Abundance series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</guid><description>Source: Tea Forté.
Tea Forté Singapore, a specialty tea company, has introduced its new Autumn in Abundance mooncake collection, featuring traditional baked mooncakes with reduced sugar, the Creative Infused line, and a special Luxury selection.
The company suggests pairing the traditional mooncakes with its organic white ginger pear tea, the Creative Infused collection with the organic green mango peach tea, and the Luxurious selections with its orchid vanilla tea.</description></item><item><title>The FastGig app has been released to connect flexible workers with job opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</guid><description>FastCo, the company known for its Asian non-executive job platform FastJobs, has launched FastGig, an app designed for the expanding gig economy. FastCo claims this is one of the first apps specifically for gig workers in Southeast Asia.
FastGig, operating as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first workforce-as-a-service (WaaS) platform, connects skilled flexible workers with companies facing staffing shortages, particularly during peak seasons.
Julian Tan, FastCo&amp;rsquo;s Founder &amp;amp; CEO, highlights FastGig as a solution to a significant market gap, providing flexibility for both workers and businesses and transforming Singapore&amp;rsquo;s gig economy.</description></item><item><title>Delicious Medallions from Swensen's</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</guid><description>Swensen&amp;rsquo;s is offering early bird discounts on their chocolate-covered Sweet Medallions mooncakes until September 20th, 2017.
The mooncakes are available in a variety of flavors like cookies &amp;rsquo;n cream surprise, durian royale, Rocher crunch, and sticky chewy chocolate.
Source: Swensen&amp;rsquo;s website. Four chocolate-covered flavours are on offer in Swensen&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017. Place your order to take advantage of the 20% early bird discount available to Swensen&amp;rsquo;s Cool Rewards and Kids&amp;rsquo; Club members.</description></item><item><title>BEAM offers self-storage services in Singapore through a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>BEAM, a new self-storage company, has launched in Singapore, offering a unique approach to traditional storage solutions. Their services are managed entirely through a mobile app.
Unlike conventional self-storage providers that lease fixed spaces, BEAM offers flexible per-item storage. This means users only pay for the space their belongings occupy, eliminating wasted costs. Additionally, while traditional facilities are often inconveniently located, BEAM provides free pick-up and delivery to their secure 6,000 sq ft facility, equipped with CCTV and access control.</description></item><item><title>Success in business relies on establishing a broad network, having a strong passion, dedicating time, and learning from numerous failures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 03:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</guid><description>Alex Foo, co-founder of the entrepreneur-focused psychometric profiling tool Starteur, offers three key tips for entrepreneurial success. These insights, derived from both his attendance at the Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 (June 22-24, USA) and his personal journey as a young entrepreneur, were shared during a Shopee University session. Foo&amp;rsquo;s trip to GES 2016 was sponsored by Shopee, the e-commerce platform by Garena. This sponsorship reflects Shopee&amp;rsquo;s commitment to nurturing the next generation of Singaporean entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>Starting October 14, the Coffee Lounge at Goodwood Park Hotel will be offering an expanded menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Goodwood Park Hotel, home to the Coffee Lounge known for its Taiwan porridge and local dishes, is launching a limited-time menu enhancement. From October 14th, guests can enjoy new additions to the &amp;ldquo;Design Your Own Local Degustation Set Menu&amp;rdquo; and a special dessert buffet featuring Mao Shan Wang durian.
This year, from October 14th to November 17th, Coffee Lounge&amp;rsquo;s popular dessert buffet will showcase Mao Shan Wang durian pastries alongside its regular offerings during lunch and dinner.</description></item><item><title>Beads Actually is introducing a special merlion bead in celebration of SG50, available for a limited time only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beads-actually-is-introducing-a-special-merlion-bead-in-celebration-of-sg50-available-for-a-limited-time-only/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beads-actually-is-introducing-a-special-merlion-bead-in-celebration-of-sg50-available-for-a-limited-time-only/</guid><description>The Singaporean store Beads Actually is offering pre-orders for a merlion bead from OHM Beads. The merlion, a creature with a lion&amp;rsquo;s head and a fish&amp;rsquo;s body and tail, is a well-known symbol of Singapore.
Only two hundred of these beads are available, exclusively through Beads Actually from July 2nd to July 31st. Following this period, it will be available for individual purchase globally.
The bead, priced at S$110, is included in a starter kit featuring either a plain bangle or a snap-clasp bracelet.</description></item><item><title>Singapore gets a sneak peek at the HUAWEI Mate 20 icon before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. The square icon at various malls in
Singapore.
People in Singapore were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through an unexpected display of an illuminated square icon projected onto buildings throughout the city over the weekend.
This symbolic imagery appeared on structures in various locations such as Raffles City, Bugis Junction, Bugis+, and Plaza Singapura.
This readily identifiable square represents the phone&amp;rsquo;s camera setup, which includes a Leica Triple Camera and flash seamlessly integrated into the back of the HUAWEI Mate 20 series smartphones.</description></item><item><title>Bookmate has teamed up with StarHub for its initial launch in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Bookmate. Pictured at the December 17 launch of Bookmate in Singapore are (from left): Simon Dunlop, Bookmate Founder, Andrew Baev, Bookmate Managing Director, and Michael Sim, StarHub Lead Futurist, i3 (Innovation, Investment, Incubation).
Bookmate, a social platform for reading e-books, has launched in Singapore, its initial entry point into the Southeast Asian market. The service offers subscribers unlimited reading for a fixed monthly price, drawing from a library of over half a million e-books provided by 600 publishers.</description></item><item><title>Preorder the HUAWEI Matebook X Pro now in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</guid><description>Huawei Consumer Business Group is introducing the HUAWEI MateBook X Pro to its Singapore laptop collection. Until August 16, 2020, customers can take advantage of special gift packages worth S$250 to S$1,200 when they purchase select laptops.
The premium MateBook X Pro boasts a sleek, metallic design with a sandblasted finish. At just 14.6 mm thick and 1.33 kg, it prioritizes portability without sacrificing a truly immersive viewing experience.
Source: Huawei.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is implementing measures to ensure that esports becomes a profitable industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</guid><description>Source: SCOGA. From left: Matthias Beyer, Partnerships Lead, Southeast Asia at Twitch, Dennis Ooi, Honorary Secretary of (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA), Kelvin Tan, President and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Nicholas Khoo, Chairman and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Raiford Cockfield III, Director of APAC Partnerships at Twitch, and Dr Charles Ling, COO, Informatics Education.
As esports&amp;rsquo; popularity explodes globally, the (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA) has established new partnerships to cultivate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s esports landscape.</description></item><item><title>Singtel will be providing the option to share up to 50GB of mobile data at the PC Show 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</guid><description>Singtel is increasing its mobile data offerings with the launch of &amp;ldquo;DataMore,&amp;rdquo; a new plan featuring larger data bundles. This launch comes less than a month after Circles.Life entered the market with a focus on data options. DataMore is designed for users who need a lot of data and is shareable with multiple users, making it perfect for families.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Mobile Marketing, highlights that this plan caters to customer demand for larger data packages at affordable prices.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is invited to a new year countdown at Clarke Quay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay.
Clarke Quay invites everyone in Singapore to celebrate the end of the year with exciting festivities. Popular radio DJs Glenn Ong from Class95FM and Sonia Chew from 987FM will host the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve countdown. The event will feature live music by the band Goodfellas, a vibrant street parade with a glow theme, and roving percussionists.
The entire event at Clarke Quay will be broadcasted live on 987FM.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with TVB programming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</guid><description>Singtel TV is adding Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s TVB Jade and TVB Xing He channels to its lineup. From September 9th to October 8th, 2019, viewers can enjoy a free preview.
Singtel customers will have access to the same TVB Jade as Hong Kong viewers, featuring Cantonese dramas, variety shows, and infotainment programs.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CEO of Consumer Singapore, shared that the company is fulfilling customer requests by introducing these channels, broadening their comprehensive TV offerings and solidifying their position as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading pay-TV provider.</description></item><item><title>In January, StarHub will be featuring high-definition Korean movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</guid><description>StarHub TV customers will be the first in Asia to enjoy the latest and greatest Korean films in high definition (HD), 24 hours a day. The company announced that tvN Movies HD, Asia’s first channel dedicated to Korean films, will launch on StarHub TV (channel 818) on January 11, 2017. For added convenience, the channel will also be available on demand as tvN Movies VOD HD. Customers can watch it anytime on StarHub TV Channel 819, or stream it via StarHub Go, StarHub&amp;rsquo;s online streaming service.</description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11.</description></item><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions.</description></item><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas.</description></item><item><title>Singapore and Japan will work together to promote collaboration and assist in the development of businesses and startups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-japan-will-work-together-to-promote-collaboration-and-assist-in-the-development-of-businesses-and-startups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-japan-will-work-together-to-promote-collaboration-and-assist-in-the-development-of-businesses-and-startups/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Economic Development Board (EDB) and Enterprise Singapore have partnered with the Japan External Trade Organisation (JETRO) to enhance support for startups and businesses in both Singapore and Japan. This agreement was formalized during the ASEAN Economic Ministers’ Meeting 2018.
The collaboration aims to create opportunities for startups and businesses by facilitating information exchange and organizing joint initiatives and events. This will strengthen the connection between the innovation ecosystems of Singapore and Japan.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases its offering of free content as the circuit-breaker in Singapore is extended</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</guid><description>Singtel TV is expanding its free preview by adding 10 more channels while the circuit breaker period is extended. This is in addition to the 95,000 hours of programming already offered for free on Singtel TV and Singtel CAST, which was launched last month to help entertain people stuck at home.
From May 1st to 31st, Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO will offer a free preview with more entertainment, factual, news, and other programming from popular channels including National Geographic and FOX Family Movies.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces three new exclusive routes with a 20% discount on all flights until February 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</guid><description>AirAsia is the sole airline offering flights for three new routes: Johor Bahru to Tawau, Singapore to Kota Bharu, and Singapore to Terengganu. The airline is currently promoting these routes with fares as low as RM69* for travel between Johor Bahru and Tawau. This offer is valid for bookings made before February 16th, 2014, for travel dates between April 18th, 2014 and January 31st, 2015.
Welcome banners at Changi Airport</description></item><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended.</description></item><item><title>Three new programs to assist Singaporean businesses in their digital transformation efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-programs-to-assist-singaporean-businesses-in-their-digital-transformation-efforts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 01:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-programs-to-assist-singaporean-businesses-in-their-digital-transformation-efforts/</guid><description>Singapore has launched new initiatives to boost digitalization among its enterprises, especially small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), which are considered the backbone of the nation&amp;rsquo;s economy. S Iswaran, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, announced three key initiatives at an industry networking event.
Minister Iswaran delivering the opening address.
The Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA) and Enterprise Singapore launched &amp;ldquo;Start Digital&amp;rdquo;, an initiative under the &amp;ldquo;SMEs Go Digital&amp;rdquo; program. Start Digital will give new SMEs a head start by providing two free foundational digital solutions for a minimum of six months.</description></item><item><title>BenQ introduces new digital signage, projectors, and interactive flat panels, creating a buzz</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</guid><description>BenQ, a leading provider of visual display technology, has introduced a range of new projectors, digital signage, and interactive flat panels, all emphasizing high quality and innovative design. The company highlighted its commitment to delivering excellent visual experiences across various sectors, including business, retail, and food &amp;amp; beverage.
Business The MX666+ projector.
The MX666+ is the first wireless business projector to feature Near Field Communication (NFC) technology and USB connectivity, making it ideal for bring-your-own-device environments.</description></item><item><title>Golden Equator Consulting assists small and medium-sized enterprises and startups in advancing towards success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 02:34:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</guid><description>Golden Equator Consulting (GE Consulting), a business consultancy firm, has established a presence in Singapore to serve small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups in the region. Sharon Chong, CEO of GE Consulting, noted that these businesses need strategic and operational support to streamline their growth and focus on core business functions.
GE Consulting offers comprehensive business consultancy services, covering areas such as business strategy, sales positioning, financial support, marketing, technology, human resources, and legal compliance.</description></item><item><title>The Butchers Club Burger offers National Day dishes in celebration of Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>The Butchers Club Burger in Singapore is launching a special menu item for National Day: The Little Red Dot Burger.
Starting July 29th and lasting for two weekends, The Little Red Dot Burger will be featured as part of a National Day Set Menu at The Butchers Club Burger Singapore. This marks the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s first National Day celebration in Singapore, and the burger itself is a tribute to a beloved local dish: satay ayam (chicken satay).</description></item><item><title>Aon announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017 award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</guid><description>Employee engagement at companies recognized as Aon Best Employers rose by two percentage points this year, reaching 82%.
Aon Best Employers are setting the standard for positive employer branding, achieving scores from 83% to 92% in employee perception across all levels of tenure.
Five special recognitions were given this year, including the introduction of a new award category: Best Employer for Startups.
Source: Aon. Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017.</description></item><item><title>OPPO empowers Singaporeans to discover the ultimate experience with #UncoverTheUltimate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</guid><description>Last week, OPPO, a global provider of smart devices, introduced its latest lineup of smartphones, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s first 5G offering, the Find X2 Pro 5G, and a new addition to its creative Reno series, the Reno3.
This unveiling follows the global online launch of the Find X2 series on March 6. The Find X2 Pro boasts a 120 Hz QHD AMOLED screen, 65 W SuperVOOC Flash Charge 2.0 technology, and the Qualcomm Snapdragon 865 processor, delivering an enhanced overall photography and video experience.</description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule.</description></item><item><title>Unveiling the intricate nyonya needlework at the Peranakan Museum in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unveiling-the-intricate-nyonya-needlework-at-the-peranakan-museum-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:39:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unveiling-the-intricate-nyonya-needlework-at-the-peranakan-museum-in-singapore/</guid><description>This image, from the Peranakan Museum website, shows an example of Nyonya needlework.
The &amp;ldquo;Nyonya Needlework: Embroidery and Beadwork in the Peranakan World&amp;rdquo; exhibition is currently on display at the Peranakan Museum in Singapore until March 26, 2017.
This exhibition showcases the artistry of Nyonya needlework, a significant aspect of Peranakan Chinese culture. Elaborate curtains, wall hangings, delicate purses, handkerchiefs, and slippers are meticulously crafted with tiny beads, silk, gold, and silver threads.</description></item><item><title>Experience a unique twist on French-inspired dining this holiday season at Sofitel So Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel So Singapore. Paulo.
At Sofitel So Singapore, Xperience restaurant&amp;rsquo;s head chef, Trevor Paulo, is celebrating his first Christmas season at the hotel with a special four-course Christmas Eve dinner.
The dinner starts with a small bite of blinis topped with dill yogurt and herring roe. The first course is a visually appealing dish of house-cured Salmon Gravlax arranged to look like a miniature garden with edible truffle &amp;ldquo;soil&amp;rdquo; and pickled shallots.</description></item><item><title>Reserve a magical Disney experience aboard the Disney Adventure through Traveloka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</guid><description>Starting in the fourth quarter of 2024, travelers can book voyages with Disney Cruise Lines departing from Singapore through the Traveloka app, according to an announcement from the Southeast Asian travel platform. This addition to Traveloka&amp;rsquo;s offerings reinforces the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to showcasing the diverse experiences and attractions available in Singapore.
Launching in late 2025, the Disney Adventure will call Singapore its home port. The ship boasts seven themed areas with Disney-themed dining and exciting onboard activities.</description></item><item><title>Anticipate more sustainable and environmentally-friendly buildings in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Building and Construction Authority (BCA) announced new initiatives during the opening ceremony of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW). These initiatives, stemming from a review of the third Green Building Masterplan, focus on improving occupant indoor environmental quality, promoting energy-efficient buildings, and incorporating green practices into existing structures.
Desmond Lee, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Social and Family Development and Second Minister for National Development, was the guest of honor at the ceremony.</description></item><item><title>Nanu, the free calling app, provides a fresh approach to connecting with customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</guid><description>Source: nanu website.
Nanu, the first entirely free mobile calling app, is experiencing rapid growth in its monthly and daily active users. Based in Singapore, the startup claims its app&amp;rsquo;s active user rates are almost twice the industry standard, with 56% monthly active users and 19% daily active users.
CEO Martin Nygate points out that many tech startups avoid disclosing these figures due to poor performance. He&amp;rsquo;s pleased to share nanu&amp;rsquo;s positive data, reflecting both strong download numbers and increasing app usage.</description></item><item><title>ARTWALK Little India combines elements of the past with modern influences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</guid><description>Source: ARTWALK Little India. Izzad Radzali Shah, Festival, ARTWALK Little India 2018, LASALLE College of the Arts, 2018. Photo: Ng Wu Gang. The multidisciplinary arts festival ARTWALK Little India is a collaboration between LASALLE College of the Arts (LASALLE) and the Singapore Tourism Board (STB), with support from the Little India Shopkeepers and Heritage Association. It returns for its fourth year in January 2018 as a featured event in Singapore Art Week.</description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach.</description></item><item><title>Singapore and Jiangsu strengthen economic ties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-jiangsu-strengthen-economic-ties/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 23:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-jiangsu-strengthen-economic-ties/</guid><description>The Singapore-Jiangsu Cooperation Council (SJCC) aims to boost opportunities for companies from both regions in areas like collaboration in third-party markets, trade and logistics, and financial services. This contributes to the existing Singapore-Jiangsu economic partnership and advances the Belt and Road Initiative (BRI). Thirteen memoranda of understanding (MoUs) reflect these goals.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Heng Swee Keat, who is also SJCC Co-Chairman, emphasized the strong, enduring relationship between Singapore and Jiangsu.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Gifts Show will be running until July 11th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-gifts-show-will-be-running-until-july-11th/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 19:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-gifts-show-will-be-running-until-july-11th/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show 2014 (SGS), now in its ninth year, will focus on showcasing products designed in Singapore and local businesses.
The show, supported by the DesignSingapore Council, will feature many Singapore-made gifts, including a new gift and souvenir line called Now &amp;amp; Then. Celcem, led by designer and Singaporean entrepreneur Edwin Low, owner of the local retail boutique Supermama, spearheads this new label. Low, the recipient of the President’s Design Award in 2013, runs Supermama, the studio responsible for the President’s Design Award’s ‘Singapore Icons’ souvenir collection.</description></item><item><title>According to Accenture, gaining digital skills could help reduce the gender gap by up to 40 years faster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</guid><description>Source: Accenture. Closing the gender gap at work.
According to Accenture research, digital skills and technologies are empowering women in Singapore to secure and progress in their careers. However, a wage disparity persists, with men earning more. Ranked 5th out of 31 countries in Accenture&amp;rsquo;s research, Singaporean women demonstrate significant progress in digital fluency, reflecting their adoption and utilization of digital tools for knowledge acquisition, networking, and enhanced efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is taking steps to enhance its resilience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-taking-steps-to-enhance-its-resilience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-taking-steps-to-enhance-its-resilience/</guid><description>Concept classroom by dream by WOMBO.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2023 centers around navigating global economic uncertainties by enhancing the country&amp;rsquo;s productivity and competitiveness.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Deputy PM and Finance Minister, Lawrence Wong, highlighted the US ban on advanced chip technology transfer to China and its ripple effects. He stated, &amp;ldquo;We are seeing a fierce competition for dominance in critical technologies, likely to intensify, leading to a concerning trend toward increased economic nationalism and protectionism worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson.</description></item><item><title>RENEW e-recycling initiative in Singapore grows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/renew-e-recycling-initiative-in-singapore-grows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/renew-e-recycling-initiative-in-singapore-grows/</guid><description>Four major electronics retailers in Singapore – Best Denki, COURTS, Gain City, and Harvey Norman – have partnered with DHL, StarHub, and TES to expand the RENEW e-waste recycling program. By placing RENEW bins in 20 of their stores, these retailers aim to make e-waste recycling more accessible to the public.
RENEW, which stands for REcycling the Nation’s Electronic Waste, is a collaborative effort by DHL, StarHub, and TES to promote responsible disposal of electronic devices and ICT equipment.</description></item><item><title>Investing in corporate bonds will be made more accessible for Singaporean investors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has launched two new regulations aimed at making it easier for retail investors – individuals who purchase securities for personal investment purposes – to participate in corporate bond offerings. These changes are part of MAS&amp;rsquo;s broader strategy to expand retail investors&amp;rsquo; investment choices by providing access to simpler, lower-risk investment products.
Corporate issuers typically rely on the wholesale bond market for funding due to the higher expenses associated with reaching retail investors.</description></item><item><title>A new e-trading platform for physical commodities, based on blockchain technology, has been launched in Singapore on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-e-trading-platform-for-physical-commodities-based-on-blockchain-technology-has-been-launched-in-singapore-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-e-trading-platform-for-physical-commodities-based-on-blockchain-technology-has-been-launched-in-singapore-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Commodities Intelligence Centre (CIC) has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first physical commodity business-to-business (B2B) e-trading platform in collaboration with key partners: Zall Smartcomm, a prominent B2B player in China; Global eTrade Services (GeTS) Asia, a subsidiary of CrimsonLogic; and Singapore Exchange (SGX). Enterprise Singapore played a crucial role in bringing these partners together.
CIC offers a comprehensive global trading platform powered by Blockchain technology. This platform provides commodity traders worldwide with a range of services, including transaction matching, simplified customs clearance, supply chain financing, flexible payment options, and enhanced resource pooling for both buyers and sellers.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with Amara Sanctuary Singapore's special promotion!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:31:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa. Singapore laksa.
To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 53rd birthday, the 5-star Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is offering a National Day special at their Shutters restaurant.
During this National Day celebration, Shutters&amp;rsquo; dinner guests will enjoy a discounted Singapura buffet, priced at S$53++ per adult, down from the usual S$75++. This offer is valid from 6:30 pm to 10:00 pm. The buffet features local favorites like Nyonya laksa, barbequed stingray, and charcoal-grilled satay.</description></item><item><title>Circles.Life introduces a range of new services centered around unlimited usage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</guid><description>For S$3, enjoy unlimited on-demand data at 4G+ speeds.
For the first time, get unlimited WhatsApp roaming in 18 countries for S$1 per day.
Source: Circles.Life. Poster for Unlimited
Data on Demand. Circles.Life, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fourth mobile operator, argues that the current unlimited data plans are actually quite restrictive. They believe that these plans should not be limited to weekends, slowed down after a small data limit, or tied to yearly contracts.</description></item><item><title>Five years later, Club HEAL still works to raise awareness about mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-later-club-heal-still-works-to-raise-awareness-about-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 01:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-later-club-heal-still-works-to-raise-awareness-about-mental-health/</guid><description>Club HEAL, a volunteer-based organization, recently celebrated its fifth anniversary with a gala dinner. Almost 600 guests and supporters attended.
Dr. Radiah Salim, the founder and president of Club HEAL, stated that the organization strives to address as many service gaps as possible.
She shared that approximately 2,000 individuals have benefited from Club HEAL&amp;rsquo;s assistance. Her hope is to see more Club HEAL locations while expanding their outreach to those facing addiction challenges.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with the One Lagi Best Deal!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</guid><description>Source: One Faber Group. Cable car visual.
In honor of Singapore’s 52nd birthday, One Faber Group is offering the One Lagi Best Deal, featuring local promotions on its leisure activities and services from Faber Peak Singapore to Sentosa Island.
Until September 17th, Singaporeans* can take advantage of a special offer: a S$52 bundle for adults and a S$42 bundle for children. The adult bundle includes a round-trip Singapore cable car ride, a standard ticket to the Wings Of Time show, a standard ticket to Sentosa Merlion, a three-course meal at the Good Old Days restaurant, and a batik orchid magnet.</description></item><item><title>The new bronze pink Xperia XZ Premium phones are now on sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The Bronze Pink Sony Xperia XZ.
After the June release of the Sony Xperia XZ Premium, Sony Mobile has launched a third color option in Singapore: Bronze Pink.
This new pink-hued phone will be available at select retailers starting July 8th. The Xperia XZ Premium has a suggested retail price of S$1,098.
Sony claims its Xperia XZ Premium is the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest smartphone, boasting a 4K HDR display.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 210, an entry-level dual SIM phone, is priced at less than S$160</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</guid><description>HTC will launch its budget-friendly smartphone, the HTC Desire 210, in Singapore on Wednesday, September 3, 2014. The phone will be sold through various retailers in two colors: Stealth Black and Polar White. A notable feature of the Desire 210 is its dual SIM card support, allowing users to manage personal and work profiles easily from a single device.
Source: HTC.
“The HTC Desire 210 brings impressive technology and design to the entry-level smartphone market,” stated Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia.</description></item><item><title>Starting today, Singtel will be accepting preorders for the Google Pixel 2 XL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</guid><description>Singtel announced a partnership with Google to become the official telecommunications provider for the highly anticipated Google Pixel 2 XL in Singapore. Starting November 15th, Singtel customers will have the exclusive opportunity to be the first in Southeast Asia to purchase this new device.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, expressed excitement about bringing the Pixel 2 XL to Singapore, highlighting its innovative features that have been eagerly awaited by Android fans.</description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore is sponsoring limited edition prints for The Schooling Effect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. From left: Tan May Lin, Epson Singapore’s GM (Sales, Marketing &amp;amp; Customer Service Division) and Tay Kay Chin, one of the collaborators for the photo book, with one of the prints available for sale as part of the collaboration.
Epson Singapore, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, is supporting The Schooling Effect. This community project is inspired by the victory of Singaporean Olympian Joseph Schooling at the 2016 Olympic Games.</description></item><item><title>In March, Dario Cecchini explores culinary partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 10:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</guid><description>The renowned Bottega di Carna at the Mondrian Singapore Duxton, known for its unique dining experience crafted by &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Butcher&amp;rdquo; Dario Cecchini, is excited to announce upcoming collaborations this March. The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s philosophy centers around respecting the entire animal and utilizing traditional methods to showcase the finest produce and ingredients.
Cecchini Returns with Exciting Collaborations Bottega di Carna X Bold &amp;amp; Braised Hawker Pop-up
March 6th-7th
Cecchini and Bottega di Carna&amp;rsquo;s Head Chef Kenny Huang are joining forces with local Chinatown eatery Bold &amp;amp; Braised at Maxwell Food Centre.</description></item><item><title>Flight Experience Singapore and McGallen &amp; Bolden offer unique leadership workshops that stand out from the rest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</guid><description>Source: McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden.
Flight Experience Singapore, the first flight simulator open to the public in Asia, has partnered with the consulting firm McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden to offer leadership workshops.
Their program, Leadership Secrets at 30,000 Feet, is designed for business leaders and executives. It uses a realistic cockpit setting to teach leadership skills. The customized, four-hour workshop draws on decades of experience from Captain Michael Caston, a pilot with experience flying Boeing 747 and 737 jets for British Airways and Singapore Airlines.</description></item><item><title>The first Founders' Friday session in Singapore by Huawei will showcase Scott Bales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</guid><description>Source: Scott Bales website.
Huawei is launching a new networking series called Founders&amp;rsquo; Friday. The series aims to connect business leaders with professionals to exchange ideas, address difficulties, and develop innovative solutions for advancing the digital world.
The inaugural event, presented alongside the HUAWEI Mate 9, features prominent digital and innovation expert Scott Bales. He will discuss essential principles for fostering a culture of innovation within organizations. Bales, the Managing Director of Singapore-based Innovation Labs Asia, brings over a decade of global experience in innovation, thought leadership, implementation planning, and strategy.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Budget of Singapore provides support for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Ministry of Finance, Singapore. Infrastructure investments were also announced as part of Budget 2015.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2015, presented by Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Tharman Shanmugaratnam, included several business initiatives. These encompassed increased training assistance, a gradual reduction in business restructuring aid, a freeze on foreign worker levies (excluding manufacturing and construction), and measures to encourage innovation and expansion.
Training and development
Shanmugaratnam emphasized the government&amp;rsquo;s commitment to continuous investment in Singaporeans&amp;rsquo; skills development.</description></item><item><title>The IPO activity in Singapore is expected to exceed that of 2016 in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</guid><description>During the first half of 2017, Singapore saw a surge in initial public offerings (IPOs), attracting US$329 million in investments, as reported by PwC Singapore. This momentum is projected to continue, potentially exceeding the total funds raised in 2016. Professional services are emerging as a leading sector, with HRnetGroup and Shopper360&amp;rsquo;s IPOs securing a combined US$134 million, a significant leap from the previous year.
While Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) and business trusts, a traditional strength for the Singapore Exchange (SGX), constituted 33% of IPO proceeds, the anticipated listing of NetLink Trust, estimated at US$1.</description></item><item><title>Tokio Marine Life Insurance Singapore enhances chatbot with recruitment features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tokio-marine-life-insurance-singapore-enhances-chatbot-with-recruitment-features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tokio-marine-life-insurance-singapore-enhances-chatbot-with-recruitment-features/</guid><description>Source: TMLS website.
The TOMI avatar.
Tokio Marine Life Insurance Singapore (TMLS), the only Japanese life insurer in Singapore, has introduced a recruitment feature to its chatbot, TOMI (Tokio Marine Insurance).
This addition makes TOMI the first chatbot in Singapore to assist an insurer&amp;rsquo;s recruitment process, further enhancing its role as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first self-learning AI chatbot designed to increase public access to life insurance.
With the goal of engaging today&amp;rsquo;s tech-savvy generation in the recruitment process, TOMI is now equipped to answer over 300 questions about becoming a financial advisor.</description></item><item><title>Velox Networks claims that it can offer B2B phone services at a 95% lower cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</guid><description>Velox Networks, a new telecommunications company in Singapore, offers a voice over internet protocol (VoIP) and cloud-based private branch exchange (PBX) communications platform. They claim their service could save businesses up to 95% compared to traditional major telcos.
Currently, Singaporean businesses primarily use traditional PBXs for business-to-business communication. Velox aims to change this with its affordable, cloud-based PBX solution that surpasses the quality of free VoIP services, which often rely on less dependable consumer-grade technology.</description></item><item><title>Artyzen Singapore will be launched in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</guid><description>Preferred Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, boasting a global network of over 650 hotels, resorts, and residences in 80 countries, is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the upcoming October debut of Artyzen Singapore.
This 20-story establishment occupies the former site of the Marie Villa mansion, conveniently situated near Orchard Road and the Singapore Botanic Gardens. The hotel features 142 generously sized rooms and suites, each spanning at least 42 square meters and offering either a balcony or terraced Sky Gardens.</description></item><item><title>CASIO introduces new watches to coincide with the 40th anniversary of G-SHOCK and the opening of its flagship store in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-new-watches-to-coincide-with-the-40th-anniversary-of-g-shock-and-the-opening-of-its-flagship-store-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-new-watches-to-coincide-with-the-40th-anniversary-of-g-shock-and-the-opening-of-its-flagship-store-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: CASIO. The new flagship store at ION Orchard mall in Singapore.
CASIO has established its latest flagship store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s ION Orchard mall. This store showcases a distinctive sculpture by Singaporean artist Jahan Loh. This artwork features a metallic half-body bust that evokes a futuristic cyborg, with the face being a representation of Casio&amp;rsquo;s iconic watch and its signature rounded rectangular bezel.
Coinciding with the store launch, G-SHOCK, a Casio brand, has unveiled its most recent addition to the G-SQUAD sports series.</description></item><item><title>Coursera unveils the top courses for learners in Singapore in 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</guid><description>In 2021, Singaporean users on Coursera showed a strong interest in courses teaching in-demand tech and data science skills. This conclusion comes from Coursera&amp;rsquo;s yearly report analyzing course selections made by over 750,000 registered learners in Singapore. The report reveals the skills, abilities, and subjects most sought after by Singaporeans.
Here are the top 10 most popular Coursera courses in Singapore for 2021:
S Course Name Partner Name 1 First Step Korean Yonsei University 2 Machine Learning Stanford University 3 The Science of Well-Being Yale University 4 Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere Google 5 Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) University of Michigan 6 Financial Markets Yale University 7 Introduction to Psychology Yale University 8 _ Chinese for Beginners_ Peking University 9 _ Foundations of Project Management_ Google 10 Learning How to Learn: Powerful mental tools to help you master tough subjects Deep Teaching Solutions Source: Coursera.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir will begin flying between Okinawa and Japan in January 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will launch its inaugural charter flights between Singapore and Okinawa, Japan.
Operated in partnership with Okinawa Tourist Service (OTS) and Jumbo Tours Okinawa, these monthly charters will run from September 9, 2014, to January 3, 2015. Utilizing Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both business and economy class seating, these direct flights aim to provide travelers with a convenient option to visit Okinawa.
From September to October 2014, flights will depart Singapore Changi Airport Terminal 2 at 10:00 am and arrive at Okinawa Naha Airport at 4:15 pm.</description></item><item><title>Accor plans to introduce the ibis Styles brand to Singapore later this year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</guid><description>Source: Accor. The ibis Style in the Macpherson area, Singapore, will be launched this year.
Accor plans to open an ibis Styles hotel in Singapore by the last quarter of 2015, introducing a trendy, lifestyle-focused brand to the country. Situated within the same complex as the MacPherson shopping mall, the hotel is conveniently located at the intersection of MacPherson and Aljunied Roads, a short 20-minute drive from the airport.</description></item><item><title>The groundbreaking ceremony for Jewel has been successfully completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Changi Airport.
Jewel Changi Airport Trustee (JCAT), a collaboration between Changi Airport Group (CAG) and CapitaMalls Asia (the shopping mall branch of CapitaLand), has initiated the construction of Jewel Changi Airport. This mixed-use development, situated in front of Terminal 1 (T1), will feature attractions, retail spaces, a hotel, and airport operational facilities.
Strategically placed at the airport&amp;rsquo;s core, Jewel aims to be a premier lifestyle destination enhancing Changi Airport&amp;rsquo;s global standing and solidifying Singapore&amp;rsquo;s attractiveness as a layover spot for travelers.</description></item><item><title>Singapore National Administrative Professionals Week is here. If you need someone to talk to, I'm here for you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</guid><description>A recent survey conducted by Zyllem, a delivery service, in honor of Singapore Administrative Professionals Day 2016, showed that 93% of respondents believe that Administrative Professionals are the unsung heroes of Singaporean businesses.
However, the survey also revealed that 64% of coworkers admitted to taking their Admin Professionals for granted. They frequently rely on them to perform tasks outside their job description, including delivering umbrellas to colleagues stuck in the rain, sending forgotten passports to colleagues at airport check-in, performing first aid, and even providing early morning wake-up calls.</description></item><item><title>Job Forward introduces the Startup Essence referral tool for startups and small to medium enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-forward-introduces-the-startup-essence-referral-tool-for-startups-and-small-to-medium-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 01:44:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-forward-introduces-the-startup-essence-referral-tool-for-startups-and-small-to-medium-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Source: Job Forward.
Job Forward, the first online social recruitment platform in Singapore, has introduced Startup Essence. This new addition to their referral-based platform helps startups and small to medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) by allowing them to build recruitment pages that attract and engage potential employees. The company aims to create a new avenue for these businesses to connect with individuals who are a good fit for their company culture.</description></item><item><title>Guangzhou businesses enter into Letters of Intent with Singapore organizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</guid><description>Source: Guangzhou Municipal Government. Cai.
The city of Guangzhou held a promotional event in Singapore to explore collaboration and innovation between the two business hubs. Two agreements were reached: one between the Sino-Singapore International Joint Research Institute and Chinese Academy of Sciences Holdings Company, and another between Guangzhou Gas Group, Guangzhou Port Group, and the industrial group Royal Golden Eagle.
Guangzhou&amp;rsquo;s Vice Mayor, Cai Chaolin, who also leads the Nansha District&amp;rsquo;s Communist Party and Development Zone, highlighted the shared attributes between Guangzhou and Singapore, such as their size, cultural similarities, and languages.</description></item><item><title>The Startup Capitals conference will begin on May 20th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</guid><description>Source: Startup Capitals&amp;rsquo; website.
Startup Capitals, a leading-edge conference inspired by the recent book of the same name by Singapore-based author and journalist Zafar Anjum, will be held on May 20th in Singapore at The POD, NLB, 100 Victoria Street.
This one-day event, coinciding with the book&amp;rsquo;s official launch, will highlight the innovation and startup ecosystems of globally impactful cities. It will unite all facets of these ecosystems – entrepreneurs, business leaders, innovators, researchers, educators, government officials, and venture capitalists – under one roof.</description></item><item><title>Buffets for Iftar are available at 21 on Rajah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</guid><description>Source: 21 on Rajah.
The buffet.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a venue to hold a corporate Iftar gathering in Singapore during Ramadan, consider the halal-certified 21 On Rajah. Situated within Days Hotel Singapore at Zhongshan Park, this all-day dining restaurant is presenting a selection of Mediterranean and Asian Iftar buffets each evening.
Chef de Cuisine Faustino Picardo Ines Jr and his culinary team have crafted diverse menus throughout the week.</description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival showcases performances by exceptionally talented artists with disabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</guid><description>The True Colours Festival, showcasing talented performing artists with disabilities from the Asia Pacific region, will run from March 22nd to 25th, 2018 in Singapore.
The festival will feature up to 20 artist/troupe performances representing Japan, China, India, Korea, Malaysia, Cambodia, Kazakhstan, New Zealand, Australia, and Singapore. Guest artists from the UK and Canada will also be featured. Performances will take place at a multimedia concert experience inside the Singapore Indoor Stadium and at the nearby True Colours Festival Village.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean companies are prioritizing cloud technology to gain a competitive edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</guid><description>Source: VMware infographic.
VMware, a leading company in virtualization and cloud infrastructure, recently shared the results of their vForum Singapore Business Survey. The survey shows a positive attitude toward hybrid cloud solutions, which combine public cloud services with internal cloud technology, as a method of driving growth, efficiency, and innovation. Almost every business surveyed (90%) believes that the cloud can facilitate innovation, and nearly half (44%) prefer a hybrid cloud model for their IT infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Singapore investors who are accredited can transition to digital investing with Jachin Capital</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</guid><description>Jachin Capital, a Singapore-based independent fund manager, is now authorized to offer its digital investment platform, iAdvisor, to accredited investors in Singapore after receiving a Capital Markets Services Licence from the Monetary Authority of Singapore. The company specializes in providing investment management solutions, including discretionary and non-discretionary options, to accredited investors and private family offices throughout the Asia-Pacific region. Jachin Capital uses a transparent, rules-based approach to build and regularly rebalance investment portfolios around specific themes or ideas.</description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals its list of 25 talented individuals under the age of 25 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</guid><description>Spotify has unveiled the top 25 most influential artists under 25 who are currently dominating the music scene in Singapore.
Shawn Mendes, an 18-year-old singer-songwriter from Canada, takes the top spot. He boasts 25 million monthly listeners on Spotify and over 500 million streams for his hit song, &amp;ldquo;Stitches.&amp;rdquo; Following closely behind Mendes are Ariana Grande, Martin Garrix, Justin Bieber, and Alessia Cara. Popular artists Gentle Bones and Fifth Harmony are also included in the list.</description></item><item><title>Today marks the grand opening of Singapore's most Instagram-worthy nightclub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</guid><description>MARQUEE Singapore, a massive new nightclub, is launching at Marina Bay Sands on April 12, 2019. The opening weekend will feature world-renowned DJs Tiësto and Afrojack, with a special appearance by American rapper A$AP Rocky.
The 8K screen serves as a backdrop for TAO&amp;rsquo;s
co-founders Tepperberg (left) and Strauss (right).
This marks the first expansion into Asia for MARQUEE, a brand with clubs in New York, Las Vegas, and Sydney. The Singapore location is also the 35th project for TAO Group, the nightlife and hospitality company partnering with Marina Bay Sands on this venture.</description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become one of the top 10 e-marketplaces worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-one-of-the-top-10-e-marketplaces-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 04:46:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-one-of-the-top-10-e-marketplaces-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Aladdin Group. A lion dance to welcome Aladdin
Street Singapore.
The Aladdin Group is launching Aladdin Street Singapore, an e-commerce platform serving both businesses and individual consumers. It will operate through two websites: a Singapore-specific site at www.aladdinstreet.com.sg, and an international platform at www.aladdinstreet.com. Both sites are expected to launch in the fourth quarter of 2016.
Aladdinstreet&amp;rsquo;s goal is to be a reliable and secure online marketplace for merchants to sell and consumers to buy premium, halal products.</description></item><item><title>Business sentiment in Singapore for 2017 is characterized by caution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</guid><description>The Singapore government has released business sentiment data for 2017, covering both the manufacturing and retail sectors.
In the manufacturing sector, a survey conducted by the Singapore Economic Development Board revealed that a weighted 76% of firms expect business conditions in the first half of 2017 to remain similar to the previous quarter. While 13% anticipate improvement, 11% foresee a decline. Overall, the net weighted balance sits at 2%, indicating a slightly positive outlook for the manufacturing sector in early 2017.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash and UOB Asset Management have collaborated to provide a mobile robo-adviser that includes an ESG option</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for UOBAM Robo-Invest.
Singtel has introduced a new digital advisor, developed by UOB Asset Management (UOBAM), on its Dash e-wallet platform. This launch expands Dash’s selection of financial services, which already encompasses payments, international money transfers, insurance, savings, and investments.
UOBAM Robo-Invest is the first robo-advisor in Singapore available on a mobile wallet and stands out by offering sustainable investing options created by UOBAM specifically for Dash users.</description></item><item><title>Numerous innovations showcased at Food&amp;HotelAsia 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</guid><description>Display at the Suntec venue.
The Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) and ProWine Asia (PWA) trade shows are predicted to draw tens of thousands of attendees during their joint four-day run in Singapore, from April 24th to 27th.
This year marks the largest event yet. Visitors can explore exhibits from over 3,500 international food, beverage, and hospitality exhibitors throughout 120,000 sq m at FHA. In addition, PWA 2018 features 300 international wine and spirits exhibitors across 7,500 sq m.</description></item><item><title>Jane's Walk is back in Singapore for its fifth year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 22:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore Peatix website. Aerial view of Queenstown.
Now in its fifth year, Jane’s Walk Singapore is hosting a weekend of free walking tours throughout the city.
Inspired by urbanist, author, and activist Jane Jacobs, Jane’s Walk is a series of free, volunteer-led walking tours. Jacobs advocated for walkable, lively neighborhoods and encouraged community involvement in urban development. Her most renowned work, The Death and Life of Great American Cities, emphasizes the importance of observation, inquiry, and exploration in understanding cities.</description></item><item><title>The Women in Business Asia Pageant hosts a workshop on digital marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</guid><description>Source: Women in Business Asia Pageant Facebook page.
To empower women entrepreneurs, the Women in Business Asia Pageant is holding a masterclass on digital marketing and social media strategies specifically for women in Singapore.
The session, titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Marketing and Social Media Hacks for Women in Business,&amp;rdquo; will run for one hour and teach participants how to build an effective, business-oriented website designed to generate leads. Attendees will discover how to incorporate both original and curated content into their marketing plans.</description></item><item><title>Establish a system of experiences that fosters success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establish-a-system-of-experiences-that-fosters-success/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 20:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establish-a-system-of-experiences-that-fosters-success/</guid><description>To stand out, be creative and build an engaging experience around your product or service that resonates with your target audience, attracting customers organically. This advice comes from Big Bird Creative Company (BBCC), a Taiwanese integrated media company renowned for its children&amp;rsquo;s content services, including education consulting, production and distribution, and brand development, both in Taiwan and internationally.
Cathy Han, President of BBCC, shared several success stories during the Media Summit at the Asian Festival of Children&amp;rsquo;s Content 2014 in Singapore this past June.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir expands its route network to include Laos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, has started its first flights to Vientiane and Luang Prabang in Laos. This addition expands SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s network to 51 destinations across 14 countries.
The inaugural flight left Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport at 1:20 PM on October 31st and arrived at Vientiane’s Wattay International Airport at 3:15 PM. The same flight continued on to Luang Prabang International Airport at 4:05 PM, landing at 5:00 PM. The return flight from Luang Prabang departed at 5:50 PM and arrived back in Singapore at 10:05 PM (all times local).</description></item><item><title>Jane's Walk Singapore offers a blend of classic and innovative walking tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Peatix page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk logo.
The annual Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore, a series of free walking tours led by community members, will take place from May 4th to 6th. Inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, these walks encourage participants to share local stories, discover the city, and connect with their neighbors.
While many tours are already at capacity, new spots may open up, so interested individuals are encouraged to check back.</description></item><item><title>Dell presents key features for IT Show 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</guid><description>Dell is featuring special deals on select products at IT Show 2018, happening in Suntec Singapore now through March 18th.
The XPS 13, available in a new rose gold color, starts at S$2,899. This 13&amp;quot; device is touted as the most powerful in its class and the smallest 13&amp;quot; available. It boasts an 8th Gen Intel Quad Core processor, a 4K Ultra HD InfinityEdge display, and introduces Dell Cinema, featuring CinemaColor, CinemaStream with wireless channels, and CinemaSound with Waves MaxxAudio Pro.</description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace.</description></item><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA.</description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans will receive increased support for SkillsFuture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</guid><description>Source: SkillsFuture Singapore. Minister Puthucheary watches on as Ng (left) and Kevin Wo, Country GM, Microsoft Singapore (right) sign the MoU.
To better equip Singapore&amp;rsquo;s workforce and businesses for a digital-centric economy, SkillsFuture Singapore (SSG) has launched new initiatives. These include a partnership with Microsoft and enhancements to the national SkillsFuture for Digital Workplace program.
Dr. Janil Puthucheary, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Transport and Ministry of Communications and Information, announced these developments at the first SkillsFuture Festival X Smart Nation (SFFXSmart Nation) event.</description></item><item><title>Collagen, probiotics, and plant-based protein were popular subjects at Vitafoods Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</guid><description>Vitafoods Asia, a nutraceutical event showcasing the newest ingredients, product advancements, and technology driving innovation in the industry, revealed emerging trends.
Chris Lee, MD, Global Health &amp;amp; Nutrition Network Europe, Informa Markets, stated, &amp;ldquo;Nutraceuticals are a booming industry in Asia, and Informa Markets aims to support its growth in the region by providing a knowledge base and platform.&amp;rdquo;
First-time attendee Rikhia Mazumdar, Global Senior Brand Manager for Reckitt Benckiser, expressed her intention to return the following year.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 in Singapore have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</guid><description>Source: The Ascendas-Singbridge Group. From left: Ho Kheng Lian, Venture Partner, Vectr Ventures; Natalie Loh, Vice President of Products, Vanitee; Kuik Xiao Shi, Co-Founder, Vanitee; Pocket Sun, Founding Partner of SoGal Ventures; Adrianna Tan, Founder, Wobe; Virginia Tan, Co-founder and Managing Director of Lean In China; Adeline Quek, Head of Regional Business Development, Grabtaxi; Mrs Nina Yang, Chief Operating Officer of Singbridge.
The Ascendas-Singbridge Group selected two startups from Singapore to compete in the finals of the Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 competition.</description></item><item><title>SingPost releases stamps showcasing classic board games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</guid><description>Source: SingPost. The new traditional board games stamp issue.
Singapore Post (SingPost) is releasing a new set of five square stamps on April 27th. Each stamp features a hand-drawn image of a traditional board game popular in Singapore during the 1970s and 80s: Chinese chess, the diamond game, aeroplane chess, snakes and ladders, and checkers.
Chinese chess (1st local denomination) is a strategic board game for two players simulating a battle between two armies.</description></item><item><title>Eko Nugroho is currently showcasing his street art exhibition through digital prints produced by HP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</guid><description>This image, from HP Inc., showcases embroidered artwork by Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho. It features his signature masked characters and intricate designs reminiscent of Japanese woodcuts.
HP Inc is the Innovation Sponsor for the &amp;ldquo;Art from the Streets&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the ArtScience Museum in Singapore. For the exhibition, HP created nine large-scale prints of significant artworks. They are also using their digital printing technology to showcase the work of Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho in fresh and unexpected ways, demonstrating that street art can be displayed anywhere and on any medium.</description></item><item><title>Blum &amp; Co transforms the cheongsam into stylish workwear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 03:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</guid><description>Blum, a Singaporean fashion brand, has launched a new line of workwear inspired by the traditional cheongsam.
Source: Blum &amp;amp; Co.
Emerging in the 1920s as a symbol of women&amp;rsquo;s liberation, the cheongsam has undergone stylistic changes throughout the years. Originally a loose-fitting, full-sleeved dress, it evolved to feature a slimmer silhouette with shorter hemlines and a side slit. Despite being prohibited in mainland China following the communist revolution, the cheongsam remained popular in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF.</description></item><item><title>The winners of the FinTech Awards have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:57:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and The Association of Banks in Singapore (ABS) awarded S$1.2 million to 12 fintech companies at the FinTech Awards, held during the third annual Singapore FinTech Festival.
This year&amp;rsquo;s winning solutions focused on financial inclusion and represented a broader range of ASEAN countries. These solutions addressed various business areas, including credit scoring, mobile security, anti-money laundering, and digital investment.
Here are the 12 award recipients:</description></item><item><title>The exclusive offers available at the 26th edition of The PC Show</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</guid><description>The PC Show, celebrating 26 years of IT and consumer electronics in Singapore, is back. Major brands like Best Denki, Canon, Courts, Creative, Dell, Epson, Harvey Norman, HP, Lenovo, M1, Newstead, Samsung, Seagate, Singtel, and Toshiba will offer exciting products, deals, and competitive prices.
Gillian Loh, Project Manager at Lines Exposition and Management Services, highlighted that attendees often look for great deals and the latest technology at the show. Organizers aim to continually improve the visitor experience, and this year they are introducing dedicated zones for specific interests and providing online updates on deals and new products.</description></item><item><title>UOB discovers misunderstandings about financing options for small and medium businesses in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: UOB infographic. Statistics gathered from the Financing for Startups and Small Businesses Survey.
A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB) revealed that a significant number of startups and small businesses in Singapore lack a comprehensive understanding of the alternative funding options available to them for early expansion. These businesses are also uncertain about how to effectively utilize options such as venture capital, venture debt, and debt and equity crowdfunding.</description></item><item><title>Carly users now have the ability to post on Carousell as well</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</guid><description>Carousell, a popular online classifieds platform, has acquired Caarly, a Singapore-based startup, as part of its strategy to dominate the classifieds market.
Caarly is a mobile-first tool designed to simplify inventory management for used car dealerships. Since launching in Singapore in 2014, Caarly has partnered with over 200 car dealerships, representing a large portion of the market in Singapore. Existing Caarly partners can continue managing their inventory on the Caarly platform and seamlessly cross-post their listings to the cars category on Carousell with just one click.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in Singapore are increasingly transitioning to cloud services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</guid><description>Parallels, a company specializing in hosting and cloud services, has released an updated report on the Singaporean cloud market for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), called Parallels SMB Cloud Insights. This 2014 report predicts significant growth for the SMB cloud services market in Singapore, projecting it to reach S$916 million by 2017. This represents a strong three-year compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 21%.
Source: Parallels. Zanni.
John Zanni, Chief Marketing Officer for Service Providers at Parallels, observed that the Asia Pacific region is poised to outpace the rest of the world in cloud adoption due to its later start.</description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural India-ASEAN Writers Festival premieres in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</guid><description>The High Commission of India in Singapore is hosting the first India-ASEAN Writers Festival in Singapore.
This festival is one of many events celebrating 25 years of friendship between India and ASEAN, coinciding with the ASEAN India Pravasi Bharatiya Divas (Overseas Indians Day). The events are scheduled for January 6-7 at the Marina Bay Sands.
The PBD Writers Festival, a key event organized by Singapore-based publishing house Kitaab International on behalf of the High Commission, aims to &amp;ldquo;celebrate the literary ties between India and the ASEAN nations,&amp;rdquo; said Zafar Anjum, Kitaab&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO.</description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces WeChat SIM card for tourists from China visiting Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced two new prepaid SIM cards, named &amp;ldquo;StarHub WeChat Go SIM&amp;rdquo;, specifically designed for Chinese tourists visiting Singapore. This launch is a collaboration between StarHub and WeChat.
The StarHub WeChat Go SIM aims to meet the connectivity needs of the increasing number of Chinese tourists. Data from the Singapore Tourism Board shows a 36% rise in tourists from China in 2016 compared to the previous year. A 2017 Hotels.</description></item><item><title>Singapore welcomes the arrival of Japanese fashion retail concepts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</guid><description>Source: WMH Group. Kafuku.
World Mode Holdings Group (WMH Group) aims to improve the Singapore fashion retail sector by establishing its first international branch, iDA Singapore (iDA’SG).
WMH Group is a Japanese fashion retail consultancy firm known for strengthening its clients&amp;rsquo; brands. As Japan&amp;rsquo;s top recruiter for beauty and fashion sales professionals, their Singapore branch will offer expert guidance and support to enhance retail staff skills.
“As Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader in retail job placements, we&amp;rsquo;ve placed 100,000 retail staff with approximately 1,000 clients, primarily in fashion and luxury.</description></item><item><title>The RYDE Carpool Challenge will begin in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s carpooling app, RYDE, has teamed up with Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage for the RYDE Carpool Challenge. The grand prize? A Mitsubishi Attrage.
The eight-month campaign, which began on April 1, 2016, aims to have RYDE users complete a collective carpool distance of 1,000,000km, thus reducing carbon emissions by 200,000kg. By encouraging carpooling, RYDE hopes to promote a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.
Each month, RYDE will select two winners: the rider and driver with the highest number of successful carpools.</description></item><item><title>Register for a Jane's Walk (if possible)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/register-for-a-jane-s-walk-if-possible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:32:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/register-for-a-jane-s-walk-if-possible/</guid><description>](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjjjftL3eBnpoP9-lZPIx2FBUIjixQblEemCMYjK1fsqWMFAnV2mbG6iaAU305MtXqwpzxONmNTYc8Z02crj7dnUv-D5-CAAuQb0naLfJdJRIYhUsM2hARYEEShQ8L3TaCSNH0-kREbc6cU/s1600/20180505_150031.jpg)
This image showcases an overseas Chinese support organization, 武裕平民互助会, with Lee Huat Motoring located just beyond the tree.
As expected, spots for Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walks are quickly filling up. Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk is a yearly event featuring free walks led by volunteers. These walks pay tribute to Jane Jacobs (May 4, 1916 - April 25, 2006), an urbanist, writer, and activist who tirelessly advocated for community involvement in urban design.
This coming May marks the 7th anniversary of Jane’s Walk Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Enhance car safety with 360-degree hands-free device viewing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</guid><description>Sprint-Cass, the sole distributor of Taiwanese brand Digidock in Singapore, is introducing a new line of Digidock mobile device holders for vehicles at IT Show 2015, happening from March 19th to 22nd at the Suntec Convention Centre. These holders are designed for cars, motorcycles, and bicycles.
Every Digidock holder features a 360-degree swivel joint, allowing users to securely position their smartphones or tablets at any desired angle. Engineered for simple attachment and removal, the holders come with interchangeable cradles and universal mounts.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout.</description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces digital remittance services for Mobile Prepaid customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 21:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile Prepaid users can now send money internationally to over 40 countries within a day using the updated StarHub Prepaid app. This new feature is possible through a partnership with Singapore fintech company and licensed major payment institution, Pay2Home.
Digital remittances through the app eliminate the need for physical queues or appointments. The StarHub Prepaid app allows users to conveniently manage everything from identity verification and checking updated currency rates to transferring funds and managing prepaid accounts.</description></item><item><title>Keppel Land enhances marketing strategy with virtual show suites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</guid><description>Keppel Land is the first developer in Singapore to utilize Oculus Rift technology to create 360-degree immersive virtual reality (VR) show suites for its Highline Residences property. These two digitally rendered suites complement the three existing physical show suites at the Highline Residences showroom in Singapore.
The new VR platform, a collaboration between Keppel Land and visualisation firm VMW Group, features virtual tours of these new unit layouts. It also allows for a virtual exploration of key landmarks in the trendy Tiong Bahru neighborhood where Highline Residences is located.</description></item><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Dell EMC was recognized as one of the top companies to work for in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</guid><description>Dell EMC Singapore has been recognized as the 8th best company to work for in Singapore in 2016. This ranking comes from a comprehensive study conducted by the Great Place to Work Institute Singapore, which evaluates workplace culture.
The study utilizes 58 metrics from employee surveys and company audits to measure the factors that contribute to a positive and successful work environment. Only organizations where a majority of employees consider it a great place to work are eligible for inclusion.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>The Palawan @ Sentosa provides eight lifestyle entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 02:42:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Shangri-La Group has introduced its first lifestyle and entertainment hub, spanning 183,000 square feet on Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Sentosa Island. This complex boasts eight unique experiences, including dining options.
Chan Kong Leong, Regional CEO for the Shangri-La Group in Southeast Asia &amp;amp; Australasia, Hong Kong, Japan and Middle East, Europe, Indian Ocean &amp;amp; The Americas, emphasized the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing enjoyable experiences and Asian hospitality. He stated that this venture aims to create excitement and bring more enjoyment to guests beyond their traditional hotel settings, allowing them to create their own memorable moments through diverse leisure and dining experiences.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks Singapore is launching a special, limited edition alice + olivia design collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-singapore-is-launching-a-special-limited-edition-alice-olivia-design-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 13:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-singapore-is-launching-a-special-limited-edition-alice-olivia-design-collection/</guid><description>Starting January 31, 2015, Starbucks Singapore is offering a limited-edition collection of merchandise designed by Stacey Bendet, the CEO and Creative Director of alice + olivia.
The collection incorporates the brand&amp;rsquo;s signature black-and-white color scheme and the famous ‘Stace Face’ logo, bringing a playful and whimsical touch to Starbucks merchandise. This special collection, which includes a ‘Stace Face’ mug, a reusable designer tote bag, and an alice + olivia Starbucks Rewards Card, is available at the Starbucks ION Orchard location.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are adapting to unprecedented circumstances</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-adapting-to-unprecedented-circumstances/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 11:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-adapting-to-unprecedented-circumstances/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic forced businesses to adapt in order to survive lockdowns. In Singapore, several companies found innovative ways to reinvent themselves:
Audio House
Audio House, a retailer known for selling electronics and appliances, typically relies on its physical showroom and in-person customer interactions. When Singapore&amp;rsquo;s lockdown restrictions forced the closure of their showroom, Audio House had to find new ways to operate.
To retain their sales team and equip them with new skills, Audio House implemented an &amp;ldquo;Online Concierge&amp;rdquo; service.</description></item><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing.</description></item><item><title>Singapore intensifies its response to COVID-19</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-intensifies-its-response-to-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-intensifies-its-response-to-covid-19/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for National Development and Second Minister for Finance, Lawrence Wong, who also co-leads the task force for COVID-19, recently announced new measures to combat the country&amp;rsquo;s recent surge in cases, which jumped from 212 on March 14 to 385 by March 20.
Wong stated that the government&amp;rsquo;s goal is to reduce social interactions and limit activities that could potentially spread the virus. He hopes these measures will result in fewer people in public spaces.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has identified Tokyo, Singapore, and Dubai as some of the top choices in its Cities Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</guid><description>Singapore at night.
The travel website TripAdvisor recently published its second annual Cities Survey, which collected data from over 54,000 user reviews. The survey evaluated cities worldwide based on traveler feedback.
Tokyo received the highest ranking for providing the best overall travel experience. It also earned top scores for its helpful residents, taxi services, public transportation, and clean streets. Tokyo ranked among the top ten cities in 13 out of 16 survey categories.</description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa.</description></item><item><title>The DBS Marina Regatta is filled with exciting activities spread out over two weekends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest water sports festival, the DBS Marina Regatta, returns for its fifth year with an expanded format spanning two weekends, May 28-29 and June 4-5. The event, which drew over 24,000 attendees last year, will feature regional dragon boat races set against the Marina Bay skyline, the return of Singapore’s only pop-up urban beach, and the debut of Southeast Asia’s tallest inflatable water slide.
This year&amp;rsquo;s regatta will premiere several new features, including themed dragon boat races and competitive kayak races.</description></item><item><title>The 5th annual PCCW Global Charity Run will be held in Singapore this June</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</guid><description>Source: PCCW Global Charity Run web page. A picture from the same event in 2017.
The 5th yearly PCCW Global Charity Run will happen this June, and both PCCW employees and the general public can participate.
This run is organized by PCCW Global, a telecommunications company operating in Asia, Africa, Latin America, and the Middle East.
All funds raised from this year&amp;rsquo;s run will be donated to Make-A-Wish Singapore, an organization that grants wishes for children facing life-threatening illnesses.</description></item><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero.</description></item><item><title>Singapore residents are being targeted by a phone-based phishing campaign, according to DBS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</guid><description>DBS Bank has issued a warning to residents of Singapore about a phishing scam making use of automated phone calls. Given their customer base of over 4 million in Singapore alone, it is highly likely that scammers will connect with a DBS account holder.
The scam, as reported on the DBS website, begins with an automated voice message in either English or Mandarin. The recipient is told they have an urgent message from DBS Bank and instructed to press either &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport consolidates early check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Travelers departing from Singapore have increased access to early check-in services for various airlines at Changi Airport. Since the beginning of the year, shared early check-in counters have been established in Terminals 2 and 3. Terminal 1 features a dedicated early check-in lounge for added convenience.
Operational from 6 am to midnight, the counters and lounge offer a centralized service point for passengers flying with 23 participating airlines.</description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence.</description></item><item><title>Seminar on Intellectual Property and Legal Issues by the RHT Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</guid><description>RHT Academy and RHTLaw Taylor Wessing are holding a half-day seminar titled &amp;ldquo;Commercial Contracts: Latest Case Law Developments, Negotiation Strategies and Intellectual Property&amp;rdquo; on March 4, 2015, at the Suntec Convention &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre in Singapore.
Designed for legal professionals, business development executives, company secretaries, and compliance officers, this seminar aims to:
Offer a practical, business-focused overview of recent key case law developments related to commercial contracts in Singapore and the UK.</description></item><item><title>Supporting mothers returning to work and mom entrepreneurs in advancing their careers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 10:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</guid><description>For more details, scan the QR code.
Among the nearly 40,000 members of Mums@Work, common challenges faced when rejoining the workforce include age, keeping up with technology and necessary skills, a lack of confidence, anxieties about new work environments, and generational differences.
This is despite over 80% of members having more than eight years of professional experience, primarily in white-collar roles within banking and finance, media and entertainment, and human resources.</description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI Mate 10 Pro was first launched in Singapore, making it the first country in the world to introduce the device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</guid><description>Huawei recently launched its Mate 10 Series smartphones, including the Mate 10, Mate 10 Pro, and PORSCHE DESIGN Mate 10, in Singapore. The launch makes Singapore the first country globally to have the Mate 10 Pro available for purchase.
A key feature of these phones is the Kirin 970 AI chipset, which significantly boosts system response speed and ensures smoother performance. According to Cheng Jiangfei, Country Head of Huawei Singapore, Consumer Business Group, the company is committed to providing Singaporean customers with the latest and greatest technology.</description></item><item><title>Song Seung Heon is in Singapore to promote Saimdang</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon spent time with fans and Singtel TV subscribers during a Singapore trip sponsored by Singtel and Oh!K.
Two hundred Singtel TV subscribers in Singapore enjoyed an exclusive meeting with Korean actor Song Seung Heon, hosted by Singtel and Oh!K.
Song&amp;rsquo;s visit was to promote his K-drama Saimdang (师任堂). Before a large public event at The Cathay, Singtel TV subscribers could take pictures with Song and chat with him.</description></item><item><title>Dermatologists have created a one-of-a-kind hand sanitizer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dermatologists-have-created-a-one-of-a-kind-hand-sanitizer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 03:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dermatologists-have-created-a-one-of-a-kind-hand-sanitizer/</guid><description>● Developed by dermatologists with a deep understanding of skin care and patient requirements.
● Eliminates 99.99% of common household germs and viruses, including SARS-COV-2, upon application.
● Remains effective for 24 hours, even after handwashing, minimizing the need for frequent reapplication.
DS Skin Clinic and its global network of clinics have introduced the DS Skin Clinic All-Day Hand Sanitizer. This innovative product is engineered to outperform existing hand sanitizers available in the market.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor has released a list of the top 10 workplaces in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</guid><description>The job and recruiting website Glassdoor has revealed the winners of its annual Employees’ Choice Awards, which included a category for Singapore for the first time.
These awards recognize the Best Places to Work in 2020 across nine countries, including Singapore. The rankings are determined by the input of employees who anonymously share their experiences through company reviews on Glassdoor. This feedback encompasses their job, work environment, and employer over the past year.</description></item><item><title>Collective Works and CapitaLand are teaming up to launch a new coworking space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</guid><description>Artist&amp;rsquo;s impression of the new coworking space at Capital Tower, Singapore.
A new high-end coworking space will be launched on the 12th floor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Capital Tower. This joint venture between two companies will occupy 22,000 square feet and support 250 businesses. The space is adaptable and caters to a variety of businesses, from new startups to large corporations. Technological features include secure server hosting, video conferencing, internet phone services, and fiber optic broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a new prepaid SIM card that also functions as a travel card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced the hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card, a first in Asia, which combines a prepaid SIM card with a stored value travel card usable for Singapore&amp;rsquo;s public transportation.
Source: Singtel. The hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card is the first in Asia to combine travel and phone services.
Priced at S$18, this SIM card provides 100 GB of 4G data, unlimited access to social media and messaging apps, and 1 GB of roaming data for select countries in the region.</description></item><item><title>Caffè Vergnano 1882 has chosen the top three baristas in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Caffè Vergnano 1882. From left: third place winner Rudel Rivera, first place winner Joseph Bringcula, and second placer Stephen Wong.
Caffè Vergnano 1882 held its first-ever Barista Challenge at South Beach. Out of 16 participants, three distinguished themselves as top contenders.
Source: Caffè Vergnano 1882. The winning latte art from Bringcula.
The competition assessed fundamental barista techniques, including the ability to brew espresso properly and steam milk to enhance its flavor.</description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year.</description></item><item><title>Men's Chorus debuts virtual choir performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-chorus-debuts-virtual-choir-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:33:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-chorus-debuts-virtual-choir-performance/</guid><description>Sing! Men’s Chorus (SMC), an all-male choir in Singapore, has launched its first virtual choir project, &amp;ldquo;Why We Sing,&amp;rdquo; marking the return of arts performances in the country. The music video, available on SMC&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel, was created over two months and conveys a message of hope: that the arts community can adapt to a new normal where the arts, especially music, are recognized for their essential role in community development.</description></item><item><title>Happn shows that the east is the ideal location for social gatherings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happn-shows-that-the-east-is-the-ideal-location-for-social-gatherings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happn-shows-that-the-east-is-the-ideal-location-for-social-gatherings/</guid><description>Source: Happn. The top 10 Happn hotspots.
For those seeking romantic connections in Singapore, heading east might be the key. Happn, a dating app that connects individuals who have crossed paths, has identified the top ten locations in Singapore where users are most likely to find potential matches. With a presence in over 40 major cities globally, including Hong Kong, Happn boasts more than 22.5 million users.
The app utilizes real-time geolocation technology to show users individuals they&amp;rsquo;ve been near, within a 250-meter radius.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides an explanation of mobile performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</guid><description>Singtel contributed to the Infocomm Development Authority&amp;rsquo;s (IDA) MyConnection SG study, highlighting connectivity, speed, and coverage as crucial aspects of user experience.
Singtel emphasized that, based on study feedback, users prioritize network coverage, call stability, customer service, and reliable data connections over pure speed. Consistent speed across a broad coverage area is key for a positive user experience. This feedback helps Singtel pinpoint areas for service enhancement.
Connectivity, as defined by Singtel, is the server connection response time, measured in milliseconds.</description></item><item><title>Canon Singapore will be hosting the Photo Marathon again in August 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-singapore-will-be-hosting-the-photo-marathon-again-in-august-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-singapore-will-be-hosting-the-photo-marathon-again-in-august-2015/</guid><description>Source: Canon eDM.
Canon Singapore has announced the details for their 13th annual Photo Marathon, taking place on August 22nd from 7 am to 8 pm at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre, Level 1, Hall C.
The competition revolves around three photography themes that are revealed on the day of the event. Participants are tasked with capturing these themes in their photographs and submitting them by the given deadline.</description></item><item><title>A new tech and innovation business club has been introduced in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</guid><description>SPECTRUM, a curated tech and innovation business club, has been established in Singapore. The organization, co-founded by Cheryl Lee and Shirley Crystal Chua, aims to create a globally connected ecosystem for businesses seeking to expand into Asia by providing expert advice, necessary resources, and strategic networks.
SPECTRUM has partnered with Golden Equator and Mistletoe to form a collaborative network of seven strategic groups: innovators, learning institutions, executors, backers, enablers, government agencies, and ecosystem builders and partners.</description></item><item><title>Rasel offers artisanal catering services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</guid><description>Rasel Catering Singapore, a top-tier halal catering service, has enhanced its offerings to become a leader in the industry.
Alan Tan, Co-Founder and Managing Director of Rasel Catering Singapore, highlighted the company’s focus on meeting the evolving needs of a global clientele. He stated, “Rasel caters to international events and weddings, recognizing the sophisticated tastes of today’s customers and their demand for high-quality halal food. Our service goes beyond just the food itself—we leverage our expertise to elevate the entire experience for our customers.</description></item><item><title>Zap Delivery in Singapore guarantees fast and reliable couriered deliveries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</guid><description>Source: Zap Delivery.
Zap Delivery, an on-demand courier service, promises quick, safe, and dependable deliveries of packages and documents within Singapore in two hours or less using their new mobile app. This app utilizes advanced authentication and real-time tracking to provide peace of mind for those awaiting deliveries.
“We’ve experienced our fair share of delivery issues, so we created a user-friendly app that fosters trust,&amp;quot; explained Michael Tan, Zap Delivery Co-founder and CEO.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces Cauca Terroir Roast &amp; Ground Coffee in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 07:21:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</guid><description>According to Cafédirect, their Cauca Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee pairs well with sweet and fruity flavors. Ideal pairings in Colombia include pan de queso (cheese bread) and alfajores (caramel cookie sandwiches). &amp;ldquo;Terroir&amp;rdquo; encapsulates the unique environmental and geographic factors of a region that influence a beverage&amp;rsquo;s taste.
Cafédirect recently introduced their Cauca Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee to Singapore. Colombians describe this high-altitude coffee as &amp;ldquo;black as night, hot as hell and sweet as love&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Escaping from the Asian Civilisations Museum: A Great Adventure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escaping-from-the-asian-civilisations-museum-a-great-adventure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escaping-from-the-asian-civilisations-museum-a-great-adventure/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Asian Civilisations Museum is hosting &amp;ldquo;Night at the Museum: The Great Escape from Asian Civilisations Museum,&amp;rdquo; featuring two evenings of movies and interactive games.
This event, possibly the first of its kind globally, is designed as a museum-wide escape room. Participants will solve puzzles, uncover museum secrets, and decipher the meanings behind ancient artifacts to &amp;ldquo;escape.&amp;rdquo; Winners have a chance to win movie tickets to Night at the Museum: Secret of the Tomb.</description></item><item><title>The new snowskin flavors at Goodwood Park are ideal combinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 13:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with new snowskin mooncake flavors that perfectly pair two complementary ingredients. This year, the hotel is even introducing its first-ever chocolate mooncake.
One of the new additions is the Yuzu Lychee Snowskin Mooncake, featuring the bright citrus flavor of yuzu combined with sweet lychee pieces. Another highlight is the limited-edition Dark Chocolate Crunchy Hazelnut Snowskin Mooncake. This decadent treat consists of a crunchy hazelnut chocolate center surrounded by rich dark chocolate mousse, all encased in a snowskin made with crushed vanilla beans and caramel.</description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance reveals the top influential brands in Asia for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Brand Alliance. The brand gallery at Marina Bay Sands is open until August 21st.
Brand Alliance, using its brand leadership platform Influential Brands, has announced the 2015 Asia’s Top Influential Brands. This announcement leverages consumer insights gathered from 2013 to 2015.
This year, the Asia’s Top Influential Brands awards expanded to include over 100 categories. These categories span various sectors, ranging from food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) to financial services and property development.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine.</description></item><item><title>Experience cutting-edge VR gaming at Bugis Junction and Bugis+, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</guid><description>This Halloween, shoppers at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bugis Junction and Bugis+ malls can participate in an immersive virtual reality (VR) gaming experience. This event marks the first time malls in Singapore have hosted a VR experience of this magnitude.
The &amp;ldquo;Time Zombies&amp;rdquo; competition invites shoppers to assume the roles of time-traveling detectives. Their mission: to stop the nefarious Dr. Virago, a mad scientist attempting to unleash a zombie apocalypse. This competition utilizes cutting-edge Arctic Fox wireless technology, allowing players to move freely within the virtual world using a wireless headset, eliminating the need for cumbersome cables or backpack computers.</description></item><item><title>Reserve a spot for a handicraft workshop at the Etsy Craft Party 2016 - Summer Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-spot-for-a-handicraft-workshop-at-the-etsy-craft-party-2016-summer-edition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-spot-for-a-handicraft-workshop-at-the-etsy-craft-party-2016-summer-edition/</guid><description>Individuals with a creative spirit or those seeking engaging team-building exercises might be interested in three craft workshops featured at the &amp;ldquo;Etsy Craft Party 2016 - The Summer Edition&amp;rdquo; on June 18, 2016. The Singapore edition of this annual Etsy event is organized by Crafty Singapore, with support from Etsy.
Source: Crafty Singapore. Finished embroidery on tiny &amp;lsquo;mini&amp;rsquo; embroidery hoops.
Needlework on a Miniature Hoop
Presented by Wish I Were Stitching (two sessions, eight participants per session)</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling.</description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Singapore polytechnics on initiatives for small and medium enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Singtel is partnering with Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) and Singapore Polytechnic (SP) to equip small and medium enterprises (SMEs) with digital skills, as part of the 99% SME initiative. This partnership aims to help SMEs in the retail and food and beverage industries thrive in the digital world.
The collaboration with NYP&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Institute of Retail Studies (SIRS) will connect SMEs with re-skilled professionals who can guide them in e-commerce, data analysis, and digital marketing strategies.</description></item><item><title>Promotions for Dell at CEE 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</guid><description>Dell is promoting several products at the Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) 2017. These products, equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors, are designed for an excellent visual experience and enhanced gameplay.
Here are some of the featured products:
Inspiron 13 5000 2-in-1
Original Price: Starting from S$1,699 Show Price: Starting from S$1,299 Features:
Latest 7th Gen Intel Core processor 13.3&amp;quot; FHD (1,920 x 1,080) IPS Truelife LED-backlit touchscreen with wide viewing angles and an infrared (IR) camera Four versatile modes: tent, stand, laptop, and tablet XPS 13 2-in-1</description></item><item><title>The Someline Apple Tree app will produce apples for charity as long as you refrain from using your phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</guid><description>Source: Google Play.
Libern Lin, a student entrepreneur attending Republic Polytechnic in Singapore, has expanded his app, Someline Apple Tree, with financial support from the Singapore Computer Society (SCS).
The app incentivizes real-life interactions by rewarding users with digital apples for reducing phone usage. Lin, the app&amp;rsquo;s creator, explained that they wanted to use the app&amp;rsquo;s concept for a good cause. So, they used the S$30,000 grant from SCS to add a charitable component to the app in line with IDA&amp;rsquo;s Code for Charity*.</description></item><item><title>Learn the fundamentals of blockchain technology at Smartcademy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-the-fundamentals-of-blockchain-technology-at-smartcademy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-the-fundamentals-of-blockchain-technology-at-smartcademy/</guid><description>Source: Unsplash, via Smartcademy. This image illustrates Blockchain technology, with cryptocurrency being one example of its use.
[
Smartcademy, a Singaporean organization focused on technology education and career development, has launched a beginner-friendly introductory course on Blockchain. This one-month program covers basic concepts and terminology, explores how Blockchain is used in finance, and explains the workings of Bitcoin. The course aims to equip individuals with the knowledge to navigate the risks and rewards of digital financial systems.</description></item><item><title>Just under half of Singaporeans believe that Budget 2016 is fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</guid><description>A recent poll of 986 Singaporeans by YouGov, a global polling and research company, revealed widespread pessimism regarding the future despite a generally neutral sentiment about the 2016 Budget.
While over a quarter of respondents viewed the current economy positively, a significant majority (over 60%) believed it was either declining or stagnant. This negative outlook was particularly pronounced among older respondents (aged 45-54).
Although half of those surveyed considered the 2016 Budget fair, a significant majority (60%) did not believe it would significantly impact their lives over the next year.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Experience the street food of Taiwan at Tea Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</guid><description>Tea Valley: Bringing Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Street Food Flavors to Singapore [Image of Tea Valley Downtown East outlet]
Tea Valley (茶食坊), a casual Taiwanese dining chain in Singapore, has ambitious plans for expansion. At a tasting event held at their first location in Downtown East, Director Lawrence Lim shared his vision for growing the brand beyond just new locations, but also in the variety of services they offer.
[Image of Lawrence Lim, Director of Tea Valley]</description></item><item><title>The IDA in Singapore has compiled a report on home computer usage in Singapore for the year 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</guid><description>A 2014 survey by the Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) of Singapore revealed a surge in smartphone, computer, and internet use among Singaporean seniors. The study, titled Annual Survey on Infocomm Usage in Households, found that 74% of Singaporean residents used a computer in the three months leading up to the survey. Senior citizens aged 50 and above showed the most significant increase in computer usage.
Between 2012 and 2014, computer use among seniors aged 50 to 59 grew by 14 percentage points, while those over 60 showed an 11 percentage-point increase.</description></item><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound.</description></item><item><title>BCM Institute offers Business Continuity Management courses specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</guid><description>The BCM Institute, in collaboration with the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC), is offering a free two-day Business Continuity Management (BCM) course designed to enhance the resilience of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) against disruptions.
Taking place on October 28-29, 2014, at the Singapore Productivity Centre, this course is presented with support from the Singapore Business Federation and SPRING Singapore. Participants will engage with the following topics:
APEC-endorsed step-by-step BCM implementation guidelines Complimentary, ready-to-use BCM templates Guidance on utilizing BCM templates Insights into BCM trends affecting SMEs, shared by an APEC ASEAN BCM Working Group Committee member SMEs meeting the criteria of an annual sales turnover not exceeding S$100 million or employing 200 or fewer staff are eligible to participate.</description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides.</description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces the Superstar 80s Pioneers Pack in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-the-superstar-80s-pioneers-pack-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 06:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-the-superstar-80s-pioneers-pack-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Drawing on Superstar 80s by Gonz.
Adidas recently released the Superstar 80s Pioneers Pack, a collaboration with skateboarder Mark Gonzales, known as Gonz, and designer NIGO.
Gonz, a renowned innovator and rule-breaker, changed skateboarding for a whole generation. His drive to create inspired the Superstar 80s by Gonz. The shoe&amp;rsquo;s all-white leather upper serves as a blank slate, inviting wearers to personalize their sneakers using the included markers.</description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels &amp; Resorts presents an art installation in Singapore to commemorate its 200 properties worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</guid><description>Video of Hall with the bottles shaping the number &amp;lsquo;200&amp;rsquo;.
To mark the opening of their 200th hotel, InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts commissioned contemporary British artist Alexander Hall, known professionally as Haut de Gamme, to create a commemorative installation.
The artwork features 200 champagne bottles, each hand-painted by Hall in his signature drip technique. Inspired by the unique character of each InterContinental property, the individually designed bottles collectively form the number “200”.</description></item><item><title>Herbalife has found that women in Singapore who work are less active than men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</guid><description>Herbalife, a worldwide nutrition company, has found some differences in the health outlooks and routines of working men and women in Singapore. Their Nutrition at Work survey showed that, compared to men, women in Singapore tend to stay at their desks longer, eat lunch at their desks more, and have more difficulty being active during a typical workday.
“Our aim as a global nutrition company is to provide members and customers with high-quality nutrition products that support healthy eating and active lifestyles,” said Dr.</description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3.</description></item><item><title>Bakerzin introduces seven new mooncake collections for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:24:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</guid><description>Bakerzin has introduced its Creme de la Creme mooncake assortment, featuring handcrafted mooncakes made with low-sugar white lotus paste. The collection includes seven distinct lines, available in both traditional baked and snow skin varieties.
[Image of Bakerzin&amp;rsquo;s 2017 mooncake collection]
Source: Bakerzin Facebook page. Bakerzin&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017.
The Bold Collection showcases baked mooncakes with unique flavors such as American ginseng, ginger, tom yam, and sakura ebi.
The Signature Collection features the return of their popular premium egg yolk blend baked mooncake.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) reveals initiatives to promote innovation in the industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) outlined its plans to support the digitalization recommendations put forth by the Committee on the Future Economy (CFE) to help prepare the financial sector for the future.
MAS will facilitate infrastructure projects aimed at driving innovation, enhancing market efficiency, improving customer service, and strengthening Singapore’s regional connectivity. Key projects include:
Electronic Marketplace for Trade Finance Assets
An electronic trade finance platform will allow participating banks to distribute trade finance assets globally, free up capital for new trade finance loans, and increase the availability of trade finance within the region.</description></item><item><title>There is something for everyone on Jane's Walks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 02:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global initiative of free walking tours led by community members, is making a comeback from May 6th to 8th. The walks are inspired by Jane Jacobs (1916-2006), an urban planner and advocate who championed community-driven city development. Grounded in the belief that everyone possesses knowledge about their surroundings, these walks celebrate Jacobs&amp;rsquo; ideas worldwide. Participants share stories about their neighborhoods, discover hidden gems, and connect with their neighbors.</description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering.</description></item><item><title>ValueChampion warns that driving in Singapore is more perilous than you might realize</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</guid><description>While Singapore boasts one of the world&amp;rsquo;s lowest road fatality rates per person, ValueChampion suggests that driving in Singapore might be riskier than in other developed nations. Anastassia Evlanova, a Senior Research Analyst at ValueChampion Singapore, highlights in a recent blog post (which builds on research from 2017) that Singapore recorded 12.13 deaths per 100,000 vehicles in 2019, surpassing rates in Japan and Australia.
She explains, &amp;ldquo;Looking at road safety solely based on deaths per capita creates a deceptive view of driving safety in Singapore.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir will be operating SIA flights SQ466 and SQ467 to Colombo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 18:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</guid><description>Starting April 8, 2017, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines (SIA), will begin flights to Colombo, the commercial hub of Sri Lanka and a diverse city home to a large population.
SilkAir will take over flights SQ466/SQ467, offering three weekly flights to Colombo. SIA will maintain its daily nighttime service, operating flights SQ468 and SQ469. Adding SilkAir to the Singapore-Colombo route allows the SIA Group to optimize resource allocation and better match capacity with demand.</description></item><item><title>DBS/POSB introduces Chinese New Year service offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</guid><description>To celebrate the Year of the Rabbit, DBS/POSB is expanding its blended digital and physical (&amp;ldquo;phygital&amp;rdquo;) Chinese New Year (CNY) gifting and rewards programs.
This CNY, customers can take advantage of the following:
Conveniently order DBS QR Gift cards (QR AngBaos) through the bank&amp;rsquo;s chatbot, digibot, and have them delivered before CNY.
A chance to win a Tesla Model 3 and other rewards, including cash rebates, by switching to QR Gift and other DBS/POSB digital transactions.</description></item><item><title>Joo Chiat Kim Choo introduces halal rice dumplings at 7-Eleven Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 23:54:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Joo Chiat Kim Choo/7-Eleven.
- Halal rice dumplings from Kim Choo Kid are now sold at all 7-Eleven stores in Singapore.
- Customers can choose from two flavors: Nonya Chicken and Salted Chicken. For convenience, the leaves have been removed.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 7-Eleven stores now offer a halal version of the famous Joo Chiat Kim Choo rice dumplings. Part of the Neo Group, this top rice dumpling maker in Singapore is known for its Nonya dumplings, made with a recipe handed down through generations.</description></item><item><title>GuocoLand will be responsible for overseeing the management of both Sofitel Singapore City Centre and Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Tanjong Pagar
Centre.
GuocoLand will oversee the operation of two new AccorHotels establishments: the Sofitel Singapore City Centre at Tanjong Pagar Centre in Singapore and the Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara in Damansara City, Kuala Lumpur. These additions contribute a total of 534 rooms to AccorHotel’s luxury brand.
Raymond Choong, President and CEO of GuocoLand Group, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership with AccorHotels, highlighting the shared vision for creating modern, convenient spaces within bustling business districts.</description></item><item><title>The BNI business referral system has the potential to yield significant returns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bni-business-referral-system-has-the-potential-to-yield-significant-returns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 03:59:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bni-business-referral-system-has-the-potential-to-yield-significant-returns/</guid><description>Sukri Kadola, the founder and CEO of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bloem Singapore, a boutique and floral design house, has taken on a new role as President of the BNI Apex chapter. This chapter is part of the BNI business network, known for its referral system. Kadola highlights the success of this system, reporting that BNI Apex has closed approximately S$6 million in business since 2012 through referrals.
Source: Bloem. Kadola. Kadola emphasizes the value of BNI&amp;rsquo;s network, stating that it provides a platform for members to connect, support each other, and generate business opportunities through referrals.</description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival includes a number of groundbreaking inclusive initiatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</guid><description>Source: True Colours Festival website. Some of the featured performers.
This coming March, twenty artists and groups will come together in Singapore for the first and largest event in the Asia Pacific region to showcase performers with disabilities. From March 22-25, 2018, Singapore will host True Colours Festival – the Asia Pacific Celebration of Artistes with Disabilities. True Colours is presented by UNESCO and The Nippon Foundation (TNF), two global organizations that advocate for the rights of people with disabilities (PWDs).</description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life.</description></item><item><title>Employers in Singapore are struggling with stress and mental health concerns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:23:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</guid><description>A large majority (72%) of Singaporean employers view stress and mental health as factors that negatively impact productivity, according to the APAC Benefits Strategy Study 2017 conducted by global professional services firm Aon.
The International Labour Organization has labeled stress a &amp;ldquo;global epidemic&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;silent killer,&amp;rdquo; particularly within many Asian countries experiencing rapid economic growth and adopting Western lifestyles, including Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and mainland China.
Early physical symptoms of stress can manifest as chronic back pain, fatigue, and headaches.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the history of Bukit Panjang, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</guid><description>Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global movement of free walking tours inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, continues to thrive in Singapore, with tours often fully booked within hours of being announced. This enthusiastic response highlights the movement&amp;rsquo;s ability to connect people with their communities and explore urban landscapes.
This year, on May 5th, a sold-out walk titled &amp;ldquo;At the Crossroads: Bukit Panjang&amp;rdquo; offered participants a unique opportunity to delve into the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s rich history.</description></item><item><title>New OCBC Securities app and Android OCBC app now offer fingerprint security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 08:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</guid><description>Source: OCBC. The iOCBC TradeMobile app allows users to perform in-depth technical analyses of stocks using standard indicators.
OCBC Securities has introduced a new mobile app called iOCBC TradeMobile for iPhone users. Existing OCBC Securities customers can now conveniently monitor their stock portfolios and access real-time market data for their stocks using Apple&amp;rsquo;s Touch ID technology. This fingerprint authentication feature, known as OneTouch, offers both OCBC Bank and OCBC Securities customers a secure and convenient way to access their banking and brokerage accounts.</description></item><item><title>Bloem marks 4th anniversary with introduction of new services and partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Sukri Kadola and Ivy Tan cut a cake during Bloem&amp;rsquo;s anniversary celebration.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s custom floral design company, Bloem, recently commemorated its fourth anniversary. The company marked this occasion by announcing new partnerships and the launch of its Concierge service.
&amp;ldquo;While many believe the economy has presented difficulties for businesses, success is subjective,&amp;rdquo; says Sukri Kadola, Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO. Eighty percent of Bloem&amp;rsquo;s revenue is generated through corporate projects.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new LVL UP plan tailored for young people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The LVL UP plan is targeted at youths.
Singtel introduced a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;LVL UP&amp;rdquo; for young adults, coinciding with the start of The PC Show 2017. The name, inspired by the gaming term &amp;ldquo;level up,&amp;rdquo; signifies advancement to higher levels of difficulty in games. This plan provides free upgrades for Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Youth Combo plans and additional data.
This plan, available to students and full-time National Servicemen aged 26 and under, offers close to S$600 in savings over two years.</description></item><item><title>IIJ Global Solutions Singapore is now providing cloud monitoring services using CA Nimsoft Monitor for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 15:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>IIJ Global Solutions Singapore, a subsidiary of a major Japanese internet and network solutions company, Internet Initiative Japan (IIJ) Group, has incorporated CA Nimsoft Monitor from CA Technologies into its cloud solutions for small and medium-sized businesses.
This addition allows IIJ Global Solutions Singapore to offer its clients extensive 24/7 monitoring and reporting services. Using this unified monitoring platform from CA Nimsoft Monitor, users can optimize resources, improve planning and investments, and reduce time spent on troubleshooting.</description></item><item><title>The Air by crazybaby (NANO) is now offered in 10 different colors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-air-by-crazybaby-nano-is-now-offered-in-10-different-colors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-air-by-crazybaby-nano-is-now-offered-in-10-different-colors/</guid><description>Source: Hwee Seng Electronics. Air by crazybaby (NANO) is available in 10 colours.
Hwee Seng Electronics, a Singaporean distributor specializing in audio electronics, has become the official distributor for Crazybaby, a provider of high-quality audio devices. Their product, Air by crazybaby (NANO), also called Nano, is now available in Singapore through Hwee Seng Electronics.
Nano earbuds combine Crazybaby&amp;rsquo;s modern and stylish look with a water-resistant build. These earbuds utilize carbon nanotube technology, which produces sound differently than traditional methods and generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t need moving parts.</description></item><item><title>A more nutritious choice of French-Vietnamese cuisine in Tanjong Pagar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz. The L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz sautéed beef and spring rolls vermicelli salad (bún bò xào chả giò).
L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz, a Vietnamese eatery located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Tanjong Pagar financial area, serves both lunch and dinner.
The name &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz&amp;rdquo; is a clever fusion of &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;euphorie&amp;rdquo; (French for &amp;ldquo;euphoria&amp;rdquo;), &amp;ldquo;phở&amp;rdquo; (the famous Vietnamese noodle soup), and &amp;ldquo;riz&amp;rdquo; (French for &amp;ldquo;rice&amp;rdquo;), hinting at the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s French-Vietnamese roots.
With origins in Saigon, Vietnam, the restaurant later established itself in Paris and played a key role in the three-decade success of Parisian Vietnamese restaurant Dong Huong.</description></item></channel></rss>