<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OC-12 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc-12/</link><description>Recent content in OC-12 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc-12/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Buildings Offer High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Do you want to upgrade your internet speed from slow copper or fixed wireless connections to the rapid speeds offered by fiber optic cables? Are you trying to avoid the high cost of installing new fiber optic cables? If so, you should consider moving into a fiber building.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; a fiber building isn&amp;rsquo;t constructed from exotic materials like carbon fiber. The term &amp;ldquo;fiber&amp;rdquo; refers to the type of telecommunication services already available within the building.</description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Maps At Your Fingertips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</guid><description>You might want to upgrade to a faster internet service, but the cost of installing fiber optic cables might seem scary. How can you figure out if upgrading from copper to fiber is affordable?
The easiest way is to compare quotes from different providers in your area. A telecom broker, like Telarus, Inc., can gather these quotes for you quickly and easily. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a report with pricing from all major providers in your area.</description></item><item><title>Same Budget, More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Is Slow Network Speed Affecting Your Business?
Are you experiencing frustrating network issues like slow downloads, choppy calls, interrupted streaming, and sluggish website loading?
Do You Need More Bandwidth?
There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance your internet connection needs more bandwidth. While your internal network might be fast enough, your external connection (WAN) might not be able to handle your current needs.
Signs You Need More Bandwidth
If your internet service hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years but your business relies more on multimedia and online tools, you probably need more bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Pushes EoC to 400 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services are constantly achieving higher bandwidth capacities, making businesses reconsider the need for fiber optic installations. MegaPath, for example, now offers EoC speeds up to 400 Mbps.
Many companies use EoC as a cost-effective alternative to T1 lines, obtaining double the bandwidth at the same price. Options like 2x2 Mbps and 3x3 Mbps are particularly favored. Others transition to mid-band Ethernet, offering 10 to 20 Mbps, which exceeds bonded T1 capabilities and suits mid-sized businesses.</description></item></channel></rss>