<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Property on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/property/</link><description>Recent content in Property on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/property/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Keppel Land enhances marketing strategy with virtual show suites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</guid><description>Keppel Land is the first developer in Singapore to utilize Oculus Rift technology to create 360-degree immersive virtual reality (VR) show suites for its Highline Residences property. These two digitally rendered suites complement the three existing physical show suites at the Highline Residences showroom in Singapore.
The new VR platform, a collaboration between Keppel Land and visualisation firm VMW Group, features virtual tours of these new unit layouts. It also allows for a virtual exploration of key landmarks in the trendy Tiong Bahru neighborhood where Highline Residences is located.</description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3.</description></item><item><title>The Ibn Battuta Gate Office building is experiencing increased demand as Expo 2020 Dubai approaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</guid><description>Source: Seven Tides website.
As Expo 2020 Dubai approaches, Ibn Battuta Gate Offices, a property developed by Seven Tides, is leveraging its prime location in New Dubai. Situated near the Mövenpick Hotel, Ibn Battuta Mall, and a metro station, the office building is attracting significant attention.
The appeal of this location is further enhanced by the planned expansion of Ibn Battuta Mall. The AED160 million project will add 28,000 square meters, including a 350-room hotel, 150 shops, 50 restaurants, and a cinema with 21 screens.</description></item><item><title>JLL reports that tech startups are a significant driver of real estate demand in the APAC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</guid><description>New types of office users are emerging in the form of startups, with more tech companies exploring unconventional spaces such as coworking facilities and industrial properties, according to JLL, a real estate and investment management firm.
The technology sector in the Asia Pacific region has experienced significant growth, driven by mobile technology, e-commerce, and the rise of fintech. This growth has fueled demand for both traditional office spaces and business parks.</description></item><item><title>CoAssets expands its crowdfunding portfolio by including small and medium-sized enterprise projects and sets its sights on Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</guid><description>CoAssets, a crowdfunding company based in Singapore, is expanding its platform to assist Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs). This expansion allows SMEs to connect with potential investors, addressing the funding challenges many businesses face. CoAssets&amp;rsquo; platform already facilitates real estate crowdfunding and will now provide a space for SMEs to seek funding.
Getty Goh, CEO of CoAssets, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s successful history in real estate crowdfunding and the increasing demand for business loans in Singapore as key drivers for this expansion.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place.</description></item></channel></rss>