<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Marketing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-marketing/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adobe aims to achieve the highest level of performance in order to increase repeat visits and online sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</guid><description>Source: Adobe.
Recent Adobe research indicates that marketers in the Asia Pacific region who use best practices are significantly outperforming their competitors.
The Adobe Digital Index Best of the Best Benchmark for Asia Pacific analyzed websites across six regions: Australia and New Zealand, Southeast Asia, India, South Korea, Hong Kong, and China, comparing the average website performance with the top 20% based on six key performance indicators: mobile and tablet traffic, stick rate, visits per visitor, time spent, and conversion rate.</description></item><item><title>Fake clicks and pageviews can artificially boost digital marketing metrics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve invested in online ads on a platform known for its excellent results, and you&amp;rsquo;re seeing those clicks increase week after week. People are clearly interested enough to visit your store locations, but actual sales remain stagnant. So, what&amp;rsquo;s the deal?
This could be a sign of ad fraud, and not necessarily originating from the platform itself.
The Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB), based in the US, emphasizes the need for greater awareness surrounding non-intentional traffic.</description></item></channel></rss>