<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Poken on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/poken/</link><description>Recent content in Poken on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/poken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Poken Enhances Face to Face Social Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</guid><description>Is jotting down contact information on scraps of paper your go-to method? Do you find yourself hoping your hand-written notes survive the journey home? Perhaps you rely on traditional business cards?
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, those methods are outdated.
Just like Facebook, MySpace, LinkedIn, and Twitter revolutionized online networking, Poken is ushering in a new era for in-person connections with a device aptly named &amp;ldquo;Poken.&amp;rdquo; Think of it as a modern-day amulet, powered by cutting-edge technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Have A Poken Card?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-a-poken-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-a-poken-card/</guid><description>The internet has revolutionized the business world. Job seekers now heavily rely on online platforms, while businesses prioritize their online presence through websites and social media channels like Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn. Embracing these technological advancements is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age. So, are you up-to-date with the latest trend, Poken cards?
While electronic business cards are gaining traction faster in Europe than in the US, their adoption is inevitable. Poken, a Swiss company, is leading this transformation with its innovative technology and comprehensive support system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-a-poken-card/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-a-poken-card/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Poken Around For Business Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</guid><description>Modern business networking goes beyond the traditional handshake and business card by utilizing technology to manage contacts. Poken offers a fresh approach to this concept.
Poken, encompassing both a device and a method, modernizes the conventional business card. While physical cards were sufficient in the past, today&amp;rsquo;s digitized world demands more. Although card readers exist, Poken offers a direct electronic solution.
The pokenPulse, resembling a USB flash drive, doubles as a 2 GB storage device and a wireless transponder...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gifts For Boomerangs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gifts-for-boomerangs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gifts-for-boomerangs/</guid><description>In the wake of economic downturns and a challenging job market, many young adults have returned to live with their parents. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for gift ideas for these &amp;ldquo;boomerang kids,&amp;rdquo; consider items that can help them regain their footing.
Rather than giving cash, which can disappear quickly, think about practical gifts with lasting value. Millennials are known for their tech-savviness and desire for social connection. A cell phone is a great tool for both, and you can easily add a line to your existing family plan for minimal cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gifts-for-boomerangs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gifts-for-boomerangs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Cards Go Green With Poken</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-cards-go-green-with-poken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 01:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-cards-go-green-with-poken/</guid><description>Wonderful, wonderful Copenhagen. It seems like it&amp;rsquo;s going to sink underwater as the ocean gets warmer and terrible storms rage on. All this is happening while people still doubt climate change and don&amp;rsquo;t believe we can reduce CO2 levels to 350 ppm.
The climate change summit starting this week in Copenhagen, Denmark, has gotten me thinking. I&amp;rsquo;m hopeful despite the doubters and cynics who believe that getting CO2 levels down to 350 ppm is as impossible as ending our addiction to sugary drinks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-cards-go-green-with-poken/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-cards-go-green-with-poken/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrating Social Media And Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</guid><description>We navigate two distinct realms: the digital sphere of communication, online activities, and social media, and the physical world of tangible experiences, relationships, and work. Although these realms overlap, their connection has been tenuous until recently.
Poken has emerged as a solution to bridge this gap between the digital and physical. As expected, it comprises both physical and virtual elements.
The tangible aspect is a device called Poken, resembling a digital avatar or a flash drive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five Years Of The Explainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 21:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</guid><description>T1 Rex’s Business Telecom Explainer turned five this month, with more than 800 posts published since its 2004 launch. Our initial goal was to clarify complex telecommunications services and provide businesses with competitive options. Over time, we&amp;rsquo;ve broadened our scope to encompass a wide range of products, services, and topics relevant to our audience. As we approach our second decade, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the &amp;ldquo;aughts&amp;rdquo; and explore potential future trends.
This explainer blog, as the name suggests, was launched alongside T1Rex...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>