<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>25 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/25/</link><description>Recent content in 25 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:09:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/25/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spotify reveals its list of 25 talented individuals under the age of 25 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</guid><description>Spotify has unveiled the top 25 most influential artists under 25 who are currently dominating the music scene in Singapore.
Shawn Mendes, an 18-year-old singer-songwriter from Canada, takes the top spot. He boasts 25 million monthly listeners on Spotify and over 500 million streams for his hit song, &amp;ldquo;Stitches.&amp;rdquo; Following closely behind Mendes are Ariana Grande, Martin Garrix, Justin Bieber, and Alessia Cara. Popular artists Gentle Bones and Fifth Harmony are also included in the list.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>The Top 25 Multinational Workplaces consist of widely recognized brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</guid><description>Great Place to Work, a global firm that assists organizations in developing positive workplace cultures, has announced its yearly ranking of the top 25 multinational workplaces worldwide. This list is derived from an extensive study of workplace environments and recognizes companies with exceptional work cultures.
To be eligible for this list, companies must meet specific requirements: placement on at least five national &amp;ldquo;Best Workplaces&amp;rdquo; lists, a minimum of 5,000 employees, and a workforce comprised of at least 40% employees based outside of the company&amp;rsquo;s home country.</description></item></channel></rss>