<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Religious Discrimination on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/religious-discrimination/</link><description>Recent content in Religious Discrimination on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/religious-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the special status of minority religious groups, stating "You are all individuals!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law, University College London
The Court of Justice recently issued five significant decisions regarding Directive 2000/78&amp;rsquo;s provisions on religious discrimination, a topic it hadn&amp;rsquo;t addressed in many years. This surge in rulings signifies the Court&amp;rsquo;s renewed focus on this area.
The latest case originated from Austria&amp;rsquo;s Supreme Court and concerned a law granting paid holidays on Good Friday to members of three minor Christian denominations, excluding others.</description></item><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church).</description></item><item><title>Is it legal to terminate employees for religious reasons related to divorce?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-legal-to-terminate-employees-for-religious-reasons-related-to-divorce/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-legal-to-terminate-employees-for-religious-reasons-related-to-divorce/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law at University College London
Despite coming into effect in 2003, the Framework Directive on Discrimination in Employment&amp;rsquo;s impact on religion-related matters remained unclear for 14 years until a series of landmark decisions by the Court of Justice. These rulings have clarified the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance on religious expression in the workplace.
It is now established that a consistently applied workplace neutrality policy prohibiting religious symbols is considered indirectly, not directly, discriminatory (the Achbita case).</description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013.</description></item><item><title>Expanding the margin of appreciation: France's prohibition on public face-veiling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 05:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</guid><description>The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) has ruled on a highly anticipated case, SAS v France, concerning France&amp;rsquo;s 2010 law prohibiting face coverings in public. The case was brought by a French woman, represented by British lawyers, who argued that the law violated several articles of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), including the right to freedom of religion, expression, and association, as well as protection from discrimination.</description></item><item><title>Faith in action: the CJEU's decisions on headscarves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer, UCL Faculty of Laws and author of Religion and the Public Order of the Euorpean Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’ordre juridique de l’Union européenne (Bruylant 2013).
Nearly two decades after the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment was implemented, the Court of Justice issued its first significant decisions regarding workplace discrimination based on religion. These rulings placed the Court in a politically sensitive area, presenting considerable risk for an international judicial body like the CJEU.</description></item><item><title>Explaining the European Court of Justice's decisions on headscarf bans in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued rulings on whether employers can prohibit employees from wearing headscarves at work. These rulings have garnered significant attention, although some of it stems from misunderstandings. This post aims to provide a clear explanation of the rulings.
Background
The EU has established laws against discrimination based on sex, nationality, race, disability, age, sexual orientation, and religion. While the ECJ has frequently addressed cases related to the first three grounds, the recent judgments in G4S v Achbita and Bougnaoui mark the first instance where the court has been asked to interpret workplace discrimination based on religious grounds.</description></item><item><title>Should there be increased use of majority voting in EU social policy decisions? Evaluating the Commission's suggestion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, PhD Candidate, University of Antwerp
In April 2019, the European Commission initiated a discussion on streamlining the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making in social policy. The goal was to enhance efficiency by utilizing &amp;ldquo;passerelle&amp;rdquo; clauses, which permit a shift from unanimous voting to qualified majority voting (QMV) and from special to ordinary legislative procedures. This change, while requiring unanimous approval from Member States, aims to bypass the complexities of Treaty revisions.</description></item><item><title>What approach should the CJEU take in addressing religious discrimination in the workplace?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer at the Faculty of Laws at UCL and the author of Religion and the Public Order of the European Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’Ordre juridique de l’Union Europeenne (Bruylant 2013).
Recent weeks have seen two opinions from Advocates General of the Court of Justice of the European Union concerning religious expression in the workplace. This follows a period where religious issues were largely absent from Luxembourg case law.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides clarification on when employers can prohibit headscarves in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Ronan McCrea, University College London
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s initial significant decisions concerning workplace policies limiting religious symbols were issued four years ago in the G4S and Micropole cases. These rulings addressed the compatibility of these policies with the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment (Directive 2000/78).
In these decisions, the Court&amp;rsquo;s Grand Chamber determined that requiring employees to maintain visible religious neutrality constituted indirect rather than direct discrimination, provided this policy was uniformly applied to all religions or beliefs.</description></item></channel></rss>