<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Panel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/panel/</link><description>Recent content in Panel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:06:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/panel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Polishing the Plexiglass Cover</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-polishing-the-plexiglass-cover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-polishing-the-plexiglass-cover/</guid><description>The refurbishment of my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) is nearly complete. I polished the plexiglass cover today, using the method described previously, and am pleased with the results. The attached photo shows the outcome, with the protective tape still in place on the back portion of the panel.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Cleaning the Panels and Installing a 3D Printed Guiding Washer for the Cabinet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:25:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</guid><description>I dedicated some time today to refining the appearance of the Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on. The first step involved adjusting the platter&amp;rsquo;s height and alignment within the aluminum panel. Achieving a centered and flush platter is crucial for the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s visual appeal. The platter was positioned too low upon arrival, even grazing the panel due to misalignment.
Therefore, I made adjustments to the main bearing and the chassis&amp;rsquo;s three suspension points to achieve the correct setup.</description></item><item><title>The BenQ interactive flat panel simplifies education and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</guid><description>BenQ, a well-known name in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, introduces the RP750K, a new interactive flat panel (IFP). This innovative IFP offers a comprehensive solution by combining a 4K Ultra HD whiteboard with annotation and collaboration tools.
The RP750K excels in dynamic classroom or corporate training settings. Its Germ-Resistant Screen, infused with a safe and robust nano-ionic silver coating, effectively eliminates most surface germs, reducing cross-infection risks. This antimicrobial protection persists even with regular cleaning and extended use.</description></item></channel></rss>