<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Money Laundering on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/money-laundering/</link><description>Recent content in Money Laundering on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/money-laundering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in Safe Interenvios addresses issues of money laundering, customer due diligence, and data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-safe-interenvios-addresses-issues-of-money-laundering-customer-due-diligence-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-safe-interenvios-addresses-issues-of-money-laundering-customer-due-diligence-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The views expressed are purely those of the author and may not in any circumstances be regarded as stating an official position of the European Commission
Background
This analysis examines a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment concerning a case, Safe Interenvios, which originated from a preliminary reference submitted by a Provincial Court in Barcelona. The Barcelona court requested the CJEU to clarify the interpretation of the third Anti-Money Laundering Directive (AML Directive) in relation to a dispute involving a financial institution, Safe Interenvios, and several banks.</description></item></channel></rss>