<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>M-Payment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/m-payment/</link><description>Recent content in M-Payment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/m-payment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maybank customers in Malaysia can now access Western Union remittances digitally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</guid><description>Maybank and Western Union have partnered to introduce the first digital remittance service in Malaysia. This service, accessible through the Maybank2u (M2u) mobile app and website, allows Maybank customers to send money to over 500,000 Western Union agent locations in more than 200 countries and territories. Available 24/7, the service facilitates transfers up to RM10,000 daily, with recipients typically receiving funds faster than traditional methods.
Datuk Lim Hong Tat, Maybank&amp;rsquo;s Group Head of Community Financial Services, highlighted that this launch strengthens Maybank&amp;rsquo;s online presence and promotes digital transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Tencent collaborate to simplify gifting and payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Wong.
Starbucks Coffee Company and Tencent Holdings, a Chinese provider of online services, are collaborating. In early 2017, they plan to launch a new social gifting feature within WeChat, a popular mobile communications service in China. Additionally, Starbucks customers at nearly 2,500 stores across mainland China can now use WeChat Pay for their purchases.
This partnership makes Starbucks the first retailer in China to provide an integrated, locally relevant social gifting and digital payment experience within WeChat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean banks are getting their customers ready for Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 09:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s website in Singapore now features a dedicated page for Apple Pay, which includes a list of participating banks and retailers. Among the banks listed, DBS and POSB have almost identical images on their websites, and UOB also has a dedicated page. Standard Chartered currently does not have any information available. DBS clarifies that Apple Pay offers a fast and secure payment method compatible with a user&amp;rsquo;s preferred DBS card. Contactless payments are also supported for iPhone and Apple Watch users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>