<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sport/</link><description>Recent content in Sport on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens promotion is now available at the Grand Hyatt Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Hong Kong. Poster for the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens 2023.
To celebrate the return of the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens from March 31st to April 2nd, 2023, Grand Hyatt Hong Kong, an official supplier and package provider, is offering special deals for a complete Sevens experience.
Exclusive packages combining accommodation and Sevens tickets are available starting from HK$3,900. Options include one- or three-night stays, paired with a choice of Friday, weekend, or three-day event tickets to suit every fan.</description></item><item><title>Exciting pre-game activities at Shangri-La hotels before the Hong Kong Sevens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 03:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</guid><description>Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Shangri-La Group is offering rugby enthusiasts special hotel and experience packages for the Hong Kong Sevens. Fans can choose to stay at the Island Shangri-La, Kowloon Shangri-La, or Kerry Hotel, with each offering exclusive day passes to the event. Packages include pre-game accommodations and breakfast. Additional breakfast and day passes are available for a bundled price.
Source: Shangri-La Group Hong Kong. The Hong Kong Rugby Sevens.
Island Shangri-La, Hong Kong</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Tough Mudder event in Asia will take place in Bali, Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 06:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Indonesia. Chairi Ibrahim, Project Manager at Seroja Partners (left), Gandrasta Bangko, Business Director at Mesa Race (middle), and Ridzki Syahputera, Partner at Seroja Partners (right) at the launch of Tough Mudder Indonesia.
The world-renowned endurance series, Tough Mudder, has officially launched in Indonesia. Known as &amp;ldquo;Probably the Toughest Event on the Planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder has attracted 2.5 million participants across 200 events in six countries. Its Asian debut will take place on October 1st and 2nd, 2016, in Bali, Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>Guests are invited by Jumeirah Dhevanafushi to discover the house reef</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-invited-by-jumeirah-dhevanafushi-to-discover-the-house-reef/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-invited-by-jumeirah-dhevanafushi-to-discover-the-house-reef/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. Underwater view of a reef.
Jumeirah Dhevanafushi, a secluded resort at the southernmost point of the Maldives, has launched a new &amp;ldquo;Underwater Snorkeling Adventure&amp;rdquo; experience, allowing guests to explore the resort&amp;rsquo;s own reef.
This package provides a guided opportunity to discover some of the planet&amp;rsquo;s most impressive coral reefs. Led by Jumeirah Dhevanafushi&amp;rsquo;s resident marine biologist, guests can explore the reefs surrounding the heart-shaped Meradhoo island, situated on the Gaafu Alifu Atoll.</description></item><item><title>Singtel releases National Day video and shows support for SEA Games 2017 athletes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-releases-national-day-video-and-shows-support-for-sea-games-2017-athletes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 04:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-releases-national-day-video-and-shows-support-for-sea-games-2017-athletes/</guid><description>Singtel has launched its first significant National Day video celebrating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s independence. Released after August 9th, the company aims to motivate Singaporeans to maintain the spirit of &amp;ldquo;Majulah,&amp;rdquo; meaning &amp;ldquo;onward&amp;rdquo; in Malay, even after the National Day festivities.
Lian Pek, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP for Group Strategic Communications and Brand, explained that the slightly delayed release is intentional. Singtel wants to extend the enthusiasm from the National Day celebrations and inspire ongoing national pride and a desire to contribute to Singapore.</description></item><item><title>JVC introduces new sports in-ear headphones that are waterproof and washable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 03:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</guid><description>Source: JVC.
JVC introduces four new sports headphone options designed to stay securely in place during physical activity, with some models offering waterproof and washable features.
The lineup includes two models in both the JVC Gumy Sport and Extreme Fitness series. The Gumy Sport headphones, HA-EN10 and HA-ENR15, utilize a Nozzle Fit earpiece constructed from soft silicone. This unique shape ensures a secure and comfortable fit, preventing the headphones from falling out during workouts.</description></item><item><title>Kramnik will face Alcántara in a rematch on Chessarena.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</guid><description>Source: World Chess. Vladimir Kramnik (pictured left) is set to have a rematch against José Alcántara (Jospem, pictured right) in August 2024.
World Chess, an organization dedicated to increasing the popularity of chess worldwide, is organizing &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims 2.&amp;rdquo; This event is a rematch following a controversial first &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims&amp;rdquo; match between chess players Vladimir Kramnik and José Alcántara. The event will be broadcasted live with commentary from well-known chess personalities and include interactive elements for viewers.</description></item></channel></rss>