<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Encryption on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/encryption/</link><description>Recent content in Encryption on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/encryption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Choose An MPLS VPN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Businesses need secure communication between their different locations. While private networks offer the highest level of security, they are expensive to build and maintain. Using the public internet is cheaper but raises security concerns.
A fully private network, offering top-notch security and performance, requires significant investment. Building a central hub and connecting each location with dedicated lines like T1 or Ethernet can become very costly, especially with increasing bandwidth demands and staffing for maintenance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure Any Public WiFi Hotspot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: you&amp;rsquo;re away from your secure office network or home WiFi, relying on public WiFi that makes you uneasy. While convenient, unsecured WiFi hotspots present a security risk. How can you be sure someone isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring your activity with malicious software when you send private emails or sensitive data?
](http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-1726600-11129503)
It&amp;rsquo;s a valid concern. Cybercrime is rampant, and tools for intercepting data on public WiFi are readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantages of SSL VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</guid><description>Cybersecurity is a significant concern for all internet users. With frequent news of hacking, data breaches, identity theft, and malicious bots, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that people are anxious about the security of their sensitive information, especially with the move towards cloud-based storage. This has led to a surge in interest in virtual private networks (VPNs).
Why would one choose a virtual private network over a traditional one?
The answer lies in our need for widespread connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Routes to Virtual Private Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</guid><description>VPNs have become the go-to solution for connecting multiple business locations due to their cost-effectiveness and ease of maintenance. Managed service providers allow businesses to enjoy secure multipoint communication without the burden of extensive staffing or high monthly line lease fees.
Virtual private networking is now cloud-based, but the choice of cloud type remains. You can opt for a VPN solution using the public internet or choose a completely private network for enhanced performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Human Rights highlights the significance of encryption in the case of Podchasov v. Russia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip &amp;amp; Frederik Zuiderveen Borgesius*
*Both authors work at the iHub and the Institute for Computing and Information Sciences, Radboud University, The Netherlands - mattis.vantschip[at]ru.nl &amp;amp; frederikzb[at]cs.ru.nl
Photo credit: Gzen92, on wikimedia commons A February 2024 ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Podchasov v. Russia highlighted the crucial role of encryption in safeguarding privacy rights. This judgment comes at a time when encryption is at the heart of many global legal discussions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Private Network Definition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</guid><description>While everyone understands the concept of a network, the meaning of a virtual private network (VPN) can be a bit unclear. Essentially, a VPN is a real network that utilizes technology to make its privacy seem virtual. For instance, the internet is inherently public, but methods exist to enhance the privacy of online communications, making them &amp;ldquo;virtually&amp;rdquo; private.
A genuinely private network necessitates stringent access control. Only authorized individuals and devices should be granted access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>