<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Immigration Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/immigration-law/</link><description>Recent content in Immigration Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/immigration-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's Returns Directive beneficial or detrimental to the well-being of undocumented migrants?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at the EU Returns Directive: Five Years On Many EU citizens are worried about the impact of immigration, especially when it comes to unauthorized migrants without legal status. Others, however, prioritize humane treatment for these individuals. To manage this challenge, the EU created the &amp;ldquo;Returns Directive&amp;rdquo; in 2008, outlining procedures for returning unauthorized migrants, including detention rules and procedural rights.
Upon its introduction, the Directive faced criticism from NGOs and academics who felt it was overly harsh...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that students from third countries have the right to enter school.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the new academic year begins, students across the EU are met with a mix of anticipation and anxiety. Juggling academics, finances, personal life, and social activities is a universal experience for students, and those from outside the EU face the added pressure of meeting immigration requirements.
These requirements are standardized by the EU&amp;rsquo;s 2004 Students’ Directive. However, the degree of uniformity across member states remains unclear. Do individual countries retain the right to impose additional entry prerequisites?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU employment law and irregular migrants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Determining the employment rights of undocumented migrants is complex. On one hand, granting them full access to employment law protections could incentivize unauthorized migration. On the other hand, applying standard employment laws to all workers, regardless of immigration status, could prevent the exploitation of undocumented migrants and deter employers from hiring them to save money.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this issue in the Tumer case, which focused on the application of the EU Directive on insolvent employers to undocumented migrants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Utilization of Prisons for Detaining Migrants in Europe and the EU Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, a researcher at the Global Detention Project and the Global Migration Centre, and a PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies in Geneva, examines a legal question: can immigration detainees be held in prisons alongside ordinary prisoners?
On July 17, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this question in its decisions regarding the combined cases of Bero and Bouzalmate and the separate case of Pham...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Feedback on the Commission's latest guidance for Family Reunions for Third-Country Nationals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Family life is essential for everyone living in the EU, regardless of their citizenship. For non-EU citizens (third-country nationals), family reunification is governed by the EU Directive on family reunion, adopted in 2003. Recently, the European Commission released new guidance on this Directive, offering potential for its better implementation and understanding. Although the guidance addresses several issues effectively, there are points that require further improvement or clarification...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's strategy to eliminate human trafficking is all talk and no action.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</guid><description>Dr Matilde Ventrella, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Wolverhampton (UK)
1. Introduction
The European Commission recently released two important documents on October 17th: a progress report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat human trafficking and a report on how a specific directive (Directive 2004/81) is being used to protect victims. This analysis will delve into the key findings of both reports and offer concluding observations.
2. Progress Report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s Fight Against Human Trafficking..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's stance on the minimum age requirement for spouses in a family reunification application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:56:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently ruled in the Noorzia case concerning the age requirement for family reunification. The case revolved around whether a national law, requiring both the sponsor and their spouse to be 21 years old when applying for family reunification, aligns with European Union (EU) law. The CJEU determined that the national law was indeed consistent with EU Directive 2003/86/EC...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Doctor U? The CJEU balances the right to a name with passport security.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many individuals possess a flexible understanding of their personal identity, this concept clashes with the perspective of law enforcement agencies. These organizations aim to establish a fixed identity for each person they gather information on to ensure absolute certainty.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently addressed these contrasting viewpoints in a case involving an individual identified as &amp;lsquo;U.&amp;rsquo; This case was among several during that week where plaintiffs were identified solely by letters, a practice the author suggests moving away from in favor of using pseudonyms for clarity and ease of reference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to effectively help in the prohibition of forced labor by the ILO?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although often used lightly, the term &amp;ldquo;wage slaves&amp;rdquo; reflects a harsh reality for millions trapped in forced labor globally, a modern form of slavery. This exploitation represents a significant aspect of human trafficking, alongside sexual exploitation.
Key international entities like the United Nations and the Council of Europe have been at the forefront of combating human trafficking. However, the International Labour Organisation (ILO) brings long-standing expertise, particularly concerning labor exploitation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 4: Immigration in the EU Referendum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
How does the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the European Union (EU) affect immigration and asylum? This piece examines this complex topic, focusing on migration to the UK by both non-EU and EU citizens.
Non-EU migration
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between non-EU and EU migration in the Brexit referendum discussion for two key reasons. Firstly, while EU migration is inherently linked to the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership, non-EU migration is not...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British lawyers have made a significant impact on EU (migration) law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk, Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen, Netherlands.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) acknowledged the significant contributions of its British members to European integration and legal precedent. This recognition prompts reflection on the impact of British legal professionals on EU law, particularly in the areas of migration and free movement.
British judges and advocates-general, with their common law background, played a key role in shaping the CJEU into a more transparent and adaptable institution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU truly dedicated to addressing violence against women, or is it just empty words?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre of the University of Oxford - @CateBriddick
Background
The European Union (EU) has a core legal commitment to fight discrimination, including sex-based discrimination, and to promote gender equality. However, it has faced ongoing and valid criticism for not upholding these commitments, especially regarding its treatment of female migrants and refugees. Therefore, the Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2016 announcement that the EU would sign and ratify the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women (the Istanbul Convention) was welcomed by activists and academics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Commission's "Guidance" on aiding and supporting migrants with facilitation and humanitarian assistance.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-guidance-on-aiding-and-supporting-migrants-with-facilitation-and-humanitarian-assistance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-guidance-on-aiding-and-supporting-migrants-with-facilitation-and-humanitarian-assistance/</guid><description>Angelo Marletta*
* FNRS Post-doctoral Research Associate at the Centre de Droit Européen of the Université Libre de Bruxelles. I am grateful to Prof. Chloé Brière for her valuable remarks and suggestions.
1. Context
In September 2020, within the framework of the New Pact on Migration and Asylum, the European Commission released its ‘Guidance on the implementation of EU rules on definition and prevention of the facilitation of unauthorised entry, transit and residence’...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-guidance-on-aiding-and-supporting-migrants-with-facilitation-and-humanitarian-assistance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-guidance-on-aiding-and-supporting-migrants-with-facilitation-and-humanitarian-assistance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What are the reasons behind the ineffectiveness of the Blue Card Directive for highly-skilled workers, and what solutions can be implemented to improve its functionality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 2009, the EU introduced the ‘Blue Card’ Directive to attract highly qualified individuals from non-EU countries. As part of a broader strategy for legal immigration, this Directive is crucial. However, a recent Commission assessment suggests that the Directive has not effectively reached its goals. This raises the question of necessary revisions for improvement.
Implementing the Directive
While all EU Member States obligated to implement the Directive have done so, the actual impact has been underwhelming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Potential Reconstruction of Hadrian's Wall: How Scottish Independence Could Impact British Border Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 11:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Hadrian&amp;rsquo;s Wall is often thought to have been built by the Romans to defend civilized Britannia from invading Picts, who are considered the ancestors of modern-day Scots. This idea is echoed in Game of Thrones, where the Wall serves to keep out wild and dangerous beings from the North.
Theresa May, the British Home Secretary, recently invoked this imagery when she suggested that if Scotland were to become independent, border control would need to be reinstated between Scotland and the remaining United Kingdom...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Irony in Immigration Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:11:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</guid><description>Daniel Thym, Professor of Public, European and International Law at the University of Konstanz
Immigration was a key issue during the Brexit debate, with &amp;ldquo;taking back control&amp;rdquo; becoming a central theme. In her January speech in Lancaster, Theresa May emphasized that controlling immigration was a primary goal of the Brexit negotiations. She stressed the public&amp;rsquo;s message that Brexit must equate to managing the influx of people from Europe to Britain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Migration in Europe and the Challenges of Insufficient Criminalization</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/</guid><description>By Amanda Spalding, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
Photo credit: Gzen92, via wikicommons media
Introduction
With a large influx of Ukrainian refugees into Europe, alongside policies like offshore asylum processing in Denmark and the UK, and increasing irregular entries reported by Frontex, the landscape of migration laws and policies is constantly shifting. Amidst these changes, it&amp;rsquo;s vital to examine the legal context, especially the human rights framework meant to safeguard individuals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mr. Avramopolous travels to Brussels: reflections on the European Parliament hearing for the new Migration Commissioner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Throughout his extensive three-hour hearing at the European Parliament, Dimitris Avramopolous, the nominee for Commissioner for migration and home affairs, consistently emphasized his commitment to liberal values. He expressed strong support for upholding the Schengen system, adopting a liberal stance on asylum and legal migration, and protecting the freedom of movement for EU citizens. However, he fell short of providing specifics on the implementation of these principles and how the various facets of EU policy in this domain would harmonize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Inquiries for potential Commissioners of Home Affairs and Justice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 01:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Emilio de Capitani, and Henri Labayle present a series of questions for Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to pose to the candidates for Commissioners of Immigration and Home Affairs and Justice. These questions aim to understand the candidates&amp;rsquo; plans and secure commitments on crucial matters.
Immigration and Asylum
Given the Commission&amp;rsquo;s stance on framing migration policy with the non-binding Global Approach to Migration and Mobility Partnerships, would the candidate propose a legally binding basis for agreements with relevant nations, based on Articles 77, 78, and 79 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>