<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Networking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-networking/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Networking on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Exchange For Miami, Dallas and Los Angeles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet is emerging as a strong contender to replace the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), as evidenced by the increasing number of Ethernet Exchanges that facilitate traffic sharing among carriers. Telx, a prominent interconnection and colocation provider, recently expanded its Ethernet Exchange services to Miami, Dallas, and Los Angeles. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the significance of Ethernet Exchange and its impact on the future of international wide-area networking.
The PSTN&amp;rsquo;s global reach and interoperability have contributed to its longstanding success, enabling communication between any two phones worldwide.</description></item></channel></rss>