<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Services Act on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-services-act/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Services Act on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:39:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-services-act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A democratic option to the Digital Services Act's collaboration between governments and online platforms in addressing disinformation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</guid><description>By Paul De Hert* and Andrés Chomczyk Penedo**
* Professor at Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium) and associate professor at Tilburg University (The Netherlands)
** PhD Researcher at the Law, Science, Technology and Society Research Group, Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium). Marie Skłodowska-Curie fellow at the PROTECT ITN. The author has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No 813497..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The complexities of the new EU Media Freedom Act</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</guid><description>Samira Asmaa Allioui, research and tutorial fellow at the Center for International and European Studies at the University of Strasbourg
Photo credit: Bin im Garten, via Wikimedia Commons
Journalists face various pressures. Recent years have seen media freedom, particularly media pluralism, under threat.
On December 15, 2023, the European Council and Parliament reached an agreement on regulations to protect media freedom, pluralism, and editorial independence within the European Union. The EU Media Freedom Act (EMFA) aims for greater transparency in media ownership and safeguards against government surveillance and spyware targeting journalists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Insights from interim proceedings: Amazon v DSA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</guid><description>Laureline Lemoine, Senior Associate, AWO Agency
Photo credit: KarleHorn, via Wikimedia Commons
A recent legal challenge to the Digital Services Act (DSA) provides insight into how Amazon is approaching its obligations under the new law. The case, initiated by Amazon after being designated a Very Large Online Platform (VLOP), centers around two main arguments.
First, Amazon contests the DSA requirement for an opt-out for recommender systems based on user profiling (Article 38), claiming it would negatively impact its business and users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unresolved concerns regarding the regulations for trusted flaggers under the Digital Services Act regime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giorgia Lo Tauro, FratiniVergano European Lawyers
Photo credit: ** Lobo Studio Hamburg**, via Wikimedia Commons
1 Introduction
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services Act (DSA) formally establishes the roles and responsibilities of &amp;ldquo;trusted flaggers,&amp;rdquo; important entities in the online world that have operated with varying degrees of influence since the early 2000s. This new framework aligns with the DSA&amp;rsquo;s goals: creating consistent, effective, and balanced rules across the EU to improve the online marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>