<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Connection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-connection/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Connection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-connection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From LAN to MAN to WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</guid><description>The world is currently experiencing a revolution in network technology. While computer networks have historically relied on various communication protocols, some adapted from the telephone industry, there’s a growing trend towards adopting IP as a universal networking standard. This shift towards IP encompasses all network types, from local area networks (LANs) to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and wide area networks (WANs).
This standardization trend originated in LANs. Today, most LANs utilize Ethernet network interfaces due to economies of scale rather than inherent superiority...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eliminating the WAN Choke Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 02:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</guid><description>The speed difference between LANs (Local Area Networks) and WANs (Wide Area Networks) is often significant. This becomes apparent when accessing the internet or transferring files, as actions that are near-instantaneous within a local network can take much longer externally. This is known as the WAN choke point.
Visualize this by comparing a highway exit onto a crowded street during rush hour or trying to fill a pool using a garden hose connected to the main water supply...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>