<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shenzhen on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shenzhen/</link><description>Recent content in Shenzhen on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shenzhen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hainan Airlines introduces direct flight between Shenzhen and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Pictured at the Auckland welcoming ceremony are the Consulate General of China in Auckland, Acting Consul General Luo Binhui, Auckland Airport CEO Adrian Littlewood, Hainan Airlines President Sun Jianfeng, and Hainan Airlines&amp;rsquo; VIP customers.
On December 30, 2016, Hainan Airlines launched its inaugural non-stop flight between Shenzhen, China, and Auckland, New Zealand. The new route connects the two cities with an 11-hour flight.
Hainan Airlines will service the Shenzhen-Auckland route with wide-body Airbus A330s, known for their spacious cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen collaborate for a flash sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 01:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</guid><description>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen have teamed up to offer the Grand Spring Voyage flash sale, featuring accommodation packages ranging from two to five nights in both cities. This convenient travel opportunity is made possible by the newly extended MTR East Rail line, which directly connects the two hotels. The journey between the nearest stations, Exhibition Centre Station in Hong Kong and Lo Wu Station in Shenzhen, is a quick 40 minutes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the VIP treatment at Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</guid><description>Source: Hard Rock Hotels. Interior, Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen.
The Hard Rock Hotel brand has debuted its first establishment in China with the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen. This new property combines pop culture with high-end hospitality to create a luxurious experience for travelers seeking a unique experience.
Opening its doors in the summer of 2017, the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen is located within Mission Hills Centreville. Situated near a golf course, the hotel also provides convenient access to a variety of leisure, wellness, and entertainment options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>