<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scale on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scale/</link><description>Recent content in Scale on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Unusual Keypad PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</guid><description>This article highlights a unique Beogram 4000 keyboard PCB. Typically, the two bulbs illuminating the position scale are wired in series, using two 12V bulbs connected between the 24V power source and ground. This setup is illustrated in the first image and diagram. Notably, this series configuration results in the bulbs having opposite polarity.
This polarity difference is ideal for the author&amp;rsquo;s polarized LED replacement boards. The second image showcases these boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination with a Red/Green LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, the light bulb illuminating the peak program meter&amp;rsquo;s dB scale malfunctioned. This common issue stems from the age of the bulbs, as their leads tend to oxidize and break under pressure.
The initial state of the display, lacking illumination for the numbers on the dB scale, is shown below:
The bulb is inserted into a waveguide that distributes light across the scale, with a textured surface behind the numbers for diffusion.</description></item></channel></rss>