<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plantronics on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plantronics/</link><description>Recent content in Plantronics on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plantronics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience all-day flexibility with the Plantronics BackBeat 100 Series Wireless Headphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</guid><description>Plantronics, a company known for its audio and wearable technology, has introduced the BackBeat 100 Series. These headphones are the newest addition to their BackBeat stereo product line and offer a unique hybrid neckband design for wireless calls and music.
The BackBeat 100 and BackBeat 105 are designed for comfort throughout the day with an ultra-lightweight build. They provide full-range sound with enhanced bass, making them ideal for listening to music and watching videos on the move...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>