<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Relay on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/relay/</link><description>Recent content in Relay on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/relay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Hood Mounting Screw Springs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</guid><description>During my quest for the ideal Beogram 4000 turntable, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that none of the early models possess the hood mounting screw springs found on the later Beogram 4002 and 4004. These springs make removing and attaching the hood significantly easier. After consulting the service manuals, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that the Beogram 4000 was not designed with these springs. It seems B&amp;amp;O employed a continuous improvement approach, refining their designs over time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/4002/4004 Relays: Professionally Manufactured PCBs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</guid><description>I recently updated the design of the Beogram 4000/4002/4004 relay adapter boards to allow for professional manufacturing. I&amp;rsquo;ve begun taking and fulfilling orders with these new boards, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled with how they turned out.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the boards:
These boards are compatible with both the older Siemens relays and the newer National relays commonly found as RPM and signal path grounding relays in the 400x series. They are designed as direct replacements for the original relays.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and Reservoir Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the tonearm and drive carriage mechanisms on this Beogram 4002 (5513), attention turned to the electronics. The initial phase involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, RPM trimmers, and the relay to guarantee smooth operation for years to come.
The main PCB in its original state is shown here.
The same PCB is pictured here after component replacement.
This image provides a detailed view of the RPM control section.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Carriage Position Switches and Fixing a Bent Output Switch Contact Tab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000, a process known as &amp;ldquo;switch day&amp;rdquo; involves cleaning the contacts of the many open switches. While some recommend desoldering the switches for thorough cleaning, it&amp;rsquo;s generally sufficient to clean the contact areas directly. This minimizes the risk of damaging the delicate contact tabs.
Effective switch functionality hinges on clean contact points, not the overall appearance of the switch. The contact tabs should be straight and have adequate spring to ensure proper contact.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Zero Force Balancing and Tracking Force Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:45:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring is almost ready for its initial test run. It&amp;rsquo;s time to fine-tune the zero force balance and set the appropriate tracking force. I documented this process in a video on my YouTube channel, featuring a Beogram 4002. You can find the video and my entire Beogram 4000 playlist through the provided links.
Let me share some observations from this specific Beogram 4000 restoration. The first stage involves achieving zero force balance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs - New Capacitors, RPM Trimmers and RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the motor and reservoir capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step involved rebuilding the PCBs. This typically involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM trimmers, and the RPM relay. The main PCB, which is difficult to remove due to its hardwiring, was &amp;lsquo;flipped&amp;rsquo; for component replacement.
After replacing the components, the rebuilt board was ready for installation. A new relay was used, as the original Siemens relays often experience oxidation, hindering proper RPM switching.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board and Adding a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>During the Beogram 4002 restoration, I took the opportunity to rebuild the output board while cleaning the keypad contacts. A common issue with these units is low or absent volume in one or both channels, often caused by the output relay. To address this, I replaced it with a modern, durable Japanese relay designed to last for many years. The original output board is shown here:
The old Siemens relay was swapped out for a custom-designed SMD relay assembly, pictured below:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs and Restoring the 33 RPM Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</guid><description>Typically, my restoration process for Beogram 4002 turntables begins with the arm lowering and tracking systems. However, this particular Beogram 4002 (5513) required a different approach. The control system needed attention, so I opted to address the PCBs first.
Upon unpacking the turntable, I discovered that the platter motor would power on as soon as it was plugged in. This unusual behavior was caused by the seller connecting the motor to the standby LED header on the circuit board – a connection point rarely used on the 5513 boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of Main and Output Printed Circuit Boards, and a New Reservoir Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the PCBs after addressing the decayed transport lock bushings. The main PCB was first, as shown below:
In addition to replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay and trimmers were targeted due to their susceptibility to corrosion and impact on RPM stability. The following image highlights the RPM section in its initial condition:
Modern, encapsulated 25-turn trimmers replaced the old ones, and a new relay was installed (interested enthusiasts can obtain a replacement relay by email or through the contact form).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit.</description></item></channel></rss>