<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MOTOBLUR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/motoblur/</link><description>Recent content in MOTOBLUR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/motoblur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Plethora of Free Android Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</guid><description>This Christmas, give the gift of a cutting-edge Android phone without breaking the bank. Although these devices boast advanced technology and typically come with a high price tag (often $500-$600), it&amp;rsquo;s possible to get one for free.
Android smartphones are essentially pocket computers, running on 3G and 4G networks and offering similar functionality to desktops and laptops. They&amp;rsquo;re capable of web browsing, social networking, email, video streaming, and more. While $500-$600 might be reasonable for such a device, why pay when you can get one for free?</description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>Doing BACKFLIPs with MOTOBLUR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 10:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</guid><description>Would you do a backflip for your current cell phone? Probably not, but Motorola&amp;rsquo;s BACKFLIP might just change your mind.
This phone&amp;rsquo;s unique feature is its reverse hinge. Unlike most phones where the keyboard is hidden beneath the screen, the BACKFLIP&amp;rsquo;s keyboard is located on the exterior, flipping open to reveal a full-size touchscreen. This design eliminates the need for a smaller internal screen, offering a more spacious keyboard and a high-resolution touchscreen experience comparable to a small computer.</description></item></channel></rss>