<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>USA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/usa/</link><description>Recent content in USA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/usa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>Is EU data protection law violated by Facebook and the USA? The CJEU hearing in Schrems.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</guid><description>Simon McGarr, a solicitor at McGarr Solicitors, provides an overview of the Schrems v Data Protection Commissioner case heard by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The case revolves around Austrian law student Max Schrems&amp;rsquo; legal challenge concerning the transfer of his personal data from Facebook to the United States. Schrems argues that such transfers violate his data privacy rights due to the risk of mass surveillance under US law.</description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations.</description></item><item><title>Schrems II and the Transfer of Personal Data: You Were Only Meant to Blow the Bloody Doors Off!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued its highly anticipated decision regarding the legitimacy of standard contractual clauses (SCCs) for transferring personal data outside the European Union. This decision is part of a larger effort to challenge the “surveillance capitalism” model employed by many online businesses. While this case significantly impacts SCCs and Facebook&amp;rsquo;s operations, it also reveals the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s stance against mass surveillance, a recurring theme in European jurisprudence.</description></item><item><title>Live. Die. Repeat. Is the 'Privacy Shield' deal stuck in a never-ending cycle of repeating the same mistakes like in the movie 'Groundhog Day'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the USA is globally recognized, some of its customs remain perplexing. Take &amp;ldquo;Groundhog Day,&amp;rdquo; where the presence or absence of a groundhog&amp;rsquo;s shadow on February 2nd supposedly predicts six more weeks of winter. Beyond the USA, it&amp;rsquo;s more famous as a film where Bill Murray relives the same day, striving for perfection and Andie MacDowell&amp;rsquo;s affections. This concept has inspired others: Tom Cruise battling aliens and wooing Emily Blunt in Edge of Tomorrow, and Peter Capaldi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to breach a diamond wall and resurrect Jenna Coleman in Doctor Who&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hell Bent.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading.</description></item><item><title>New developments in EU case law regarding extradition to non-EU countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A recent European Court of Justice (ECJ) decision in the Pisciotti case concerning the extradition of citizens from one EU Member State to a non-EU country (in this instance, the USA) provides further legal precedent in this domain and carries potential implications for Brexit. This ruling expands on the September 2016 Petruhhin judgment, which dealt with extraditing citizens from one EU Member State to Russia.</description></item><item><title>In order to create more responsive rules, the EU-US transatlantic trade and partnership (TTIP) negotiations are crucial.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</guid><description>Dr. Elaine Fahey, Senior Lecturer, The City Law School, City University London
The script
The EU and US have concluded six rounds of discussions on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Agreement (TTIP). This agreement aims to reduce trade barriers and other obstacles, such as differing regulations and standards, across various industries. TTIP is promoted as potentially setting a global trade standard. Some argue it&amp;rsquo;s already irrelevant, but while this downplays its potential influence, skepticism is understandable.</description></item><item><title>Is the Commission's draft EU-US Privacy Shield adequacy decision a new shield for transatlantic privacy or just more of the same?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</guid><description>Dr. Maria Tzanou (Lecturer in Law, Keele University)
In October 2015, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruled in the Schrems case that the US Safe Harbor framework did not adequately protect personal data transfers from the EU. The court found that US mass electronic surveillance practices violated fundamental EU privacy rights.
To address this, the European Commission and the US agreed on a new framework called the EU-US Privacy Shield.</description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU/Canada free trade deal and investor protection disputes a blessing in disguise or a cause for concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent news suggests the EU/Canada free-trade agreement (CETA) faces obstacles due to the German government&amp;rsquo;s opposition to rules concerning investor/state dispute settlement. This situation carries potential implications for various aspects, including the EU/Canada and EU/USA trade deals, the EU&amp;rsquo;s broader trade and investment policies, and even the UK&amp;rsquo;s potential departure from the EU (&amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;).
Background
After commencing negotiations in 2009, the EU and Canada reached a preliminary agreement in 2013, pending finalization of technical points.</description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002.</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v.</description></item></channel></rss>