<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PBX Systems on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-systems/</link><description>Recent content in PBX Systems on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:24:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are T1 Lines Obsolete?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you been relying on a T1 line for a long time? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable, given their long history. When the Internet was new, a T1 line provided businesses with a dependable, high-bandwidth connection that made dial-up modems seem incredibly slow. These days, similar bandwidth options are available at comparable prices, making those old T1 lines appear slow in comparison. So, are T1 lines still a viable business solution, or are they outdated?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Converting From Regular Phone Lines to T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</guid><description>Your business is thriving, and your team is expanding, but your phone system isn&amp;rsquo;t keeping pace. The limited lines, tangled mess of wires, and sky-high bills are holding you back. There&amp;rsquo;s a better solution than relying on outdated analog lines.
T1 lines are the answer for businesses ready for a professional phone system. This technology allows multiple calls on a single line using your existing copper wiring. It&amp;rsquo;s like consolidating numerous lines into one connection for your phone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>