<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PPM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ppm/</link><description>Recent content in PPM on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ppm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (III)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</guid><description>This article, the third in a series about restoring a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s peak program meters (PPM), focuses on installing and calibrating the rebuilt PPM.
The initial step involved switching the original current limiting resistors with values suitable for modern SMD LEDs. These LEDs are more efficient and brighter, requiring significantly larger resistors to match the original brightness. Testing showed that 470 Ohm and 330 Ohm resistors for red and green LEDs, respectively, produced slightly brighter output compared to the original 180 Ohm and 120 Ohm resistors.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoring the Peak Program Meters with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s Peak Program Meter (PPM), even though it was fully functional. This decision stemmed from my success in restoring a different Beocord&amp;rsquo;s PPM that had several broken segments.
Since the technology behind these PPMs is similar to that of a 7-segment display, I realized that the segments in this unit were also susceptible to future breakage. Therefore, I chose to preemptively address the issue while I had the opportunity.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: Going over the service manual electrical adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-going-over-the-service-manual-electrical-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:38:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-going-over-the-service-manual-electrical-adjustments/</guid><description>After finishing my previous work on the Beocord 5000 cassette deck, I planned to make some recordings, but realized I needed to perform a full electrical adjustment procedure outlined in the service manual. This process is more time-consuming for two-head decks like this one, as it involves recording, rewinding, and playback for each adjustment.
Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the adjustments made:
Reference +5 VDC: With the Beocord stopped, I monitored the +5 VDC power supply at a test point and adjusted trimmer 3R24 on the power supply board until it measured +5 VDC.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (II)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s rebuilt Peak Program Meters (PPM) display passed a 24-hour test, confirming its functionality.
To reattach the red-green covers, I secured the display to ensure a tight seal, preventing light leakage. Using a soldering iron, I melted the plastic posts of the covers, replicating the original attachment method.
During cleaning, the glue holding the light guide dissolved, indicating it was likely polyvinyl ester-based. I used &amp;lsquo;Aleene&amp;rsquo;s Original Tacky Glue&amp;rsquo; as a substitute, providing a clear and durable bond.</description></item></channel></rss>