<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Green on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/green/</link><description>Recent content in Green on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/green/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visa Eco Benefits promote sustainability in every transaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</guid><description>Visa, a digital payment company, has introduced Visa Eco Benefits in the Asia Pacific region. This suite of sustainability solutions aims to help Visa cardholders understand the environmental effects of their everyday spending. They can track their carbon footprint from Visa transactions and explore options for offsetting their impact through carbon offsets or charitable donations via their bank&amp;rsquo;s app or website.
Banks in the Asia Pacific region that adopt Eco Benefits can offer these solutions to their Visa cardholders, addressing the increasing demand for environmentally conscious financial services.</description></item><item><title>Discover the most environmentally friendly hotels worldwide with GreenHotelWorld</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</guid><description>Source: GreenHotelWorld website.
GreenHotelWorld, in collaboration with TripAdvisor, now boasts the largest selection of verified eco-friendly hotels on a single platform. This was achieved by incorporating hotels from TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s GreenLeaders Program.
With a global reach, GreenHotelWorld curates over 8,000 hotels recognized for their demonstrably sustainable practices. Their categorization process utilizes standards from the Global Sustainable Tourism Council (GSTC), a respected international body that sets benchmarks for sustainable tourism and accredits green hotel certifications.</description></item><item><title>Anticipate more sustainable and environmentally-friendly buildings in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Building and Construction Authority (BCA) announced new initiatives during the opening ceremony of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW). These initiatives, stemming from a review of the third Green Building Masterplan, focus on improving occupant indoor environmental quality, promoting energy-efficient buildings, and incorporating green practices into existing structures.
Desmond Lee, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Social and Family Development and Second Minister for National Development, was the guest of honor at the ceremony.</description></item><item><title>IHG will no longer provide mini toiletries as bathroom amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</guid><description>Source: IHG. A shower with sink showing miniatures as amenities.
The InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) is transitioning from small, individual toiletry bottles to larger, bulk amenity dispensers in all 843,000 rooms across its portfolio of hotels. This change, to be fully implemented by 2021, is part of a larger sustainability initiative and establishes IHG as the first global hotel company to entirely eliminate miniature bathroom products in favor of bulk-sized options.</description></item><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses becomes a part of the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</guid><description>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is among the first to sign the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative. This initiative, spearheaded by the UN Environment Programme and UN World Tourism Organization with the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, aims to tackle plastic waste in the tourism sector.
By signing the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative, Six Senses reinforces its commitment to eliminate, innovate, and circulate its plastic use by 2025, aiming to be plastic-free as early as 2022.</description></item><item><title>Green Your Cell Phone For St. Patrick's Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</guid><description>On this St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day, let&amp;rsquo;s think about being green in more ways than one! Before the festivities begin, take a few moments to consider how you can help the environment.
You might be surprised to learn that millions of old cell phones are discarded yearly. They contain valuable resources like gold – enough to create a significant treasure if they were all collected. Instead of letting these resources go to waste, retrieve that old phone you have lying around, and let&amp;rsquo;s discover how it can benefit you and the planet.</description></item><item><title>The RYDE Carpool Challenge will begin in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s carpooling app, RYDE, has teamed up with Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage for the RYDE Carpool Challenge. The grand prize? A Mitsubishi Attrage.
The eight-month campaign, which began on April 1, 2016, aims to have RYDE users complete a collective carpool distance of 1,000,000km, thus reducing carbon emissions by 200,000kg. By encouraging carpooling, RYDE hopes to promote a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.
Each month, RYDE will select two winners: the rider and driver with the highest number of successful carpools.</description></item><item><title>Anyone can begin eliminating plastic from their lives at any time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</guid><description>Douglas Yeo, pictured second from the right, is the Course Director at DIWA and a dedicated environmental advocate. Although widely recognized for his role as a diver in the 2018 Thai cave rescue and his nomination for Singaporean of the Year, Yeo is also the driving force behind a growing movement to eliminate plastic use.
Known as the PlasticFREE initiative, this DIWA-supported campaign encourages individuals to minimize plastic waste. Participants are invited to start with small changes in their own lives and then spread the message to friends and family.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Every Home And Business Is A Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s blog posts are dedicated to Blog Action Day 2009&amp;rsquo;s theme: global warming, climate change, and alternative energy. We already established that alternative energy is a viable option, as solar and wind power are readily available. However, skeptics often question how to ensure a consistent energy supply when natural resources like sunlight and wind are inconsistent.
This is a valid concern since traditional power plants fueled by coal, nuclear, or natural gas have built-in energy storage within their fuel sources and steam boilers.</description></item><item><title>Creating new ideas in environmentally friendly buildings and construction areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</guid><description>Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier trade show for green building solutions, has commenced at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre. The event is anticipated to draw visitors from over 50 nations, all eager to witness the latest advancements in Asian green building, HVAC-R (heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, and refrigeration), water, energy, and heating technologies.
BEX Asia, which runs until September 14, 2017, is held in conjunction with Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional trade show specializing in energy-efficient solutions for industrial, commercial, and residential structures.</description></item><item><title>Malaysia to identify energy-efficient government buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</guid><description>Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Energy Commission, under the Ministry of Energy, Science, Technology, Environment and Climate Change (MESTECC), has introduced the National Building Energy Intensity (BEI) Labelling for Government Buildings.
This program strives to enhance energy efficiency in government-owned buildings within Malaysia, encouraging building owners to prioritize and improve energy conservation. Buildings are assigned a star rating based on their energy efficiency, with a five-star rating indicating the highest level of efficiency.
The initial phase, concluding in late 2018, encompasses 100 buildings belonging to ministries, departments, and agencies under MESTECC and the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Department.</description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras.</description></item><item><title>Get a ride and offset your carbon emissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 21:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</guid><description>Grab users will soon have the option to lessen the environmental impact of their trips by utilizing a new carbon offset feature integrated into the Grab app.
Source: Grab.
Explaining the carbon
offset feature.
A recent study across six Southeast Asian countries revealed that 82% of Grab users are concerned about climate change and are taking steps to minimize their environmental impact. However, 44% of those concerned but not actively addressing it cited a lack of knowledge on how to act, while 31% found it too challenging.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Green Building Week has officially begun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 01:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</guid><description>The DVUCA city management system dashboard uses data from Singapore and other cities to quickly compare water and power consumption. It can even provide granular insights, such as indicating if someone is at their desk.
Singapore Green Building Week has commenced, featuring Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, a Southeast Asian trade show for the region&amp;rsquo;s green building market, and Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional exhibition for HVAC-R*, water, and energy solutions.</description></item><item><title>The Building and Construction Authority of Singapore advocates for the development of super low energy buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-building-and-construction-authority-of-singapore-advocates-for-the-development-of-super-low-energy-buildings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-building-and-construction-authority-of-singapore-advocates-for-the-development-of-super-low-energy-buildings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Building and Construction Authority (BCA) initiated the Super Low Energy (SLE) Programme to advance environmental sustainability within the country. The program includes initiatives like the SLE Buildings Technology Roadmap and the SLE Challenge to promote the development and adoption of cost-effective SLE buildings.
Lawrence Wong, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for National Development and Second Minister for Finance, announced the program at the opening of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW) 2018.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s green building journey commenced in 2005 with the introduction of the BCA Green Mark and three Green Building Masterplans.</description></item><item><title>Singapore SMEs are being advised to view sustainability as a key to achieving growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 01:51:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</guid><description>Ang explains why sustainability is important for Singapore SMEs.
Embracing sustainability provides a competitive edge for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). It aligns them with the practices of larger corporations, potentially opening doors to becoming their suppliers.
Wilson Ang, Executive Director of Global Compact Network Singapore (GCNS), highlighted this during Fuji Xerox DocuWorld in Singapore. He emphasized that sustainability attracts a more discerning investor base, prompting SMEs to adapt to remain competitive.</description></item><item><title>Cachet Hotel Group unveils the fresh appearance of URBN Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</guid><description>The Cachet Hotel Group (CHG) has revamped its stylish URBN Hotel in Shanghai, a former warehouse. Led by CHG&amp;rsquo;s renowned fashion designer, Jay Godfrey, the updated interiors offer guests a modern, zen-like ambiance. The use of recycled and reclaimed wood materials adds a natural touch, further enhanced by the neutral color scheme.
Source: CHG. The Jay Godfrey Courtyard Suite.
Photo - http://photos.prnasia.com/prnh/20140911/0861406560
The URBN Shanghai boasts a unique Jay Godfrey-designed suite.</description></item></channel></rss>