<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beocord Display Repair on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beocord-display-repair/</link><description>Recent content in Beocord Display Repair on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:45:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beocord-display-repair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Ready for Bench Testing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-ready-for-bench-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-ready-for-bench-testing/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I finished the seven-segment display repair. The LEDs performed without issue during a 24-hour burn-in test. I double-checked the LEDs after reassembling the display using my specialized test equipment. My test setup has two parts for evaluating the Beocord display. The left side tests all LEDs illuminated simultaneously, while the right side allows me to test each LED channel or individual LED by adjusting jumpers.
During individual LED testing, I observed some light bleed from the middle &amp;ldquo;dot&amp;rdquo; LEDs into the neighboring segments.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Seven Segment Display Board Reworked</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-seven-segment-display-board-reworked/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-seven-segment-display-board-reworked/</guid><description>Setting up the Beosystem display board rework station took a bit longer than anticipated, but it&amp;rsquo;s finally ready for LED display repairs and testing. A working Beocord display helped confirm the test setup&amp;rsquo;s functionality.
The display board, with its front and back sides visible, now features markings indicating segment numbers and polarities.
Thirty-one LEDs comprise the display. The image provides a close-up view of the original LED lights.
Here, the original LED is juxtaposed with the replacement SMD LED.</description></item></channel></rss>