<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PCI Compliance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pci-compliance/</link><description>Recent content in PCI Compliance on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pci-compliance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Merchant Account Credit Card Processing Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</guid><description>Even the smallest businesses need a way to process credit card payments. Instead of making it a difficult process, choose a reliable credit card processing company to simplify things. Elite Processing Systems handles the complexities of electronic payments, allowing you to concentrate on your customers and what you offer. They provide a full range of financial services for small businesses, going above and beyond traditional credit card processing.
You might have heard of Elite Processing Systems (EPS).</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless For Rural Retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</guid><description>Small businesses outside of cities often struggle to obtain affordable and reliable broadband. While some resort to satellite or T1 lines for internet and point-of-sale systems, others have discovered that 3G wireless offers a secure and cost-effective alternative for credit card processing.
](http://www.sheepfort1.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
We associate 3G with mobile phones and laptops, but a lesser-known application exists. This service combines the widespread availability of 3G signals with powerful multi-carrier equipment and a secure VPN network, making it suitable for business needs.</description></item><item><title>POS For Temporary Store Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</guid><description>A common sight during the holidays is the &amp;ldquo;pop-up shop.&amp;rdquo; These temporary stores occupy vacant spaces in malls and shopping centers, offering seasonal goods like decorations, costumes, and calendars. Once the season ends, so do their operations. Despite their temporary nature, these businesses require robust point-of-sale (POS) systems, even more so than traditional stores.
The need for efficient POS systems stems from the concentrated bursts of customer traffic these stores experience.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Access Wireless Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</guid><description>Wireless internet isn&amp;rsquo;t just for mobile devices. Businesses can also benefit from fixed wireless services.
One affordable option utilizes existing cell towers to provide broadband similar to a T1 line at nearly half the cost. Accel Networks, for instance, partners with major carriers to leverage their bandwidth, achieving 99.9% reliability and quick installation times. This solution is ideal for businesses requiring PCI-compliant connections, like convenience stores or gas stations, especially those in areas with limited wired options.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Includes Canada &amp; Puerto Rico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 09:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</guid><description>People often associate broadband with wired connections, like T1 lines commonly used by small to medium businesses, or the increasingly popular Ethernet option known for its speed and affordability. While satellite is vital for many chain stores, there&amp;rsquo;s another reliable broadband solution that avoids construction costs and high monthly fees: fixed wireless broadband, now available across the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Accel Networks, a leading provider of fixed wireless broadband, leverages existing 2.</description></item></channel></rss>