<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Renovation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/renovation/</link><description>Recent content in Renovation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/renovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout.</description></item><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces the Bunyani financing campaign for completion works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new campaign called &amp;ldquo;Bunyani&amp;hellip; from skeleton structure to delivery&amp;rdquo; to provide financing options for owners of residential, investment, and industrial land plots. This campaign aims to help customers complete various construction phases, including finishing works, maintenance, and restoration.
Ahmad Al-Khaled, Deputy General Manager Commercial Services at KFH, stated that the campaign offers clients simplified financing solutions. These include financing of up to KD70,000, a repayment period of 15 years, a grace period of 12 months for the first installment, and a competitive profit rate.</description></item></channel></rss>