<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Private Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dedicated-private-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Private Lines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dedicated-private-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is.</description></item><item><title>Long Haul Voice, Video and Data via MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses need to transmit voice, video, and data across long distances, whether between cities, across the country, or even internationally. While both the internet and dedicated private lines are viable options, there&amp;rsquo;s another solution you might not be familiar with: MPLS networks. This article will explore why MPLS is a strong option for long-distance data transport and how to decide which solution best suits your needs.</description></item><item><title>Dynamically Allocate T1 Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a reliable choice for transmitting voice and data for many years. Traditionally, it was believed that the purpose of the line (voice or data) needed to be determined before installation. For voice communication, a channelized T1 line or ISDN PRI configuration was used, with each of the 23 or 24 channels dedicated to a single phone call. Conversely, a clear channel T1 line was used for point-to-point data transmission or dedicated internet access, allowing for the full 1.</description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits.</description></item></channel></rss>