<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SDH on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sdh/</link><description>Recent content in SDH on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sdh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choosing Dark Fiber vs Lit Fiber Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</guid><description>When applications require the bandwidth of fiber optic transmission, businesses face a choice: use existing &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber services or establish their own transport services using purchased or leased &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; fiber.
Deciding between these options involves weighing performance, cost, and installation time. Focusing solely on cost can lead to extended installation delays, potentially impacting operational needs. While a cost-effective solution might be suitable with ample planning time, immediate bandwidth demands may necessitate prioritizing availability over cost.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic.</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1.</description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Network For Orange County</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a rising demand for high-bandwidth, low-latency internet connectivity from businesses, particularly in sectors like finance, automation, cloud computing, and medical imaging. This surge is driving the expansion of fiber optic networks, with a prime example being the ongoing development in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
AboveNet, a prominent fiber optic network provider in the US and Europe, is constructing a major &amp;ldquo;feeder ring&amp;rdquo; in Orange County, California. This ring will connect various business locations, including office buildings, data centers, and carrier hotels, to an existing fiber optic backbone already serving the Irvine and Costa Mesa business districts.</description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Leads in High Bandwidth Ethernet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 22:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a significant change in high-bandwidth services, moving away from older SONET/SDH technology and towards Ethernet IP technology. This shift, driven by the long-term transition from analog to digital communications and the widespread use of Ethernet, could indicate a turning point for Ethernet in fiber optic communication, as argued by AboveNet.
AboveNet, a provider of high-bandwidth services in 15 major U.S. markets and the UK, specializes in fiber optic MAN and WAN connectivity, offering speeds from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps at lower prices than traditional telecom providers.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary.</description></item></channel></rss>