<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Policing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/policing/</link><description>Recent content in Policing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 06:09:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/policing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Evolution of EU Criminal Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 06:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2014 was significant for the European Union, marked by events such as European Parliament elections, the establishment of a new European Commission, and notable legislative and case-law developments. This post, the first in a series, reviews key developments in specific EU law areas.
The most substantial change in EU criminal law occurred on December 1st, ending the five-year transition period for EU criminal law measures enacted before the Lisbon Treaty came into effect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Council v H: Another Court victory in the Common Foreign and Security Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</guid><description>Graham Butler, PhD Fellow at the Centre for Comparative and European Constitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen, Denmark
Introduction
This summer, the Court of Justice (the Court) issued two significant decisions influencing the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) legal landscape. Despite the Treaty of Lisbon&amp;rsquo;s integration of this largely intergovernmental area (previously the Second Pillar) into the unified ‘EU’, its legacy persists. Enduring evidence of CFSP as a distinct yet incorporated legal domain allows it to be termed ‘CFSP law’...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Impact on UK's Participation in EU Policing and Criminal Law: EU Referendum Brief 5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
This piece examines the relationship between EU membership and UK policing and criminal law, exploring potential impacts of Brexit.
Summary
The UK held veto power over EU laws in this domain before the Treaty of Lisbon (enacted December 1, 2009). Subsequently, the UK secured two opt-out mechanisms: the ability to opt into (or out of) any new EU law in this area post-Treaty, and the option to retroactively opt out of pre-existing EU laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Assessing the Commission's Proposal to Enhance Europol's Authority: A Review of the Amendment to Regulation (EU) 2016/784 (Europol Regulation)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</guid><description>Niovi Vavoula and Valsamis Mitsilegas, Queen Mary University
Introduction The European Union Agency for Law Enforcement Cooperation (Europol) plays a crucial role in supporting EU Member States&amp;rsquo; cross-border police cooperation, as defined by Regulation (EU) 2016/794 (Europol Regulation). Referred to as the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;criminal information hub,&amp;rsquo; Europol facilitates information exchange between Member States, Europol itself, other EU bodies, international organizations, and third countries. It also generates criminal intelligence using information from various sources, including Member States and partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contrasting torture and other forms of ill-treatment: Cestaro v. Italy and the necessity of a "prohibited purpose" condition.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contrasting-torture-and-other-forms-of-ill-treatment-cestaro-v-italy-and-the-necessity-of-a-prohibited-purpose-condition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 06:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contrasting-torture-and-other-forms-of-ill-treatment-cestaro-v-italy-and-the-necessity-of-a-prohibited-purpose-condition/</guid><description>Christina Kosin (LL.M. Edinburgh), Ph.D. candidate and academic assistant at the German Police University, argues that the &amp;ldquo;prohibited purpose&amp;rdquo; requirement, while crucial, is not the only factor differentiating torture from inhuman or degrading treatment. The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo;s (ECtHR) judgment in Cestaro v. Italy illustrates this point.
The Judgment
Mr. Cestaro, a peaceful protester at the 2001 G-8 summit in Genoa, Italy, was subjected to severe beatings by Italian police while staying at a school being searched for radical protesters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contrasting-torture-and-other-forms-of-ill-treatment-cestaro-v-italy-and-the-necessity-of-a-prohibited-purpose-condition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contrasting-torture-and-other-forms-of-ill-treatment-cestaro-v-italy-and-the-necessity-of-a-prohibited-purpose-condition/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>