<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Etiqa on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/etiqa/</link><description>Recent content in Etiqa on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:01:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/etiqa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etiqa has introduced the first-ever complimentary inflight insurance for travelers from Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</guid><description>The first complimentary in-flight insurance plan in Singapore offers up to S$50,000 in personal accident coverage.
For an added S$4, travelers can purchase coverage for flights delayed by three hours or more.
Claims can be paid out instantly through PayNow.
Etiqa, an online insurance provider based in Singapore, has introduced the nation&amp;rsquo;s first complimentary in-flight insurance for travelers. The company also launched a flight delay add-on for S$4, enabling travelers to receive compensation for flights delayed by three consecutive hours, which is a lower threshold compared to the industry average of six to twelve hours.</description></item><item><title>Customers who are retrenched will have their bills waived by Singtel Bill Protect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-are-retrenched-will-have-their-bills-waived-by-singtel-bill-protect/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-are-retrenched-will-have-their-bills-waived-by-singtel-bill-protect/</guid><description>Singtel and Etiqa Insurance Singapore have teamed up to introduce Singtel Bill Protect, a free insurance plan designed to help Singaporeans navigate tough economic times and maintain their connectivity even if they encounter financial difficulties. This launch comes as retrenchments in Singapore have increased for three consecutive quarters, according to the Ministry of Manpower&amp;rsquo;s latest labor market reports.
In response to growing economic uncertainty and job insecurity, the Bill Protect plan aims to support Singtel customers experiencing financial strain due to job loss by providing waivers on their upcoming Singtel mobile and fixed broadband bills.</description></item></channel></rss>