<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Passenger Name Records on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/passenger-name-records/</link><description>Recent content in Passenger Name Records on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:49:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/passenger-name-records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>At the oral hearing on the PNR directive at the Court of Justice of the European Union, the focus was on flights, rock concerts, and finding a needle in a haystack.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</guid><description>Christian Thönnes, Research Associate at the Max Planck Institute for the Study of Crime, Security and Law in Freiburg, Department of Public Law.
July 13, 2021, marked a crucial moment for the future of privacy and security in the European Union. On this day, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held a hearing regarding its preliminary ruling procedure C-817/19. This procedure was initiated after the Constitutional Court of Belgium submitted ten questions to the CJEU, prompted by a legal challenge from the Belgian NGO Ligue des Droits Humains.</description></item><item><title>Is there a need for additional anti-terrorist legislation in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 01:42:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Following the horrific attacks in Paris two days ago, the EU Commission wasted no time in announcing its intention to propose new anti-terrorism measures within a month. While the specifics of this legislation remain unclear, the very notion of enacting new laws is fundamentally flawed.
The EU institutions were right to express sympathy for the victims and emphasize their commitment to defending freedom of speech. Utilizing existing EU anti-terrorism laws, such as the European Arrest Warrant (EAW), to apprehend suspects who may have fled to another Member State, would also be appropriate.</description></item><item><title>Is the Passenger Name Record Directive legally valid? Thoughts on the upcoming CJEU case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-passenger-name-record-directive-legally-valid-thoughts-on-the-upcoming-cjeu-case/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-passenger-name-record-directive-legally-valid-thoughts-on-the-upcoming-cjeu-case/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, a legal expert in human rights and data protection, believes the EU Court of Justice should examine whether the PNR Directive aligns with the Charter of Fundamental Rights. This follows a similar inquiry by Belgium&amp;rsquo;s Constitutional Court.
Korff suggests that any large-scale surveillance, such as that under the PNR Directive, needs to meet two criteria. First, there should be strong proof from the European Commission and EU member states that these measures genuinely help combat crimes related to PNR.</description></item></channel></rss>