<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Presentation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/presentation/</link><description>Recent content in Presentation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 21:43:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/presentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The book guarantees to save presentations from completely missing the mark</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-guarantees-to-save-presentations-from-completely-missing-the-mark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 21:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-guarantees-to-save-presentations-from-completely-missing-the-mark/</guid><description>Presentations are a common way to share information, manage projects, and plan, taking up a significant part of the workweek. However, they often waste time and resources.
Ed Gruwez, a Belgian communications expert, believes most presentations are ineffective and poorly designed, failing to achieve their goals despite considerable preparation time. He points out their negative impact on corporate decisions and employee satisfaction.
Gruwez emphasizes the ubiquity of presentations in professional settings and the significant financial and time resources wasted on ineffective ones.</description></item><item><title>Evernote introduces a new and improved app with a redesigned interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</guid><description>Evernote has announced three updates: a brand new app, a significantly enhanced feature, and a major app redesign.
As detailed in a recent blog post, the company will introduce &amp;ldquo;Scannable,&amp;rdquo; a mobile scanning app. Scannable can transform physical items like business cards and receipts into digital content that can be easily shared and acted upon. It also integrates with the ScanSnap Evernote Edition desktop scanner, enabling shared scanning across a user&amp;rsquo;s network and essentially turning it into a shared office resource.</description></item></channel></rss>