<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Miller on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/miller/</link><description>Recent content in Miller on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:43:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/miller/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brexit and the Protection of EU Transnational Rights - Part II The Stance of the Supreme Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:43:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
This piece expands on a previous one concerning the High Court&amp;rsquo;s stance on protecting EU Law-based transnational rights within the context of the Miller case. It examines the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the High Court&amp;rsquo;s position and the resulting implications for EU law. The significance of transnational rights persists for two primary reasons. Firstly, beyond the immediate impact on EU and UK citizens facing Brexit-related disruptions, it highlights the fundamental nature of individual rights within the EU legal framework.</description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures.</description></item><item><title>Reading between the lines of the High Court's Brexit ruling: Protecting EU transnational rights and their safeguards.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 08:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
This piece revisits the recent High Court ruling on the UK government&amp;rsquo;s authority to initiate the process of leaving the EU. It delves deeper into the judgment&amp;rsquo;s EU law implications, going beyond the political turmoil it has caused and potentially extending beyond the immediate consequences of Brexit. The article argues that the judgment, though focused on UK constitutional law, also touches upon the issue of safeguarding transnational rights, such as those of British citizens in other EU countries, during a Member State&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal.</description></item></channel></rss>