<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sql Server on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sql-server/</link><description>Recent content in Sql Server on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sql-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Users of Forecaster and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>Have you ever encountered a problem where you vaguely recall a solution but can&amp;rsquo;t seem to locate the specific article or link? This happened to me recently with a client attempting to use their Dynamics GP user ID for Forecaster 7. As expected, it was unsuccessful due to GP&amp;rsquo;s encryption method when generating user IDs in SQL. This encryption prevents the same ID from functioning in Forecaster, even with proper database permissions.</description></item><item><title>Importing 725,000 Records into Dynamics GP in Just Half a Minute</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/importing-725-000-records-into-dynamics-gp-in-just-half-a-minute/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/importing-725-000-records-into-dynamics-gp-in-just-half-a-minute/</guid><description>In a recent project, I tackled a complex integration challenge for a client dealing with large-volume remittance data. This client received consolidated monthly payments from major trading partners, accompanied by massive remittance advice files. These files, reaching sizes of 140MB and containing up to 725,000 rows, detailed the allocation of the payments across thousands of customer invoices.
Previously, the client&amp;rsquo;s accounting team manually processed these files in Excel, painstakingly entering transactions and applying payments.</description></item><item><title>Error message: Unable to create SSPI context</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-message-unable-to-create-sspi-context/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:06:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-message-unable-to-create-sspi-context/</guid><description>A client encountered a &amp;ldquo;Cannot generate SSPI context&amp;rdquo; error with their eConnect integration. This error typically signals a problem with Windows authentication on the SQL Server.
Troubleshooting began by checking basic network connectivity between the workstation and the SQL server using ping commands to verify DNS resolution. When those checks showed no issues, the focus shifted to the SQL Server service&amp;rsquo;s configuration.
Investigating the SQL Server service revealed it was configured to run under the domain Administrator account – a practice generally discouraged.</description></item><item><title>Understanding and Embracing the SQL Server Browser Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-and-embracing-the-sql-server-browser-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:42:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-and-embracing-the-sql-server-browser-service/</guid><description>I previously discussed some difficulties I encountered logging into GP because the SQL Server Browser service wasn&amp;rsquo;t running.
I want to explain the background of the SQL Server Browser service and why it should be running on a Dynamics GP SQL 2005 server.
In the past, SQL Server 7.5 only permitted one instance per machine, listening for connections on port 1433. This simplicity had a drawback: only one instance was allowed.</description></item><item><title>Looking for SQL objects and data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-sql-objects-and-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:56:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-sql-objects-and-data/</guid><description>When working with Dynamics GP and SQL Server, finding a specific table, stored procedure, table column, or data value is often necessary. This is especially true when troubleshooting issues with third-party modules where the table name or database location is unknown.
Several methods exist for searching SQL Server for a specific object. One straightforward approach uses the INFORMATION_SCHEMA views. These views are helpful when the object type (table, stored procedure, etc.</description></item><item><title>The APPLY operator in SQL Server</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apply-operator-in-sql-server/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 08:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apply-operator-in-sql-server/</guid><description>The SQL Server APPLY operator is a powerful tool that can simplify complex queries, much like a delicious treat for your database code.
It&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly common to discover useful features in SQL Server that you were previously unaware of. For instance, the APPLY operator would have been incredibly helpful in a scenario involving retrieving vendor addresses in Microsoft Dynamics GP.
The task was to fetch both the primary and &amp;ldquo;remit to&amp;rdquo; addresses for each vendor.</description></item><item><title>Mysterious eConnect Error: The stored procedure does not exist. Be mindful of your schemas!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mysterious-econnect-error-the-stored-procedure-does-not-exist-be-mindful-of-your-schemas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 16:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mysterious-econnect-error-the-stored-procedure-does-not-exist-be-mindful-of-your-schemas/</guid><description>During a Dynamics GP Visual Studio Tools AddIn upgrade from GP 9 to GP 2010, a peculiar eConnect error surfaced after a smooth installation on the client server. The error indicated a non-existent stored procedure, &amp;rsquo;taCreatePayrollBatchHeaderInsert&amp;rsquo;, despite it being present in the SQL database.
Verification of the eConnect domain user&amp;rsquo;s SQL Login and user setup for the company database, including permissions, showed no discrepancies. Debugging the database connection string revealed the correct GP company database was being referenced.</description></item><item><title>Tip for SQL: How to search for special characters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tip-for-sql-how-to-search-for-special-characters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 10:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tip-for-sql-how-to-search-for-special-characters/</guid><description>While it&amp;rsquo;s challenging to stay updated on every post by Aubrey, the soon-to-be-renowned expert in GP, I came across a useful SQL tip I&amp;rsquo;d like to pass along.
I seldom need to construct queries that involve searching for special characters like &amp;ldquo;_&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;%&amp;rdquo;. So, when I needed to locate all customer IDs starting with an underscore earlier today, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recall the proper syntax.
A quick online search provided numerous solutions, offering at least two straightforward methods for this type of query.</description></item></channel></rss>