<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Selector on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/selector/</link><description>Recent content in Selector on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/selector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Speed Indictor Light Bulbs with RGB LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 11:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</guid><description>During the wait for a 3D-printed part for a Beogram 4002 turntable restoration, the author decided to upgrade its speed indicator lights. Using a method from a previous video, they replaced the incandescent bulbs with RGB LEDs for a more authentic look.
The original setup with incandescent bulbs was documented before the upgrade.
The new setup utilizes both the red and green diodes of an RGB LED for a natural appearance, addressing the issue of amber LEDs failing to illuminate red scale markers properly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Unit Switches Immediately to 45 RPM After Pressing Start</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable being restored exhibited a peculiar issue during initial testing. Upon starting, the tonearm moved as expected but the speed immediately switched to 45 RPM. Pressing the 33 RPM button temporarily resolved the issue, but the speed reverted back upon release.
This unusual behavior pointed to a potential problem with transistors TR3 or TR2. Examining the circuit diagram, we can see how speed selection operates:
The speed control mechanism utilizes a flip-flop circuit with transistors TR3 and TR4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>