<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fengshui on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fengshui/</link><description>Recent content in Fengshui on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fengshui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap provides insights on the metal rat year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-provides-insights-on-the-metal-rat-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-provides-insights-on-the-metal-rat-year/</guid><description>Thriving in the Year of the Metal Rat: A Guide by Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap [Image of a golden rat with the caption &amp;ldquo;Year of the Metal Rat feng shui advice 2020&amp;rdquo;]
Source: The Joey Yap Group. Dato&amp;rsquo; Yap.
Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap, renowned expert in Chinese Metaphysics and founder of the Mastery Academy of Chinese Metaphysics, has created a comprehensive guide for navigating the year of the rat. This resource, Everything About The Year of The Metal Rat 2020 All In One Place, is available on his portal.</description></item><item><title>Tips for choosing the correct date for the appropriate occasion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-choosing-the-correct-date-for-the-appropriate-occasion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 18:55:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-choosing-the-correct-date-for-the-appropriate-occasion/</guid><description>Source: Unsplash via Joey Yap. Diary with pen.
According to the principles of fengshui, certain times are more auspicious than others for making significant life choices and improving potential outcomes.
Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap, the creator of the Mastery Academy of Chinese Metaphysics, emphasizes the importance of timing: &amp;ldquo;Timing is truly everything. The concept that some days are better suited for specific activities is not complicated. To maximize your time and achieve desired results, you must consider the crucial aspect of dates.</description></item><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap reveals video predictions for each Chinese zodiac animal for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Joey Yap, founder and CEO of the Mastery Academy of Chinese Metaphysics and Chief Consultant of the Joey Yap Consulting Group, created 12 videos outlining the year ahead for the 12 Chinese zodiac animal signs in areas such as career, relationships, business, and health.
The videos are in English and include traditional Chinese subtitles.
The year of the fire rooster starts on January 28, 2017. Yap considers the rooster one of the luckiest animals in 2017.</description></item><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap reveals his forecasts for the Year of the Earth Boar, 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</guid><description>Over 5,000 attendees were present at Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap&amp;rsquo;s yearly Feng Shui &amp;amp; Astrology seminar in January 2019.
During the seminar, Dato&amp;rsquo; Yap provided insights into the Year of the Earth Boar, covering both the year&amp;rsquo;s forecasts and the projected global economic climate.
He specifically highlighted February 8th, 11th, and 12th as auspicious dates to resume work in 2019.
A notable collaboration with EZ-Link resulted in the launch of special edition EZ-Link cards.</description></item><item><title>Joey Yap's advice for the 12 zodiac signs in 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-s-advice-for-the-12-zodiac-signs-in-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 23:38:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-s-advice-for-the-12-zodiac-signs-in-2019/</guid><description>Joey Yap, a renowned author, speaker, and expert in Chinese metaphysics, has provided his forecasts for the 12 zodiac signs, along with a flying stars chart, based on traditional Chinese metaphysical principles. These predictions cover the year of the earth boar, spanning from February 5, 2019, to January 24, 2020.
Dog Birth years: 1934, 1946, 1958, 1970, 1982, 1994, 2006, 2018
Overall: This year brings excellent financial prospects for Dogs, presenting opportunities to enhance wealth through carefully chosen investments and assistance from others.</description></item><item><title>Positioning your company in the southwest corner of the office could enhance its success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/positioning-your-company-in-the-southwest-corner-of-the-office-could-enhance-its-success/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/positioning-your-company-in-the-southwest-corner-of-the-office-could-enhance-its-success/</guid><description>Source: Joey Yap Private Limited.
Infographic on the impact of directions in 2018.
Dato’ Joey Yap, a prominent speaker, author, and Chief Consultant at Joey Yap Private Limited, a consultancy specializing in fengshui and Chinese astrology, has put together a list of 2018 fengshui direction predictions for a prosperous year of the earth dog.
In fengshui, different directions are believed to influence different aspects of a person&amp;rsquo;s life, and these influences shift each lunar year.</description></item><item><title>Joey Yap provides predictions for the 12 animal signs in the year 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-provides-predictions-for-the-12-animal-signs-in-the-year-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 19:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-provides-predictions-for-the-12-animal-signs-in-the-year-2018/</guid><description>Source: Joey Yap Private Limited.
Infographic for the 12 animal signs in 2018.
Chinese culture places significance on the lunar year, believing it brings new fortunes. Each of the 12 animal signs in the Chinese zodiac is thought to face unique opportunities and obstacles.
Within the Chinese zodiac, each year aligns with one of 12 animals and one of five elements. Although the year of the fire rooster (January 28, 2017, to February 15, 2018) is still ongoing, a shift is anticipated on February 16, 2018, as the year of the earth dog commences.</description></item></channel></rss>