<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MSP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/msp/</link><description>Recent content in MSP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:06:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/msp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Services Give Small Companies an Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</guid><description>During the ongoing economic downturn, businesses of all sizes face the challenge of maintaining competitive electronic services with limited budgets. Managed services present a solution, particularly for smaller companies lacking substantial IT departments and hiring capacity.
The concept of managed services is straightforward: you delegate management to an external provider. Consider your phone system. One option is to independently research, purchase, and install a PBX system, along with the necessary hardware and staff.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Deals for MSPs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</guid><description>Managed Service Providers (MSPs) can provide more value to their clients by helping them find better deals on WAN bandwidth, in addition to their existing IT services. Many companies are unaware of the changes in the telecommunications market and the cheaper options now available.
A basic bandwidth service that businesses should consider is T1, which offers reliable voice and/or data services with a service level agreement. T1 prices have significantly decreased this decade, often by 50% or even 67%.</description></item></channel></rss>