<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Apps on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apps/</link><description>Recent content in Apps on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Social Commerce Apps For Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</guid><description>E-commerce is no longer a novelty; it&amp;rsquo;s a cornerstone of modern business. The next big shift, social commerce, is already underway. This evolution utilizes social media platforms, primarily Facebook and Twitter, to connect with customers where they are most active. The question for businesses is how to best harness this power.
While older methods like DIY websites, email campaigns, and blogs still exist, they are becoming outdated. The solution lies in hosted solutions, with Facebook as the foundation.</description></item><item><title>Eliminating uncertainty in analytics with BeyondCore Apps for Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</guid><description>Source: BeyondCore website.
BeyondCore has introduced BeyondCore Apps for Office, a solution that provides automated analysis for the Microsoft Office suite with a single click. The company recognized the need for accessible and efficient analytics tools for business users who require data-driven insights to make informed decisions and improve their operations.
Arijit Sengupta, CEO and Founder of BeyondCore, highlighted the challenges of traditional analytics, describing it as a manual and time-consuming process.</description></item></channel></rss>