<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Funding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/funding/</link><description>Recent content in Funding on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:02:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/funding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New focus on Kickstarter: A mouse glove as a replacement for traditional computer mice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</guid><description>A new Kickstarter project called the &amp;ldquo;Mouse Glove&amp;rdquo; aims to revolutionize how we interact with technology, potentially replacing touch screens entirely.
Source: Kickstarter website
The creators of the Mouse Glove claim their invention offers a more ergonomic and intuitive user experience compared to traditional mice. By promoting a more natural hand position, they believe it can reduce the risk of repetitive strain injuries like carpal tunnel syndrome.
The glove replicates standard mouse functionalities, including left and right clicks, scrolling, and cursor control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Golden Equator Consulting assists small and medium-sized enterprises and startups in advancing towards success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 02:34:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</guid><description>Golden Equator Consulting (GE Consulting), a business consultancy firm, has established a presence in Singapore to serve small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups in the region. Sharon Chong, CEO of GE Consulting, noted that these businesses need strategic and operational support to streamline their growth and focus on core business functions.
GE Consulting offers comprehensive business consultancy services, covering areas such as business strategy, sales positioning, financial support, marketing, technology, human resources, and legal compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore businesses can access cybersecurity and financing services from Acronis and Minterest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyberprotection company, has partnered with Minterest, a Singaporean online financial services provider, to offer financing to Singaporean businesses. This collaboration, called Acronis #CyberFit Financing, Powered by Minterest, aims to help businesses in Singapore stay resilient and #CyberFit during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Acronis and Minterest want to empower businesses by providing easily accessible, customized financing solutions. This will help businesses navigate challenging times while also strengthening their cybersecurity defenses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new tech and innovation business club has been introduced in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</guid><description>SPECTRUM, a curated tech and innovation business club, has been established in Singapore. The organization, co-founded by Cheryl Lee and Shirley Crystal Chua, aims to create a globally connected ecosystem for businesses seeking to expand into Asia by providing expert advice, necessary resources, and strategic networks.
SPECTRUM has partnered with Golden Equator and Mistletoe to form a collaborative network of seven strategic groups: innovators, learning institutions, executors, backers, enablers, government agencies, and ecosystem builders and partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Focus of Kickstarter campaign: Sitting cross-legged on a CrossChair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 21:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</guid><description>Dave McClintock designed a chair that lets you comfortably rest with your legs up. Its unique design is so flexible, it even allows for the sukhasana yoga pose while seated.
McClintock explained that the chair caters to millions of workers who experience fatigue, back pain, and stiff muscles from prolonged sitting. While crossing your legs can alleviate these issues, traditional office chairs lack the ergonomics. The CrossChair solves this by enabling various sitting positions, including cross-legged, promoting movement and reducing discomfort...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An improved chair designed to alleviate back discomfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</guid><description>Simon Hong, a neuroscientist, is seeking funding for his invention, the Chairbot. This robotic chair aims to eliminate back pain by suggesting new positions to the user based on their current posture.
Source: Kickstarter page
The Chairbot&amp;rsquo;s unique design features a split seat that encourages users to alternate between sitting and standing, reducing strain on the spine. Hong explains on the Kickstarter page that this constant shifting prevents the spinal trauma associated with maintaining a single posture for long periods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A white paper by the Dubai Chamber examines the funding landscape for startups in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Cover for the white paper.
A recent report highlights the need for a simplified guide to help UAE startups navigate the funding landscape and connect with eager investors. The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, in partnership with Roland Berger, published this white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Helping Startups Access Funding,&amp;rdquo; during the March edition of Dubai Startup Hub&amp;rsquo;s Entrepreneurship Advocacy Series. Dubai Startup Hub, the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s entrepreneurial arm, offers guidance and clarity to new businesses through various programs and workshops...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AsiaKredit has introduced a consumer lending platform in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>AsiaKredit&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make financial services more accessible in the Philippines. They aim to achieve this by making credit easier to obtain and improving the approval rates for individuals with limited or no credit history.
Source: pera247 website. Screenshot of the pera247 app.
Pera247 is a completely digital platform offering short-term loans, up to 90 days, through a mobile wallet. These loans are typically small, unsecured, and target consumers with limited financial history...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the fast Phone Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</guid><description>The Phone Finder helps locate lost smartphones, even if they&amp;rsquo;re on silent mode, for up to three years. When the Phone Finder device is clicked within 15 meters of the missing phone, the phone will ring, vibrate, and flash, making it easier to find. If the phone is out of range, the Phone Finder website displays its location on a map.
Source: Kickstarter
Creator Gabsow Tom selected Bluetooth 2.1 for its forward and backward compatibility, allowing the Phone Finder to work with any smartphone, regardless of its iOS or Android version...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Men's cufflinks that can be customized are now offered on Indiegogo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</guid><description>CuffloCs, customizable cufflinks designed for men, are seeking funding on Indiegogo. These unique cufflinks feature a secure compartment for holding small items. According to creator Josh Jablonski, CuffloCs can accommodate a variety of small objects, such as jewelry charms, pebbles, or even photographs.
Source: Indiegogo.
&amp;ldquo;The screw/on off design ensures the security of your items within the double-sided glass, and the cufflink can be effortlessly disassembled to switch up the design,&amp;rdquo; explains Jablonski on his Indiegogo page...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the standing desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 03:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</guid><description>If you need a desk that allows you to work comfortably while standing, Steven Yu might have a solution. His StandDesk is height-adjustable, ranging from 71cm to 114cm, and incorporates design elements that make frequent adjustments easy.
Source: Kickstarter. The all-black StandDesk version.
&amp;ldquo;The StandDesk is more than a product; it&amp;rsquo;s a positive step towards improving people&amp;rsquo;s lives globally,&amp;rdquo; Yu stated on his Kickstarter page.
An intuitive &amp;lsquo;up/down&amp;rsquo; control button effortlessly raises or lowers the desk to the desired height...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: Customizable, reusable clothing in an instant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 13:33:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</guid><description>SiDi Huang, the creator behind ZipSeam, has developed an innovative solution for achieving a tailored look without the need for traditional sewing. ZipSeam offers a quick and easy way to create secure, temporary seams in loose clothing, providing a better fit for the wearer.
This invention has a wide range of applications, from the modeling industry and hand-me-downs to simply adjusting the fit of clothes you love. It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that this project has garnered significant attention and support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CrowdsUnite offers convenient crowdsourcing updates all in one location</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 22:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</guid><description>CrowdsUnite (crowdsunite.com) aims to be the &amp;ldquo;Yelp&amp;rdquo; for crowdfunding, featuring over 800 platforms in its database. The website provides guidance on crowdfunding and helps startups find the best platforms for their needs.
Alex Feldman, CEO of CrowdsUnite, points out that crowdfunding sites vary in features, customer support, and transparency. He emphasizes the risk of fraudulent campaigns that disappear with investors&amp;rsquo; money.
Source: CrowdsUnite blog. Feldman presents crowdfunding at a July 2014 talk in New York, US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The main focus of Kickstarter is iFind, which is powered by ambient electromagnetic radiation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</guid><description>WeTag&amp;rsquo;s iFind tags use Bluetooth to connect with iOS or Android devices and don&amp;rsquo;t require charging. Like similar tracking devices, the tag is attached to an item and located using a smartphone.
If the item goes out of range, the &amp;lsquo;Rope&amp;rsquo; feature notifies the owner. The &amp;lsquo;UHelp&amp;rsquo; feature leverages nearby phones to help find the lost object through Bluetooth. WeTag highlights a unique feature: shaking the iFind tag will cause the paired phone to vibrate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Concentrating on Kickstarter: Making Solar Power Accessible to Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 10:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</guid><description>Spor Solar Charges aims to make convenient solar-powered battery charging accessible to everyone. Their product, Spor, is a portable battery charger for USB devices that can recharge itself using solar energy. It can also be powered up using a standard AC outlet. The company claims that Spor can charge multiple devices simultaneously and replenish a phone&amp;rsquo;s battery almost as quickly as a wall outlet, according to their Kickstarter page.
Source: Kickstarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>