<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SD-WAN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sd-wan/</link><description>Recent content in SD-WAN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sd-wan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How AI is Helping to Improve Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Customer service calls are increasingly frustrating due to rising costs and labor shortages, negatively impacting both customers and companies. Tech expert David Pogue, in a CBS News report, suggests a blend of human agents and AI as a solution.
One such AI, called Grace, can handle customer interactions independently. However, AI like Grace can falter in complex situations, necessitating a transfer to human agents. While some of the best agents are located internationally and may have accents, this can be a hurdle for some US customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How SD-WAN Hands-Off Seamlessly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 05:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It would be ideal if WAN network connections never failed, but unfortunately, that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. Even the most reliable copper, fiber, or wireless connections eventually experience downtime. This can interrupt phone calls, halt ongoing work, and lead to lost productivity and revenue. However, imagine a solution that ensures your connections remain virtually uninterrupted, experiencing only minor, momentary glitches regardless of the underlying issue.
This solution exists and is called SD-WAN, or Software-Defined Wide Area Networking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>