<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cancer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cancer/</link><description>Recent content in Cancer on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:42:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cancer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shopee Malaysia is showing support for breast cancer awareness by going pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</guid><description>Shopee, a popular online marketplace in Malaysia, is partnering with the Pink Ribbon Deeds (PRIDE) Foundation for a &amp;ldquo;Goes Pink&amp;rdquo; campaign throughout October to raise awareness about breast cancer. The campaign involves both online and offline initiatives.
Shopee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Goes Pink&amp;rdquo; collection features pink and white products across various categories like mobile accessories, beauty products, and home goods, encouraging users to purchase and show their support. With over 2 million app installs in Malaysia, Shopee aims to leverage its platform to spread awareness nationwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce the risk of cancer in your workplace with International SOS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/</guid><description>International SOS has used World Cancer Day to highlight the impact of cancer on the workplace and encourage companies to take action. They emphasize that many cancer cases are preventable and point out that workplaces can contribute to cancer risk factors like unhealthy habits and exposure to harmful substances.
The organization&amp;rsquo;s Medical Director, Dr. Kate O&amp;rsquo;Reilly, stressed the growing impact of cancer on the workforce, stating that it affects not just the individual but the entire organization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Go on a date with some dried fruit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/go-on-a-date-with-some-dried-fruit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 20:44:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/go-on-a-date-with-some-dried-fruit/</guid><description>Studies suggest that dates, a popular fruit during Ramadan, could be considered a superfood.
A 2002 study discovered that dates may be effective in combating cancer-causing mutations. In a 2009 study, healthy individuals who consumed 100g of dates daily for four weeks showed remarkable results.
Despite the sugar content of the Hallawi and Medjool dates, their blood sugar levels remained stable. The research also indicated that dates could potentially inhibit plaque buildup in arteries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/go-on-a-date-with-some-dried-fruit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/go-on-a-date-with-some-dried-fruit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is debate over whether mobile phones can cause cancer, with some believing they can and others disagreeing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</guid><description>There have been many concerns about mobile phones and cancer risks. Since the first mobile phone&amp;rsquo;s debut in 1984 and their rise in popularity in the 1990s, it&amp;rsquo;s taken time to study the long-term effects of mobile phone radiation, as some cancers take years to manifest. We might only now be starting to see the impact.
A recent study in Pathophysiology suggests that radiation from mobile and cordless phones could contribute to a specific brain tumor called glioma...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Early detection is crucial for certain cancers that are caused by bad luck</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/early-detection-is-crucial-for-certain-cancers-that-are-caused-by-bad-luck/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 23:17:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/early-detection-is-crucial-for-certain-cancers-that-are-caused-by-bad-luck/</guid><description>Source: Johns Hopkins Medicine. Credit: C Tomasetti, B Vogelstein and Illustrator Elizabeth Cook, Johns Hopkins. Researchers at the Johns Hopkins Kimmel Cancer Center have discovered that about two-thirds of adult cancers can be attributed to random genetic mutations, while the remaining third stem from environmental and hereditary factors. Published in Science, the paper, titled Variation in cancer risk among tissues can be explained by the number of stem cell divisions, emphasizes that this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean two-thirds of all cancers are solely due to chance, as the impact of chance varies between cancer types...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/early-detection-is-crucial-for-certain-cancers-that-are-caused-by-bad-luck/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/early-detection-is-crucial-for-certain-cancers-that-are-caused-by-bad-luck/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>