<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Protection Reform on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-protection-reform/</link><description>Recent content in Data Protection Reform on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:27:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-protection-reform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Returning to the past: Revisiting fundamental data protection principles in the proposed Data Protection Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-to-the-past-revisiting-fundamental-data-protection-principles-in-the-proposed-data-protection-regulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:27:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-to-the-past-revisiting-fundamental-data-protection-principles-in-the-proposed-data-protection-regulation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2015 is not living up to the futuristic vision presented in the Back to the Future films, particularly with the absence of hoverboards (drones are a disappointing alternative). Instead of establishing a data protection framework suitable for 2015, the Council seems poised to agree on maintaining the core legal principles from 1995 – which are outdated in the context of technology law.
Background
Negotiations regarding the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed General Data Protection Regulation appear to be nearing their final stages within the Council.</description></item><item><title>The Council is making initial progress in reforming EU data protection law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 data protection rules, laid out in a Directive, are undergoing a major transformation. The Commission has proposed a new Regulation, sparking discussions since early 2012. While negotiations continue, June saw a significant step forward: the Council (composed of EU Member States&amp;rsquo; justice ministers) agreed on its stance regarding the proposal&amp;rsquo;s application outside the EU. This agreement, though partial, provides valuable insight into the negotiation&amp;rsquo;s trajectory.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item></channel></rss>