<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Annulment Actions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/annulment-actions/</link><description>Recent content in Annulment Actions on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/annulment-actions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions.</description></item><item><title>Determining the Impact of the Advocate General on the European Union Court of Justice: Is it Correlation or Causation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</guid><description>Carlos Arrebola and Ana Julia Mauricio (PhD students at the University of Cambridge)
It is widely claimed, especially in publications like The Guardian, that Advocate Generals significantly influence the European Court of Justice (ECJ)&amp;rsquo;s decisions. This belief is also prevalent among legal professionals specializing in EU law. However, there is limited empirical evidence to support this assumption. Our research investigates whether this perceived influence is accurate or merely a misconception.</description></item></channel></rss>