<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sql Reporting Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sql-reporting-services/</link><description>Recent content in Sql Reporting Services on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sql-reporting-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SQL Reporting Services, Dynamics GP, and Report Models can be frustrating.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-reporting-services-dynamics-gp-and-report-models-can-be-frustrating/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-reporting-services-dynamics-gp-and-report-models-can-be-frustrating/</guid><description>I really enjoy using SQL Reporting Services and Dynamics GP, especially the standard reports included with Dynamics GP. However, I feel a slight dread when asked to modify one, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even a developer!
Why the apprehension? I might be revealing my non-technical side, but reports based on report models make me particularly nervous. Sometimes, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky and the necessary field is already there, requiring just minor adjustments. However, a recent request wasn&amp;rsquo;t so straightforward.</description></item><item><title>Things that I adore about SQL Reporting Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/things-that-i-adore-about-sql-reporting-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/things-that-i-adore-about-sql-reporting-services/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;ve been rather quiet online lately, I can assure you it&amp;rsquo;s not due to a lack of things to share! My recent travels and the beautiful spring weather have lured me away from my computer.
However, SQL Reporting Services has been on my mind, particularly with recent client projects and an upcoming training session I&amp;rsquo;m delivering on using it with Microsoft Dynamics GP 10.0. Revisiting the material has reminded me of some useful features I tend to overlook.</description></item><item><title>One, two, SQL Report Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/one-two-sql-report-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 05:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/one-two-sql-report-security/</guid><description>Microsoft Dynamics GP offers a valuable feature: standard SQL Reporting Services (SSRS) reports. These reports are beneficial for several reasons: they can be accessed online by individuals without GP accounts, they can be easily exported to Excel or Word, users can modify them and retrieve extra information, they allow for custom reports using standard report models, and they offer subscription features that send reports directly to your inbox.
While I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of SSRS reports, this post will focus on their security aspects.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to use Report Builder 3.0 without SQL Reporting Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-use-report-builder-3-0-without-sql-reporting-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-use-report-builder-3-0-without-sql-reporting-services/</guid><description>Many people connect SQL Server 2008 R2 Report Builder (Report Builder 3.0) with SQL Server Reporting Services, which makes sense because using Report Builder with SQL Server Reporting Services allows you to share reports you create with others through the Report Manager website. However, many don&amp;rsquo;t realize that Report Builder 3.0 can function similarly to Crystal Reports, enabling you to create and run reports directly on your desktop without needing SQL Server Reporting Services.</description></item></channel></rss>