<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Texas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/texas/</link><description>Recent content in Texas on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/texas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service.</description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps).</description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport.</description></item><item><title>iWeb To Help Queenie The Elephant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iweb-to-help-queenie-the-elephant/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iweb-to-help-queenie-the-elephant/</guid><description>My wife and I are advocating for better living conditions for circus and zoo elephants. We believe animal sanctuaries like PAWS and The Elephant Sanctuary in Tennessee offer a more humane environment. Our focus is on Queenie, an elephant previously used for rides and performances at the Shrine Circus. Since losing her exhibitor&amp;rsquo;s license, she has been confined in Texas, often tethered to a tree.
We are urging the USDA to relocate Queenie to the spacious PAWS sanctuary in California.</description></item></channel></rss>