<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/communications/</link><description>Recent content in Communications on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Text Messaging To The Stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/</guid><description>Instead of texting Hollywood stars, how about sending a message to another planet? You can join a project called &amp;ldquo;Hello From Earth,&amp;rdquo; which sent text messages to Gliese 581d, a planet outside our solar system. Located 20 light years away in the constellation Libra, it will take about 20 years for your message to reach these potential extraterrestrials.
While we don&amp;rsquo;t know who or what might receive our messages, many people chose to send greetings of peace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Velox Networks claims that it can offer B2B phone services at a 95% lower cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</guid><description>Velox Networks, a new telecommunications company in Singapore, offers a voice over internet protocol (VoIP) and cloud-based private branch exchange (PBX) communications platform. They claim their service could save businesses up to 95% compared to traditional major telcos.
Currently, Singaporean businesses primarily use traditional PBXs for business-to-business communication. Velox aims to change this with its affordable, cloud-based PBX solution that surpasses the quality of free VoIP services, which often rely on less dependable consumer-grade technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center Telecom Service Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</guid><description>Contact centers manage various communication methods like phone calls, faxes, emails, and mail for businesses and organizations. These centers often use a lot of telecommunications technology, making them a significant expense for the company. A typical center might have analog phone lines, digital phone lines (T1 or DS3), SIP trunking for VoIP, dedicated internet, and private lines for specific needs.
Contact center managers need voice and data services that reduce costs without sacrificing performance or reliability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I'm Sorry, Dave. I Can't Let You Use That Channel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-sorry-dave-i-cant-let-you-use-that-channel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-sorry-dave-i-cant-let-you-use-that-channel/</guid><description>Despite the recent surge in spectrum auctions, leading to the perception that all available frequencies are allocated, opportunities for innovation remain. While unoccupied spectrum bands are scarce, similar to unclaimed land, existing communication channels often have unused capacity.
The challenge in maximizing spectrum utilization stems from the operational nature of transmitters and receivers. Simultaneous transmissions on the same channel create interference, rendering communication unintelligible. This interference is noticeable with walkie-talkies, overlapping radio stations, and even WiFi networks and wireless phones sharing the 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-sorry-dave-i-cant-let-you-use-that-channel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-sorry-dave-i-cant-let-you-use-that-channel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smart Grids Picking the Bones of BPL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</guid><description>Were you eagerly anticipating the day when your electrical outlets would provide both electricity and high-speed internet? That dream might not materialize. Broadband over Power Line (BPL), as a consumer internet option, appears to be fading. However, despite complaints from amateur radio operators about interference, BPL is not disappearing entirely. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s transforming into a utility-focused communication system, potentially offering a solution that benefits everyone.
The turning point for BPL may have been the recent news that Current Communications is ending its BPL service in Dallas, initially intended for 2 million homes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The introduction of InboxRank is brought to you by Unified Inbox</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-introduction-of-inboxrank-is-brought-to-you-by-unified-inbox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 16:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-introduction-of-inboxrank-is-brought-to-you-by-unified-inbox/</guid><description>Unified Inbox has introduced InboxRank, a smart sorting tool designed to simplify communication management across various platforms such as email, social media, SMS, and instant messaging.
Source: Unified Inbox.
InboxRank prioritizes information by analyzing various factors related to individual user&amp;rsquo;s inbox activity. It continuously learns and adapts to user preferences over time. Key factors considered include:
Communication frequency between the sender and receiver. The duration of their acquaintance (determined by the date of initial contact)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-introduction-of-inboxrank-is-brought-to-you-by-unified-inbox/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-introduction-of-inboxrank-is-brought-to-you-by-unified-inbox/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TW Telecom's Extensive Service Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</guid><description>tw telecom is a full-service communications provider with a privately owned, nationwide fiber optic network. They provide service in 75 major markets and over 8,800 commercial buildings. Their network spans more than 26,000 route miles and features a 10 Gbps IP backbone. They offer a wide array of services, from affordable T1 lines to high-speed Carrier Ethernet services ranging from 2 Mbps to 10 Gbps.
You might recognize the name tw telecom from its previous iterations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Helping Your Business Achieve Hyperconnectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It took a whole generation to connect the entire world to the internet. Now, get ready for an even bigger change: we&amp;rsquo;re moving towards hyperconnectivity, and it&amp;rsquo;s happening fast.
Everything, Everywhere, All at Once
Hyperconnectivity means that anything and anyone who can be connected will be connected all the time. We&amp;rsquo;ve already shifted from logging in to having always-on internet for our computers and phones. The next step is to let our devices communicate with each other without us...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verizon enhances e-business capabilities with increased support for private IP services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</guid><description>Verizon Communications is expanding its Private IP services network, offering businesses a secure way to deliver e-business applications and conduct business-to-business e-commerce. The expansion includes 10 additional countries across the Middle East, Africa, and Asia-Pacific regions.
Verizon business and wholesale customers in the Middle East and Asia Pacific now have expanded access to Private IP Multiprotocol Private Label Switching (MPLS) services in Bangladesh, Cambodia, Laos, Nepal, Iraq, Lebanon, and Yemen. Chennai, India, gains an additional location, offering customers enhanced network resiliency and reach through increased access to MPLS services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>