<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HSDPA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hsdpa/</link><description>Recent content in HSDPA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hsdpa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G1 Google Android Phone Gets Vocal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</guid><description>Choosing your next smartphone can be tough. Touchscreen phones like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone, the BlackBerry Bold, and Samsung Delve are appealing, but some prefer a physical QWERTY keyboard. The BlackBerry Pearl&amp;rsquo;s trackball navigation is another option. Connectivity matters too, with 3G being desirable but not always accessible. WiFi capability for fast web browsing is also important.
The HTC-built G1 for T-Mobile might be the solution if you want it all. This &amp;ldquo;Android Phone,&amp;rdquo; marking Google&amp;rsquo;s entry into mobile wireless, operates on T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s network, offering quad-band service and various data features.</description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP).</description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T HSUPA Aircards Have the Edge Over EDGE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</guid><description>Major wireless carriers, including AT&amp;amp;T, are heavily invested in upgrading their cellular data capabilities to meet the increasing demand for broadband internet access. This demand stems from the desire for constant connectivity, enabling activities like web browsing and mobile video streaming. AT&amp;amp;T is eager to capitalize on this demand and provide the desired connectivity.
Those accustomed to traditional wired broadband connections and basic cell phones may not fully grasp the advancements in mobile broadband technology.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry's Bold Move to HSDPA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</guid><description>BlackBerry, the company known for its wireless devices, is launching a new model called &amp;ldquo;Bold&amp;rdquo; with enhanced features like a sharper display, increased storage, a faster processor, and a 2-megapixel camera. However, the most significant advancement lies in its connectivity. The Bold surpasses standard EDGE data services by incorporating tri-band HSDPA and Wi-Fi, catering to the growing demand for desktop-like web browsing and video streaming among professionals.
Adding to the excitement, rumors are circulating about Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone selling out in anticipation of a new model featuring HSDPA technology.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile 3G Aircard For PC and Mac</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</guid><description>Want to connect your laptop to T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s 3G network and get free access to their HotSpots? The T-Mobile webConnect USB Laptop Stick can make that happen.
This device is a wireless modem with a USB connector that plugs into your PC or Mac. PCs require Windows XP or Vista, while Macs need OS X 10.3.9 or higher.
This aircard provides internet access virtually anywhere in the U.S. with T-Mobile cellular coverage.</description></item><item><title>HTC Aria Social Networking Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to stay connected, forget dogs – get FriendStream! This service lets you interact with friends through Facebook, Twitter, and Flickr, all from the HTC Aria, a cutting-edge Android smartphone.
The Aria boasts a sleek, seamless design crafted from a single piece of black aluminum. It&amp;rsquo;s compact enough for your pocket yet powerful enough for work and play. Its sizable 3.2-inch touchscreen features pinch-to-zoom functionality, automatically adjusting text size for comfortable website browsing.</description></item></channel></rss>