<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Entry Ban on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entry-ban/</link><description>Recent content in Entry Ban on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entry-ban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to deport and prohibit unemployed EU citizens from returning?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Germany&amp;rsquo;s recent exploration of expelling unemployed EU citizens has sparked interest among critics of EU free movement in the UK. As this topic gains traction, it&amp;rsquo;s timely to clarify the circumstances under which EU citizens can be expelled.
While the EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive empowers Member States to expel citizens for reasons related to public policy, security, or health, it explicitly prohibits using these grounds for economic reasons. Consequently, the rules for expelling unemployed EU citizens lie elsewhere within the Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Following the Dano ruling, under what circumstances can unemployed EU citizens be deported?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Dano case focused on benefit applications, not deportation. Therefore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly affect deportation. However, due to the Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the EU citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive, it might indirectly impact deportation.
Earlier this year, I published a blog post about when unemployment could justify deporting or banning EU citizens. This post expands on that analysis, considering the Dano judgment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The decision in Celaj by the CJEU: Implications of criminal penalties, entry bans, and the Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</guid><description>By Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a decision on October 1, 2015, in the case of Skerdjan Celaj (C-290/14) that once again addressed the relationship between immigration and criminal law. Specifically, the court examined whether national criminal penalties for unlawful migration align with the EU Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Court of Justice has made a ruling on the Schengen Conundrum, which involves a non-EU citizen who has been ordered to leave one Member State but holds a valid residence permit in another Member State.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</guid><description>Professors Elspeth Guild, Queen Mary University of London and Kingsley Napley, and Steve Peers, University of Essex
This article examines a case presented to the Court of Justice concerning the situation of a non-EU citizen residing in one Member State while facing potential expulsion by another.
Background
This issue presents legal complexities due to the involvement of two separate EU law sources. Article 25 of the Schengen Convention, amended in 2010, dictates that a Member State considering issuing a residence permit must first check the Schengen Information System (SIS) for any entry bans (alerts) on the individual...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmonisation of criminal law and foreign policy sanctions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post builds on and updates research for the 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law(OUP, 2023)
In late 2023, EU Member States and the European Parliament reached an agreement on a Directive designed to standardize criminal law related to violations of EU foreign policy sanctions. (Update: The Directive was formally adopted in April 2024 and subsequently published in the EU Official Journal)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Imprison them: the suggestion to revise the EU's Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, established to manage irregular migration by non-EU citizens, mandates that Member States issue return decisions to unauthorized individuals and enforce their removal. While the Directive allows for voluntary departure periods, it also outlines rules for detention and entry bans. Initially considered lenient by migrant support groups, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has since interpreted the Directive more broadly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>