<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 95/46 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-95/46/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 95/46 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-95/46/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies.</description></item><item><title>The extent of the 'household exception' to EU data protection law: Is it like Big Brother's Little Brother?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, co-author of &amp;ldquo;EU Law&amp;rdquo; by Steiner and Woods, examines a case about data protection and CCTV use.
Introduction
The Czech Supreme Administrative Court referred a question to the Court of Justice regarding the &amp;ldquo;household activity&amp;rdquo; exception in the EU Data Protection Directive. This case, Ryneš, involved CCTV footage capturing images beyond the operator&amp;rsquo;s property, raising questions about the exception&amp;rsquo;s scope, especially since the Directive states data processing must be &amp;ldquo;exclusively&amp;rdquo; for personal and household purposes.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in C-582/14 Breyer establishes IP addresses as personal data.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The opinions presented are solely those of the author and should not be interpreted as representing the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s official stance.
Background
The Breyer case saw the German Supreme Court (Bundesgerichtshof) request clarification from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on whether dynamic IP addresses constitute personal data under the EU Data Protection Directive and to what extent their storage and processing is permissible for maintaining website functionality.</description></item><item><title>Do national data retention laws fall under the jurisdiction of the Charter?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
After the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidated the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive, a crucial question emerged: do those same rules affect national data retention laws? This post will explain why that&amp;rsquo;s the case.
We begin with Article 51 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights. It states that the Charter applies to EU institutions and bodies, but to Member States &amp;lsquo;only&amp;rsquo; when &amp;lsquo;implementing&amp;rsquo; EU law.</description></item><item><title>Is EU data protection law violated by Facebook and the USA? The CJEU hearing in Schrems.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</guid><description>Simon McGarr, a solicitor at McGarr Solicitors, provides an overview of the Schrems v Data Protection Commissioner case heard by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The case revolves around Austrian law student Max Schrems&amp;rsquo; legal challenge concerning the transfer of his personal data from Facebook to the United States. Schrems argues that such transfers violate his data privacy rights due to the risk of mass surveillance under US law.</description></item><item><title>Has workplace privacy become obsolete? Thoughts on the Barbulescu ruling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The question of when employers can access employee emails, texts, or internet usage is crucial for both parties involved. A recent judgment in the case of Barbulescu v Romania tackled this issue, but unfortunately, misleading headlines like &amp;ldquo;EU court allows employers to read all employee e-mails&amp;rdquo; have emerged. This is inaccurate for two reasons: the ruling originates from the European Court of Human Rights, not an EU court, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant employers unrestricted access to employee emails.</description></item><item><title>The impact of Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein v. Wirtschaftsakademie Schleswig-Holstein GmbH on Facebook fan pages and EU data protection regulations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
Case Summary
The Wirtschaftsakademie, a business using a Facebook fanpage, was ordered by the Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein (ULD), a German data protection authority, to deactivate their page. The ULD argued that the page failed to warn visitors about potential data collection by Facebook through cookies.
This case highlights the benefits and data implications associated with Facebook fanpages. Page administrators benefit from free, anonymous user statistics through &amp;ldquo;Facebook Insights,&amp;rdquo; while Facebook gathers data for targeted advertising.</description></item><item><title>Returning to the past: Revisiting fundamental data protection principles in the proposed Data Protection Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-to-the-past-revisiting-fundamental-data-protection-principles-in-the-proposed-data-protection-regulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:27:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-to-the-past-revisiting-fundamental-data-protection-principles-in-the-proposed-data-protection-regulation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2015 is not living up to the futuristic vision presented in the Back to the Future films, particularly with the absence of hoverboards (drones are a disappointing alternative). Instead of establishing a data protection framework suitable for 2015, the Council seems poised to agree on maintaining the core legal principles from 1995 – which are outdated in the context of technology law.
Background
Negotiations regarding the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed General Data Protection Regulation appear to be nearing their final stages within the Council.</description></item><item><title>Is Europe v Facebook the start of the end for NSA surveillance of EU citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>The &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; Case: Challenging US Data Surveillance in Europe Since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about the NSA&amp;rsquo;s extensive spying activities, concerns have grown about the effectiveness of US data protection, particularly for EU citizens who benefit from stronger protections under the Data Protection Directive. One concern is the NSA&amp;rsquo;s ability to access communications processed by US-based social media companies like Facebook.
The Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s recent decision to refer questions in the &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; case to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) could potentially lead to the end of NSA access to EU citizens&amp;rsquo; data.</description></item><item><title>Regardless of the CJEU's decision, data retention could potentially continue to exist under national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
A central question regarding internet privacy is whether governments should be allowed to store data about everyone&amp;rsquo;s online and phone activities in the name of fighting terrorism and serious crime. This issue, known as &amp;ldquo;data retention,&amp;rdquo; raises crucial questions about balancing privacy and security, both nationally and within the European Union. Initially, the EU&amp;rsquo;s electronic privacy (e-Privacy) Directive offered member states the choice to implement data retention rules, deviating from the usual rule of communication confidentiality outlined in the directive.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU affirms that data protection authorities are independent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent judgment on data protection, while not as impactful as a prior ruling, is still significant. In Commission v Hungary, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) expanded on earlier decisions in Commission v Germany and Commission v Austria concerning the independent operation of data protection authorities. The judgment&amp;rsquo;s implications, however, reach beyond this specific area.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive mandates that data protection authorities be established to uphold the Directive&amp;rsquo;s regulations, in addition to individual legal action.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item><item><title>Rights for data protection and administrative procedures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the cases of YS and M and S clarified data protection rights for asylum-seekers. This judgment could also have wider implications for accessing documents in administrative procedures.
Two asylum-seekers in the Netherlands wanted to see file notes related to their cases. Instead of relying on the EU’s asylum procedures Directive, which grants access to reasons for negative decisions and interview reports but not all documents, they invoked the data protection Directive.</description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002.</description></item></channel></rss>