<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EVDO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/evdo/</link><description>Recent content in EVDO on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/evdo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cell Phone Plans With Aircards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</guid><description>Wireless modem aircards liberate you from the constraints of WiFi hotspots, transforming your laptop into a truly mobile computer. But how do they work, and what kind of service plans are necessary?
Essentially, an aircard functions as a specialized two-way radio, transmitting and receiving digital computer data instead of voice calls.
While they might resemble them, aircards don&amp;rsquo;t operate on cell phone networks. Currently, the majority adhere to either EVDO (Sprint and Verizon Wireless) or EDGE and HSPA (AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile) standards for cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>Will WiMAX Become WiMedium?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</guid><description>WiMAX, a wireless broadband standard, was envisioned as the key to 4G mobile networks and roaming. However, other technologies are catching up and might become the dominant force in 4G.
WiMAX aimed to broaden WiFi&amp;rsquo;s reach from a few hundred feet to many miles, allowing mobile devices to seamlessly switch between towers for continuous connectivity, similar to cell phone networks. It promised significantly faster speeds compared to existing cellular broadband, suitable for indoor and outdoor use.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part I</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-i/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 15:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-i/</guid><description>The recent collapse of the AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile merger, while seemingly a win for consumers against a potential monopoly, wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly about market control. Even if the merger succeeded, Verizon and Sprint would still offer competition. The real issue was bandwidth.
The evidence is clear: immediately after the deal failed, AT&amp;amp;T purchased $1.9 billion in spectrum from Qualcomm with FCC approval, while Verizon, after acquiring $3.6 billion worth of spectrum from Comcast and Time Warner Cable, also bought $315 million of spectrum from Cox.</description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>An Android Phone to Devour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</guid><description>Interested in getting a Google Android smartphone? The Motorola DEVOUR Silver might be the one for you. This Android 1.6 smartphone features a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and a 3.1-inch touchscreen, all within a sleek silver design.
The DEVOUR uses MOTOBLUR, a service that seamlessly syncs your messages, status updates, and contacts directly to your customizable home screens. This eliminates the need to log in or open individual apps, giving you instant access to your information.</description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2.</description></item><item><title>I'm Not Paying For That Aircard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 07:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</guid><description>Fast and dependable office internet connections are great when you&amp;rsquo;re stationary, but mobile work demands solutions like WiFi hotspots or cellular broadband. While these options are suitable, not all laptops are equipped for cellular broadband.
Aircards, sometimes called wireless modems, bridge this gap. Similar to WiFi access cards, these devices allow laptops to connect to cellular broadband networks. In the past, laptops primarily used built-in modems, requiring separate cards for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>Taking a Read on the Amazon Kindle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taking-a-read-on-the-amazon-kindle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 17:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taking-a-read-on-the-amazon-kindle/</guid><description>Despite predictions that computers would lead to the disappearance of paper, the opposite has occurred. The demand for paper has increased significantly due to printers, and traditional media like newspapers and books remain popular. This raises the question: why is paper so persistent in the digital age?
Several factors contribute to this. E-books lack the tactile experience of physical books and the convenience of annotating paper copies. Additionally, reading on backlit screens can cause eye strain, unlike paper.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Cell phones today are capable of much more than just voice calls. The mobile networks have evolved to carry both voice and data, offering wireless broadband internet access that rivals DSL and cable connections.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t explored mobile internet recently, you might be surprised by its speed and availability. Currently, two competing systems are widely available, with two even faster networks in their early stages.
AT&amp;amp;T promotes its HSDPA and EDGE networks, notably featuring the Apple iPhone.</description></item></channel></rss>