<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e1/</link><description>Recent content in E1 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Border Private Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</guid><description>When considering private line services for business locations, we often focus on domestic connections. However, international business operations necessitate cross-border line services, which not all carriers provide.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/international/PrivateLines/international_private_lines.php)
International connectivity involves navigating varying regulations, practices, and technical requirements. For example, the US and Europe employ slightly different companding standards for digitized phone calls. While both use the G.711 CODEC for PCM, the US and others utilize Mu-law compression, while Europe and most of the world use A-law.</description></item></channel></rss>