<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>World Bank on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/world-bank/</link><description>Recent content in World Bank on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/world-bank/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The World Bank has released its 2017 forecast for the Thai economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</guid><description>The 2016 Thailand Economic Monitor, published today by the World Bank, projects Thailand&amp;rsquo;s economic growth to reach 3.1% in 2016 and 3.2% in 2017, surpassing the previous year&amp;rsquo;s 2.8%.
The report identifies private consumption and public investments, such as rail infrastructure projects, as primary growth drivers. Tourism has also performed well in 2016, with tourist arrivals, particularly from China, rising by 13.1% in the third quarter. A temporary slowdown and economic inactivity following the passing of HM King Bhumibol Adulyadej in October are anticipated to be partially counterbalanced by year-end holiday tax incentives for shopping and domestic tourism.</description></item><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training.</description></item><item><title>The Philippines' economic outlook has improved according to the World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</guid><description>The World Bank has improved its economic forecast for the Philippines from 2016 to 2018.
They now predict the Philippine economy will grow by 6.8% in 2016, up from their previous prediction of 6.4% made in October (World Bank Philippines Economic Update October 2016). This adjustment is based on stronger than expected growth in the third quarter of 2016, fueled by increased investment and private consumption. This follows robust economic performance in the first half of 2016, driven by the government’s pre-election spending.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank ranks the UAE in the top 10 for enhancing the business environment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-ranks-the-uae-in-the-top-10-for-enhancing-the-business-environment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:35:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-ranks-the-uae-in-the-top-10-for-enhancing-the-business-environment/</guid><description>A new World Bank Group study reveals that local businesses in the Middle East have faced difficulties over the past year. While some economies, such as the UAE—one of the top 10 global improvers—enhanced their business environments, the Middle East and North Africa region saw relatively slow regulatory reform.
According to Doing Business 2015: Going Beyond Efficiency, 55% of economies in the region implemented business regulatory reforms. This is comparable to 60% in East Asia and the Pacific but indicates that the reforms were limited in scope.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Bhutan made significant improvements to its business climate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</guid><description>Bhutan has significantly improved its business environment, earning a global ranking of 71st out of 189 countries in the World Bank Group&amp;rsquo;s annual ease of doing business assessment. This achievement places Bhutan at the top spot within the South Asia Region.
The Doing Business 2016: Measuring Regulatory Quality and Efficiency report highlights two key reforms implemented by Bhutan. First, obtaining an electricity connection is now faster, taking only 61 days compared to 93 days five years ago.</description></item><item><title>South Asia has the potential to become the leading export region in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</guid><description>By implementing policies that enhance productivity, South Asia could substantially increase its global market share in electronics, motor vehicles, and apparel by 2030, according to a new World Bank report titled &amp;ldquo;South Asia’s Turn: Policies to Boost Competitiveness and Create the Next Export Powerhouse.&amp;rdquo; The report emphasizes that improving firm productivity is crucial for boosting competitiveness in Pakistan and the rest of South Asia. While acknowledging the region&amp;rsquo;s investment climate challenges, the report focuses on less-explored factors like the impact of cities and clusters, global value chains, and firms&amp;rsquo; capacity for innovation and efficient resource utilization.</description></item></channel></rss>