<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advertisement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advertisement/</link><description>Recent content in Advertisement on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advertisement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The more specific the mobile advertisement, the higher its earnings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</guid><description>Smaato, a mobile advertising company, has observed that the most successful advertising categories in China during the first quarter of the year were shopping, e-commerce, communication, and technology. These categories achieved high eCPMs (effective cost per mille), reaching up to US$0.30.
When analyzing mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad expenditures in China during the same period, entertainment (30%) and games (22%) were the top two categories.
Ajitpal Pannu, Smaato&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, noted that both monetization and brand spending increased when essential parameters were shared globally with advertising partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the second quarter of 2014, China's RTB ad spending increased by 616% compared to the previous quarter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</guid><description>Smaato, a company specializing in mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad exchange (SMX) and supply side platform (SSP), has reported significant growth in mobile RTB in its Q2 2014 Global Mobile RTB Insights Report.
Source: The Smaato RTB Insights Report for Q2 2014. RTB spending in the APAC region for the top five countries.
Smaato&amp;rsquo;s findings show a 69% increase in RTB spending in the second quarter of 2014 compared to the first quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Facebook introduces a user-friendly, streamlined video advertising format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</guid><description>Over one-third of mobile internet users in Saudi Arabia are receptive to video advertisements, exceeding the global average of 22%.
Facebook is introducing &amp;ldquo;Slideshow,&amp;rdquo; a new, user-friendly video ad format designed to increase reach across various devices and connection speeds.
In a blog post announcing Slideshow, Facebook highlights a recent report indicating that people in regions like the Philippines, where connectivity can be slow, costly, or both, and where feature phones are common, are even more receptive to video ads...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>