<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>External Trade on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-trade/</link><description>Recent content in External Trade on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-trade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk.</description></item><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Hard Brexit? Transforming Britain's £24 billion worth of unicorns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The pro-Brexit group &amp;ldquo;Change Britain&amp;rdquo; recently released a statement claiming significant financial benefits for the UK following a &amp;ldquo;hard Brexit,&amp;rdquo; where the UK leaves both the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market and customs union. This claim was widely circulated in the media despite being fundamentally flawed.
While the report attempts to offer a thorough analysis, it highlights the poor quality of the overall Brexit debate. The report&amp;rsquo;s claim of a £24 billion benefit originates from three key areas: ending contributions to the EU budget, potential savings from reduced regulation, and the anticipated benefits of new trade agreements.</description></item><item><title>Continuing the saga of EU/Armenia relations with Case C-180/20 Commission v Council (CEPA) and the 'centre of gravity' test in the CFSP.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</guid><description>Narine Ghazaryan, Assistant Professor in EU and International Law, Radboud University Nijmegen
Photo credit: Jesper Ahlin Marceta via Wikicommons
Introduction
The recent ruling in Case C-180/20 (the CEPA case) marks a new chapter in the ongoing debate about the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) and its boundaries. This case saw the Commission challenge the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to deviate from a proposed Council Decision concerning the EU-Armenian Comprehensive and Enhanced Partnership Agreement (CEPA).</description></item><item><title>Background information for next week's hearing on the scope of EU external trade policy: Opinion 2/15</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</guid><description>Dr Andrés Delgado Casteleiro
Senior Research Fellow, Max Planck Institute Luxembourg for International, European and Regulatory Procedural Law
Introduction
On September 13th and 14th, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) convened a full court hearing to discuss Opinion 2/15. This opinion focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to establish a new Free Trade Agreement (FTA) with Singapore. This blog post will provide a concise summary of the key issues likely to arise during these hearings.</description></item><item><title>The relationship between the EU and Morocco and the issue of the Western Sahara: the European Court of Justice and the principles of international law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</guid><description>Markus W. Gehring: University Lecturer, University of Cambridge; J.S.D. (Yale), LL.M. (Yale), Dr jur. (Hamburg), MA (Cantab); Deputy Director, Economic Law at CIGI
On December 21, 2016, the Court of Justice issued its appeals decision in the case of Council v. Front Polisario. This Grand Chamber judgment, reached under an expedited procedure, overturned the prior decision made by the EU General Court in Front Polisario v Council roughly a year before.</description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI.</description></item><item><title>The EU's upcoming trade policy is beginning to form with the release of the Opinion on the EU/Singapore FTA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s authority regarding trade agreements has been debated for years in the European Court of Justice (ECJ), as it significantly affects the balance of power between the EU and its Member States concerning international economic policies. Treaty revisions, especially the Treaty of Lisbon, have altered these rules, making this issue even more important due to recent controversies surrounding EU trade negotiations (notably with Canada and the USA) and the UK-EU trade talks post-Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join.</description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter.</description></item></channel></rss>