<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4G Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g-wireless/</link><description>Recent content in 4G Wireless on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g-wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is 4G and Why Do You Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re constantly bombarded with ads for 3G phones and wireless aircards, and now 4G is emerging. But what does this new technology mean and why should you care?
2G, 3G, 4G—these &amp;ldquo;Gs&amp;rdquo; represent different generations of wireless broadband. This technology evolves so rapidly that various generations often coexist in the same region. This is intentional. If you&amp;rsquo;re in an area with weak 3G coverage, your device automatically connects to slower 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC ThunderBolt Screams On LTE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:58:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</guid><description>The HTC ThunderBolt, a smartphone with lightning-fast speed, embodies the next generation of mobile connectivity. It operates on Verizon&amp;rsquo;s LTE network with exceptional performance.
Not long ago, having a smartphone with cutting-edge 3G broadband was a status symbol. Technology evolves rapidly, and the speed that impressed us a few years ago seems archaic compared to today&amp;rsquo;s standards.
While 3G seemed remarkably fast at the time, its approximate speed of 1 Mbps pales in comparison to 4G&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telexplainer Expectations For 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</guid><description>As we begin a promising new year for business and technology, let&amp;rsquo;s explore some key trends for 2011 and how to leverage them.
Bandwidth demands will continue to escalate this year, as they do annually. The economic recovery will likely generate increased internet traffic as more individuals return to work. Expect bandwidth demand to surge proportionally with employment, if not more. During the recession, businesses learned to enhance individual productivity by investing in technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Insurance Keeps You in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 05:32:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Constant connectivity has its perks for individuals and businesses, but technology isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof. A broadband outage can be incredibly isolating. Fortunately, there are safeguards against such situations.
Consumers can utilize their mobile data as a backup. Modern smartphones can act as wireless hotspots, allowing devices like computers and printers to connect. While speed and data limits might be concerns, it provides a temporary solution. Another option is using public Wi-Fi hotspots, though availability might be an issue during widespread outages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>