<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plan/</link><description>Recent content in Plan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel will be providing the option to share up to 50GB of mobile data at the PC Show 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</guid><description>Singtel is increasing its mobile data offerings with the launch of &amp;ldquo;DataMore,&amp;rdquo; a new plan featuring larger data bundles. This launch comes less than a month after Circles.Life entered the market with a focus on data options. DataMore is designed for users who need a lot of data and is shareable with multiple users, making it perfect for families.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Mobile Marketing, highlights that this plan caters to customer demand for larger data packages at affordable prices.</description></item><item><title>Google Drive prices have been significantly reduced by Google</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 23:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</guid><description>A blog post published on March 13 revealed that Google significantly reduced prices for cloud storage. The monthly fees have been adjusted to US$1.99 for 100GB (previously US$4.99), US$9.99 for 1TB (previously US$49.99), and US$99.99 for 10TB, with the option to purchase additional terabytes as required.
A 15 GB plan remains free of charge. This storage space can be utilized across Drive, Gmail, and Google+ Photos.
Source: Google
Existing paying users will be automatically transitioned to the corresponding updated plan without incurring additional costs.</description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill.</description></item><item><title>du offers corporate mobile plans for SMEs in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Du offers five corporate mobile plans designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These plans include data and free calls to colleagues within the business.
Ranging from AED 50 to AED 450 per month, the plans provide data, national calling minutes, national text messages, and free calls to numbers within a designated &amp;lsquo;business calling circle&amp;rsquo;. Three of the plans also include free international minutes and texts. Businesses can purchase additional &amp;lsquo;packs&amp;rsquo; to add more minutes, texts, or members to their calling circle.</description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has launched new mobile plans that include HBO content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</guid><description>Singtel has launched three innovative &amp;ldquo;XO&amp;rdquo; postpaid mobile plans, the first to offer premium entertainment as part of the package.
These new XO plans are designed to provide both generous data allowances and significant handset discounts, offering customers the best of both worlds. Additionally, XO plans include an HBO GO subscription, giving customers access to top-tier video entertainment.
The XO 78 Plan provides customers with 30 GB of data, 300 minutes of talk time, 300 SMS messages, and a 24-month HBO GO subscription for S$78 per month.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides triple the mobile data for a low price, along with Wi-Fi calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</guid><description>Singtel launched a new mobile data add-on called DataX3 at their iPhone 7 event held at Marina Bay Sands Convention Centre. For S$9.90 per month, DataX3 allows customers to triple their mobile data limit. This add-on is available to Singtel Combo Plan customers (Combo 2 and above). It follows the successful launch of the DataX2 add-on earlier this year.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, highlighted the importance of affordable mobile data for communication, shopping, banking, and entertainment in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>