<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cracked on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cracked/</link><description>Recent content in Cracked on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cracked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Brand New Hood Fatally Damaged Due to Bent Hood Hinges! - Straightening Hinges Out and Installation of Another Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) for a Florida-based client and installed a new dust cover purchased from beoparts-shop in Denmark. These dust covers are remarkable replicas, made with the same die-cast process as the originals, resulting in a seamless finish.
However, a problem arose with this particular dust cover. When closing it, there was slight friction on the hinge approximately halfway through its movement. While I initially dismissed it as an insignificant tolerance issue common in older manufacturing, the issue escalated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of a Wobbly Carriage Pulley with a New Aluminum Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</guid><description>As I was finishing the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5523), I noticed a concerning noise coming from the carriage when it moved quickly, especially when returning to its starting position. This led me to believe there was an issue with the carriage pulley. Upon inspection, I discovered that the pulley was cracked, which is a common problem with this model. It seems the original plastic can&amp;rsquo;t handle the stress from the setscrew over time and eventually cracks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Aluminum Pulley for the Carriage Servo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</guid><description>Recently, I completed the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable. The final piece I needed was a new aluminum pulley for the carriage servo. The original pulley was cracked and causing unwanted noise and vibration, particularly during rapid carriage movements like starting and stopping. This was not acceptable for a quality turntable.
A standard replacement pulley wasn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with this early 5501 model. These early models use a unique end groove detection system requiring a pulley with four holes that function as an optical chopper to monitor the carriage speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Restoration of the Carriage Position Sensor - Development of a New Beolover Part</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) being restored had a broken carriage position sensor photo resistor housing with damaged mounting tabs. After removing the housing and extracting the photo resistor, a replacement housing was designed and 3D printed.
The new housing consists of two parts. The photo resistor is placed on the insert part after straightening its leads. The main housing is then slid over the insert, sandwiching the photo resistor. This assembly is then inserted into the existing mounting cutouts and soldered to the PCB...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Aluminum Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all spring terminals in the switches, this Beogram 4000 received another upgrade: a replacement for the old, unstable plastic carriage pulley, now made from aluminum. The original pulley is shown below:
And here it is equipped with one of Nick&amp;rsquo;s well-crafted aluminum pulleys:
Contact me if you need a pulley for your Beogram; I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to connect you with Nick. These pulleys are compatible with the 4002 and 4004 models as well...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Arm, Replacement of the Damper Gasket and Re-Glueing of a Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 required a few final adjustments before it could be returned to its owner following a wiring sleeve replacement on the carriage harness and a fix for an intermittent solenoid.
During its initial restoration in 2020, I was unfamiliar with some common problems that these turntables develop. One such issue involves the damper gasket, which tends to harden over time. This hardening can lead to uneven arm lowering due to inconsistent airflow around the gasket...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Pulley, Hood Bumpers and Shipping Back to Italy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 14:02:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</guid><description>A Beolover always aims for perfection, and I realized my restoration of the Beogram 4000 wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite finished. Working on a Beogram 8000 reminded me of the importance of rubber hood bumpers for a smooth, quiet closing action. I discovered these bumpers were missing on the Beogram 4000, leaving only remnants of degraded rubber.
To fix this, I carefully removed the old rubber with a small drill bit by hand, avoiding any damage to the plexiglass...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 3000 (5228): Restoration of the Plexiglass Hood - Repair of a Cracked Hinge and Installation of 3D Printed Mounting Brackets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 3000 turntable with a damaged plexiglass dust cover. The plastic mounting brackets that held the cover were broken, and one of the plexiglass hinges was also broken.
and one of the plexiglass hinges was broken off:
To address these issues, I created a repair kit. This kit includes 3D-printed replacement mounting brackets, a specialized tool for reinstalling the spring tensioning block, and laser-cut plexiglass pieces for fixing the broken hinge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Lever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 11:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</guid><description>A customer asked for help with a broken part, a solenoid lever, from their Beogram 4002 Type 5503 turntable. The AC-powered versions of this model use a mechanical switch to control the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s current after the arm lowers. To accomplish this, the solenoid arm has a tab that depresses the switch once the arm is down. Some later AC versions use a plastic extension riveted to the lever to achieve this, a design change I observed to be problematic in my experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>