<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NAS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nas/</link><description>Recent content in NAS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HPE has reduced the entry threshold for its storage portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</guid><description>Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) recently improved its entry storage products to help budget-conscious customers leverage their data and speed up applications. These new HPE MSA Storage options deliver the most budget-friendly dual-controller hybrid flash array from a major vendor while the new HPE StoreEasy 1650 Expanded makes storing large amounts of information more economical.
Being able to quickly and effectively use information is crucial for success. &amp;ldquo;Agility and speed are critical for staying competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s economy, no matter the business size,&amp;rdquo; said Manish Goel, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Storage at HPE.</description></item><item><title>Iomega Zips Into Network Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</guid><description>Do you recall the Zip drive? When floppy disks were the standard for backups, Zip drives offered a remarkable hundredfold increase in capacity using removable cartridges. While hard drives now boast hundreds of gigabytes and beyond, leaving floppies and even Zip disks in the past, Iomega, the company behind the Zip drive, has continued to innovate. Their product line has expanded beyond desktops and into the server room.
Iomega, now a part of EMC, a Fortune 500 company specializing in enterprise storage solutions, still caters to individuals and small offices.</description></item></channel></rss>