<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Label Switching on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/label-switching/</link><description>Recent content in Label Switching on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/label-switching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why International MPLS Connections Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 14:08:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple branches, even those with only two, are realizing the benefits of MPLS network services for domestic and global connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS offers, particularly for international connections, and why it&amp;rsquo;s a practical solution even for single-link setups.
Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS) is a network technology designed to carry data for numerous users while maintaining security, service quality, and crucial network attributes such as bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>