<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Teabox on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/teabox/</link><description>Recent content in Teabox on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 01:27:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/teabox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brewing the ideal cup of coffee at work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brewing-the-ideal-cup-of-coffee-at-work/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 01:27:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brewing-the-ideal-cup-of-coffee-at-work/</guid><description>Teabox, an online retailer specializing in premium Indian teas, emphasizes the importance of specific brewing methods for different tea varieties.
&amp;ldquo;Water quality is paramount for tea, as it constitutes the majority of the beverage. Excessive boiling can deplete oxygen levels in water, hindering proper flavor infusion. Similarly, over-steeping can lead to flavor loss and excessive bitterness,&amp;rdquo; explains Kaushal Dugar, CEO of Teabox.
The company provides a useful guide for brewing a perfect cup of tea:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brewing-the-ideal-cup-of-coffee-at-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brewing-the-ideal-cup-of-coffee-at-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Teabox shortens tea supply chain to deliver fresher teas to the market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:25:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/</guid><description>Kaushal Dugar, CEO of Teabox, which launched in 2012, comes from a family with over 70 years in the tea industry. He started the company to revolutionize the tea trade.
Source: Teabox. Dugar.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been passionate about entrepreneurship,&amp;rdquo; Dugar shared, noting that the tea industry, valued at US$90 billion, uses outdated practices. He pointed out that while India is a top tea producer, its tea isn&amp;rsquo;t as renowned as tea from Japan or China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Selecting the appropriate tea for the workplace break room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 16:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find pre-mixed tea sachets or teabags in office pantries. While these are convenient and widely available, Teabox, an online retailer specializing in premium Indian teas, suggests there might be downsides to these options.
Source: Teabox website.
Teabox CEO, Kaushal Dugar, explains that tea dust, a byproduct of tea production, lacks the full flavor, taste, and aroma of whole tea leaves. This tea dust is often what ends up in teabags, resulting in a less flavorful and potentially less nutritious cup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>