<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pakistan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pakistan/</link><description>Recent content in Pakistan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:37:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pakistan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IMF predicts a positive outcome for Pakistan's economic growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</guid><description>The IMF Executive Board finalized its regular economic assessment of Pakistan on June 14, 2017.
The IMF determined that Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic outlook is positive, with real GDP expected to reach 5.3% in FY2016/17 and rise to 6% in the medium term. This growth is attributed to increased investments from the China Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), greater energy availability, and structural reforms that support economic expansion. While inflation has gradually risen, the IMF team stated it remains manageable, and the financial sector is stable.</description></item><item><title>The IMF mission has stated that Pakistan's economic reform efforts must extend beyond the EFF program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</guid><description>An IMF team, led by Harald Finger, visited Dubai between July 26th and August 4th, 2016, to discuss the final review of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic program supported by a three-year IMF Extended Fund Facility (EFF). The team met with key officials, including Finance Minister Ishaq Dar and State Bank of Pakistan Governor Ashraf Wathra.
The mission concluded with a staff-level agreement on the completion of the twelfth and final review under the EFF, subject to approval by IMF management and the Executive Board.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents.</description></item><item><title>South Asia has the potential to become the leading export region in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</guid><description>By implementing policies that enhance productivity, South Asia could substantially increase its global market share in electronics, motor vehicles, and apparel by 2030, according to a new World Bank report titled &amp;ldquo;South Asia’s Turn: Policies to Boost Competitiveness and Create the Next Export Powerhouse.&amp;rdquo; The report emphasizes that improving firm productivity is crucial for boosting competitiveness in Pakistan and the rest of South Asia. While acknowledging the region&amp;rsquo;s investment climate challenges, the report focuses on less-explored factors like the impact of cities and clusters, global value chains, and firms&amp;rsquo; capacity for innovation and efficient resource utilization.</description></item><item><title>ZEE5 is attracting viewers from Pakistan and Bangladesh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 01:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</guid><description>Source: Zee5. Images for the #ShareTheLove campaign.
Following its initial launch in over 190 countries, the digital entertainment platform ZEE5 is setting its sights on Pakistan and Bangladesh.
The company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;#ShareTheLove&amp;rdquo; campaign highlights the cultural and entertainment commonalities between ZEE5 and these two nations. ZEE5 aims to foster a sense of shared enjoyment by providing a diverse content library that resonates with Pakistani and Bangladeshi audiences, featuring Hindi and Bengali original series like &amp;ldquo;Rangbaaz,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Kaali,&amp;rdquo; and the upcoming &amp;ldquo;Sharate Aaj,&amp;rdquo; original films such as &amp;ldquo;Aranyadeb&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Tigers,&amp;rdquo; and digital premieres of movies like &amp;ldquo;Namaste England&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Praktan.</description></item><item><title>ADIB introduces the Spice credit card specifically for Non-Resident Indians and Non-Resident Pakistanis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</guid><description>Source: ADIB. The new Spice Card offers a range of cashbacks if the owner hits a minimum spend.
Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) has introduced the Spice Card, a new product designed specifically for non-resident Indians (NRIs) and non-resident Pakistanis (NRPs) living in the UAE.
The ADIB Spice Card provides NRIs and NRPs with opportunities to save money through a variety of competitive offers and discounts. These include cashback rewards of 9% on dining, 7% on supermarket purchases, 4% on fuel, and 1% on utility bills.</description></item></channel></rss>