<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bahrain on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bahrain/</link><description>Recent content in Bahrain on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 04:13:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bahrain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gulf Air reveals its summer 2018 schedule</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air. Plane in Gulf Air livery.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has launched its Summer 2018 schedule, increasing both flight frequency and passenger capacity to popular destinations for the peak travel season between mid-June and mid-September 2018.
Flights to Amman, Jordan, will increase to three times daily, while flights to Beirut, Lebanon, will increase to twice daily. Istanbul, Turkey, a popular summer destination, will have 12 weekly flights during peak season, and flights to Baghdad, Iraq, will permanently increase to five times per week.</description></item><item><title>TAKAUD will be hosting its first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</guid><description>Source: _Middle East Pensions Conference _website.
With the support of the Central Bank of Bahrain, TAKAUD, a leading provider of savings, investment, and pension solutions in the MENA region, is gathering government officials and financial service leaders to discuss the development of robust pension plans for citizens and foreign workers across the region.
The first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference will occur in Bahrain on October 18, 2016. The conference aims to raise awareness and encourage action towards bringing Middle Eastern pension standards in line with developed countries.</description></item><item><title>Bahrain becomes a member of the Cruise Arabia Alliance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</guid><description>Bahrain has joined the Cruise Arabia Alliance, solidifying the organization&amp;rsquo;s presence in the region. Other members include Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Sharjah, Qatar, and Oman. The alliance promotes collaboration among its members to maintain high standards of service for cruise lines and their passengers.
This announcement took place at the Seatrade Middle East Cruise Forum in Doha, Qatar, hosted by the Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA). Alongside this news, Bahrain also shared that the 2015/2016 cruise season will include 68,000 passengers and 32 visits from major cruise lines.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents.</description></item><item><title>Investors demonstrate trust in the cryptocurrency investment platform CoinMENA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</guid><description>CoinMENA, a cryptocurrency exchange based in Bahrain, has successfully raised US$9.5 million in its initial seed funding round. Major investors included BECO Capital, Kenetic, Arab Bank Switzerland, and others.
Founded in early 2021 by Dina Saman, Talal Tabbaa, and Yazan Barghuthi, CoinMENA aimed to simplify and enhance the safety of cryptocurrency investments in the region. The platform is officially licensed by the Central Bank of Bahrain and has partnered with the Dubai World Trade Centre to establish a prominent blockchain and cryptocurrency hub in the UAE.</description></item></channel></rss>