<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Environmental Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environmental-law/</link><description>Recent content in Environmental Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environmental-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation.</description></item><item><title>ClientEarth: a significant milestone in the Court of Justice of the European Union's environmental law rulings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-a-significant-milestone-in-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-s-environmental-law-rulings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-a-significant-milestone-in-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-s-environmental-law-rulings/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther, Trainee, Research Department of the CJEU
Background
Yesterday, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on a case referred by the UK Supreme Court. This case involved the UK&amp;rsquo;s failure to request an extension to meet nitrogen oxide limits as outlined in EU law. The environmental NGO, ClientEarth, brought the case forward in the UK, arguing that the UK was violating Article 13 of Directive 2008/50/EC (the ‘Air Quality Directive’).</description></item><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options.</description></item><item><title>New discoveries in the "Mellifera" case shed light on access to environmental justice under the Aarhus Regulation, but the underlying issues remain unchanged.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</guid><description>Mario Pagano, PhD candidate in EU environmental law, European University Institute
Background
The Aarhus Convention is a crucial piece of international law concerning environmental democracy rights. Established in 1998, this UN Convention lays out three procedural rights directly connected to environmental protection: the right to environmental information, the right to participate in environmental decision-making, and the right to legal recourse on environmental issues (the three Aarhus &amp;ldquo;pillars&amp;rdquo;).
The Aarhus Convention Compliance Committee (ACCC), formed in Geneva in 2002, ensures that the legislation of the Convention&amp;rsquo;s Parties aligns with the Convention itself.</description></item><item><title>A missed chance to enhance access to justice in environmental issues: the CJEU's ruling on the applicability of the Aarhus Convention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</guid><description>**
**
Dr. Apolline J. C. Roger, Senior Teaching Fellow in EU environmental law, University of Edinburgh Law School.
The right to access justice is a crucial safeguard for environmental NGOs and citizens, allowing them to contest public authorities&amp;rsquo; decisions that impact the environment and public health. By joining the Aarhus Convention in 2005, the EU acknowledged this right as a pillar of good governance and a key element of the human right to a healthy environment.</description></item><item><title>The labeling of the European Union in the International Maritime Organization is more of a focus than the EU's actual competence.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</guid><description>Cathleen Berg, doctoral student, University of Bayreuth
Advocate General (‘AG’) Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s November 25, 2021, opinion regarding a legal challenge from the European Commission against the European Council (Case C-161/20) highlights the contrasting interests between the European Union (‘EU’) and its Member States. This disagreement centers around how they exercise their authority within the International Maritime Organization (‘IMO’), an organization where the EU currently holds neither membership nor observer status. If the Court of Justice sides with AG Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s analysis, this case could significantly impact how the EU interest is represented within IMO committees, potentially shifting power from the Commission to the Member States.</description></item><item><title>The Advocate General's Opinion in Grupa Azoty once again exposes a significant deficiency in EU judicial protection, but fails to address the issue.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-grupa-azoty-once-again-exposes-a-significant-deficiency-in-eu-judicial-protection-but-fails-to-address-the-issue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-grupa-azoty-once-again-exposes-a-significant-deficiency-in-eu-judicial-protection-but-fails-to-address-the-issue/</guid><description>Professor Geert van Calster, University of Leuven
Photo credit: Wojciech Antosz, via Wikimedia Commons
Executive summary: In early March, Advocate General Pikamäe issued an opinion in the case of Grupa Azoty S.A. et al v European Commission (Joined Cases C 73/22P and C 77/22 P). This case is an appeal concerning the ability to partially overturn the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2020 &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on certain State aid measures in the context of the system for greenhouse gas emission allowance trading post-2021.</description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period.</description></item><item><title>Is there a difference this time? The Commission's work programme for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently released its yearly plan, outlining a different approach than previous years. Beyond the typical policy revisions, this Commission aims to introduce fewer new EU initiatives and withdraw more pending proposals.
Is this approach truly different from past Commissions? Comparing this year&amp;rsquo;s plan to those of previous Commissions offers insights.
In 2005, the incoming Barroso Commission put forward 32 pages of proposals, without mentioning any withdrawals.</description></item><item><title>Brexit and the new Heathrow runway are interconnected.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-new-heathrow-runway-are-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 20:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-new-heathrow-runway-are-interconnected/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Zac Goldsmith, the Member of Parliament for Richmond Park, recently resigned, triggering a by-election. This decision stems from his opposition to the proposed Heathrow Airport runway expansion. Goldsmith, intending to run as an independent, aims to frame the by-election as a referendum on the runway. His opponents, particularly the Liberal Democrats, plan to broaden the conversation to include Brexit. However, Brexit and the Heathrow expansion are fundamentally intertwined.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of the Environment and Climate Provisions in the Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Introduction
The start of the new year marked a significant shift in the UK-EU relationship, ending the Brexit transition and ushering in the provisional Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). This post delves into the TCA&amp;rsquo;s environmental and climate change provisions, drawing on prior analyses of the TCA&amp;rsquo;s overview, social security provisions, human rights aspects, and dispute settlement mechanisms. (Updated as of April 28, 2021, to reflect the final TCA article numbering).</description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones.</description></item><item><title>How can legislation empower Europe? By phasing out fossil fuels and implementing the Sustainability Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 02:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</guid><description>Ewan McGaughey, Reader in Law, King’s College London
Photo credit: Geopolitical Intelligence Services, via Wikicommons
Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine has prompted initiatives like RePowerEU and similar UK programs, aiming to eliminate reliance on Russian fossil fuels. President Biden has even called for a complete end to fossil fuel use, arguing that dependence on any authoritarian regime for energy is no longer acceptable. This shift recognizes the need to transition to renewable energy sources rapidly, acknowledging everyone&amp;rsquo;s fundamental right to benefit from scientific advancements.</description></item><item><title>Enhancing democratic processes through citizen involvement in policy development: a comparative analysis of the EU, Germany, and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-democratic-processes-through-citizen-involvement-in-policy-development-a-comparative-analysis-of-the-eu-germany-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 08:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-democratic-processes-through-citizen-involvement-in-policy-development-a-comparative-analysis-of-the-eu-germany-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Susan Rose-Ackerman, a Henry R. Luce Professor of Law and Political Science, Emeritus, and Professorial Lecturer in Law at Yale University, and Lena Riemer, a Fox Fellow at Yale University and a Doctoral candidate at Freie Universität Berlin, explore the evolving landscape of public participation in executive regulatory processes.
While elections and referendums are fundamental to democratic participation, they possess inherent limitations in reflecting citizen preferences and addressing complex policy issues.</description></item><item><title>Implementing the European Green Deal and Making the EU Maritime Transport Sector "Fit for 55": Is Pain Necessary for Gain?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</guid><description>Killian O’Brien, DAAD Lecturer (Fachlektor), University College London
To achieve its European Green Deal objectives, the EU aims to cut greenhouse gas emissions by at least 55% of 1990 levels by 2030. As part of this goal, the European Commission introduced the “Fit for 55” legislative package on July 14, 2021. This collection of measures aims to rapidly decarbonize the EU economy by significantly altering the trajectory of emissions and aligning EU policies and legislation across 12 sectors.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU Grand Chamber "Ilva" judgment: Balancing environmental law and human rights from a Kirchberg perspective.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</guid><description>Jacques Bellezit, University of Strasbourg (France)
Photo credit: mafe de baggis, via Wikimedia Commons
To understand the historical development of European construction, one must acknowledge the European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC). Established following the Schumann Declaration on May 9th, 1950, the ECSC marked the first attempt to create a common market for coal and steel, deemed strategic materials. This initiative aimed to not only bolster post-war reconstruction in Europe but also to curb rearmament efforts on both sides of the Rhine during the nascent Cold War.</description></item><item><title>What implications does the climate case against ING have for monetary policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</guid><description>Annelieke Mooij, Assistant Professor, Tilburg University
Photo credit: Sandro Halank, via Wikimedia Commons
The Dutch environmental organization “milieudefensie” threatened legal action against ING bank in the Netherlands. On February 14, 2024, ING declared it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t yield to the organization&amp;rsquo;s demands, making a lawsuit highly probable. While seemingly a domestic issue, this case could have significant European implications, particularly for the Monetary Union and the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) independence.</description></item></channel></rss>