<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Criteo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/criteo/</link><description>Recent content in Criteo on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:38:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/criteo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Criteo predicts that half of all e-commerce in Asia will be conducted through mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-predicts-that-half-of-all-e-commerce-in-asia-will-be-conducted-through-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-predicts-that-half-of-all-e-commerce-in-asia-will-be-conducted-through-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, reports in its Q4 2014 State of Mobile Commerce Report that mobile transactions now represent more than 30% of global e-commerce transactions.
Source: Criteo.
Jonathan Wolf, Chief Product Officer at Criteo, stated that a lack of information about mobile commerce has led many marketers to underestimate the potential of this market. Criteo&amp;rsquo;s State of Mobile Commerce Report leverages their extensive transaction-level data, encompassing billions of transactions, to provide a clearer picture of the global mobile commerce landscape.</description></item><item><title>Criteo emphasizes that e-commerce must be integrated into the retail strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, predicts that mobile will play an even greater role in the e-commerce industry this quarter.
Eric Eichmann, President and COO of Criteo, believes that 2015 will be a year of significant change for e-commerce as consumer online shopping habits continue to evolve rapidly. The increased use of multiple devices presents a challenge for marketers targeting consumers. Eichmann suggests that advertisers who adapt quickly by investing wisely in solutions such as cross-device targeting and mobile-optimized websites and apps will be best equipped to meet consumer demand and boost sales.</description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors.</description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users.</description></item><item><title>Criteo provides three suggestions for increasing sales conversions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 23:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance display advertising, offers advice based on its collaborations within the travel industry on converting leads into customers. This guidance is relevant across all sectors.
Tip #1: Strategically Time Your User Acquisition
Travel app downloads peak during summer (June-September), providing a window before peak season to engage a larger active user base*. Capitalize on your customers&amp;rsquo; planning and buying cycles by aligning download promotions for optimal new customer acquisition, Criteo recommends.</description></item><item><title>Deep linking achieves a significant milestone in mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</guid><description>Instead of relying on traditional search engine strategies, using deep links to guide potential customers straight to the point of sale might be more effective at boosting conversion rates for e-commerce.
A recent study by Lotlinx, a company specializing in deep-linking inventory platforms for the auto industry, reveals that deep-linking attracts double the number of genuine shoppers and doubles their engagement compared to conventional search engine marketing approaches.
Criteo, TapCommerce, and ActionX have recently collaborated to introduce a standardized specification and best practice guide for deep-linking within mobile applications.</description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter.</description></item><item><title>Attract retail attention with apps and promotions leading up to a holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</guid><description>Criteo has noticed a major shift from websites to apps for online shopping. They found a 25% decrease in website traffic but a 4% rise in app traffic, with Thailand (18%) and Singapore (9%) experiencing the largest gains.
All Southeast Asian nations saw growth in overall app traffic volume, with Singapore (207%) and Indonesia (128%) leading the way.
When compared to October 2020, Thailand and Singapore had the highest increases in indexed sales in the app environment, at 12% and 10%, respectively.</description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers.</description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4.</description></item><item><title>Criteo measures the passion for travel among Singaporeans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</guid><description>Mobile travel purchases saw a 35% surge between 2011 and 2016, a trend predicted to continue its upward trajectory. Accessibility (74%) and convenience (69%) are the primary motivators for respondents&amp;rsquo; preference to browse travel products online. A significant 78% choose smartphones over desktops/laptops for browsing due to their on-the-go functionality.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology firm, highlights the continuous growth of mobile travel sales, emphasizing it as a prime growth avenue.</description></item></channel></rss>