<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PCB on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pcb/</link><description>Recent content in PCB on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pcb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable and have reached the stage of addressing cosmetic details. A common issue with this model, as with approximately 90% of them, is a worn keypad. The original coating deteriorates over time due to exposure to skin oils and acids. This results in unsightly smudges, especially on units that have seen regular use. I recently acquired some refurbished keypads from a contact in Denmark to have on hand for my restoration projects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/4002/4004 Relays: Professionally Manufactured PCBs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</guid><description>I recently updated the design of the Beogram 4000/4002/4004 relay adapter boards to allow for professional manufacturing. I&amp;rsquo;ve begun taking and fulfilling orders with these new boards, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled with how they turned out.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the boards:
These boards are compatible with both the older Siemens relays and the newer National relays commonly found as RPM and signal path grounding relays in the 400x series. They are designed as direct replacements for the original relays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Upgrade of the Tracking System with a LED Based Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</guid><description>With the DC motor operating correctly, the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) continued with the arm lowering mechanism and tracking feedback system.
The arm lowering mechanism, consisting of a solenoid and damper, was disassembled, cleaned, and lubricated. This process involved removing the damper, linkages, retaining washer, and spring. Detailed videos illustrating the rebuilding process are available. After reassembly, the arms were meticulously aligned parallel to each other and the keypad edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Extraction of Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 12:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Having restored a Beocord 5000 before, I&amp;rsquo;ve refined the process of removing the tape mechanism, simplifying the steps from my previous post and video.
I began by removing the plexiglass cover for polishing, which provided better access to the tape mechanism. To prepare for a full recap, I also lifted the preamplifier and radio amplifier boards. The photo shows the unit opened up:
&amp;lsquo;Chartz&amp;rsquo; from Beoworld.org suggested leaving the solenoid in place during removal, which led me to realize that even loosening the solenoid fixture is unnecessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Floating Chassis Height</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</guid><description>After adjusting the main platter bearing in a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to set the height of the floating chassis. The goal is to make sure the aluminum surface of the platter is level with the surrounding aluminum panels. You can adjust the height by turning the nuts on the leaf springs that hold the chassis and provide vibration isolation. Using an 8 mm hex wrench is recommended...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002/4004: Replacement of a Broken Cable Clamp/PCB Holder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a broken cable clamp/PCB holder presented an opportunity to test a replacement part file. A fellow Beogram enthusiast from New Zealand shared the file, and in return, received access to parts in my Shapeways store. Photos document the broken clamp, the 3D-printed replacement, and the final installation. The new clamp fits securely with the PCB, keeping the audio cable properly positioned. With the successful trial complete, the part was made available for purchase in my store for other B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Preamplifier and the Radio Amplifier Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s review the Beocord 5000! This model contains many tantalum capacitors that, due to their age (around 35 years), should be replaced. Tantalum capacitors pose a fire risk if they short circuit because of the intense heat released when tantalum reacts with oxygen. While tantalum capacitors were favored in the 1970s due to their smaller size compared to aluminum electrolytic capacitors, advancements in manufacturing have closed the size gap. Today, modern aluminum capacitors can be just as small as the older tantalum ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Power Supply, Motor Control, Electronic Switch and Operational Control Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</guid><description>The restoration continues! Today, I replaced the remaining electrolytic capacitors on my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716). New electrolytics bring peace of mind!
The power supply board, including its reservoir and AC motor capacitors, along with the motor control, electronic switch, and operational control boards, were all addressed:
The Motor Control board, responsible for the take-up motor, had only one Tantalum capacitor that needed replacement:
Here it is after the replacement:
Next is the Electronic Switch board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Redesigned Drop-In Tracking Sensor Light Bulb Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I decided to upgrade the tracking sensor light bulb with a new SMD LED design I had created. My previous design lacked stability with the intensity adjustment trimmer, so I redesigned it to be more secure and visually appealing.
The new design incorporates the trimmer directly onto the circuit board and houses it within the light shield. This required modifications to the 3D printed housing to accommodate the trimmer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor and Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently obtained a main PCB and DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002. I began with the motor refurbishment, a process that often requires several days for the bearings to become saturated with oil.
The motor is depicted here:
Disassembly was necessary to access the bearings, visible as two small rings on the black component in the front:
The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was noticeably oily, suggesting prior tampering. This was supported by a damaged commutator brush that was bent out of its intended form:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED and Improvement of the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>Replacing the sensor arm LED is typically the final step in converting a Beogram 4002 to use all LEDs. After restoring the DC motor, the next task was to install a recently designed flex-PCB-based LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb. The image below shows the sensor arm with the detector assembly removed:
Upon zooming in on the full-resolution image, a small black spot is visible on the glass bulb. This spot indicates significant tungsten evaporation from the filament, suggesting the bulb is nearing the end of its life and could soon fail, rendering the Beogram inoperable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 551x: Exciting!! Replica DC Motor Bearing Prototypes from Beoparts Successfully Tested</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</guid><description>I received another set of Beogram 4002 platter motor components and an RPM panel from a customer in the Netherlands to restore. My work started with the motor, as it usually does.
I disassembled the motor to get to the bearings.
Typically, I would show a picture of the bearings being oiled in a vacuum chamber, but I received new Oilite bearings from www.beoparts-shop.com specifically for these DC motors, which I am testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</guid><description>During the ongoing restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the incandescent bulbs illuminating the RPM trimmer scales were replaced with LEDs for enhanced longevity. Custom-designed circuit boards housing SMD LEDs were crafted to seamlessly replace the original bulbs, ensuring a direct fit.
These LED assemblies are offered to fellow enthusiasts, with an instructional video demonstrating their installation available online.
The following images detail the RPM trimmer panel, initially showcasing the rear view with original bulbs in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor, Main PCB and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 18:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, experiencing RPM fluctuations, recently arrived from a customer for repair. The restoration process involved addressing issues with the DC platter motor, the main PCB, and the RPM adjustment panel.
The platter motor was disassembled to lubricate the bearings. After immersing them in oil and applying a vacuum, the bearings were left undisturbed for two days to ensure proper saturation. Once the bubbling ceased, indicating full replenishment, the bearings were extracted and the motor was reassembled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Carriage Position Switches and Fixing a Bent Output Switch Contact Tab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000, a process known as &amp;ldquo;switch day&amp;rdquo; involves cleaning the contacts of the many open switches. While some recommend desoldering the switches for thorough cleaning, it&amp;rsquo;s generally sufficient to clean the contact areas directly. This minimizes the risk of damaging the delicate contact tabs.
Effective switch functionality hinges on clean contact points, not the overall appearance of the switch. The contact tabs should be straight and have adequate spring to ensure proper contact...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Keypad Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with LEDs. This enhances the unit&amp;rsquo;s lifespan and prevents issues that incandescent bulbs, susceptible to vibration, can experience during shipping.
The top two bulbs illuminate the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s unique position indicator, while the vertical bulbs light the RPM trimmers. I recently designed SMD LED-based PCB replacements for the position indicator bulbs (available via email).
Standard red LEDs with current-limiting resistors can replace the RPM trimmer bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with an SMD LED Light Source and Adjustment of the Feedback Sensisitivy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 turntable had a damaged part (the tracking sensor aperture) that was bent and obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. This issue prevented the tracking system from working correctly. The initial setup used an incandescent light bulb:
Upon removing the bulb housing, it was evident that the aperture was bent and rubbing against the optical sensor housing:
The aperture was carefully straightened, and the bulb assembly was replaced with a new SMD LED light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Exchanging the Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 12:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</guid><description>After removing the tape mechanism from the Beocord 5000 (4715) for rebuilding, I replaced the old, worn-out belts. My process was largely based on the one shown in my YouTube video.
However, I made one key improvement. I learned that the eject lever&amp;rsquo;s alignment with the tape mechanism is vital for the eject key to function correctly after reassembly. Previously, I had only marked the position of part #256 (&amp;ldquo;lever&amp;rdquo;) with a pencil, leading to time-consuming readjustments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Incandescent Light Bulbs in Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, all four incandescent bulbs in the control panel were found to be non-functional. This highlighted the fragility of these bulbs and emphasized the need for a more durable solution. To address this, the original bulbs were replaced with custom-designed LED replacements.
Specifically, the two position indicator bulbs were replaced with surface-mounted LED (SMD LED) units. The two bulbs responsible for illuminating the RPM trimmers were replaced with high-intensity red LEDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>