<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Land on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/land/</link><description>Recent content in Land on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:40:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/land/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Pottinger Hong Kong is now open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</guid><description>Sino Group, a hospitality branch of Sino Land Company, manages various properties including hotels, a yacht club, serviced apartments, and residential dining establishments. They have recently introduced The Pottinger Hong Kong, a luxurious 68-room boutique hotel. Situated on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s oldest paved street, the hotel holds a notable position on a site recognized as a Grade I historic place by the Antiquities Advisory Board of Hong Kong.
As per the Sino Group of Hotels, The Pottinger Hong Kong features 68 upscale guestrooms and suites, with sizes varying from 23 to 68 square meters.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place.</description></item></channel></rss>