<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellular Backhaul on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-backhaul/</link><description>Recent content in Cellular Backhaul on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:57:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-backhaul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dark Fiber Community Builds Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a narrative circulating that our infrastructure is failing. While this might be true in some areas, a massive construction project is currently underway to create a robust fiber optic network across the nation. This &amp;ldquo;nervous system&amp;rdquo; for information technology promises practically limitless, low-lag bandwidth for the foreseeable future.
This surge in fiber optic infrastructure isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by failing systems, but rather by existing infrastructure reaching full capacity. The late 20th century witnessed a fiber optic boom, which initially seemed excessive when the tech bubble burst...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>