<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Family Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family-law/</link><description>Recent content in Family Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:15:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Child abduction: an additional expansion of the EU's exclusive external authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Parental child abduction is a serious issue, often arising from custody disputes during family law proceedings. While abduction by a stranger presents a clear danger, abduction by a non-custodial parent violates court decisions and can hinder the custodial parent&amp;rsquo;s rights, especially when the child is taken to another country.
The Hague Convention, established in 1980, seeks to address this problem. This international treaty, with 93 signatory countries including all EU members, provides a framework for resolving international parental child abduction cases.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of the UK government's proposals for cross-border civil litigation post-Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you&amp;rsquo;re a well-known UK politician who spends most of their time speaking on British radio or working in the US, only occasionally attending their primary job in France or Belgium. Imagine this politician is divorcing their German spouse. Which court and legal system would handle the divorce and child custody matters?
This scenario falls under the larger subject of international civil litigation, also known as private international law, which is the focus of the UK government&amp;rsquo;s most recent position paper on Brexit negotiations.</description></item><item><title>Guardianship, freedom of movement, and child rights: the SM ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*This blog post expands on research that informed the upcoming revised edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Defining a &amp;ldquo;family member&amp;rdquo; legally can be complex, especially when it comes to immigration law and child welfare. The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment in the SM case highlights these complexities, particularly where EU free movement law intersects with the family law of non-EU nations.</description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach.</description></item></channel></rss>