<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Empowerment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/empowerment/</link><description>Recent content in Empowerment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/empowerment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dream Collective is empowering potential female leaders in Singapore with their first-ever bootcamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</guid><description>Source: The Dream Collective.
The Dream Collective, a global platform for training women in corporate leadership, has introduced the Emerging Leaders Bootcamp - Singapore Edition. This program offers a new approach to female empowerment and initiates a crucial conversation about developing female leadership talent in the corporate world. Modeled after MBA programs from top business schools, the program collaborates with major corporations to find, develop, and empower high-potential young women with leadership skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dove encourages women to push boundaries and redefine beauty and success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</guid><description>Women are rejecting the idea that their appearance should limit their potential, sharing empowering stories in Dove&amp;rsquo;s new film, #MyBeautyMySay. The film aims to motivate women to defy stereotypes and societal expectations.
Dove&amp;rsquo;s Global Beauty Confidence Report reveals that women desire the freedom to express themselves authentically but feel restricted by judgments about their appearance. For example, 70% of women receive more compliments on their looks than their work achievements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Great Women Connect Series begins with Great Women Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Great Women Malaysia. Puan Nadira Yusoff.
The Great Women Connect Series debuted today in Malaysia. This new program seeks to provide a space for women in business worldwide to connect and exchange ideas and experiences related to trade. It also aims to foster international partnerships, helping women, especially those in Malaysia, build networks and realize their full potential.
Great Women Malaysia (GMW) is an initiative that strives to empower Malaysian women, particularly those in underserved and rural areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>