<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Children on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/children/</link><description>Recent content in Children on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:26:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can the Dublin III Regulation strengthen family reunification? The CJEU's ruling on the ability to appeal denials of take charge requests.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Leiden University
Photo credit: DFID
Unaccompanied minors can appeal a receiving EU member state&amp;rsquo;s denial of a request to assume responsibility for their asylum case. This conclusion from the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) comes from its judgment in the I. &amp;amp; S. case. Interestingly, the District Court of Haarlem in the Netherlands initially posed the question because the Dublin III Regulation, which governs such transfers, doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly provide for this appeal right...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advocating for children? The Directive on procedural safeguards for children suspected or accused in criminal proceedings.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</guid><description>Protecting Young Suspects in the EU: A Look at the New Directive If we don&amp;rsquo;t stand up for children, then we don&amp;rsquo;t stand for much.
Marian Wright Edelman
Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
Ensuring fair treatment within the criminal justice system is crucial, and this fairness necessitates different safeguards based on individual circumstances. Children, being particularly vulnerable, require special protective measures, as recognized by international standards such as the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child and the Council of Europe Guidelines on child-friendly justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Child abduction: an additional expansion of the EU's exclusive external authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Parental child abduction is a serious issue, often arising from custody disputes during family law proceedings. While abduction by a stranger presents a clear danger, abduction by a non-custodial parent violates court decisions and can hinder the custodial parent&amp;rsquo;s rights, especially when the child is taken to another country.
The Hague Convention, established in 1980, seeks to address this problem. This international treaty, with 93 signatory countries including all EU members, provides a framework for resolving international parental child abduction cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disregard the children! CJEU supports automatic exclusions from family benefits in Case C-308/14 Commission v UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</guid><description>Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School The Court of Justice is increasingly distancing itself from the social welfare systems of Member States. Although the Court once suggested that citizenship is paramount and forms the basis for financial solidarity, guaranteeing some support from a host state for EU citizens facing temporary hardship, this stance is changing.
With the Court moving away from the concept of citizenship, the idea of a reasonable burden may be disappearing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>