<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>National on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/national/</link><description>Recent content in National on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/national/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India and Bangladesh have initiated connectivity projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</guid><description>The Prime Ministers of India and Bangladesh, Narendra Modi and Sheikh Hasina, respectively, along with West Bengal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Minister, Mamata Banerjee, inaugurated multiple connectivity initiatives between the two nations.
These projects include the inauguration of the second Bhairab and Titas Railway Bridges, situated on the 320-km Dhaka-Chittagong railway line in Bangladesh. Additionally, the International Rail Passenger Terminus in Kolkata, India, was also inaugurated.
The dignitaries also launched the first run of the Bandhan Express, connecting Kolkata to Khulna in southwest Bangladesh, covering a distance of over 150km...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Butchers Club Burger offers National Day dishes in celebration of Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>The Butchers Club Burger in Singapore is launching a special menu item for National Day: The Little Red Dot Burger.
Starting July 29th and lasting for two weekends, The Little Red Dot Burger will be featured as part of a National Day Set Menu at The Butchers Club Burger Singapore. This marks the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s first National Day celebration in Singapore, and the burger itself is a tribute to a beloved local dish: satay ayam (chicken satay)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with Amara Sanctuary Singapore's special promotion!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:31:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa. Singapore laksa.
To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 53rd birthday, the 5-star Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is offering a National Day special at their Shutters restaurant.
During this National Day celebration, Shutters&amp;rsquo; dinner guests will enjoy a discounted Singapura buffet, priced at S$53++ per adult, down from the usual S$75++. This offer is valid from 6:30 pm to 10:00 pm. The buffet features local favorites like Nyonya laksa, barbequed stingray, and charcoal-grilled satay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre now offers complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Guests at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) can enjoy free Wi-Fi access through the &amp;lsquo;ADNEC Free Wi-Fi&amp;rsquo; network.
Humaid Matar Al Dhaheri, Acting Group CEO of Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company, stated that providing complimentary Wi-Fi highlights ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s focus on using technology to improve visitor experiences. This service eliminates the need for visitors to seek out basic internet access, aligning with ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing its technological infrastructure and enhancing service offerings to meet the changing needs of its stakeholders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore National Administrative Professionals Week is here. If you need someone to talk to, I'm here for you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</guid><description>A recent survey conducted by Zyllem, a delivery service, in honor of Singapore Administrative Professionals Day 2016, showed that 93% of respondents believe that Administrative Professionals are the unsung heroes of Singaporean businesses.
However, the survey also revealed that 64% of coworkers admitted to taking their Admin Professionals for granted. They frequently rely on them to perform tasks outside their job description, including delivering umbrellas to colleagues stuck in the rain, sending forgotten passports to colleagues at airport check-in, performing first aid, and even providing early morning wake-up calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils National Day film for 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest National Day film celebrates the resilience of Singaporeans as they face the challenges of COVID-19. Titled This is the year, the film is available on Singtel TV and social media platforms.
This is the year highlights the difficulties brought on by the pandemic and pays homage to the spirit of progress that drives Singaporeans forward.
Source: Singtel video. This is the year we will not have the F1 race...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>