<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Team Collaboration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/team-collaboration/</link><description>Recent content in Team Collaboration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:36:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/team-collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Take a Conference, Save the Carbon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</guid><description>While conference calls have been a common business tool, they are often reserved for specific projects or occasional use. Similarly, web conferencing, its internet-based counterpart, allows for incorporating visuals like charts and graphs but remains irregularly utilized. So, when does integrating conferencing into daily operations become a more practical approach rather than just another tool?
Several factors suggest a potential shift. Firstly, technological advancements have made it possible. Computers and speakerphones are commonplace, with many conference rooms equipped with internet access and large display screens or projectors.</description></item><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free.</description></item></channel></rss>