<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Schengen on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/schengen/</link><description>Recent content in Schengen on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/schengen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to suspend Schengen due to Greece? Is it necessary to do so?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</guid><description>A recent leak of a Council document proposes a potential suspension of the Schengen system for a duration of up to two years. This proposal stems from what are being termed &amp;ldquo;systemic deficiencies&amp;rdquo; in Greece&amp;rsquo;s management of its external borders, particularly concerning the influx of refugees and migrants. Such a suspension would provide any Schengen country the option to reinstate or implement border controls along their shared internal borders. While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely that every Schengen country would exercise this option, it&amp;rsquo;s anticipated that several would choose to do so, especially given that a number already have active border controls in place.</description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario.</description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance.</description></item><item><title>Are potential asylum-seekers entitled to a Schengen visa?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
In a recent decision concerning the Koushkaki case, the Court of Justice provided clarity on applying for a Schengen visa. The court effectively ruled that individuals have a right to a visa if they fulfill the established requirements. However, this decision also implicitly raises questions about denying visa applications from potential asylum-seekers.
The judgment
Mr. Koushkaki, an Iranian citizen residing in Iran, applied for a Schengen visa to visit Germany but was denied due to insufficient proof of financial support for his stay and return.</description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Potential Reconstruction of Hadrian's Wall: How Scottish Independence Could Impact British Border Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 11:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/potential-reconstruction-of-hadrian-s-wall-how-scottish-independence-could-impact-british-border-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Hadrian&amp;rsquo;s Wall is often thought to have been built by the Romans to defend civilized Britannia from invading Picts, who are considered the ancestors of modern-day Scots. This idea is echoed in Game of Thrones, where the Wall serves to keep out wild and dangerous beings from the North.
Theresa May, the British Home Secretary, recently invoked this imagery when she suggested that if Scotland were to become independent, border control would need to be reinstated between Scotland and the remaining United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Are the new proposals for simplifying Schengen visa applications for third-country national family members of EU citizens comprehensive enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU citizens with family members who are non-EU citizens often face obstacles to free movement, especially when those family members are from Asia, Africa, or the Caribbean. Traveling outside of the Schengen area with these family members often requires obtaining visas, adding complexity to their trips.
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent proposals on visas, if adopted, could bring some relief. One proposal focuses on revising the existing &amp;ldquo;Schengen visa&amp;rdquo; rules, which permit travel across Schengen countries for three months.</description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU's new law on travel authorization for non-EU citizens creating a brave new world?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A new European Union (EU) law regarding travel authorization for non-EU citizens visiting the EU was recently announced. This new law will impact millions of travelers annually, potentially including British citizens post-Brexit. This law, though not immediately applicable, holds significant future implications. This explanation aims to clarify its reach and functionality. (Update: the final law was officially published in September 2018).
Basics of the system</description></item><item><title>A leaked document discloses that the EU is considering suspending the Schengen agreement for a period of two years.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</guid><description>Commentary by Steve Peers
This is Council document 14300/15, from December 1, 2015, called &amp;ldquo;Integrity of the Schengen area,&amp;rdquo; and sent to Coreper (representatives of EU member states) and the Council - likely the Justice and Home Affairs ministers meeting December 3rd and 4th. (An official version of the document is available here).
The first three sections are relatively standard (see here for discussion), but section 4 proposes initiating a process to formally permit the reinstatement of internal border controls within the Schengen zone for a duration of up to two years.</description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state.</description></item><item><title>The UK is now part of the Schengen Information System, bringing the Panopticon Home.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The idea of a &amp;ldquo;Panopticon,&amp;rdquo; a prison where guards could potentially see any inmate at any point, was conceived over two centuries ago by British philosopher Jeremy Bentham. He believed that the constant threat of observation would motivate prisoners to act appropriately. This concept is now often used to illustrate contemporary patterns in widespread monitoring and societal control.
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) initial move in this direction was the establishment of the Schengen Information System (SIS) during the 1990s.</description></item></channel></rss>