<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>3D Printed on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3d-printed/</link><description>Recent content in 3D Printed on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3d-printed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and one of the challenges is finding modern replacements for the large capacitors used in the 1970s. I received a 3D-printed adapter that allows me to neatly install smaller, current-generation capacitors.
These photos show the adapter with the new capacitors in place:
For reliability, I used two 300uF capacitors wired together to replace the original 150uF motor capacitor. The remaining capacitors are high-quality Rubycon, Panasonic, and Multicomp components chosen for their longevity.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Deteriorated Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002, deteriorated transport lock bushings, evidenced by small orange plastic pieces within the unit, were discovered. To address this, 3D-printed replacement bushings were designed for convenient installation without major disassembly. These bushings are comprised of two halves, insertable from above and below the sub-chassis.
The replacement bushings are available for purchase, with each bushing requiring two of the 3D-printed parts. A video detailing the installation process is accessible online.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings with 3D Printed Replacement Parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5523) arm lowering mechanism, I removed the circuit boards for refurbishment. This presented an ideal opportunity to swap the deteriorated transport lock bushings with 3D-printed replacements. The old bushings tend to break down, scattering fragments within the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s casing, often lodging beneath the floating chassis. These fragments can obstruct the chassis&amp;rsquo;s movement, hindering its ability to isolate the turntable and tonearm from the enclosure.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Missing Leaf Spring on a Plate Lock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</guid><description>During the rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5513), I encountered an issue while adjusting the sub-chassis, platter, and tonearm. The large aluminum plate wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly against the plinth when it was pushed back, making it impossible to align the platter flush with the plate.
The problem originated from one of the locking mechanisms in the back left corner. These locks, equipped with leaf springs, are designed to secure the plate to the frame when the plinth is moved back.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002/4004: Replacement of a Broken Cable Clamp/PCB Holder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a broken cable clamp/PCB holder presented an opportunity to test a replacement part file. A fellow Beogram enthusiast from New Zealand shared the file, and in return, received access to parts in my Shapeways store. Photos document the broken clamp, the 3D-printed replacement, and the final installation. The new clamp fits securely with the PCB, keeping the audio cable properly positioned. With the successful trial complete, the part was made available for purchase in my store for other B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Repair of a Broken Out DIN-7 Jack With 3D Printed Inserts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-din-7-jack-with-3d-printed-inserts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-din-7-jack-with-3d-printed-inserts/</guid><description>Repairing the broken DIN 7 jack on the Beocord 9000 was simpler than anticipated. The part is identical to the one used for the Beomaster 8000&amp;rsquo;s Phono input. A 3D printed part, designed previously, was used to replace the fragile tabs on these sockets, which often break and cause the jack to fall into the panel cutout. Images of the broken jack and the 3D printed replacements are included.
A short video demonstrating the installation process and the repaired plug is provided.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Transport Lock Bushings and cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>Many Beogram 4002 (5513) turntables, including the one I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring, require replacement of the transport lock bushings and cabinet guidance washers. These components are crucial for proper platter and arm alignment. Without them, alignment is unreliable and won&amp;rsquo;t hold during transport.
This image shows the front transport lock missing its bushing:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the disassembled mechanism with the lower part of the new bushings installed:
The top part of the bushing is added next:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of New Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 and it was time to replace the large capacitors. This is a process I enjoy, made easier with a 3D printed adapter I designed. This adapter allows for the use of smaller, modern capacitors while maintaining a neat and organized appearance. I have a previous post detailing the connections for anyone who might find it helpful, as there are several jumpers that require re-soldering.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration involved replacing the motor phase capacitor and reservoir. I used a 3D-printed adapter I designed, which allows for secure mounting of modern, smaller capacitors in the original location using the factory bracket. This post provides a closer look at the replacement process and includes a comprehensive wiring diagram for the capacitors. This can be particularly helpful for those tackling this task for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A Broken Off Solenoid Plunger and New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, recently serviced and returned to a customer, unexpectedly came back with a faulty tonearm. The culprit was a broken solenoid plunger, a part responsible for lowering the tonearm. This unusual breakage was likely due to material fatigue.
To fix the issue, the solenoid was replaced with one from a donor Beogram 4002. During the repair, it was discovered that the transport lock bushings had also deteriorated and needed replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</guid><description>I recently provided a customer with replacement capacitors for his Beogram 4000 turntable, along with a 3D-printed adapter I designed.
He had been experiencing problems with the motor, as it was only displaying half waveforms. This suggested an issue with either the phase capacitor or the power supply reservoir capacitors. After installing the new components, the problem was completely resolved. You can find more details about this process in my original post here: link to my original post about this procedure.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings and Missing Cabinet Guiding Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration involved addressing the common issue of fragile orange transport lock bushings and missing cabinet guiding washers. Many Beograms used plastic washers, which are prone to cracking and falling apart. This was evident in the restoration project, as some washers were missing entirely.
To rectify this, five new 3D-printed washers were installed. For aesthetic purposes, using a black washer for the front-center position is recommended to avoid visibility through the gap between the aluminum panel and the plinth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 3000 (5228): Restoration of the Plexiglass Hood - Repair of a Cracked Hinge and Installation of 3D Printed Mounting Brackets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 3000 turntable with a damaged plexiglass dust cover. The plastic mounting brackets that held the cover were broken, and one of the plexiglass hinges was also broken.
and one of the plexiglass hinges was broken off:
To address these issues, I created a repair kit. This kit includes 3D-printed replacement mounting brackets, a specialized tool for reinstalling the spring tensioning block, and laser-cut plexiglass pieces for fixing the broken hinge.</description></item></channel></rss>