<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Temporary Protection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/temporary-protection/</link><description>Recent content in Temporary Protection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:20:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/temporary-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>People without nationality and refugees escaping Ukraine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</guid><description>Chris Nash, Director of the European Network on Statelessness*
*Reblogged from the Network website
As the number of people seeking refuge from the conflict in Ukraine approaches two million, our organization and our members working in the region are working to understand the specific needs of stateless individuals displaced by this crisis.
Based on previous experiences, including our research from the Stateless Journeys initiative, we know that stateless people fleeing from conflict encounter additional obstacles when crossing borders and seeking asylum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Temporary Protection Directive: A Crucial Element Missing from the European Migration Agenda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-temporary-protection-directive-a-crucial-element-missing-from-the-european-migration-agenda/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-temporary-protection-directive-a-crucial-element-missing-from-the-european-migration-agenda/</guid><description>Meltem Ineli-Ciger, PhD Candidate, University of Bristol Law School[1]
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s Temporary Protection Directive came into effect in 2001, marking the first EU directive on international protection after the Treaty of Amsterdam&amp;rsquo;s implementation in 1999. This directive provides a practical and streamlined structure for managing mass arrivals of displaced individuals, standardizing and harmonizing the protection they receive. Despite this, the directive has never been put into practice. While the Council contemplated activating it in the early 2000s due to increasing asylum seekers from Iraq and Afghanistan, no action was taken (Klug)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-temporary-protection-directive-a-crucial-element-missing-from-the-european-migration-agenda/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-temporary-protection-directive-a-crucial-element-missing-from-the-european-migration-agenda/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating a legal minefield: the potential dangers of expanding the reach of the EU Temporary Protection Directive past March 2025.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 07:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</guid><description>Dr Meltem Ineli-Ciger, Associate Professor, Suleyman Demirel University Faculty of Law; Migration Policy Centre Associate, European University Institute
Photo credit: Falin, on Wikimedia Commons
A crucial question arises as the March 2025 deadline for the Council Directive 2001/55/EC (Temporary Protection Directive), applicable to those fleeing the Ukraine conflict, approaches. This issue revolves around the fate of these individuals once this directive expires. Numerous experts, including myself, have explored potential solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Questions and Answers on Temporary Protection for Ukrainians in the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-and-answers-on-temporary-protection-for-ukrainians-in-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-and-answers-on-temporary-protection-for-ukrainians-in-the-european-union/</guid><description>Temporary Protection for People Fleeing Ukraine: What You Need to Know By Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*updated March 2 2022 to include the Commission proposal for use of the temporary protection Directive, and guidance for applying EU external borders law. Updated March 3 to refer to the Council agreeing on the decision. Updated March 4 to discuss the text of the decision. Updated March 28 to refer to guidance on and discussion of implementation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-and-answers-on-temporary-protection-for-ukrainians-in-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-and-answers-on-temporary-protection-for-ukrainians-in-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>