<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Air on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/air/</link><description>Recent content in Air on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/air/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing.</description></item><item><title>Berkeley Earth raises concerns about air pollution in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</guid><description>Source: Berkeley Earth website.
A recent study published in PLOS ONE by Berkeley Earth reveals that air pollution causes approximately 4,000 deaths per day in China, representing 17% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total deaths. This non-profit organization, established to investigate concerns raised by global warming skeptics, determined that the air quality for 38% of China&amp;rsquo;s population would be deemed &amp;ldquo;unhealthy&amp;rdquo; by United States standards.
Berkeley Earth&amp;rsquo;s analysis of hourly measurements from 1,500 ground stations over a four-month period indicated coal as the most likely source of PM2.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents.</description></item><item><title>Dyson's latest Pure Cool fans also function as air purifiers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-s-latest-pure-cool-fans-also-function-as-air-purifiers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-s-latest-pure-cool-fans-also-function-as-air-purifiers/</guid><description>Dyson has introduced the Dyson Pure Cool purifying fans, which leverage the company&amp;rsquo;s expertise in airflow, filtration, and electronics to address indoor air pollution and purify entire rooms.
Dyson first entered the purifying fan market in 2015, responding to the growing global concern of indoor air pollution. Dyson points out that we breathe mostly indoor air, which can contain invisible, microscopic particles. Urban pollution, particulate matter, and pollen can infiltrate indoor spaces like offices, mix with pollutants from sources like cleaning products, and become trapped.</description></item><item><title>The new iPad Air 2 from Apple is thinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-ipad-air-2-from-apple-is-thinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 11:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-ipad-air-2-from-apple-is-thinner/</guid><description>Apple unveiled its slimmest iPad yet, the iPad Air 2, at a highly anticipated event on October 16th.
The updated iPad boasts an enhanced Retina display for improved contrast, a richer color palette, and superior cameras. Available in gold, alongside the classic silver and space gray, both the iPad Air 2 and the new iPad mini 3 feature Touch ID. In the US, these models will also offer Apple Pay, a new payment system.</description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer.</description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board.</description></item><item><title>Starting in October, Air China will offer nonstop flights from Beijing to Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</guid><description>Air China will commence nonstop flights between Beijing and Mumbai starting October 25, 2015. This decision comes as a response to the growing travel demand between these two BRICS nations, driven by strengthening political and economic ties.
Source: Air China.
The route will operate four times a week, with flights on Tuesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays, and Sundays. The seven-hour journey departs Beijing at 7:40 PM local time and arrives in Mumbai at 1 AM the following day.</description></item></channel></rss>