<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Telephone Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-telephone-line/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Telephone Line on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-telephone-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines.</description></item><item><title>Fractional ISDN PRI For Telephone Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</guid><description>ISDN PRI is a great option for businesses that need a robust phone system. It provides 23 digital lines with features like fast call switching and Caller ID on a single, cost-effective line. However, not all businesses need that many lines.
Smaller businesses or those with lower call volumes can opt for Fractional ISDN PRI, which offers the same features but with fewer lines. This option allows businesses to customize the number of lines they need, typically around 12, leading to significant cost savings.</description></item></channel></rss>