<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TRUFFLE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/truffle/</link><description>Recent content in TRUFFLE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/truffle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High Bandwidth Dissimilar Line Bonding From Mushroom Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</guid><description>Want to create your own high-bandwidth internet connection without the exorbitant cost of dedicated services like SONET OC3? Combining consumer-grade options like DSL, cable, or wireless might seem appealing, but achieving a reliable, high-speed connection this way is practically impossible with standard routers.
Instead of another router, consider the Truffles appliance from Mushroom Networks. This innovative device combines multiple internet connections, regardless of type, into a single, high-bandwidth connection.
While traditional &amp;ldquo;T1 bonding&amp;rdquo; offered by carriers has limitations in terms of speed and requiring identical lines from a single provider, Truffles takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bonded T1 Solution Increases Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</guid><description>A 1.5 Mbps T1 bandwidth has long been a standard for small businesses, often proving sufficient for their needs. Some businesses even utilize an Integrated T1 solution for combined internet and telephone services. However, as bandwidth demands increase, many find T1 bandwidth limiting their productivity.
A simple solution to increase bandwidth is adding a second T1 line, doubling it to 3 Mbps. However, for these lines to function as a single, larger line, they should be ordered from the same provider with a &amp;ldquo;bonded T1 solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Broadband Bonding is Mushrooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:52:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</guid><description>Businesses with high bandwidth demands now have a delicious new option for boosting their WAN capacity thanks to the TRUFFLE from Mushroom Networks, Inc.
What makes the TRUFFLE so appealing? This device can combine the bandwidth of multiple broadband connections – think DSL, Cable, T1, even satellite – to create a single, faster, and more reliable connection, similar to T1 line bonding but with more flexibility. The TRUFFLE BBNA6401 model, for instance, can aggregate up to 6 different connections, reaching download speeds of up to 50 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>