<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General Principles of Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-principles-of-law/</link><description>Recent content in General Principles of Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-principles-of-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal.</description></item><item><title>Is there a conflict or disagreement between the European Court of Justice and the Danish Constitutional Court? The Danish Supreme Court is questioning the Mangold-principle.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-conflict-or-disagreement-between-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-danish-constitutional-court-the-danish-supreme-court-is-questioning-the-mangold-principle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-conflict-or-disagreement-between-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-danish-constitutional-court-the-danish-supreme-court-is-questioning-the-mangold-principle/</guid><description>Sune Klinge, PhD Fellow, Centre for Comparative and European Consitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
The Danish Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Ajos case, concerning the scope of the EU employment equality Directive and age discrimination. This decision follows a ruling from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) that provided two paths for the Danish court: interpret national law in harmony with the Directive or disapply conflicting national provisions.</description></item><item><title>Is it permissible for Member States to confiscate the assets of asylum-seekers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk (Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen) and Steve Peers
Recently, several countries within and outside the EU have made headlines for seizing assets from asylum-seekers upon entry. This raises the question of whether this practice aligns with EU law. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine national practices, the development of relevant EU regulations, and finally, draw our conclusions.
Denmark
In November 2015, the Danish government put forward 34 measures aimed at deterring asylum seekers.</description></item><item><title>Rights for data protection and administrative procedures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the cases of YS and M and S clarified data protection rights for asylum-seekers. This judgment could also have wider implications for accessing documents in administrative procedures.
Two asylum-seekers in the Netherlands wanted to see file notes related to their cases. Instead of relying on the EU’s asylum procedures Directive, which grants access to reasons for negative decisions and interview reports but not all documents, they invoked the data protection Directive.</description></item></channel></rss>