<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Training on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/training/</link><description>Recent content in Training on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:35:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What qualities define exceptional training?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:35:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading training sessions, including a Dynamics GP Distribution Partner Academy and a customized Forecaster training. These distinct classes got me thinking about the elements of exceptional training and what makes it truly valuable. I&amp;rsquo;d love to share my thoughts and hear yours!
Relevant Content: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for training content to align with student needs. While this can be challenging with pre-determined classes, instructors can bridge the gap by connecting content to real-world scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Fitch Learning has teamed up with Golden Education to provide a certificate in quantitative finance in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:47:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</guid><description>Fitch Learning has partnered with Golden Education, a financial education company in China, to provide the Certificate in Quantitative Finance (CQF) program to professionals throughout the country. The CQF is gaining recognition in China, as demonstrated by a 55% increase in enrollment by Chinese participants from 2018 to 2019.
The CQF program includes six modules, two elective advanced modules, three exams, and a final project. Quantitative finance utilizes mathematical modeling to examine financial markets and securities.</description></item><item><title>Flight Experience Singapore and McGallen &amp; Bolden offer unique leadership workshops that stand out from the rest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</guid><description>Source: McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden.
Flight Experience Singapore, the first flight simulator open to the public in Asia, has partnered with the consulting firm McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden to offer leadership workshops.
Their program, Leadership Secrets at 30,000 Feet, is designed for business leaders and executives. It uses a realistic cockpit setting to teach leadership skills. The customized, four-hour workshop draws on decades of experience from Captain Michael Caston, a pilot with experience flying Boeing 747 and 737 jets for British Airways and Singapore Airlines.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Budget of Singapore provides support for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Ministry of Finance, Singapore. Infrastructure investments were also announced as part of Budget 2015.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2015, presented by Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Tharman Shanmugaratnam, included several business initiatives. These encompassed increased training assistance, a gradual reduction in business restructuring aid, a freeze on foreign worker levies (excluding manufacturing and construction), and measures to encourage innovation and expansion.
Training and development
Shanmugaratnam emphasized the government&amp;rsquo;s commitment to continuous investment in Singaporeans&amp;rsquo; skills development.</description></item><item><title>New Deep Dive Now Accessible: Management Reporter!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</guid><description>I previously shared information about the &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s New Deep Dives&amp;rdquo; series for Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010. We recently released another installment focused on Management Reporter. Access it here! Craig Anderson from MSX Group, an expert in Management Reporter, developed and presented this topic. MSX Group and Craig are leading authorities on Management Reporter, and we were thrilled to leverage their expertise for this installment!</description></item><item><title>The demand for online training in the Middle East exceeds the available supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</guid><description>Online professional training courses are gaining popularity in the Middle East, but the availability of suitable courses hasn&amp;rsquo;t matched the increased demand, according to research by GulfTalent, a recruitment firm that operates an online recruitment portal for the region.
GulfTalent’s study shows that one out of five professionals interested in pursuing training prefers online courses. This signifies a significant shift, given that online training was practically nonexistent ten years ago.</description></item><item><title>COPC releases contact center training schedule for the second half of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</guid><description>COPC, a consulting firm specializing in customer experience enhancement, has announced its training schedule for the latter half of 2015. The firm offers in-person classes focusing on operational areas within customer contact.
Kathleen Jezierski, COO of COPC, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s approach: &amp;ldquo;Customers interact with companies through many touch points such as phone, email, social media, mobile and the web. We take our call center expertise and apply our proven best practices to manage these newer channels to deliver a unified experience.</description></item><item><title>Singapore welcomes the arrival of Japanese fashion retail concepts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</guid><description>Source: WMH Group. Kafuku.
World Mode Holdings Group (WMH Group) aims to improve the Singapore fashion retail sector by establishing its first international branch, iDA Singapore (iDA’SG).
WMH Group is a Japanese fashion retail consultancy firm known for strengthening its clients&amp;rsquo; brands. As Japan&amp;rsquo;s top recruiter for beauty and fashion sales professionals, their Singapore branch will offer expert guidance and support to enhance retail staff skills.
“As Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader in retail job placements, we&amp;rsquo;ve placed 100,000 retail staff with approximately 1,000 clients, primarily in fashion and luxury.</description></item><item><title>The fourth group of entrepreneurs successfully complete the eFounders Fellowship program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-group-of-entrepreneurs-successfully-complete-the-efounders-fellowship-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-group-of-entrepreneurs-successfully-complete-the-efounders-fellowship-program/</guid><description>Thirty-eight entrepreneurs from Asia have successfully finished the fourth eFounders Fellowship program. This joint effort between the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) and Alibaba Business School equips entrepreneurs with valuable skills and encourages them to share their knowledge.
This initiative stems from a commitment made by Jack Ma, Alibaba Group&amp;rsquo;s founder and former Executive Chairman, as UNCTAD Special Adviser for Young Entrepreneurs and Small Business. This commitment aims to empower 1,000 entrepreneurs in developing countries over five years, creating leaders for inclusive and sustainable economic development through the digital economy.</description></item><item><title>The BenQ interactive flat panel simplifies education and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</guid><description>BenQ, a well-known name in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, introduces the RP750K, a new interactive flat panel (IFP). This innovative IFP offers a comprehensive solution by combining a 4K Ultra HD whiteboard with annotation and collaboration tools.
The RP750K excels in dynamic classroom or corporate training settings. Its Germ-Resistant Screen, infused with a safe and robust nano-ionic silver coating, effectively eliminates most surface germs, reducing cross-infection risks. This antimicrobial protection persists even with regular cleaning and extended use.</description></item><item><title>Supporting mothers returning to work and mom entrepreneurs in advancing their careers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 10:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</guid><description>For more details, scan the QR code.
Among the nearly 40,000 members of Mums@Work, common challenges faced when rejoining the workforce include age, keeping up with technology and necessary skills, a lack of confidence, anxieties about new work environments, and generational differences.
This is despite over 80% of members having more than eight years of professional experience, primarily in white-collar roles within banking and finance, media and entertainment, and human resources.</description></item><item><title>Brief Lab introduces new online certification program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</guid><description>The Brief Lab, an organization that trains professionals to be concise communicators, is marking its one-year anniversary with a redesigned website and the introduction of its first online certification program, Brief Practitioner.
Source: The Brief Lab website.
The Brief Practitioner program is geared towards professionals who want to embrace conciseness and become certified in a structured approach to lean communication. The online course is designed for those who aim to champion these methodologies within their organizations.</description></item><item><title>Browser Based Video Conferencing and Webinars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</guid><description>Once restricted to businesses, video conferencing is now accessible to anyone with an internet connection and a web browser. MegaMeeting offers a suite of products for PCs, Macs, and Linux computers that don&amp;rsquo;t require typical downloads or installations. As long as you can use a web browser, you can participate in video conferences and webinars.
MegaMeeting&amp;rsquo;s web-based system utilizes the Flash Player 9 plugin, commonly found in browsers like Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari.</description></item><item><title>Project management is expected to face challenges in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</guid><description>ESI International, a company that provides project management training, believes that in the coming year, project managers (PMs) will experience several changes. These include dealing with combined in-person and remote work environments, needing stronger talent management skills, and aligning project results with company goals.
Raed Haddad, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at ESI International, noted that strategy and execution are often discussed separately. He anticipates a stronger emphasis on connecting these two aspects, as more companies start seeing strategic execution as a crucial skill.</description></item><item><title>Learn the fundamentals of blockchain technology at Smartcademy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-the-fundamentals-of-blockchain-technology-at-smartcademy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-the-fundamentals-of-blockchain-technology-at-smartcademy/</guid><description>Source: Unsplash, via Smartcademy. This image illustrates Blockchain technology, with cryptocurrency being one example of its use.
[
Smartcademy, a Singaporean organization focused on technology education and career development, has launched a beginner-friendly introductory course on Blockchain. This one-month program covers basic concepts and terminology, explores how Blockchain is used in finance, and explains the workings of Bitcoin. The course aims to equip individuals with the knowledge to navigate the risks and rewards of digital financial systems.</description></item><item><title>BCM Institute offers Business Continuity Management courses specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</guid><description>The BCM Institute, in collaboration with the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC), is offering a free two-day Business Continuity Management (BCM) course designed to enhance the resilience of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) against disruptions.
Taking place on October 28-29, 2014, at the Singapore Productivity Centre, this course is presented with support from the Singapore Business Federation and SPRING Singapore. Participants will engage with the following topics:
APEC-endorsed step-by-step BCM implementation guidelines Complimentary, ready-to-use BCM templates Guidance on utilizing BCM templates Insights into BCM trends affecting SMEs, shared by an APEC ASEAN BCM Working Group Committee member SMEs meeting the criteria of an annual sales turnover not exceeding S$100 million or employing 200 or fewer staff are eligible to participate.</description></item><item><title>Flightleaders.com will enhance its programs in 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</guid><description>Source: Flightleaders.com website. An aircraft cockpit.
Flightleaders.com, an aviation-inspired leadership training provider and part of the McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden Group, intends to expand its program offerings throughout 2018.
Dr. Seamus Phan, a Leadership Trainer with Flightleaders.com specializing in corporate leadership and philosophical approaches, believes corporate training will be highly sought after due to generational gaps in the workplace. He argues this need goes beyond technological advancements and other disruptive trends, as managing people and leadership will remain critical challenges.</description></item><item><title>Stars at INSEAD drive innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</guid><description>New research from INSEAD suggests that good mentors are incredibly valuable.
The study, titled &amp;ldquo;Where Do Stars Come From? The Role of Star vs. Nonstar Collaborators in Creative Settings,&amp;rdquo; was published in Organization Science. The authors, Manuel Sosa, Jürgen Mihm, and Haibo Liu, examined the skills needed to effectively combine different elements for maximum creativity and innovation, leading to organizational success.
Their research specifically focused on a new aspect of collaborative creativity: the impact of collaborating with high-achievers (&amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo;) versus average performers (&amp;ldquo;non-stars&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>SMU and Alibaba Cloud introduce groundbreaking upskilling program beyond China for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>Singapore Management University (SMU) and Alibaba Cloud have teamed up to introduce a series of courses designed to enhance the skills of over 1,000 working professionals in Singapore.
This joint initiative, known as the SMU-Alibaba Series, marks Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s first professional continuing education program outside of China. Set to commence in March 2019, the program will be delivered through SMU Academy, the university&amp;rsquo;s professional training division.
With a specific focus on empowering small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), the Series aims to equip businesses with the necessary competencies to navigate the challenges posed by rapid technological advancements and evolving consumer behavior.</description></item><item><title>GLG increases its presence in Singapore with office expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</guid><description>GLG, a professional learning platform connecting professionals with experts for knowledge sharing, has expanded its presence in Singapore with a new and larger office. The company&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Alexander Saint-Amand, highlighted the rapid growth of GLG&amp;rsquo;s business in Singapore, emphasizing the region&amp;rsquo;s significance for the company&amp;rsquo;s mission to transform professional learning.
The new 6,000-square-foot office, located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, can accommodate 64 employees. GLG&amp;rsquo;s leadership, including Evan Auyang, Head of Asia-Pacific and Managing Director, and David Anderson, Head of GLG Southeast Asia, underscored Singapore&amp;rsquo;s strategic importance as a business hub and its concentration of leading professionals and companies.</description></item><item><title>A digital sales training platform that enables users to engage in role-playing exercises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 19:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</guid><description>Role-playing is crucial for sales training, allowing two people to act out real-life sales scenarios.
While businesses utilize meeting software for training remote sales teams, this technology often lacks features for practicing pitches online.
uniRow&amp;rsquo;s TrainingCloud.com is designed specifically to facilitate online role-playing during sales training. Trainers can conduct, record, and share role-plays for evaluation and learning purposes.
Nimit Kumar, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of uniRow, emphasizes the importance of hands-on practice in sales training.</description></item><item><title>Learn about data science quickly with CEG Digital's online course</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</guid><description>CEG Digital, the flexible learning branch of global education provider Cambridge Education Group (CEG), has teamed up with the Web Science Institute at the University of Southampton (WSI), a top-100 university, to offer short online courses.
Dr. Elena Simperl, WSI Associate Professor and Scientific Director of the European Data Science Academy, emphasized the importance of data science skills, stating, &amp;ldquo;Data science is crucial for our economy. Our new series of short professional courses complement our postgraduate degrees and target decision-makers, business analysts, IT developers, and others interested in cutting-edge data science technologies and applications in fields like digital marketing, finance, and healthcare.</description></item><item><title>The Pi1M Training Programme offered by Digi provides benefits to small business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Participants of the Pi1M Training Programme gathered for a group photo.
Digi Telecommunications recently conducted a training program for community members residing near the company-managed Pusat Internet 1 Malaysia (Pi1M) centers. This tailored program reflects Digi&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering online entrepreneurship within its Pi1M communities. Currently, Digi manages 34 Pi1Ms across Pahang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Johor, Melaka, and Sarawak, with plans to establish 70 more centers by year&amp;rsquo;s end.</description></item><item><title>John Tschohl highlights 10 errors in corporate training</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/john-tschohl-highlights-10-errors-in-corporate-training/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 21:31:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/john-tschohl-highlights-10-errors-in-corporate-training/</guid><description>John Tschohl, President of the Service Quality Institute, argues that a significant amount of time and money invested in training is often unproductive. He emphasizes that ineffective training leads to wasted resources, particularly considering labor time as a major expense. Tschohl, a seasoned trainer and author, identifies ten common pitfalls in training programs:
Excessive Group Sizes: Productive discussions are hampered by large groups. Limiting sessions to around 15 participants fosters engagement and skill development.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel Cyber Security Institute aims to enhance the skills of individuals and businesses in the field of cyber security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</guid><description>Singapore Telecommunications established the Singtel Cyber Security Institute (CSI) to bolster the cyber security skills of businesses and governments in the Asia Pacific region. The CSI is the first organization of its kind in the region, merging an advanced cyber range with an educational institute to provide companies with realistic training to handle complex cyber threats.
Bill Chang, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Group Enterprise CEO, highlighted the lack of preparedness among companies, with over 85% lacking robust cyber response plans or realistic training opportunities.</description></item><item><title>IamThirsty.com.sg is excited to announce that there are 10,000 training courses available on its portal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iamthirsty-com-sg-is-excited-to-announce-that-there-are-10-000-training-courses-available-on-its-portal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 15:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iamthirsty-com-sg-is-excited-to-announce-that-there-are-10-000-training-courses-available-on-its-portal/</guid><description>The online learning platform IamThirsty.com.sg has reached a milestone, now offering over 10,000 courses. Since its launch in February, the platform has seen a 25% increase in its course selection. This growth is projected to accelerate significantly following the Singapore government&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the SkillsFuture initiative.
IamThirsty.com.sg boasts an impressive average user engagement time of 23 minutes, a stark contrast to its competitors, who average just 3 minutes.
Winnie Khoo, Founder and CEO of IamThirsty.</description></item><item><title>IBM has raised concerns about the skills gap in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</guid><description>Source: IBM. Cover for the Upskilling India report.
IBM has released a study conducted by the IBM Institute for Business Value (IBV), in partnership with the Economist Intelligence Unit. This study assesses India&amp;rsquo;s increasing skills gap and offers suggestions to address the issue.
The study surveyed Indian executives, and most believe that the Indian workforce&amp;rsquo;s skills are on par with or better than those of other nations. However, only 40% reported that new employees possess the necessary skills.</description></item><item><title>Brexit must ensure that health is not negatively impacted, which includes ensuring that there are adequate rules in place for medical professional qualifications.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield argues that a Leave.EU tweet claiming EU regulations unnecessarily extend doctor training is misleading.
Hervey presents four key arguments: Firstly, the UK, as a long-standing EU member, significantly shaped EU medical training standards. While these standards do influence UK medical qualifications, their impact is limited, and the UK has the authority to propose changes. The current system, including the duration of training, reflects the UK&amp;rsquo;s active participation in shaping these regulations.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action.</description></item><item><title>SCALA, the Singapore Workforce Development Agency, is offering a logistics reskilling program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 14:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</guid><description>The Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA) and Supply Chain and Logistics Academy (SCALA) joined forces to launch the Logistics Professional Conversion Programme (PCP). The initiative aims to help professionals, managers, executives, and technicians (PMETs) gain the necessary skills to enter the logistics industry.
This program seeks to create opportunities for newcomers and seasoned professionals in logistics, allowing them to expand their skillsets and advance their careers. Over the next two years, the PCP will offer 150 positions for PMETs, specifically as Logistics Officers and Logistics Executives.</description></item><item><title>The increasing involvement of women in commerce and industry in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) in the Philippines has reported a rise in the number of women participating in skills training programs for traditionally male-dominated fields.
Amelito Cardenas, a supervising specialist at TESDA Pangasinan, mentioned that more women are enrolling in technical-vocational (tech-voc) and private institutions to learn trades such as welding and automotive repair, as reported by the Philippines Information Agency.
Cardenas also shared that TESDA offers a free training program specifically for women who run sari-sari stores and carinderia.</description></item><item><title>Consuming a balanced amount of protein helps dieters maintain muscle mass at a slower rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</guid><description>Source: Nestlé.
Nestlé Research Center collaborated with global scientists and found that consistent protein intake throughout the day might reduce muscle loss during weight loss attempts.
Published in the American Journal of Physiology - Endocrinology and Metabolism, the study explored ways to promote weight loss in obese older men while preventing muscle loss. Muscle loss can hinder weight loss, decrease strength and functional capacity, and heighten the risk of disability and mortality.</description></item><item><title>CIMB introduces a program to enhance the skills of non-executive employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</guid><description>CIMB Group, the second-largest financial services provider in Malaysia, has initiated a program to enhance the skills, productivity, career advancement prospects, and earning potential of its non-executive employees. This program, known as the CIMB Accelerated Career Enhancement Programme (CIMB ACE), was officially launched by Dato’ Sri Richard Riot Anak Jaem, the Minister of Human Resources.
The CIMB ACE program aligns with PR1ME (Program Majudiri 1Malaysia), a national initiative launched by the Prime Minister of Malaysia in November 2013.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the opportunity to apply for government grants to assist with their studies in infocomm, media, and design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</guid><description>Singaporeans working in Infocomm, Media, and Design can apply for the SkillsFuture Study Awards until June 14, 2016.
Announced during the Ministry of Communications and Information’s Committee of Supply Debate for 2016, the SkillsFuture Study Award encourages Singaporeans to enhance their skills in sectors crucial for future economic growth. Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, stated that 310 awards will be granted to Singaporeans in the early or middle stages of their careers who are looking to advance their skills in these sectors.</description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community.</description></item><item><title>At Shopee University: achieving that perfect Instagram shot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-shopee-university-achieving-that-perfect-instagram-shot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 17:34:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-shopee-university-achieving-that-perfect-instagram-shot/</guid><description>To celebrate the launch of Shopee University, Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, hosted a practical Shopee University session for the media. This session gave attendees a preview of the experience Shopee sellers and the public can expect.
Each free session lasts around 60 to 90 minutes. Students must complete two basic and two advanced classes to qualify for expert classes. After that, they can attend unlimited expert sessions. The photography class showcased here is considered an advanced to expert level class.</description></item><item><title>The Dalio Market Principles Online Program has been launched on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalio-market-principles-online-program-has-been-launched-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 02:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalio-market-principles-online-program-has-been-launched-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Wealth Management Institute (WMI) has introduced the Dalio Market Principles (DMP) Online Program to provide accessible, high-quality investment education globally.
This program, grounded in Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s five decades of experience and research, aims to help participants grasp the interconnected forces influencing markets and economies. Using advanced technology like generative AI, it delivers an engaging learning journey accessible from anywhere, at any time.
Dalio, Founder, CIO Mentor and Member of the Board at Bridgewater Associates, emphasizes the unprecedented changes the world is witnessing.</description></item><item><title>Tech Jobs Come Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</guid><description>Although the Great Recession continues, the impact varies across industries. In fact, the technology sector is performing quite well in terms of employment. From November to December of last year, while 85,000 jobs were lost overall, the tech industry actually added 5,200 new positions. This suggests that technology might be a promising field.
However, having technological skills doesn&amp;rsquo;t guarantee employment. Many factory workers, for instance, would likely agree. The manufacturing sector was already moving overseas even before the recession.</description></item><item><title>SmartUp introduces the Digital Readiness Experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</guid><description>Source: SmartUp website.
Screen capture of the SmartUp
platform.
SmartUp, a mobile-first knowledge-sharing platform, has introduced a Digital Readiness Experience. This offering utilizes microlearning modules to educate the workforce on trending technology topics.
This multi-week Digital Readiness Experience is available for purchase by SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s corporate clients for their employees, as explained by Deborah Tan-Pink, SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s Global Head of Marketing.
&amp;ldquo;The Digital Readiness Experience is a four-to-six-week program designed to shift attitudes and knowledge.</description></item><item><title>The language learning app HelloTalk has reached 1 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</guid><description>Source: HelloTalk app page at the Play Store.
The mobile language learning app HelloTalk has reached over one million registered users globally, according to its developer, HelloTalk.
The HelloTalk app allows users to teach each other their native languages using their mobile devices. Users can communicate in real-time with native speakers through various features, helping them practice their target language.
Over one million HelloTalk users, representing over 200 countries, use the app to learn various languages.</description></item></channel></rss>