<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eurozone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eurozone/</link><description>Recent content in Eurozone on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eurozone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The European Citizens' Initiative and Greek debt: A surprising pairing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</guid><description>Anastasia Karatzia, Law Lecturer, University of Essex
Introduction
Decisions from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on the European and Monetary Union (EMU) are infrequent. Recent cases on this topic, including landmark judgments like Pringle and Gauweiler, have addressed measures enacted during the Eurozone crisis. Among these decisions is Anagnostakis v Commission, a case challenging the Commission&amp;rsquo;s refusal to register a proposed European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI) titled &amp;ldquo;One million signatures for solidarity.</description></item><item><title>Looking beyond austerity: the future of employment law in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Catherine Barnard, Trinity College Cambridge
Contrary to critics, the EU social model (ESM) is not dead, argues Professor Barnard. Although facing significant challenges, the ESM has historically demonstrated a capacity for renewal. This post explores potential future directions for the model.
While some believe a Social Union is necessary for Europe, this post focuses on a potentially more agreeable agenda for the EU-28, particularly in the area of employment law.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft UK/EU renegotiation deal considered to be 'legally binding and irreversible'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The draft agreement regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership has sparked significant debate. While some, mostly within the UK, believe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough, others, primarily from the remaining EU member states, argue it grants excessive revisions to EU law for a single member state. These are primarily substantive concerns. While I have previously addressed some immigration-related issues within the draft, I will delve into other substantive matters later.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural report of the European Fiscal Board and the outlook for the EU's fiscal framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-report-of-the-european-fiscal-board-and-the-outlook-for-the-eu-s-fiscal-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 05:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-report-of-the-european-fiscal-board-and-the-outlook-for-the-eu-s-fiscal-framework/</guid><description>Paul Dermine (PhD candidate in EU institutional law, Maastricht University) and Diane Fromage (Assistant Professor of European Law, Faculty of Law, Maastricht University)
EU Fiscal Governance after the Crisis: A Time for Reflection and the European Fiscal Board&amp;rsquo;s First Report
Recent developments suggest that the Eurozone may be entering a new phase. With the sovereign debt crisis subsiding and economic growth gradually returning, discussions about reforming the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) are resurfacing at both the EU and member state levels.</description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the Euro's downfall? EU regulations on exiting EMU or defaulting on debts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The stability of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) is once again in question after a period of relative calm. This follows the announcement of early elections in Greece. Should the anti-austerity party, Syriza, gain control of the government, the consequences could be significant.
It is crucial to note that such an outcome is not guaranteed. Syriza holds a small lead in the polls, and even if they become the leading party, they might not secure enough seats to hold a majority.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Thomas Piketty to bring about reform in both capitalism and democracy within the European Union?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</guid><description>Steve Peers
French economist Thomas Piketty unexpectedly became a prominent intellectual figure, especially in the UK and US, with his book &amp;ldquo;Capital,&amp;rdquo; which presents a new perspective on the relationship between capitalism and democracy.
Maintaining his engagement with current issues, Piketty has contributed to a proposal for EU reform, connecting his academic work to practical solutions.
The EU, once adept at managing capitalism but less so democracy, now struggles with both.</description></item></channel></rss>