<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Success on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/success/</link><description>Recent content in Success on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/success/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor outlines four key pillars for a successful expansion into emerging markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, has published an e-book titled &amp;ldquo;Succeed in Emerging Markets: Selection, Strategy and First Steps&amp;rdquo;. This e-book presents a four-pillar model designed to guide businesses entering emerging markets.
The first pillar, &amp;ldquo;market,&amp;rdquo; examines macroeconomic stability, consumer market size, growth, and openness.
The second pillar, &amp;ldquo;population,&amp;rdquo; delves into demographics to help businesses assess how their products or services align with the competitive landscape.
The third pillar, &amp;ldquo;access,&amp;rdquo; evaluates the ease of market entry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Success in business relies on establishing a broad network, having a strong passion, dedicating time, and learning from numerous failures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 03:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</guid><description>Alex Foo, co-founder of the entrepreneur-focused psychometric profiling tool Starteur, offers three key tips for entrepreneurial success. These insights, derived from both his attendance at the Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 (June 22-24, USA) and his personal journey as a young entrepreneur, were shared during a Shopee University session. Foo&amp;rsquo;s trip to GES 2016 was sponsored by Shopee, the e-commerce platform by Garena. This sponsorship reflects Shopee&amp;rsquo;s commitment to nurturing the next generation of Singaporean entrepreneurs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips for achieving success with your startup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</guid><description>Thinking about launching a business from your great idea? Fabian Vandenreydt, a leader at Innotribe and the SWIFT Institute, who has witnessed the ups and downs of fintech startups, highlights key success factors.
First, clearly define the problem you&amp;rsquo;re addressing and ensure it&amp;rsquo;s a genuine issue. Developing a fantastic product is futile without a problem to solve. Vandenreydt emphasizes that starting with a problem is crucial for success.
Second, articulate a detailed solution implementation plan and understand your target market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are now blending their physical and digital experiences. How should companies respond?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</guid><description>A new study emphasizes the importance of personalization in merging online and offline shopping experiences for &amp;ldquo;phy-gital&amp;rdquo; consumers. The study found that while companies are embracing digital technologies, they are lagging in implementing personalization strategies that consumers desire.
The study revealed that personalized promotions significantly influence purchasing decisions, encouraging consumers to buy familiar products and explore new ones. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between consumer expectations and company investments. While consumers value enhanced search and comparison features, companies prioritize features like shopping lists and social elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singapore retailer utilizes Qlik and Deloitte Digital solution to monitor customer narratives over time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</guid><description>Inverted Edge, a Singapore-based online retailer, is enhancing the customer experience at its Scotts Square location. Using technology from Qlik, a visual analytics company, and design by Deloitte Digital, the store provides a unique and interactive digital shopping experience.
Source: Inverted Edge website.
In addition to its selection of high-quality, modern luxury clothing, the store features a dynamic display of customer photos and stories from social media. This constantly updated feed showcases how customers style their purchases and shares their experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HubSpot uncovers the true desires of buyers when it comes to salespeople</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</guid><description>HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s recent report, Asia Pacific Buyers Have Spoken: Sales Needs to Evolve, reveals what Asia Pacific buyers desire in a sales experience, from initial call topics to the best time for sales interactions.
The report suggests that sales isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily becoming more challenging, but rather traditional sales strategies are losing their effectiveness. The mismatch between current sales tactics and buyer expectations is the root of the problem. HubSpot asserts that conversions will increase if salespeople align their approach with buyer preferences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Outlier Effect And Your Success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-outlier-effect-and-your-success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-outlier-effect-and-your-success/</guid><description>Is a feeling of sadness common for you during this time of year? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable, particularly when the excitement of the holidays fades and life slows down. It&amp;rsquo;s a time when we reflect on our accomplishments and disappointments. And then we come across stories about overnight successes, making us question if some people are just wired for success while others aren&amp;rsquo;t.
Malcolm Gladwell&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Outliers,&amp;rdquo; challenges the notion of what truly defines success...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-outlier-effect-and-your-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-outlier-effect-and-your-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Having good toilet facilities is beneficial for business, according to MyTravelResearch.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/having-good-toilet-facilities-is-beneficial-for-business-according-to-mytravelresearch-com/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 19:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/having-good-toilet-facilities-is-beneficial-for-business-according-to-mytravelresearch-com/</guid><description>Source: Restroom Association Singapore website. The Restroom Association Singapore runs the Happy Toilet program. Their website features an interactive map highlighting Singaporean toilets that earned three, four, five, or six-star Happy Toilet ratings. This initiative, launched in 2003, evaluates public restrooms based on criteria like design, cleanliness, functionality, upkeep, and user experience.
Finding clean, dependable, and functional public restrooms remains a global challenge, according to Bronwyn White, Co-founder of MyTravelResearch...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/having-good-toilet-facilities-is-beneficial-for-business-according-to-mytravelresearch-com/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/having-good-toilet-facilities-is-beneficial-for-business-according-to-mytravelresearch-com/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra emphasizes the importance of educating and incentivizing employees to guarantee the success of UC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that makes audio solutions, believes the tech industry needs to rethink its definition of success for unified communications (UC) deployments.
Source: Jabra website.
Currently, only 10% of companies use UC. This is because employees don&amp;rsquo;t want to give up their current tools and ways of working. Companies are spending a lot of money on UC, but employees don&amp;rsquo;t see how it can help them be more productive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>