<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Toxic Waste on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/toxic-waste/</link><description>Recent content in Toxic Waste on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 19:32:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/toxic-waste/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recycle Your Old iPhone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-old-iphone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 19:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-old-iphone-for-cash/</guid><description>The release of the new iPhone 3G is approaching, and early adopters and tech enthusiasts are eager to get their hands on it. The enhanced features, including faster data speeds, GPS, and expanded application support, make it a significant upgrade. However, the cost of upgrading from the first-generation iPhone is a concern for many.
Recent reports suggest that AT&amp;amp;T will offer a trade-in program for iPhones purchased after May 27th in pristine condition.</description></item><item><title>Would You Eat This Cell Phone?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-eat-this-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-eat-this-cell-phone/</guid><description>Electronic waste is a significant environmental concern, leading communities to implement recycling initiatives for electronics like TVs and computers. While sending old devices to recyclers is helpful, addressing the problem at its source is crucial.
Our reliance on electronics is undeniable, and reverting to a world without them is improbable. However, we must acknowledge the environmental impact of discarding billions of electronic devices.
Recycling is a positive step, but designing less toxic electronics is even more effective.</description></item><item><title>Green Solution For Old Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-solution-for-old-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 11:36:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-solution-for-old-cell-phones/</guid><description>Do you secretly collect old cell phones? It seems like everyone has a drawer or basement corner filled with them, all sharing one common trait: they no longer work.
The issue with cell phones is that they become outdated long before they stop working. While some might suffer accidental drops or crushing defeats, most could easily be revived with a simple charge and a cellular service plan. However, that&amp;rsquo;s where the catch lies - the cost of the plans.</description></item><item><title>Greening The Product Life Cycle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/greening-the-product-life-cycle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/greening-the-product-life-cycle/</guid><description>Products used to be designed, made, transported, sold, used, and discarded without much connection between those stages. However, we are transitioning to a time where each step in a product&amp;rsquo;s life will be synchronized and often designed to minimize environmental impact.
The old saying &amp;ldquo;use it up, wear it out, make it do or do without&amp;rdquo; reflects a different mindset than the industrial age&amp;rsquo;s emphasis on planned obsolescence and disposability. As environmental concerns grow, we might be shifting back towards those earlier values of resourcefulness.</description></item></channel></rss>