<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Forwarding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/forwarding/</link><description>Recent content in Forwarding on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:55:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/forwarding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flat Rate Toll Free Numbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-toll-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:55:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-toll-free-numbers/</guid><description>Are you searching for a reliable toll-free number for your business with predictable billing? Look no further than flat-rate toll-free service. Enjoy a consistent monthly bill and a comprehensive package of features without any additional charges. Additionally, there&amp;rsquo;s no risk involved as you can test the service with a complimentary 14-day trial.
iTeleCenter offers an unlimited calling flat-rate service for just $49 per month. With this plan, you can say goodbye to per-minute charges, feature fees, activation fees, surcharges, hidden fees, confusing plans, and contracts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-toll-free-numbers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-toll-free-numbers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL introduces new freight service from Taiwan to Austria for shipments smaller than a full container</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding has introduced a new weekly Less-than-Container-Load (LCL) service originating in Taiwan and arriving in Vienna, Austria, by way of Koper, Slovenia. This service, departing every Monday from Keelung or Kaohsiung, allows Taiwanese exporters to ship cargo with a 35-day transit time to Vienna.
Kelvin Leung, CEO, Asia Pacific at DHL Global Forwarding, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to understanding industry trends and supporting exporters. He highlighted the increasing demand for Asian products in Eastern Europe and positioned the new service as a way to strengthen trade partnerships and improve the speed and efficiency of services for Taiwanese businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>