<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tableau Public on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tableau-public/</link><description>Recent content in Tableau Public on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tableau-public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tableau Public undergoes a makeover as participation increases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</guid><description>Source: Tableau Public gallery. This Tableau Public visualization displays the world&amp;rsquo;s largest stadiums. Interact with the visualization here.
Tableau reported that 36,000 users joined Tableau Public in 2014, publishing a record number of data stories on the free platform. Tableau Public allows users to create, share, and discover data stories on the web. It comprises a downloadable authoring tool for exploring and visualizing data, a cloud platform for hosting, sharing, and embedding interactive visualizations, and a learning program offering support and training to a global community of data enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Create interactive data visualizations with our free tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/create-interactive-data-visualizations-with-our-free-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/create-interactive-data-visualizations-with-our-free-tool/</guid><description>Source: Tableau Public website.
Unlike print, online content typically benefits from interactivity, often through clickable links. What if we applied this interactivity, similar to interactive infographics, to modern graphics to present more data in the same amount of space?
Tableau Software, a company focused on making data accessible, allows us to create interactive infographics using Tableau Public, a free tool that enables embedding visualizations into web pages. Although not new (videos from 2010 are available online), Tableau Public is poised for increased popularity given the rise of infographics.</description></item></channel></rss>