<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unified Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Unified Communications on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item><item><title>Tata Communications updates the jamvee unified communications platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications provider, recently launched the newest version of its cloud-based unified communications platform, jamvee.
Source: Jamvee website.
Leveraging Tata Communications&amp;rsquo; robust global network, jamvee consolidates various client software and devices into a single, secure, and versatile platform. This approach streamlines communication and collaboration within and across organizations, allowing employees, suppliers, and customers to connect seamlessly using any combination of audio, video, messaging, and content sharing tools, regardless of their device or browser.</description></item><item><title>Here’s Why Companies Actually Want BYOD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The concept of &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) can be a real headache for IT managers. While employees may enjoy the convenience, it poses a significant risk to a company&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data. When personal devices connect to the company network, carefully constructed security protocols are often bypassed. So, what can be done?
Many companies address this issue by drawing a hard line. Recognizing the challenges of managing diverse personal devices, they prohibit their use for business purposes altogether.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>Why Business Needs Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There was a time when the only way to communicate electronically was with that clunky black phone on your desk. While that phone might still be there, modern technology has made it lighter and brought a wealth of new communication methods. Email, text messages, mobile phone calls, and video chats are now commonplace across various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, smartphones, and even watches.
A significant challenge, particularly in business, is that these platforms and applications don&amp;rsquo;t always work well together.</description></item><item><title>E911 For Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>The transition from traditional phone lines to internet-based calling has brought about some unexpected issues, particularly with emergency services. We often take 911 for granted, assuming help will always be on the way. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case with internet-based phone systems.
Imagine a scenario where a fire breaks out in your office. You dial 911, report the emergency, and evacuate. However, the fire department ends up at your company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters instead of your current location.</description></item><item><title>Can You Save 50% With Unified Communications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</guid><description>As your company expands, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely seen a simultaneous increase in your telephone costs. While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this is simply due to having more employees making calls, the reality is that not all phone expenses are unavoidable.
Unified communications technology can help you significantly reduce unnecessary costs. This approach combines your voice, data, and video networks into a single, unified system, leading to cost savings for businesses of all sizes, even those with just one location.</description></item><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand.</description></item><item><title>Your Desk Just Moved To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 10:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The 20th century saw a significant shift in employment, moving from farm work to factory jobs and finally to office positions. Now, the 21st century is experiencing another major change as workplaces transition from offices to the cloud.
The Cloud is Here and Now
Contrary to the idea of the cloud being a distant concept, it has become an integral part of our present reality. Nearly everything we do has or will soon have a cloud connection.</description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access.</description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item><item><title>Jabra introduces the Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company known for creating intelligent audio devices, has introduced the Jabra Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset. This new headset is a unified communication (UC) upgrade from their original Jabra Stealth and is designed specifically for professionals who are often on the go.
Weighing in at a mere 0.24 ounces (approximately 6.8 grams), the Jabra Stealth UC is remarkably lightweight, making it both inconspicuous and incredibly easy to carry around.</description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications.</description></item><item><title>Jabra emphasizes the importance of educating and incentivizing employees to guarantee the success of UC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that makes audio solutions, believes the tech industry needs to rethink its definition of success for unified communications (UC) deployments.
Source: Jabra website.
Currently, only 10% of companies use UC. This is because employees don&amp;rsquo;t want to give up their current tools and ways of working. Companies are spending a lot of money on UC, but employees don&amp;rsquo;t see how it can help them be more productive.</description></item></channel></rss>