<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecommunications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecommunications/</link><description>Recent content in Telecommunications on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecommunications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore.</description></item><item><title>Is The End Of Cellular Phone Near?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</guid><description>Cell phones are essential to modern life, but a recent development calls into question the future of cellular service. The release of the Apple iPad and its allowance of VoIP applications over 3G cellular networks, along with AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network adjustments for this capability, signal a potential shift in the telecommunications landscape.
Why is this significant? Cellular networks have historically blocked VoIP due to its potential to congest networks and cannibalize voice call revenue.</description></item><item><title>Contract Expiration Means Opportunity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</guid><description>Business telecom services often come with fixed-price contracts lasting 1 to 3 years, providing price stability but limited cost-saving opportunities. However, the fear of potential price increases upon contract renewal is often overstated. In many cases, businesses can find better deals by exploring alternative providers.
The misconception about limited options arises from a perceived lack of competition. While you may have negotiated what seemed like the best price at the time, there are often numerous competitive service providers not listed in traditional directories.</description></item><item><title>DS1 Telephone Service Lowers Business Phone Bills</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</guid><description>DS1, more commonly known as T1, is a digital telecommunications standard that can potentially save businesses substantial amounts of money on their phone bills. Despite its benefits, many people are unfamiliar with it.
Although the terms are often used interchangeably, there&amp;rsquo;s a slight distinction between DS1 and T1. DS1 (Digital Signal 1) refers to the format of the digital signal transmitted over the line, while T1 describes the physical four-wire copper connection itself.</description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Services Proliferate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</guid><description>The increasing need for bandwidth in the business world has driven the rapid expansion of high-speed voice and data services. While T1 lines were once considered high-end, businesses now have a variety of options, including various DSx copper and fiber optic connections, wireless broadband, and even point-to-point laser technology.
DS3 is gaining popularity as companies find their T1 connections inadequate. Upgrading from a DS1&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 Mbps to DS3&amp;rsquo;s 45 Mbps accommodates more users and allows for dedicated internet connections.</description></item><item><title>T1 PRI is More Than Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</guid><description>T1 lines are the most common way to link PBX phone systems to the telephone network. T1 PRI service is often the preferred choice because it can transmit Caller ID information to business phones or call centers. However, there are additional ways that T1 PRI can offer the most budget-friendly phone line trunking.
T1 PRI is a highly specialized telecom service. T1 lines have been in use for over half a century to carry phone calls, and more recently, for point-to-point data, dedicated internet service, and connections to private networks.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</guid><description>The current focus on infrastructure often overlooks a critical element: fiber optic broadband. While roads, bridges, and utilities are essential, fiber optic networks are the backbone of the 21st-century economy. Just as electricity revolutionized the 20th century, fiber optics will define this one.
We&amp;rsquo;ve outgrown the limitations of traditional wireline systems. Fiber optic technology, with its capacity for high bandwidth, is the only way to meet the growing demand for data-intensive applications.</description></item><item><title>Tell Me You're Not PAYING For Equipment Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</guid><description>Stop wasting money on expensive equipment leads that often lead nowhere.
There&amp;rsquo;s a smarter way to generate sales and marketing leads for your telephone systems and IT networking equipment: commission-based leads. This means you receive qualified leads from serious businesses in your area as they emerge, completely free of charge. You then select the leads you want to pursue and focus your efforts on closing the deal. Only after a successful sale and payment from the customer do you share a small percentage with the agency that provided the lead.</description></item><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency.</description></item><item><title>E-Rate Discounted Broadband Internet for Schools and Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</guid><description>Educational institutions and libraries are demanding high-speed internet, which has become essential for business, personal growth, and various types of learning. While most public resources have some internet access, there is increasing pressure to enhance speed for more users and advanced applications. The main obstacle is the cost.
Discounted Service is Available A government program offers discounts of 20% to 90% on broadband internet upgrades for most K-12 schools and libraries.</description></item><item><title>Attention: Telephone System Dealers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</guid><description>For businesses selling, installing, or servicing business telephone systems, a new business model called the VAR Network is gaining popularity nationwide. This model helps generate more business without requiring upfront expenses.
The VAR Network is an online database system showcasing business profiles of numerous telephone and computer networking dealers. This fully automated platform connects potential customers seeking telecom assistance with qualified dealers in their area. Dealers are notified of potential matches and can choose to pursue these opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Do national data retention laws fall under the jurisdiction of the Charter?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
After the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidated the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive, a crucial question emerged: do those same rules affect national data retention laws? This post will explain why that&amp;rsquo;s the case.
We begin with Article 51 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights. It states that the Charter applies to EU institutions and bodies, but to Member States &amp;lsquo;only&amp;rsquo; when &amp;lsquo;implementing&amp;rsquo; EU law.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times.</description></item><item><title>Free Telecom Consulting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, many companies are hesitant to hire consultants due to budget constraints. While consultants can potentially save money in the long run, the initial expense can be difficult to justify. So, how can businesses access consulting services without breaking the bank? The answer is free consulting.
One company offers free technical consulting specializing in business telecommunications. By submitting an online inquiry or calling their toll-free number, businesses can connect with a consultant for immediate assistance.</description></item><item><title>High Quality Call Termination With SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Prioritizing voice packets on a network ensures high-quality VoIP calls within an organization. However, connecting to the outside world poses a challenge due to the incompatibility between modern packet-switched networks and the traditional circuit-switched phone system. To bridge this gap, organizations can either manage the conversion internally or outsource it to a third-party provider through SIP trunking.
SIP trunking offers a potentially cost-effective solution by consolidating multiple phone lines into a single &amp;ldquo;trunk&amp;rdquo; line and utilizing the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for call switching.</description></item><item><title>Carrier Neutral Connectivity at Colocation Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses struggling to find enough bandwidth might be overlooking a simpler solution. Instead of waiting for carriers to come to them, companies can benefit by going where the carriers already are.
Colocation Centers: A Hub for Connectivity
Carriers are drawn to locations called colocation centers, or colos, and carrier hotels. These large data centers are designed to accommodate multiple tenants, unlike typical data centers that serve a single company.</description></item><item><title>Twice the T1 Line Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your internet connection feeling a little slow? That T1 line that used to be more than enough might be struggling to keep up with your current needs. You&amp;rsquo;re not the only one experiencing this. While T1 bandwidth was sufficient for even large companies a decade ago, today, even small and medium-sized businesses are finding themselves needing more. The shift towards online applications and connectivity, while beneficial for productivity, has led to a significant increase in bandwidth demands.</description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Phone Lines For PBX Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 16:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</guid><description>Many modern business phone systems utilize T-1 lines to link their buildings to the local telephone company. This is because merging multiple individual lines into one or two T-1 lines is more cost-efficient. This holds true whether your internal phone system is analog or digital, as even most VoIP systems rely on T-1 lines for external calls.
Smaller setups like basic one or two-line phones or key systems with 4-6 lines typically use analog lines.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth is Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Business bandwidth solutions are significantly more expensive than residential options like DSL or Cable. While this is partly due to their guaranteed reliability and dedicated lines, another factor is the complex infrastructure involved. Providing business-grade services often requires collaboration between a long-haul carrier and the local phone company for the final connection.
Despite recent price drops in dedicated T1 connections, high-bandwidth services remain costly, potentially hindering smaller companies needing to transmit large amounts of data.</description></item><item><title>New EU Regulatory Guidelines for Net Neutrality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
New EU regulations designed to ensure equal treatment of internet traffic were enacted in the fall of 2015 and implemented in April 2016. These net neutrality rules were intended to prevent discrimination by internet service providers and promote innovation, but their effectiveness was debated.
The regulations stipulate that internet providers should treat all traffic the same, regardless of the source, content, or device. However, the vague language and exceptions within the regulations led to uncertainty regarding the level of protection for users and permitted provider activities.</description></item><item><title>Finding Information on PBX Telephone Systems Pricing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 15:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</guid><description>Planning a new office building or hotel? Upgrading your old business phone system? Finding the right PBX system at the right price is essential for a smart decision.
Instead of searching endlessly, utilize an online clearinghouse like the VAR Network. This platform connects businesses with qualified PBX and network equipment vendors.
The VAR Network focuses on these two interconnected technologies. Most businesses rely on both for internal communication and internet access.</description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues.</description></item><item><title>Broadview Networks OfficeSuite Brings The Cloud To SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</guid><description>Smaller companies often want to adopt money-saving technologies like VoIP, private networks, and cloud services, but the initial investment can be daunting. While internet-based options seem appealing, their quality and reliability are often a concern. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for businesses of all sizes to access these advanced tools without breaking the bank.
Broadview Networks&amp;rsquo; OfficeSuite offers a comprehensive solution, effectively serving as a company&amp;rsquo;s central office across multiple locations. This enterprise-grade PBX system provides the functionality of a traditional system with the convenience of easy administration through a web browser.</description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable.</description></item><item><title>Telexplainer Expectations For 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</guid><description>As we begin a promising new year for business and technology, let&amp;rsquo;s explore some key trends for 2011 and how to leverage them.
Bandwidth demands will continue to escalate this year, as they do annually. The economic recovery will likely generate increased internet traffic as more individuals return to work. Expect bandwidth demand to surge proportionally with employment, if not more. During the recession, businesses learned to enhance individual productivity by investing in technology.</description></item><item><title>Where Are T1 Lines Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of unreliable DSL and cable internet for your business, consider a T1 line. While DSL and cable are suitable for home use, T1 offers a different level of service. As a regulated telecommunications service, T1 ensures consistent bandwidth and reliable uptime, unlike the consumer-grade alternatives.
T1 lines are widely accessible for businesses and function similarly to utilities. If your business has electricity, water, and phone service, you can likely get a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>The Pi1M Training Programme offered by Digi provides benefits to small business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Participants of the Pi1M Training Programme gathered for a group photo.
Digi Telecommunications recently conducted a training program for community members residing near the company-managed Pusat Internet 1 Malaysia (Pi1M) centers. This tailored program reflects Digi&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering online entrepreneurship within its Pi1M communities. Currently, Digi manages 34 Pi1Ms across Pahang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Johor, Melaka, and Sarawak, with plans to establish 70 more centers by year&amp;rsquo;s end.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Concatenation for Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Many businesses are choosing Carrier Ethernet services for their wide area and metropolitan area networks. Ethernet is directly compatible with local area networks and offers greater bandwidth than traditional telecom services like T1 (1.5 Mbps) and DS3 (45 Mbps). The demand for bandwidth is rising as more content shifts from emails and simple websites to videos and high-resolution images. Ethernet (10 Mbps), Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), and Gigabit Ethernet (1,000 Mbps) often provide the most cost-effective solutions for bandwidth expansion.</description></item><item><title>There Will Be Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</guid><description>The 19th and 20th centuries were defined by the gold rush and oil boom, respectively. Similarly, the 21st century is witnessing a fiber optic revolution. Fiber optic communication has become essential for modern businesses. This era presents lucrative opportunities for entrepreneurs to capitalize on the insatiable demand for high-bandwidth communication. A new technology has emerged, promising to reshape the competitive landscape.
Consider a scenario where two telecommunications providers are discussing the industry.</description></item><item><title>LMDS Fills the Fiber Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</guid><description>Although fiber optic bandwidth is widely available across the country, connecting businesses to this network over the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; is a different story. It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to realize that less than 20% of commercial buildings are equipped for fiber optic telecommunications services.
This is primarily due to the high cost of installing fiber optic cables, a process that&amp;rsquo;s difficult to justify when businesses already have access to telephone and data services through existing copper lines.</description></item><item><title>Branching Out With MPLS and VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</guid><description>Is secure communication between multiple locations critical for your business? As businesses increasingly rely on electronic forms and transactions, traditional methods like fax machines, overnight mail, and dial-up connections are no longer sufficient. To stay competitive, businesses need real-time access to sales and inventory data, rapid transfer of large files like medical images and CAD drawings, and instant delivery of important documents. A broadband connection linking all your key locations is essential.</description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>How Does Cloud Computing Work In Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is frequently used today. But what exactly is it, and how can it benefit your business by improving efficiency, speed, and affordability? Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into it.
In business, the term &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; often carries a negative connotation, implying uncertainty and unpredictability. Naturally, clarity and predictability are preferred, especially from a financial standpoint. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable why people might be skeptical when advised to transition their business to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>How AI is Helping to Improve Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Customer service calls are increasingly frustrating due to rising costs and labor shortages, negatively impacting both customers and companies. Tech expert David Pogue, in a CBS News report, suggests a blend of human agents and AI as a solution.
One such AI, called Grace, can handle customer interactions independently. However, AI like Grace can falter in complex situations, necessitating a transfer to human agents. While some of the best agents are located internationally and may have accents, this can be a hurdle for some US customers.</description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond.</description></item><item><title>TW Telecom's Extensive Service Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</guid><description>tw telecom is a full-service communications provider with a privately owned, nationwide fiber optic network. They provide service in 75 major markets and over 8,800 commercial buildings. Their network spans more than 26,000 route miles and features a 10 Gbps IP backbone. They offer a wide array of services, from affordable T1 lines to high-speed Carrier Ethernet services ranging from 2 Mbps to 10 Gbps.
You might recognize the name tw telecom from its previous iterations.</description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation.</description></item><item><title>Staying Out of the Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 19:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</guid><description>While the use of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is widespread in information technology, understanding its complexities is crucial. The cloud often represents large, intricate networks that users may not fully comprehend.
Although many users are content with the cloud&amp;rsquo;s seemingly magical abilities, David G. Rusin, CEO of American Fiber Systems, argues against perceiving internet clouds as uniform entities. He emphasizes the differences in integrity, reliability, and delivery among cloud providers, highlighting the importance of scrutinizing these aspects.</description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Steal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</guid><description>Everyone appreciates a bargain, especially for telecommunications services. The current prices for Ethernet might even make you wonder if they&amp;rsquo;re legitimate. To see just how competitive these prices are, take a moment to compare Ethernet costs for your business locations.
The reason Ethernet services are so affordable now is due to rapid technological advancements. Until recently, traditional telephone company services were the only option. Today, competition has introduced alternatives that have completely changed the landscape.</description></item><item><title>How T1 and E1 Lines Compare</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-and-e1-lines-compare/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-and-e1-lines-compare/</guid><description>T1 and E1 are two widely used digital line services for voice and data, each prevalent in different geographical regions. While T1 is common in the US, Canada, Japan, and South Korea, E1 dominates Europe and most other parts of the world. The &amp;ldquo;T&amp;rdquo; in T1 comes from &amp;ldquo;T-Carrier,&amp;rdquo; a standard developed by Bell Labs after World War II for carrying multiple phone calls between switching centers. Similarly, the &amp;ldquo;E&amp;rdquo; in E1 stands for &amp;ldquo;Europe.</description></item><item><title>QT Talk is Both VoIP and Dial-Around</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</guid><description>Many people are interested in VoIP phone service because of its features and affordability, but they also want the freedom of mobile calling. QT Talk offers a solution that combines the advantages of VoIP with the flexibility of cellular service.
QT Talk provides a feature-rich VoIP service, including their popular North America Plus plan. For a low monthly fee, users enjoy unlimited calls to the U.S., Canada, and Puerto Rico, along with a reduced rate to select international destinations.</description></item><item><title>Ignore That PBX Behind the Curtain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:31:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</guid><description>Operating a small business doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to sound like it, especially with tools like virtual PBX systems. These systems can give your two-person office the professional edge of a Fortune 500 corporation.
Traditional PBX systems, standard in large companies, offer features such as individual extensions, direct dialing, call transferring, and outside line access. However, they come with a hefty price tag. iTeleCenter, a virtual PBX solution, offers an affordable alternative that transforms your existing phones into a robust communication system.</description></item><item><title>Experimenting with EU governance in the Telecoms sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:29:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</guid><description>Marta Cantero (Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Helsinki | FiDiPro Project)
Creating a unified digital market for telecommunications within Europe is a primary goal of the current European Commission. [i] However, achieving this single market remains a distant prospect. The current multi-tiered regulatory model for European telecommunications relies heavily on individual nations&amp;rsquo; regulatory bodies to implement the EU&amp;rsquo;s telecom framework. Furthermore, enforcing this framework falls upon the Member States themselves under their own national procedures.</description></item></channel></rss>