<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1696SMBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1696smbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 1696SMBG4000 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1696smbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Wiring Sleeve of Carriage Harness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable, previously restored in 2020, was brought in for repairs due to an oscillating solenoid issue. However, upon inspection, a more critical problem was discovered: the wiring harness sleeve was severely damaged, exposing the wires.
This level of damage had never been encountered before. Thankfully, the wires themselves were still intact. The timing of the solenoid problem was fortunate, as further use could have led to wire damage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Smoking Solenoid Resistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</guid><description>This continues my series &amp;ldquo;A Fun Evening with&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A Beogram 4000 turntable, which I had previously restored, was returned with a malfunctioning arm lowering mechanism and a burning smell.
I removed the turntable from its case and took off the aluminum plates to examine it. When I powered it on, it initially started up as usual, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower at the record&amp;rsquo;s starting point. Instead, there was a strong burning smell and a plume of smoke coming from the circuit board with the carriage switches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair and Exploration of an Intermittently Oscillating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</guid><description>This section details the work done on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s oscillating solenoid, and what was learned about winding solenoid coils and comparing them to the original.
The arm lowering mechanism is shown here:
When the control logic initiates arm lowering, the solenoid pushes the solenoid lever forward. The lever opens the solenoid switch when fully extended, decreasing the current flowing through the solenoid to a level just enough to keep it engaged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Arm, Replacement of the Damper Gasket and Re-Glueing of a Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 required a few final adjustments before it could be returned to its owner following a wiring sleeve replacement on the carriage harness and a fix for an intermittent solenoid.
During its initial restoration in 2020, I was unfamiliar with some common problems that these turntables develop. One such issue involves the damper gasket, which tends to harden over time. This hardening can lead to uneven arm lowering due to inconsistent airflow around the gasket...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Time with a Suddenly Activating Solenoid, an Anemic Carriage Motor, and an AC Motor Driver with a Weak Driver Amplitude</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-time-with-a-suddenly-activating-solenoid-an-anemic-carriage-motor-and-an-ac-motor-driver-with-a-weak-driver-amplitude/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 18:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-time-with-a-suddenly-activating-solenoid-an-anemic-carriage-motor-and-an-ac-motor-driver-with-a-weak-driver-amplitude/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m repairing a Beogram 4000 turntable and encountered some unusual problems. After rebuilding the boards and motors, I noticed the carriage moved slowly. The 24V rail was only reading 21V, significantly lower than the expected 23.8V.
Then, the arm lowering solenoid began activating erratically when the carriage was touched. It turned out the chassis had a 30V potential relative to the system ground, a dangerous situation.
I found a short circuit between the 24V reservoir capacitor and ground...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-time-with-a-suddenly-activating-solenoid-an-anemic-carriage-motor-and-an-ac-motor-driver-with-a-weak-driver-amplitude/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-time-with-a-suddenly-activating-solenoid-an-anemic-carriage-motor-and-an-ac-motor-driver-with-a-weak-driver-amplitude/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently arrived from a UK seller for restoration. This report outlines its pre-restoration condition.
Upon arrival, the unit was quite dirty but in good overall shape. The dust cover showed typical scratches from storage, many deep enough to feel with a fingernail. However, it can be polished back to good condition. Positively, the dust cover features an aluminum strip instead of the less durable plastic type, and the hinges appear to be intact...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>