<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unified Threat Management on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified-threat-management/</link><description>Recent content in Unified Threat Management on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 21:26:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified-threat-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Security Threat Protection In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 21:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>In the past, castles relied on moats to provide extra security beyond their walls. This stopped attackers from directly reaching the castle. Similarly, today&amp;rsquo;s networks need more than just firewalls.
Firewalls are effective but can be overwhelmed. Cloud-based security acts as a modern moat, providing a barrier outside the network. MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s Unified Threat Management (UTM) uses this approach, offering cloud, on-site, or hybrid security solutions.
MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s UTM is a multi-layered Security as a Service (SaaS) solution that handles simple and complex threats, while also managing security alerts, logs, and compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>