<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Financial Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financial-services/</link><description>Recent content in Financial Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Merchant Account Credit Card Processing Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</guid><description>Even the smallest businesses need a way to process credit card payments. Instead of making it a difficult process, choose a reliable credit card processing company to simplify things. Elite Processing Systems handles the complexities of electronic payments, allowing you to concentrate on your customers and what you offer. They provide a full range of financial services for small businesses, going above and beyond traditional credit card processing.
You might have heard of Elite Processing Systems (EPS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Entry to the EU's Financial Services Market in the Absence of a Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (Twitter: @KulpaBart)
Introduction
When Boris Johnson became British Prime Minister, a no-deal Brexit appeared increasingly possible. UK-based financial services firms were left wondering if and how they would be able to continue serving clients in the remaining 27 EU countries. These firms currently depend on &amp;ldquo;passporting rights,&amp;rdquo; which allow them to operate across borders. According to The Economist, in 2016, 5,476 British financial services firms used 336,421 European passports to offer their products across the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Commission's suggestions for environmentally-friendly finance and the efforts of financial regulators to promote sustainability.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</guid><description>Thomas Piticchio The rising popularity of green politics has led investors to demand more sustainable investment options and increased transparency regarding their money&amp;rsquo;s whereabouts and usage. Consequently, financial intermediaries are introducing &amp;ldquo;green&amp;rdquo; financial products. These products are undergoing regulatory development by the European Commission, aiming to direct capital towards sustainability and clarify what defines a sustainable investment.
In 2018, the European Commission tasked a group of specialists from social, financial, and academic fields to formulate a sustainable finance strategy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Insatiable Demand For Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>10 Gbps used to be a bandwidth amount so large that only major telecommunications companies needed it. That&amp;rsquo;s no longer true, as businesses are now using that much WAN bandwidth and wanting even more.
Beyond internet providers, who could need 10 Gbps? According to Carrier Ethernet News, the finance, streaming entertainment, and medical industries are leading the demand for high bandwidth. Some are even hoping for 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>