<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spain on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spain/</link><description>Recent content in Spain on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Union and the Crisis in the Spanish Constitution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</guid><description>Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated both to Université Saint-Louis Bruxelles and Université libre de Bruxelles
Background
For over a month, Spain has been grappling with a constitutional crisis stemming from pro-independence sentiments in Catalonia. These sentiments culminated in an independence referendum held on October 1, 2017, orchestrated by the Catalan government under President Carles Puigdemont. Barcelona claims that 90% of the 43% voter turnout favored independence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it cheerleading or judging? The CJEU supports the EU's unified patent system.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:33:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Two recent rulings by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirm the EU regulations for a unitary patent system are legal. This analysis examines the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning and evaluates its coherence.
Background
Establishing EU-wide patent regulations has been a long-standing challenge. The Lisbon Treaty introduced Article 118 TFEU, aiming to streamline intellectual property rules. While most rules fall under ordinary legislative procedures (requiring qualified majority voting), language regulations necessitate unanimous agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>As the lawyers entered the bar, the Court of Justice made it easier for legal professionals to practice across borders.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Julian Lonbay, Senior Lecturer,
Postgraduate Research Admissions Tutor, Birmingham Law School, University
of Birmingham
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice judgment in the Joined Cases C-58/13 and C-59/13 Angelo Alberto Torresi and Pierfrancesco Torresi v Consiglio dell&amp;rsquo;Ordine degli Avvocati di Macerata considered whether EU law permits citizens to pursue the fastest route to professional qualification, even if it bypasses significant portions of training mandated by national law for entry into the corresponding national profession...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 1: The Impact of the Revised European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement on Health - Patients and Reciprocal Healthcare (Updated as of March 18, 2018)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, holding the Jean Monnet Chair in EU Law at the University of Sheffield, has reviewed the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s revised draft legal text on the Withdrawal Agreement (WA) as of March 15, 2018. Her analysis focuses on how the revised text impacts reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the EU-27 post-Brexit, particularly for UK pensioners residing in other EU countries and the use of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) for emergency care...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union and Spanish mortgage legislation: safeguarding consumers, addressing floor clauses, and expediting repayment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</guid><description>Juan Carlos Benito Sánchez, PhD Fellow at the University of Louvain (Belgium).
Twitter: @jcbensan
Over recent years, the European Court of Justice has issued several judgments invalidating parts of Spanish mortgage law, both in terms of its content and procedures, and how it’s interpreted by the courts. These rulings were based on the fact that these laws went against EU consumer protection regulations. In particular, the Court based its decisions on Council Directive 93/13/EEC of 5 April 1993 on unfair terms in consumer contracts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>