<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regional on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regional/</link><description>Recent content in Regional on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regional/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hubspot's new, modern Asia Pacific headquarters in Singapore is designed with Millennials in mind</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot. Pictured at the official opening ceremony, from left: Jeetu Mahtani and JD Sherman.
HubSpot has officially launched its Singapore office and revealed plans to add 150 employees to its Singapore-based team over the next three years. Currently, HubSpot Singapore has 30 employees.
The Singapore office, warmly referred to as SingSpot, joins the Sydney, Australia office as HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s second location in the Asia Pacific region and will serve as the company’s Asia Pacific headquarters.</description></item><item><title>The 5-Min Video Challenge has been introduced by the Singtel Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</guid><description>Source: The 5-Min Video Challenge website. Invitation to enter the local rounds.
Singtel Group launched The 5-Min Video Challenge to promote creative content across its global markets. The competition is a collaborative effort among Singtel&amp;rsquo;s associates, including Optus, AIS, Airtel, Globe, and Telkomsel. Winning videos will be shared with over 600 million customers within the Singtel Group.
Content creation is a key element of the Group&amp;rsquo;s strategy for customer engagement in a world where mobile devices are everywhere and demand for online video entertainment is high.</description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin.</description></item></channel></rss>