<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1981EAABG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1981eaabg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 1981EAABG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1981eaabg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): A New Arrival from Texas - A Wrong Hood and Some Blown Fuses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-a-new-arrival-from-texas-a-wrong-hood-and-some-blown-fuses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:54:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-a-new-arrival-from-texas-a-wrong-hood-and-some-blown-fuses/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5524) turntable from Texas. This particular model features a universal voltage DC motor and a power switch located beneath the unit.
The turntable arrived securely packaged in a specialized container, ensuring it was free from any shipping damage. Here&amp;rsquo;s a photo of the turntable as I received it:
B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts might immediately notice something peculiar about this image. The hood&amp;rsquo;s color seems to suggest it belongs to a Beogram 4000, not a 4002.</description></item></channel></rss>