<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recall on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recall/</link><description>Recent content in Recall on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lenovo issues global recall for Thinkpad batteries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</guid><description>Lenovo has expanded a battery recall that was first announced on March 27, 2014. This recall now includes all affected lithium-ion batteries globally. The batteries, as announced in late April 2015, were manufactured for ThinkPad notebook computers shipped between February 2010 and June 2012.
Lenovo stated that they are offering free-of-charge replacement batteries for all recalled batteries in the interest of public safety.
The batteries were sold with new notebook computers or as optional or replacement batteries for the following models:</description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time).</description></item><item><title>Apple is recalling Beats speakers and offering refunds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</guid><description>Apple initiated a voluntary recall of Beats Pill XL speakers due to a potential fire safety risk. The company determined that in rare cases, the battery in these speakers may overheat.
This recall only affects the specific Beats Pill XL speaker model shown in the images and no other Beats or Apple products.
Apple prioritizes customer safety and urges all Beats Pill XL users to stop using their devices.
To return their speakers and receive a refund of US$325 (or equivalent in local currency) as Apple Store credit or electronic payment, owners can visit www.</description></item><item><title>UMW Toyota Motor has expanded its Special Service Campaign to include almost 30,000 cars in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:57:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Toyota Motor Corporation (TMC) issued global recalls related to airbag inflators in some vehicle models on April 11, 2013, and May 13, 2015, and expanded the recall on June 25, 2015.
Responding to this, UMW Toyota Motor is expanding its Special Service Campaign in Malaysia. UMW Toyota Motor has confirmed with TMC that this campaign affects 29,985 Toyota Vios, Corolla Altis, and Yaris models manufactured between April 2007, and December 2008.</description></item></channel></rss>