<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Arts on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arts/</link><description>Recent content in Arts on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LASALLE Show will begin in April 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</guid><description>From the beginning of April to the end of May, the public and industry professionals are invited to view almost 900 graduating student projects at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s LASALLE College of the Arts yearly graduation showcase.
The projects featured at The LASALLE Show are developed throughout the students&amp;rsquo; final year and embody the culmination of their artistic growth and the realization of their aspirations. The LASALLE Show also provides insights into current trends in contemporary arts and design and highlights the emerging work of young artists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, come to DiverseCity in KL to experience a diverse range of performing and visual arts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</guid><description>DiverseCity 2016, also known as the Kuala Lumpur International Arts Festival, ran from August 31st to October 2nd, 2016. The festival showcased a diverse range of artistic expressions, including visual arts, crafts, music, dance, and literature at various locations around Klang Valley in Malaysia. Many events were free to attend.
Taking place annually for five weeks at multiple venues in and around Kuala Lumpur, DiverseCity highlights the rich cultural tapestry of Malaysia and explores the country&amp;rsquo;s close relationship with the ASEAN community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>