<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Servers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dedicated-servers/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Servers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dedicated-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs Dedicated Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</guid><description>There are many ways to host your emails, websites, and software applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the pros and cons of each option to help you determine the best fit for your business.
You might be tempted to manage your own hosting, which is how many companies started and how some large companies still operate. The basic requirement is a computer that functions as a file server and a bandwidth connection. Internally, this connection can be your Local Area Network (LAN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Rush To Cloud Service Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are moving away from managing their own servers and rapidly shifting towards public data centers. This article explores the reasons behind this trend and its potential future.
Cost savings have always been a major driver for companies considering data center colocation. Instead of investing in their own data centers, companies can move their equipment to a colocation facility. These facilities provide economies of scale by housing servers and network devices from multiple companies, sharing the costs of cooling, power, security, and bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Have Reseller Hosting When You Don’t Resell Anything?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:16:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</guid><description>Web hosting companies offer various plans, from shared hosting to dedicated servers and cloud services. One option is &amp;ldquo;reseller hosting,&amp;rdquo; which many website owners use without actually reselling hosting.
Many website owners use reseller hosting to manage multiple websites easily. Basic web hosting, like HostGator&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hatchling&amp;rdquo; plan, is affordable for individuals and small businesses with simple websites. These plans offer shared resources like disk space and bandwidth at a low cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>