<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Travel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-travel/</link><description>Recent content in Business Travel on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:31:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Set Up Secure Remote Computer Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/set-up-secure-remote-computer-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/set-up-secure-remote-computer-access/</guid><description>Ever wondered how to access your computer remotely while traveling, working remotely, or at a different office? There&amp;rsquo;s a simple solution you can try for free.
This technology, called remote access, allows you to securely connect to another computer and use it as if you were physically present. With remote access, you can forget about syncing files and applications between your laptop and desktop. You can directly log in to your remote desktop from your laptop to run applications, manage files, and even print remotely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/set-up-secure-remote-computer-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/set-up-secure-remote-computer-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take Your Office PC With You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</guid><description>Mobile professionals often rely on their laptops but might find themselves needing files left on their office desktops. Traveling long distances back for these files isn&amp;rsquo;t always feasible.
Imagine accessing your office desktop from anywhere, anytime. This eliminates the worry of having the right files and removes the need for duplicates. Your laptop and a special application are all you need to make any computer your office computer.
GoToMyPC is a remote access software, or KVM application, that allows this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>