<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Winner on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/winner/</link><description>Recent content in Winner on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:57:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/winner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The winners of the FinTech Awards have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:57:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and The Association of Banks in Singapore (ABS) awarded S$1.2 million to 12 fintech companies at the FinTech Awards, held during the third annual Singapore FinTech Festival.
This year&amp;rsquo;s winning solutions focused on financial inclusion and represented a broader range of ASEAN countries. These solutions addressed various business areas, including credit scoring, mobile security, anti-money laundering, and digital investment.
Here are the 12 award recipients:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CHKLC has announced the winners of the 2014 HK Corporate Governance Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</guid><description>The Chamber of Hong Kong Listed Companies (CHKLC) recently revealed the winners of the Hong Kong Corporate Governance Excellence Awards 2014. The CHKLC defines corporate governance as respecting shareholder rights and values, maintaining board and management integrity, and demonstrating transparency and accountability.
Dr. Eddy Fong, Judging Panel Chairman, highlighted that the awardees went beyond standard practices, tailoring their governance strategies to address industry-specific risks and challenges.
&amp;ldquo;Furthermore,&amp;rdquo; he stated, &amp;ldquo;winning companies view sustainability as inseparable from good corporate governance, crucial for long-term growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt reveals top employers for Singapore and the region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 04:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</guid><description>Source: Best Employers website.
Aon Hewitt, a global human resources solutions firm, unveiled its list of top employers in Singapore for 2015 on February 27th. Launched in Asia in 2001, Aon Hewitt’s Best Employers study is currently the most thorough of its kind in the Asia Pacific region. Recognition as an Aon Hewitt Best Employer signifies that a company:
1. Cultivates strong employee commitment and top-tier performance;
2. Achieves strong business results through effective human resources strategies; and, 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>