<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contractors on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contractors/</link><description>Recent content in Contractors on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contractors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Painless Way to Find Network Technicians</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</guid><description>Your company might be large and technologically advanced, utilizing an internal data network and a PBX phone system, or even a converged enterprise VoIP system. However, you may lack the resources for a dedicated IT department, let alone a telecom team. Hiring necessary services on an as-needed basis is a reality for your business. But is there a simple solution for finding contractors to handle this work?
Now there is. The solution is called the VAR Network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>