<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Campaign on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/campaign/</link><description>Recent content in Campaign on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/campaign/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vote MPLS &amp; Ethernet for Better Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</guid><description>The 2008 election season is upon us. To determine which candidates best serve your interests, we suggest considering MPLS and Ethernet for reliable bandwidth, improved performance, and reduced costs over 1-3 years. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into their platforms to see if they deserve your vote.
IP Networking is currently the leading technology. Initially confined to local offices, IP has expanded to WANs at state, regional, and national levels. Today, almost all network designs are centered around IP or Internet Protocol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KKBOX has initiated a Cpop campaign on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</guid><description>Source: Twitter. Screenshot of Tia Ray&amp;rsquo;s tweet.
Twitter and KKBOX, a popular music streaming service in Asia, are collaborating to increase global recognition and appreciation of Chinese pop music, known as Cpop (#Cpop).
To achieve this, KKBOX is developing exclusive Cpop content (#OnlyOnTwitter) for their main Twitter account (@KKBOX). This includes weekly live question and answer sessions with Cpop artists, personalized video messages from Cpop musicians and producers using Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Challenger app, frequent #KKvote contests to encourage international fan participation, and live streams of Cpop concerts and the yearly KKBOX music awards through Periscope (@KKBOXTW)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces the Bunyani financing campaign for completion works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new campaign called &amp;ldquo;Bunyani&amp;hellip; from skeleton structure to delivery&amp;rdquo; to provide financing options for owners of residential, investment, and industrial land plots. This campaign aims to help customers complete various construction phases, including finishing works, maintenance, and restoration.
Ahmad Al-Khaled, Deputy General Manager Commercial Services at KFH, stated that the campaign offers clients simplified financing solutions. These include financing of up to KD70,000, a repayment period of 15 years, a grace period of 12 months for the first installment, and a competitive profit rate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GMC uses Instagram to showcase PanoGrams and highlight #GMCprecision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</guid><description>Source: GMC.
GMC launched a new Instagram campaign using panoramic photography and the hashtag #GMCprecision.
The month-long US campaign, which began on May 22nd, highlights the meticulous design of GMC vehicles. Using Instagram&amp;rsquo;s new Carousel format, GMC is one of the first car companies to create “PanoGrams.&amp;quot; This format lets users swipe through a series of pictures in a single ad, similar to a multi-page spread in a magazine. These PanoGrams form one panoramic image and include a link to GMC&amp;rsquo;s website for further details...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The APAC region is strongly featured in Warc's list of the top 100 marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Warc, a provider of marketing intelligence, has introduced the Warc 100, a new ranking of the top marketing campaigns globally based on their effectiveness and strategic impact.
The Asia Pacific region contributed over 30 entries, including one from the UAE, with Australia having the second-highest representation after the US with 11 entries.
Among the top 10 campaigns from the Asia Pacific are: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s More Fun in the Philippines&amp;rdquo; by the Philippines Department of Tourism and BBDO Guerrero (ranked 3rd), &amp;ldquo;Overstay Checkout&amp;rdquo; by Art Series Hotels and Naked Communications (5th), &amp;ldquo;Smoking Kid&amp;rdquo; by Thai Health Promotion Foundation and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (7th), &amp;ldquo;Old Parts for New&amp;rdquo; by ORBIS International and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (8th), and &amp;ldquo;Car Creation&amp;rdquo; by NRMA Insurance and Whybin\TBWA (10th)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>