<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ATT Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/att-wireless/</link><description>Recent content in ATT Wireless on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/att-wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LG Xenon Exotic Messaging Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-xenon-exotic-messaging-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:11:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-xenon-exotic-messaging-phone/</guid><description>The LG Xenon gets its name from the element Xenon, which gives off a blue glow when electrically charged, just like the blue version of this phone. But the red one is named for being &amp;ldquo;red hot&amp;rdquo; - a nod to its impressive messaging features.
Messaging is the heart of the LG Xenon. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for those who love to text, featuring a full-length slide-out QWERTY keyboard for effortless typing. And when you&amp;rsquo;re not messaging, the Xenon easily transitions back to a sleek and pocket-friendly candybar-style phone.</description></item><item><title>Doing BACKFLIPs with MOTOBLUR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 10:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</guid><description>Would you do a backflip for your current cell phone? Probably not, but Motorola&amp;rsquo;s BACKFLIP might just change your mind.
This phone&amp;rsquo;s unique feature is its reverse hinge. Unlike most phones where the keyboard is hidden beneath the screen, the BACKFLIP&amp;rsquo;s keyboard is located on the exterior, flipping open to reveal a full-size touchscreen. This design eliminates the need for a smaller internal screen, offering a more spacious keyboard and a high-resolution touchscreen experience comparable to a small computer.</description></item><item><title>From Here to Samsung Eternity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-here-to-samsung-eternity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-here-to-samsung-eternity/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a frigid winter day with howling winds and accumulating snow outside. However, right here before me, I&amp;rsquo;m captivated by a Hawaiian beach scene playing on a screen. A young couple enjoys the crashing waves. It&amp;rsquo;s so realistic that I&amp;rsquo;m tempted to step into the picture and join them on the warm sand. Despite knowing it&amp;rsquo;s just a TV screen, I feel a noticeable warmth. This captivating scene effectively blocks out the dreary winter weather outside my window, showcasing the impressive power of visual suggestion.</description></item></channel></rss>