<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Subsidiarity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/subsidiarity/</link><description>Recent content in Subsidiarity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/subsidiarity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>