<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fibre Channel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fibre-channel/</link><description>Recent content in Fibre Channel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fibre-channel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity.</description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary.</description></item></channel></rss>