<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Company on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/company/</link><description>Recent content in Company on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suzhou is gaining more recognition in the MICE industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</guid><description>The Suzhou Culture and Expo Centre Company (SCECC), which manages the Suzhou Culture and Arts Centre and the Suzhou International Expo Centre, claims that Suzhou is arguably the top Meetings, Incentives, Conferences and Exhibitions (MICE) destination in China.
SCECC highlights Suzhou&amp;rsquo;s success in hosting significant events, such as the 53rd World Table Tennis Championships earlier this year and Armani&amp;rsquo;s selection of the city&amp;rsquo;s Humble Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Garden as the venue for the global debut of its Pivoine Suzhou perfume.</description></item><item><title>Asian companies place a high value on feedback received during exit interviews</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</guid><description>A recent report from Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, reveals that most companies believe in the value of honest feedback during exit interviews, whether formal or informal. In fact, seven out of ten Asian companies conduct these interviews.
Titled &amp;ldquo;Acquiring Insights From The Exit Process To Build A Better Workplace,&amp;rdquo; the report highlights how improvements made based on exit interview feedback can help organizations attract and retain top-tier talent.</description></item><item><title>Proposed changes to the tenure of independent board directors in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/proposed-changes-to-the-tenure-of-independent-board-directors-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/proposed-changes-to-the-tenure-of-independent-board-directors-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Singapore Exchange Regulation (SGX RegCo) is asking for public opinion on its suggestion to implement a strict nine-year limit for independent board directors (IDs) and end the two-tier voting system for long-serving IDs.
The consultation document states that if directors wish to stay on after the limit, they must be reclassified as non-independent, even if their appointment was previously approved by a two-tier vote.
They are also seeking feedback on making it mandatory for companies to disclose the exact amount and breakdown of board directors&amp;rsquo; and the CEO&amp;rsquo;s pay in their annual report, identifying them by name.</description></item></channel></rss>