<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Collaboration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/collaboration/</link><description>Recent content in Collaboration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tata Communications updates the jamvee unified communications platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications provider, recently launched the newest version of its cloud-based unified communications platform, jamvee.
Source: Jamvee website.
Leveraging Tata Communications&amp;rsquo; robust global network, jamvee consolidates various client software and devices into a single, secure, and versatile platform. This approach streamlines communication and collaboration within and across organizations, allowing employees, suppliers, and customers to connect seamlessly using any combination of audio, video, messaging, and content sharing tools, regardless of their device or browser.</description></item><item><title>Huddle rooms equipped with video capabilities have the potential to enhance collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huddle-rooms-equipped-with-video-capabilities-have-the-potential-to-enhance-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huddle-rooms-equipped-with-video-capabilities-have-the-potential-to-enhance-collaboration/</guid><description>India, China, and Singapore are leading the way in Asia Pacific when it comes to using collaboration technology in huddle rooms (small meeting rooms). However, there&amp;rsquo;s still a significant opportunity to boost productivity further through advanced collaboration tools.
A new study by Polycom (now a part of Plantronics) reveals that although content sharing is the preferred collaboration method for Singaporean workers, the country&amp;rsquo;s adoption of video conferencing lags behind other countries in the region.</description></item><item><title>Hosted PBX Adds Video Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems, also known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, are gaining popularity with businesses of all sizes. This technology offers advanced features without requiring a large upfront investment. Now, these systems are evolving to incorporate video services as well.
MegaPath, a leading network and cloud service provider, is enhancing its hosted PBX offerings by including cloud-based unified communications video services.
A new generation of business phones makes voice and video integration possible.</description></item><item><title>Guangzhou businesses enter into Letters of Intent with Singapore organizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</guid><description>Source: Guangzhou Municipal Government. Cai.
The city of Guangzhou held a promotional event in Singapore to explore collaboration and innovation between the two business hubs. Two agreements were reached: one between the Sino-Singapore International Joint Research Institute and Chinese Academy of Sciences Holdings Company, and another between Guangzhou Gas Group, Guangzhou Port Group, and the industrial group Royal Golden Eagle.
Guangzhou&amp;rsquo;s Vice Mayor, Cai Chaolin, who also leads the Nansha District&amp;rsquo;s Communist Party and Development Zone, highlighted the shared attributes between Guangzhou and Singapore, such as their size, cultural similarities, and languages.</description></item><item><title>Dropbox is revamping its platform to help users become even more productive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-is-revamping-its-platform-to-help-users-become-even-more-productive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-is-revamping-its-platform-to-help-users-become-even-more-productive/</guid><description>Dropbox, a leading platform for collaboration, has introduced a redesigned workspace. This updated workspace, accessible through the Dropbox desktop app, website, and mobile app, acts as a central hub for files, tools, and teams. A new desktop app, currently available in early access, provides a streamlined entry point to this unified workspace.
“Work is becoming increasingly fragmented—our files are spread across various devices and platforms, and we&amp;rsquo;re using multiple apps that don&amp;rsquo;t communicate with each other, making it challenging for teams to keep up,” said Drew Houston, CEO of Dropbox.</description></item><item><title>Dropbox and Microsoft collaborating more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Dropbox and Microsoft are joining forces to make it easier for their users to work together. This collaboration will allow users to seamlessly work with Dropbox and Microsoft Office on their phones, tablets, and computers. Given that over 1.2 billion people use Microsoft Office and 35 billion Office files are stored in Dropbox, this partnership has the potential to benefit a lot of users.
This integration will enable users to edit their Dropbox documents directly in the relevant Office application.</description></item><item><title>Entrepreneurs may find synergy in collaborating with larger corporations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-may-find-synergy-in-collaborating-with-larger-corporations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-may-find-synergy-in-collaborating-with-larger-corporations/</guid><description>Large corporations are missing out on a $1.5 trillion global growth opportunity by not collaborating with entrepreneurs on digital innovation, reveals a new study by Accenture. This missed opportunity, representing 2.2% of global GDP, exists despite the fact that businesses of all sizes recognize the need for digital transformation.
The report, &amp;ldquo;Harnessing the Power of Entrepreneurs to Open Innovation,&amp;rdquo; surveyed over 1,000 entrepreneurs and 1,000 large companies across G20 nations. Findings indicate that 82% of corporations acknowledge the learning potential startups offer in digital business transformation.</description></item><item><title>Browser Based Video Conferencing and Webinars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</guid><description>Once restricted to businesses, video conferencing is now accessible to anyone with an internet connection and a web browser. MegaMeeting offers a suite of products for PCs, Macs, and Linux computers that don&amp;rsquo;t require typical downloads or installations. As long as you can use a web browser, you can participate in video conferences and webinars.
MegaMeeting&amp;rsquo;s web-based system utilizes the Flash Player 9 plugin, commonly found in browsers like Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's Virtual Teleportation Replaces Airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-virtual-teleportation-replaces-airports/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 21:36:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-virtual-teleportation-replaces-airports/</guid><description>Star Trek fans have always dreamed of instantly teleporting to any destination. While true teleportation is still science fiction, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovative technology, TelePresence, offers a virtual solution.
TelePresence allows users to participate in meetings around the world as if they were physically present. High-definition video, superior audio, and a unique virtual table setup create an incredibly realistic experience, making participants feel like they&amp;rsquo;re in the same room, even when separated by vast distances.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography.</description></item><item><title>Rural Broadband Stimulus Hopes To One-Up Dial-up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 12:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</guid><description>Right before the 4th of July holiday, the much-awaited government funding plan for expanding rural broadband access was officially announced through a &amp;ldquo;Notice of Funds Availability (NOFA)&amp;rdquo; and a call for applications.
The application window is short, running from July 14th to August 14th, 2009, so interested parties need to act fast.
Don&amp;rsquo;t expect to see immediate changes if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to use these new broadband services rather than provide them.</description></item><item><title>Cisco has launched new personal hardware to improve collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</guid><description>At Cisco Live! 2014 in the US, Cisco unveiled new personal collaboration tools. The company recognizes that teamwork often spans continents, demanding tools that enable seamless and immediate collaboration, regardless of location.
Source: Cisco. The Cisco DX80 in action.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution comes in the form of the DX70 and DX80 desktop collaboration devices. These Android-based devices act as hubs for collaboration tools and applications. Featuring large touch screens, the DX70 and DX80 combine Cisco&amp;rsquo;s expertise in HD video, high-quality audio, and web conferencing with integrated business applications and web browsing.</description></item><item><title>WebRTC set to boost business productivity for browsers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably used a web browser like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, or Safari on your phone or computer to visit websites.
Some companies believe browsers can be much more than tools for accessing websites; they think browsers can simplify our lives. Tata Communications suggests that incorporating the right features into browsers could significantly boost employee productivity.
&amp;ldquo;Despite some positive developments, most of us are still dealing with separate, disconnected communication platforms.</description></item><item><title>GoToMeeting Really is Like Being There</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotomeeting-really-is-like-being-there/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 11:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotomeeting-really-is-like-being-there/</guid><description>GoToMeeting is advertised as a business tool that can take the place of in-person presentations. The idea itself is appealing: consider the expenses of travel combined with the value of time spent commuting to and from the meeting location, multiplied by the number of attendees. The cost of even a small meeting can be surprisingly high. When you realize the actual cost, it becomes hard to justify having in-person business meetings unless absolutely necessary, especially when an electronic alternative exists that can eliminate the inefficiencies and leave you with only the cost of the meeting content.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone Offers Awareness In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The traditional office phone, once a large and stationary fixture on every desk, is becoming a relic of the past. Modern business communication has evolved into a dynamic and multifaceted process, incorporating instant messaging, online collaboration tools, file sharing, and web-based applications alongside traditional voice calls and conferencing. This evolution begs the question: are conventional PBX systems still equipped to handle the demands of today&amp;rsquo;s business environment?
As outdated phone systems increasingly hinder productivity, many companies are turning to cloud-based solutions for a more modern approach.</description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access.</description></item><item><title>I Heard What You Wrote Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-heard-what-you-wrote-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-heard-what-you-wrote-last-summer/</guid><description>Ever been stuck in a class or meeting, diligently taking notes but unsure if you&amp;rsquo;re capturing everything accurately? Recording the session with a digital recorder alongside note-taking could help, but then syncing the audio and text becomes a nightmare. What if there was a single device that could automatically synchronize your notes and audio? Thankfully, there is!
The Livescribe Pulse(tm) smartpen records audio as you write. Yes, you read that right—you write, it records.</description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network.</description></item><item><title>SMB Cloud Computing Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</guid><description>While large companies have widely adopted cloud computing, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) may wonder about its relevance for them. Broadview Networks offers a range of cloud services ideal for such businesses. Already a prominent communications provider in the Northeastern and Mid-Atlantic US, Broadview provides various connectivity options, including T1 lines, Ethernet, fiber optic connections, and traditional phone lines.
What distinguishes Broadview is its ability to provide both cloud services and the reliable connectivity these services require, unlike many cloud providers that only offer the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Job Posting Tool Offers Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-posting-tool-offers-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-posting-tool-offers-free-trial/</guid><description>As the economy improves, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to start thinking about hiring again, but many companies dread the deluge of resumes and calls that come with advertising open positions. The cost of advertising and the staff time needed to screen applicants can be overwhelming. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to streamline and simplify your hiring process.
ZipRecruiter offers a web-based system designed to significantly reduce the workload for you and your staff.</description></item><item><title>Lark Technologies is providing a free collaboration tool for businesses in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:59:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Lark Technologies, headquartered in Singapore, is now offering its comprehensive, enterprise-level collaboration platform, Lark, free of charge across Southeast Asia. This includes Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, the Philippines, Thailand, and Vietnam. Lark provides a range of features, including unlimited video calls and online collaboration tools, to facilitate seamless teamwork remotely. Users can view colleagues&amp;rsquo; schedules, initiate video calls directly from calendar events, and collaborate on documents during video meetings.
Joey Lim, APAC Commercial Lead at Lark, highlighted that with an estimated 90% of Asia Pacific employees currently working remotely, the company aims to empower teams to maintain productivity regardless of physical location.</description></item><item><title>The Great Women Connect Series begins with Great Women Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Great Women Malaysia. Puan Nadira Yusoff.
The Great Women Connect Series debuted today in Malaysia. This new program seeks to provide a space for women in business worldwide to connect and exchange ideas and experiences related to trade. It also aims to foster international partnerships, helping women, especially those in Malaysia, build networks and realize their full potential.
Great Women Malaysia (GMW) is an initiative that strives to empower Malaysian women, particularly those in underserved and rural areas.</description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications.</description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing.</description></item></channel></rss>