<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TB on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tb/</link><description>Recent content in TB on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:48:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hitachi drives are endorsed with a vote of confidence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</guid><description>In a January 2014 blog post, cloud storage company Backblaze reported that Hitachi and Western Digital hard drives have been the most reliable in their data centers.
Backblaze engineer Brian Beach revealed that Seagate&amp;rsquo;s 1.5TB drives had an annual failure rate of about 14%, significantly higher than Hitachi&amp;rsquo;s 2TB drives at approximately 1% and Western Digital&amp;rsquo;s 1TB drives at 3%. For 3TB drives, Seagate again had the highest failure rate at around 9%, while Western Digital stood at about 3% and Hitachi at roughly 1%.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces hard disk drives with high speed and high capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</guid><description>Sony Introduces Speedy and Durable Portable Hard Drives Boasting data transfer speeds up to 138MBps for both reading and writing, Sony&amp;rsquo;s latest portable hard disk drives (HDDs) promise both performance and resilience. Built to withstand the bumps of everyday use, these drives are shock-resistant, splash-resistant (IPX4 rating), and dust-resistant (IP5X rating). They can even tolerate drops from up to 6.5 feet thanks to their robust rubber damper design.
Source: Sony. The new 2TB drive.</description></item></channel></rss>