<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Russia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/russia/</link><description>Recent content in Russia on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:46:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon examine important legal matters related to EU sanctions against non-EU countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:46:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*
I recently attended a hearing at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning a case brought by Russian energy company Rosneft against EU sanctions imposed after Russia&amp;rsquo;s intervention in Crimea. The case, heard by the High Court of Justice (England &amp;amp; Wales), asks the CJEU to clarify the legitimacy of several aspects of these EU sanctions.</description></item><item><title>How can legislation empower Europe? By phasing out fossil fuels and implementing the Sustainability Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 02:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</guid><description>Ewan McGaughey, Reader in Law, King’s College London
Photo credit: Geopolitical Intelligence Services, via Wikicommons
Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine has prompted initiatives like RePowerEU and similar UK programs, aiming to eliminate reliance on Russian fossil fuels. President Biden has even called for a complete end to fossil fuel use, arguing that dependence on any authoritarian regime for energy is no longer acceptable. This shift recognizes the need to transition to renewable energy sources rapidly, acknowledging everyone&amp;rsquo;s fundamental right to benefit from scientific advancements.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Union a cause worth sacrificing for? Contemplating the future of Ukraine and the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</guid><description>There were many reasons to criticize the Yanukovych government in Ukraine, but the protests that led to its downfall were sparked by Yanukovych&amp;rsquo;s refusal to sign an agreement with the European Union. This strong desire for EU membership among some Ukrainians raises important questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s future.
The first steps after the planned elections would be straightforward. A pro-European government would likely ratify the association agreement, which connects Ukraine to EU law more closely than previous agreements.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Human Rights highlights the significance of encryption in the case of Podchasov v. Russia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip &amp;amp; Frederik Zuiderveen Borgesius*
*Both authors work at the iHub and the Institute for Computing and Information Sciences, Radboud University, The Netherlands - mattis.vantschip[at]ru.nl &amp;amp; frederikzb[at]cs.ru.nl
Photo credit: Gzen92, on wikimedia commons A February 2024 ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Podchasov v. Russia highlighted the crucial role of encryption in safeguarding privacy rights. This judgment comes at a time when encryption is at the heart of many global legal discussions.</description></item></channel></rss>