<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Genuine on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/genuine/</link><description>Recent content in Genuine on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/genuine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server.</description></item><item><title>The inexpensive cellphone you recently purchased may be counterfeit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 02:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</guid><description>The global black market for counterfeit and substandard cell phones is a significant issue, costing the industry an estimated US$6 billion each year, as reported in a recent study by the Mobile Manufacturers Forum (MMF). This comprehensive analysis, &amp;ldquo;Counterfeit/Substandard Mobile Phones - A Resource Guide for Governments&amp;rdquo;, examines the prevalence of these phones across all major brands.
According to MMF Secretary General Michael Milligan, research suggests approximately 148 million counterfeit or substandard cell phones were sold in 2013 alone, primarily through established retail channels.</description></item></channel></rss>