<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Surveillance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/surveillance/</link><description>Recent content in Surveillance on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 14:07:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/surveillance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The European Union should consider the UK police's use of live facial recognition technology when developing regulations for law enforcement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-should-consider-the-uk-police-s-use-of-live-facial-recognition-technology-when-developing-regulations-for-law-enforcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 14:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-should-consider-the-uk-police-s-use-of-live-facial-recognition-technology-when-developing-regulations-for-law-enforcement/</guid><description>Divergent Approaches to Regulating Live Facial Recognition Dr. Asress Adimi Gikay, a Senior Lecturer in AI, Disruptive Innovation, and Law at Brunel University London, explores the contrasting approaches to regulating live facial recognition (LFR) in the UK and the European Union.
Recent suggestions by UK officials to use LFR for searching national passport databases to combat shoplifting have sparked debate, particularly as London, a city with a high concentration of CCTV cameras, grapples with AI safety concerns.</description></item><item><title>Dear UK Members of Parliament, We are writing to urge you to prioritize democratic scrutiny of any proposed changes to UK surveillance laws. Thank you.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:53:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</guid><description>Steve Peers
I have concerns about the lack of democratic oversight regarding UK law changes that impact privacy rights, especially those connected to EU law. Because of this, I joined others in signing an open letter to MPs. This letter was published in the Guardian and other publications. I want to recognize Andrew Murray and Paul Bernal for leading this effort.
This is the complete letter to all members of the House of Commons:</description></item><item><title>Is it necessary for the EU to prohibit the real-time use of remote biometric identification systems for law enforcement purposes?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-for-the-eu-to-prohibit-the-real-time-use-of-remote-biometric-identification-systems-for-law-enforcement-purposes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 23:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-for-the-eu-to-prohibit-the-real-time-use-of-remote-biometric-identification-systems-for-law-enforcement-purposes/</guid><description>Asress Adimi Gikay (PhD)
Senior Lecturer in AI, Disruptive Innovation, and Law
Brunel Law School &amp;amp; Brunel Centre for AI(London, UK)
Twitter: @DrAsressGikay
Photo credit: Irbsas, via Wikimedia commons
Why a Complete Ban on Real-Time Remote Biometric Identification Systems Is Not the Answer
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposed Artificial Intelligence Act (EU-AIA), intended to regulate AI use, has faced criticism since its introduction two years ago. A key point of contention is the regulation&amp;rsquo;s stance on law enforcement&amp;rsquo;s use of Real-Time Remote Biometric Identification Systems (RT-RBIS) in public spaces.</description></item><item><title>The ECtHR Grand Chamber makes a ruling on mass surveillance in the case of Big Brother Watch v UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, an expert in internet law from the University of Essex, provides an in-depth analysis of a significant ruling by the Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) concerning the United Kingdom&amp;rsquo;s surveillance regime, specifically its Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA).
This ruling is the culmination of a series of legal challenges against the UK&amp;rsquo;s surveillance practices, brought to light by revelations of extensive government surveillance programs.</description></item></channel></rss>