<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Public Prosecutor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-public-prosecutor/</link><description>Recent content in European Public Prosecutor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-public-prosecutor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU bolsters criminal law protection of the EU's finances in The Italian Job.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Contrary to popular belief, fraud against the EU budget is not typically committed by corrupt EU officials. As per EU reports, the usual culprits are individuals or companies exploiting EU funds managed by Member States. These violations also extend beyond spending to include EU income reduction, such as evading customs duties on imports.
Establishing and upholding EU-wide regulations for such misconduct has been challenging. However, the Court of Justice (CJEU) significantly strengthened the law in this area with its recent Taricco judgment.</description></item><item><title>The European Public Prosecutor’s Office and Fundamental Rights: A Disquieting Lack of Discussion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</guid><description>Michiel Luchtman, Jannemieke Ouwerkerk, Marloes van Noorloos, Pim Geelhoed, Jorrit Rijpma, and Louis Middelkoop are affiliated with the Meijers Committee (www.commissie-meijers.nl/en).
The EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed European Public Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office (EPPO) has sparked significant debate among Member States. The EPPO&amp;rsquo;s role would be to investigate and prosecute fraudulent use of EU funds, with discussions already underway to expand its jurisdiction to include terrorism and other serious crimes. Current political dialogue centers around the necessity of this supranational entity and the potential impact on national sovereignty, particularly within the sensitive realm of criminal justice.</description></item></channel></rss>