<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wide Area Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wide-area-network/</link><description>Recent content in Wide Area Network on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wide-area-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Metropolitan and wide area networks are getting faster. Undersea cables are moving from 10 to 40 and even 100 Gbps, and land-based fiber lines are already at 100 Gbps. This means large companies, healthcare organizations, and video producers are starting to find their networks inadequate. The good news is that there are more affordable options than ever before.
There are several practical ways to boost your MAN or WAN bandwidth beyond one Gigabit per second, up to 10 Gbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>40 Gbps Bandwidth Available For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</guid><description>XO Communications has increased business bandwidth options by offering two 40 Gbps network services across its nationwide fiber optic network. Randy Nicklas, XO Communications&amp;rsquo; CTO, highlights the advantages of these new 40 Gbps services:
You can listen to the interview directly on this page:
Clearly, we&amp;rsquo;re entering a new era of high-bandwidth applications for businesses and service providers like cable companies. High-speed financial trading needs the fastest speeds, with even milliseconds of delay impacting outcomes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ENLAN Spans The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</guid><description>The concept of unifying all your company locations under a single extended LAN is gaining momentum. Instead of grappling with the complexities of managing countless connections for numerous branch offices or retail locations, a single managed network can streamline this process.
TW Telecom offers a service called ENLAN, which stands for Extended Native LAN. This service provides users with a high-speed, dependable, and secure network that extends the reach of what is typically considered the WAN or Wide Area Network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigaMAN and Gigabit Ethernet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</guid><description>Organizations in need of truly fast wide area network connections should consider gigabit Ethernet services like GigaMAN. These high-bandwidth circuits are now more affordable than ever.
Ethernet WAN services are a newer option for businesses and organizations, offering end-to-end Ethernet protocol signal maintenance. This eliminates the need for protocol conversion between a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN and traditional TDM telco circuits.
Ethernet speeds range from 10 Mbps (standard) to 100 Mbps (Fast Ethernet) and 1000 Mbps (Gigabit Ethernet)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How SD-WAN Hands-Off Seamlessly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 05:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It would be ideal if WAN network connections never failed, but unfortunately, that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. Even the most reliable copper, fiber, or wireless connections eventually experience downtime. This can interrupt phone calls, halt ongoing work, and lead to lost productivity and revenue. However, imagine a solution that ensures your connections remain virtually uninterrupted, experiencing only minor, momentary glitches regardless of the underlying issue.
This solution exists and is called SD-WAN, or Software-Defined Wide Area Networking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN to Complement Your LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your company&amp;rsquo;s Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at blazing speeds of 1 Gbps or more, making internal network operations seem almost instantaneous. However, accessing resources outside your physical location can feel painstakingly slow. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be convenient if your LAN could extend across cities or even to remote offices? You might be surprised to learn that this is a possibility.
Yes, The WAN is Ethernet Networks can be broadly categorized as either owned or leased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Topology Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</guid><description>Businesses have various choices for connecting their branch offices, franchisees, suppliers, customers, and remote employees. The ideal network structure depends on the specific goals, whether it&amp;rsquo;s basic off-site backups or creating a virtual company spanning multiple states. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some prevalent WAN topologies used today.
The most widespread WAN is the Internet, connecting almost everyone everywhere. It&amp;rsquo;s a massive mesh network with affordable connections available through various methods like wireline, wireless, and fiber optic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>