<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Email on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/email/</link><description>Recent content in Email on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices.</description></item><item><title>Send Fax From Email On Your Computer or Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</guid><description>Do you recall fax machines with thermal paper rolls? Those messages had a distinct look and tended to fade. To preserve them, you&amp;rsquo;d copy them onto regular paper using a laser printer, then diligently wash the strange residue off your hands.
Fax technology has significantly evolved. Thermal paper is out, and even traditional fax machines are becoming rare. Cloud-based electronic transmission and storage are the modern alternatives.
Sending and receiving faxes via email is the contemporary approach.</description></item><item><title>Adobe provides a list of suggestions for creating email campaigns that are optimized for mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Adobe&amp;rsquo;s recent email survey suggests that email is not going away anytime soon, at least not in the United States. The survey, which focused on American white-collar workers, revealed that individuals frequently check both their personal and work email. Interestingly, smartphones have surpassed computers as the preferred device for email access. This trend is likely even more pronounced in Asia, a region with high mobile device adoption rates. A study by Experian highlighted that email remains a leading marketing channel in Singapore, especially for driving online traffic to physical stores.</description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry introduces WatchDox by BlackBerry Email Protector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-introduces-watchdox-by-blackberry-email-protector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 22:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-introduces-watchdox-by-blackberry-email-protector/</guid><description>BlackBerry has launched WatchDox by BlackBerry Email Protector, a new product designed to give businesses greater control over file security. This is achieved by incorporating digital rights management (DRM) at the file level for emails, ensuring protection beyond the company&amp;rsquo;s firewall.
WatchDox by BlackBerry is a comprehensive file management platform that facilitates file syncing and sharing across multiple operating systems. By integrating DRM security into individual files, the solution reduces the risks of data breaches.</description></item><item><title>GetResponse introduces its email marketing platform in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>GetResponse, an email marketing platform, has officially launched in the ASEAN region. The company enhanced its cloud-based platform earlier this year to include support for Chinese, Malay, and Thai languages. This move has contributed to a significant 41.6% surge in new account registrations. GetResponse has observed a 35.8% year-over-year growth in email marketing activities within ASEAN.
Source: GetResponse website.
Simon Grabowski, CEO of GetResponse, emphasized the significance of email marketing, especially for small and medium-sized businesses working with limited budgets.</description></item><item><title>SMB Cloud Computing Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</guid><description>While large companies have widely adopted cloud computing, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) may wonder about its relevance for them. Broadview Networks offers a range of cloud services ideal for such businesses. Already a prominent communications provider in the Northeastern and Mid-Atlantic US, Broadview provides various connectivity options, including T1 lines, Ethernet, fiber optic connections, and traditional phone lines.
What distinguishes Broadview is its ability to provide both cloud services and the reliable connectivity these services require, unlike many cloud providers that only offer the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Don't fall for the scam of cheap Ray-Ban sunglasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</guid><description>Source: ESET.
ESET&amp;rsquo;s spam filters have identified a growing trend of fraudulent emails enticing recipients with deeply discounted luxury items, particularly Ray-Ban sunglasses. These counterfeit websites lack encryption and might be designed to capture victims&amp;rsquo; payment information. While ESET had issued prior warnings about this scam targeting Facebook users, the shift to email attacks broadens the potential victim pool significantly.
“Providing payment card information on these fake websites poses a substantial financial risk,&amp;quot; cautions Lukáš Štefanko, an ESET Malware Researcher.</description></item></channel></rss>