<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sexual Orientation Discrimination on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sexual-orientation-discrimination/</link><description>Recent content in Sexual Orientation Discrimination on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:38:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sexual-orientation-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mixed messages are being sent by the CJEU regarding LGBTI asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many nations have severe punishments for individuals identifying as LGBTI, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recognizes persecution based on sexual orientation as grounds for asylum in the EU. This protection falls under the &amp;lsquo;particular social group&amp;rsquo; category within the EU&amp;rsquo;s qualification Directive.
The CJEU has previously clarified that individuals seeking asylum on the basis of sexual orientation are not required to conceal their sexual orientation in their home country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contemplating EU Gender Equality Law on Surrogate Mothers' Day in Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:57:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The desire to have children has always been deeply understood, especially for women facing medical obstacles to childbirth. Adoption was the traditional solution, but recent decades have introduced alternatives like IVF and surrogacy.
While the EU doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly regulate these practices, it does address maternity leave through the Pregnant Workers&amp;rsquo; Directive. The Directive on Sex Discrimination in Employment further tackles the employment aspects of pregnancy. This directive prohibits discrimination against women undergoing IVF treatment even before pregnancy, as established by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Mayr case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jonathan Sumption's perspective on human rights is not coherent when considering the historical context of gay rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</guid><description>In his Reith Lecture, “Human Rights and Wrongs,” Jonathan Sumption argues that the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) has overstepped its boundaries. He believes the court continuously expands its interpretation of the European Convention on Human Rights, creating new rights and encroaching on areas that should be determined by elected officials.
Sumption has raised similar concerns previously, stating in 2016 that the ECtHR is at the forefront of creating fundamental law that goes beyond the original text of the Convention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anticipating the ECJ Decision in Coman: Progressing Towards EU-wide Recognition of Same-Sex Marriages across Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Photo: Mr Adrian Coman (right) with his spouse, Mr Claibourn Robert Hamilton (left)
(picture from PinkNews http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/29/romania-goes-to-court-over-whether-to-recognise-gay-couples-marriage/)
Introduction
The question of legal recognition for same-sex relationships has become a major topic in recent decades, sparking intense discussions globally in legislative bodies, courts, and the media, with strong opinions on both sides. This complex and delicate issue intersects with human rights, religious beliefs, moral perspectives, traditions, and constitutional principles like equality, personal freedom, and inherent human worth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dr. David L. Parris v. Trinity College Dublin and Others represents yet another missed chance to effectively protect LGB rights under EU law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>By Dr. Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Introduction
The recent ruling in the Parris case represents a missed chance for the European Court of Justice (ECJ) to provide meaningful protection to LGB individuals and same-sex couples under EU law. While recent cases like Asociaţia Accept and Hay suggested a shift towards stronger protection of LGB rights, the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s judgment in Parris, similar to the Léger case preceding it, reveals a hesitancy to address matters considered sensitive by Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disappointing CJEU ruling upholds ban on blood donation by gay and bisexual men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice in Case C-528/13 Léger determined that permanent bans on blood donation by gay and bisexual men solely based on their sexual history with other men might be justified in certain situations to ensure high health protection standards. This piece argues that this ruling is disappointing and could lead to accusations of inadequate LGB rights protection or even ingrained homophobia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it against EU law to tolerate discrimination against women who are breastfeeding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, leader of the UK Independence Party, recently expressed that while he personally had no issue with public breastfeeding, businesses should set their own rules. He suggested businesses could ask breastfeeding women to move to a less conspicuous area, implying a discreet approach would be preferable.
His statement was prompted by incidents where a restaurant asked a woman to cover her baby while breastfeeding and another establishment suggested using the disabled restroom for this purpose...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>