<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UK Case Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-case-law/</link><description>Recent content in UK Case Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-case-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Although you have children together, your marriage is not genuine': Marriages of convenience, UK courts, and EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Aleksandra Jolkina, PhD in Law, Queen Mary University of London
Over the last twenty years, UK authorities have become increasingly wary of marriages within the UK between mobile EU citizens and third-country nationals (TCNs) with uncertain or irregular residence status. In the current climate of Euroscepticism, such marriages are often criticized as &amp;ldquo;marriages of convenience,&amp;rdquo; intended to circumvent British immigration laws. This piece examines how UK courts interpret the concept of marriages of convenience, the potential implications for families of EU citizens residing in the UK, and the anticipated changes after Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK Motor Insurance Law in the EU: Road Accidents and Off-Road Responsibilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</guid><description>James Marson (Reader in Law, Sheffield Hallam University), Katy Ferris (Assistant Professor in Business Law, Nottingham University Business School) and Neil Fletcher (Senior Lecturer, Sheffield Hallam University)
Introduction
While the UK has seen notable legal victories concerning member state liability for breaches of EU law, the ability to hold the state accountable for individual losses remains limited. Establishing a breach significant enough to warrant damages is often a hurdle, except in motor vehicle insurance law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>