<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KFH on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kfh/</link><description>Recent content in KFH on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:56:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kfh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces Visa Infinite debit card for exclusive VIP clients</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new debit card, Visa Infinite, exclusively for its ‘Priority’ private banking customers.
Each customer is assigned a personal relationship manager who oversees the issuance of the new card and serves as their primary point of contact for all KFH services. According to Private Banking General Manager, Matthew Welch, the card offers customers unique benefits and support services.
These benefits include access to over 500 airport lounges globally, special offers and priority reservations at a wide range of upscale restaurants, and a 24/7 international concierge service for reservations, ticket bookings, car rentals, and taxi arrangements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces the Bunyani financing campaign for completion works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new campaign called &amp;ldquo;Bunyani&amp;hellip; from skeleton structure to delivery&amp;rdquo; to provide financing options for owners of residential, investment, and industrial land plots. This campaign aims to help customers complete various construction phases, including finishing works, maintenance, and restoration.
Ahmad Al-Khaled, Deputy General Manager Commercial Services at KFH, stated that the campaign offers clients simplified financing solutions. These include financing of up to KD70,000, a repayment period of 15 years, a grace period of 12 months for the first installment, and a competitive profit rate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the Al Rabeh salary account by Kuwait Finance House</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced the Al-Rabeh account, a salary account that offers customers chances to win valuable prizes like Range Rovers and gold each quarter. Al-Rabeh is also designed as an investment savings account, providing customers with annual dividends.
This account caters to individuals who want to transfer their salaries and manage their personal finances while benefiting from savings and investment opportunities. The Al-Rabeh account is available in Kuwaiti Dinars (KD) and requires regular salary transfers to be eligible for prize draws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>