<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Requirements on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-requirements/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Requirements on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-requirements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DS3 Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Mid-sized and larger businesses that have outgrown the capacity of T1 lines have turned to DS3 Internet Service as the next step in their telecommunications services. Currently, there are more choices for businesses, both small businesses with high bandwidth demands and larger companies seeking this service level.
DS3, short for Digital Signal level 3, is a well-established telecommunications standard for transmitting digital data. It provides a reliable 45 Mbps bandwidth suitable for dedicated point-to-point connections, PBX telephone systems, or internet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Future Proofing Your WAN With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Wide area networks (WANs) are changing. While once reliant on telephone technology, core networks are shifting towards packet-switched services to handle the increasing dominance of data and video traffic over voice. This shift raises questions for businesses about adapting their connections to stay current.
Many organizations face growing bandwidth demands. As their service contracts near renewal, they are reevaluating options, considering newer Ethernet services as alternatives to traditional T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive.</description></item></channel></rss>