<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Western Sahara on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/western-sahara/</link><description>Recent content in Western Sahara on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/western-sahara/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The relationship between the EU and Morocco and the issue of the Western Sahara: the European Court of Justice and the principles of international law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</guid><description>Markus W. Gehring: University Lecturer, University of Cambridge; J.S.D. (Yale), LL.M. (Yale), Dr jur. (Hamburg), MA (Cantab); Deputy Director, Economic Law at CIGI
On December 21, 2016, the Court of Justice issued its appeals decision in the case of Council v. Front Polisario. This Grand Chamber judgment, reached under an expedited procedure, overturned the prior decision made by the EU General Court in Front Polisario v Council roughly a year before.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides additional clarification on how the EU-Morocco Fisheries Partnership Agreement applies to Western Sahara.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-additional-clarification-on-how-the-eu-morocco-fisheries-partnership-agreement-applies-to-western-sahara/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-additional-clarification-on-how-the-eu-morocco-fisheries-partnership-agreement-applies-to-western-sahara/</guid><description>By Markus W. Gehring, Lecturer in Law, University of Cambridge
On February 27, 2018, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in a case referred by the High Court of England and Wales. The case, Western Sahara Campaign UK v. HM Revenue and Customs, Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, C-266/16, concerned the legality of EU fishing activities in waters adjacent to Western Sahara.</description></item></channel></rss>