<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Connection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-connection/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Connection on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-connection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks.</description></item><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Wireless SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Traditionally, business phone lines and dedicated internet relied on physical wires. However, wireless SIP trunking is emerging as a new option.
](http://www.affordablevpn.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
Airband Communications, a frontrunner in this technology, offers business-class voice services packaged with wireless internet access. This is comparable to a SIP trunk or an integrated voice and data service in the wired world, but Airband&amp;rsquo;s offering presents unique benefits.
Similar to other integrated services, a single connection provides both phone and internet access, only in this case, it&amp;rsquo;s wireless.</description></item><item><title>Speed of Metro Ethernet Zooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</guid><description>Forget Superman, when it comes to speed and affordability, Metro Ethernet is the real superhero of business bandwidth solutions. It surpasses conventional options like T1 and DS3, offering significantly faster speeds at a lower cost.
Metro Ethernet is in high demand, rapidly becoming the go-to choice for businesses. Its speed can be significantly higher than what you&amp;rsquo;re currently using, and it&amp;rsquo;s generally more cost-effective per Mbps compared to other options, including T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>Telecommunication DS3 Affordable For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</guid><description>Modern businesses need increasing levels of bandwidth to accommodate computer-driven processes that enhance productivity. When a T1 line reaches its capacity, and more bandwidth is necessary, there are options to consider.
A logical next step, if bandwidth needs have gradually increased, is to bond a second T1 line with the first. This doubles the capacity, providing a 3 Mbps WAN connection. Additional T1 lines can be bonded to further multiply the bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>Same Budget, More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Is Slow Network Speed Affecting Your Business?
Are you experiencing frustrating network issues like slow downloads, choppy calls, interrupted streaming, and sluggish website loading?
Do You Need More Bandwidth?
There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance your internet connection needs more bandwidth. While your internal network might be fast enough, your external connection (WAN) might not be able to handle your current needs.
Signs You Need More Bandwidth
If your internet service hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years but your business relies more on multimedia and online tools, you probably need more bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>SDN Performance Takes a Leaf of Faith</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cloud computing has highlighted the importance of reliable internet connections, known as WANs (Wide Area Networks). In the past, slow file transfers or unreliable internet were acceptable because crucial tasks were handled within the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network. However, now that businesses rely on cloud services, the performance of the WAN is just as crucial as the internal network (LAN).
WAN Challenges
The main challenge with WANs is that businesses don&amp;rsquo;t control them like they do their internal networks.</description></item></channel></rss>