<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Canon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/canon/</link><description>Recent content in Canon on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/canon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11.</description></item><item><title>Canon has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Canon Singapore has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution providing businesses with real-time delivery tracking and automated scheduling. Designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) that rely on scheduling, delivery, and documentation for their core operations, FleetnexG offers a way to optimize resources and boost efficiency.
Vincent Low, Director &amp;amp; General Manager of Business Imaging Solutions at Canon Singapore, highlights the need for SMEs to go beyond timely order fulfillment. He emphasizes that optimizing resources for greater efficiency and productivity is crucial for success in today&amp;rsquo;s business landscape.</description></item><item><title>Compact prints on-the-go with the Canon Mini Photo Printer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compact-prints-on-the-go-with-the-canon-mini-photo-printer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 20:39:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compact-prints-on-the-go-with-the-canon-mini-photo-printer/</guid><description>Canon has unveiled its most compact photo printer to date. Weighing a mere 160 grams, this pocket-sized device employs inkless printing technology, enabling instant printing and sharing of smartphone photos.
Source: Canon. The Canon Mini Photo Printer.
&amp;ldquo;Nowadays, photos of meaningful events often remain confined to our social media feeds. We at Canon aim to change this by encouraging spontaneity through the ultra-portable Canon Mini Photo Printer. Now, sharing printed photos with loved ones can be instantaneous,&amp;rdquo; stated Edwin Teoh, Head of Marketing, Singapore Operations, Canon Singapore.</description></item><item><title>The EOS M6 Mark II from Canon offers exceptional video production capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eos-m6-mark-ii-from-canon-offers-exceptional-video-production-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eos-m6-mark-ii-from-canon-offers-exceptional-video-production-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Canon the EOS M6 Mark II.
Canon has expanded its EOS M series of mirrorless cameras with the new EOS M6 Mark II. This stylish and portable camera is significantly lighter and smaller than a typical mid-range DSLR.
Edwin Teoh, Head of Marketing for Canon Singapore, highlights the EOS M6 Mark II&amp;rsquo;s portability and enhanced features, emphasizing its ability to capture life&amp;rsquo;s important moments. He also points out the camera&amp;rsquo;s advanced video capabilities, catering to the increasing popularity of videography and vlogging.</description></item><item><title>Canon Singapore will be hosting the Photo Marathon again in August 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-singapore-will-be-hosting-the-photo-marathon-again-in-august-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-singapore-will-be-hosting-the-photo-marathon-again-in-august-2015/</guid><description>Source: Canon eDM.
Canon Singapore has announced the details for their 13th annual Photo Marathon, taking place on August 22nd from 7 am to 8 pm at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre, Level 1, Hall C.
The competition revolves around three photography themes that are revealed on the day of the event. Participants are tasked with capturing these themes in their photographs and submitting them by the given deadline.</description></item><item><title>Follow the light from day to night on 28 July in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Canon. The Canon PhotoMarathon XVI will include assignments that extend from day into night.
Returning for its 16th year, the Canon PhotoMarathon XVI is scheduled for July 28th in Singapore. This year, Canon is expanding the event by incorporating community support and introducing new competition elements.
Building upon Canon’s ongoing support of local sports, Canon recently announced a partnership with Olympian Joseph Schooling. In line with the Canon PhotoMarathon’s goal to inspire and connect the photography community, Schooling will reveal one of the competition themes at the event.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Gadget Gift Guide for Christmas 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</guid><description>As 2017 comes to a close, treat yourself to a range of exciting new gadgets! WorkSmart Asia presents its top picks for this year, featuring:
Limited Edition Star Wars Shavers Source: Philips Singapore. Philips limited edition shavers, inspired by Star Wars. From left: the Poe Dameron-inspired Philips _Star Wars _Shaver SW6700/14; the BB-8-inspired SW5700/07 and the Stormtrooper-inspired SW170/04.
Philips introduces a new line of limited-edition shavers inspired by iconic Star Wars characters.</description></item><item><title>The Canon PhotoMarathon is scheduled to take place in Singapore in November</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 14:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</guid><description>Source: Canon eDM. Now in its 12th year, the Canon PhotoMarathon 2014 is the biggest photography competition in the region. Taking place in Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, Vietnam, India, Thailand, and Cambodia, the competition offers a fantastic chance for companies to form teams and compete in the Corporate Challenge category.
Companies can participate by assembling a team of at least three individuals who register as a group. In contrast to the open and student divisions, corporate teams are evaluated collectively.</description></item><item><title>Canon has introduced a second camera to its mirrorless EOS R range and has also revealed its RF lens roadmap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-introduced-a-second-camera-to-its-mirrorless-eos-r-range-and-has-also-revealed-its-rf-lens-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-introduced-a-second-camera-to-its-mirrorless-eos-r-range-and-has-also-revealed-its-rf-lens-roadmap/</guid><description>Canon has introduced the EOS RP, the second camera in their EOS R series of full-frame mirrorless interchangeable-lens cameras.
The EOS RP is the lightest and most compact camera in Canon&amp;rsquo;s full-frame lineup, but it still packs impressive capabilities. It boasts the new RF lens mount and Canon&amp;rsquo;s proprietary technology, including a DIGIC 8 image processor and Dual Pixel CMOS AF for exceptional optical quality.
Significantly smaller than other EOS cameras, the EOS RP weighs only 485g, making it comfortable to use, especially for those new to full-frame cameras.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Canon PhotoMarathon XVI 2018 have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-canon-photomarathon-xvi-2018-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 20:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-canon-photomarathon-xvi-2018-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>The winners of the 16th Canon PhotoMarathon XVI 2018 in Singapore have been revealed.
This annual photography competition, being the largest in the region, challenges photography enthusiasts to test their skills under a time constraint. A new challenge category, &amp;lsquo;dusk,&amp;rsquo; was introduced this year, allowing participants to capture a blend of daytime and nighttime scenes.
Here is a list of the winners:
Best Of Show - Student: Timothy John Low Wen, Nanyang Polytechnic Best Of Show - Open: Azril Azam Bin Abdul Rahim Team Category Winner: ORBIGUD School Challenge Winner: Anglo-Chinese School (Independent) Theme 1: Solitude Student Category 1st: Myo Thi Ha Kyaw, Nanyang Technological University 2nd: Evita Lee Ann Hwee, Christ Church Secondary School 3rd: Ong Yi Feng Jayden, Edgefield Secondary School Open Category 1st: Aht Yomyai 2nd: Zhang Dongli 3rd: Ahmad Iskandar Bin Abdullah Theme 2: Simplicity Student Category 1st: Jessie Chia, National University Of Singapore 2nd: Timothy John Low Wen, Nanyang Polytechnic 3rd: Teo Xu Kai, Temasek Polytechnic Open Category 1st: Ong Kah Hong 2nd: Azril Azam Bin Abdul Rahim 3rd: Siyuan Ma Canon Challenge Winner: Shrirang Rajaram Nirgun Theme 3: Glow Student Category 1st: Lester Thomas Daniel, Singapore Polytechnic 2nd: Mikaela Gn, Anglo-Chinese School (Independent) 3rd: Benjamin Tay Tze Min, Hwa Chong Institution Open Category 1st: Nursanto Soeradi Somo 2nd: Gerdie Hutomo 3rd: Mai Hung Son</description></item><item><title>New Canon PIXMA all-in-one printers have been released in vibrant colors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-canon-pixma-all-in-one-printers-have-been-released-in-vibrant-colors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 22:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-canon-pixma-all-in-one-printers-have-been-released-in-vibrant-colors/</guid><description>Canon is releasing three new PIXMA all-in-one printers in stylish colors like Millennial Pink, Brilliant Green, and Navy Blue, offering options for everyone.
These PIXMA TS8370, TS6370, and TS5370 all-in-one printers blend design and functionality. They offer various connectivity choices and productivity tools, making them perfect for home offices and small businesses.
PIXMA TS8370 Photo All-in-One - A Compact Six-Ink Photo Printer
This printer, available in red, white, and black, has top-tier features and photo print quality.</description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:</description></item></channel></rss>