<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trend Micro on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trend-micro/</link><description>Recent content in Trend Micro on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trend-micro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phones become unresponsive due to Android vulnerability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</guid><description>Trend Micro has identified a weakness in the Android operating system that can cause a phone to seem non-functional. Affected phones exhibit symptoms like no ringing or notification sounds, an inability to make calls, and an unresponsive screen. Additionally, locked phones cannot be unlocked.
This vulnerability affects Android versions from 4.3 (Jelly Bean) to 5.1.1 (Lollipop), encompassing over half of all Android devices currently in use. Despite being reported to the Android Engineering Team in late May, no official fix has been released through the Android Open Source Project (AOSP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trend Micro advises Windows users to update their operating system to safeguard against the Winshock bug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</guid><description>A recently discovered flaw in Microsoft Windows has Trend Micro urging all Windows users to immediately update their systems. The issue exists in Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s data transfer platform, which is designed for secure communication. Trend Micro warns that users who don&amp;rsquo;t update are highly vulnerable to attacks, potentially allowing hackers to take control of their systems without any user interaction.
This bug, nicknamed &amp;ldquo;Winshock,&amp;rdquo; received a severity score of 9.3 out of 10 from the Common Vulnerability Scoring System...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trend Micro demonstrates ways to enhance the security of Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</guid><description>In 2014, Android controlled the global smartphone market, shipping one billion units and representing 81% of all smartphones shipped, as reported by Strategy Analytics.
Trend Micro researcher, Paul Oliveria, points out that Android&amp;rsquo;s popularity stems from its affordability, efficient data storage, and availability across various brands and price points.
This widespread use makes Android a prime target for hackers. To combat this, Trend Micro proposes seven security measures for mobile users:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trend Micro cautions that hackers are focusing on small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Trend Micro website.
Trend Micro warns that hackers are shifting tactics, moving away from mass spamming and towards sending personalized emails containing harmful attachments to compromise businesses. This method, the company cautions, could become the standard attack strategy in the Asia Pacific region.
A Trend Micro report titled &amp;ldquo;Piercing the HawkEye: Nigerian Cybercriminals Use a Simple Keylogger to Prey on SMBs Worldwide&amp;rdquo; reveals that two Nigerian hackers, known as &amp;ldquo;Uche&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Okiki,&amp;rdquo; are using inexpensive keylogging software called Hawkeye to target small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>