<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FastE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/faste/</link><description>Recent content in FastE on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/faste/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet and Colocation For Texas Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</guid><description>Texas is known for its expansive size, thriving businesses, massive data generation, and a critical need for extensive bandwidth. Alpheus, a Texas-based telecommunications company, is acutely aware of these needs and caters its services to businesses across various sectors including finance, energy, government, healthcare, IT, legal, and media.
Headquartered in Houston, Alpheus boasts a robust fiber optic network that interconnects major Texan cities like Dallas, Fort Worth, Waco, Bryan, Austin, San Antonio, Laredo, McAllen, Harlingen, Corpus Christi, Victoria, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>FastE Is The New DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than their T1 lines can provide have usually upgraded to DS3. However, a faster and more affordable option, Fast Ethernet (FastE), is now available.
While you might not know Fast Ethernet as a Metro or Carrier bandwidth service, the term is likely familiar. Fast Ethernet refers to 100 Mbps Ethernet, one of the standard LAN speeds alongside 10 Mbps and 1,000 Mbps Ethernet (Gigabit Ethernet or GigE).</description></item><item><title>Finding Fiber Lit Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 18:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</guid><description>To secure high bandwidth at affordable rates, you need to be in a &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; building. This term refers to buildings equipped with active fiber optic bandwidth services, utilizing laser light to transmit data through fiber optic strands.
If your building is &amp;ldquo;lit,&amp;rdquo; obtaining fiber optic bandwidth is typically straightforward, though construction costs might apply if cabling to your space is absent. However, a bigger challenge arises if your building lacks fiber optic connectivity.</description></item></channel></rss>