<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Protection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protection/</link><description>Recent content in Protection on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Caution: Superman is poisonous</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</guid><description>According to a McAfee blog post, Superman poses a significant online threat. The company argues that the widespread presence of superheroes beyond comic books allows hackers and scammers to exploit them for cybercrime.
McAfee&amp;rsquo;s survey, which used their SiteAdvisor site ratings, revealed that Superman is the &amp;ldquo;Most Toxic Superhero.&amp;rdquo; The study found that searches combining &amp;ldquo;Superman&amp;rdquo; with terms like &amp;ldquo;free torrent download,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;watch,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;free app,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; have a 16.5% chance of leading to websites containing threats like spyware, adware, spam, phishing, viruses, and other malware.</description></item><item><title>Today is World Backup Day. Have you ensured the safety of your data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</guid><description>A recent worldwide study funded by Acronis, a prominent name in hybrid cloud data protection, highlights a rising awareness of the importance of safeguarding personal data on computers, mobile phones, and tablets.
Almost half of the surveyed individuals possess more than four devices per household requiring protection, and 45% are most afraid of misplacing photos and videos. Security and privacy were identified as crucial factors in data backup.
Evolving Concerns in Personal Data Security The traditional worries of hardware malfunctions and accidental deletions are no longer the sole reasons for data loss apprehension.</description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2017 is compatible with Facebook, wireless backups, and remote backups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:47:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</guid><description>Source: Acronis. Acronis True Image 2017.
Acronis, a major provider of hybrid cloud data protection, released Acronis True Image 2017, its newest personal backup software.
This iteration combines the existing full image local and cloud backup with new features such as wireless backup for mobile devices to either local Windows computers or the Acronis Cloud. It also allows for an unlimited number of mobile devices and provides complete Facebook account data backups.</description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Dell has launched backup appliances for midmarket businesses, along with complimentary Windows data recovery software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</guid><description>Dell has introduced new data protection solutions tailored for small and medium-sized businesses to enhance the protection of their crucial systems, applications, and data, both on-site and in cloud environments. These solutions include data deduplication appliance models and the new Dell Data Protection | Endpoint Recovery – Free Edition.
Back up more and store less The latest additions to the Dell DR series of deduplication appliances are the Dell DR4300e, DR4300, and DR6300.</description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces an improved True Image family and guarantees regular updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</guid><description>Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, recently launched its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 products in Singapore.
During the launch event, Acronis Co-Founder and CEO, Serguei Beloussov, emphasized the increasing importance of data protection, stating that it will soon be as essential as basic necessities. He believes that data represents a comprehensive record of our lives and preserving it should be a top priority, with the goal of eventually retaining all data indefinitely.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Upgrade with SyncDrive Platter Motor, Commander Remote Control and Internal RIAA Pre-Amplifier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</guid><description>A customer from Kentucky requested a full upgrade for their Beogram 4002 turntable, including three modifications: a SyncDrive motor for enhanced speed stability, a Commander remote control system for convenient operation and keypad protection, and a Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier for direct connection to modern audio equipment.
All upgrades were installed without soldering. The SyncDrive replaced the original DC motor, connecting to existing mounting points and the main circuit board. The Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier replaced the output board, using compatible connectors for easy installation.</description></item><item><title>Are you still using Windows XP? Norton and Qihoo 360 are here to assist you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</guid><description>The AV-Test Institute, located in Germany, tested ten antivirus programs for Windows XP. Out of these, Qihoo 360 Internet Security 9 and Norton Internet Security 2014 proved most effective.
Source: Qihoo 360. AV-TEST Report: Exploit Protection on Windows XP
The institute designed 54 attack simulations using various methods and vulnerabilities to thoroughly test each program. The tested antivirus solutions included products from Qihoo 360, Avast, AVG, Avira, Bitdefender, Eset, Kaspersky, and Norton.</description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE.</description></item></channel></rss>