<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carrier on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carrier/</link><description>Recent content in Carrier on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carrier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Better Than a T3 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 voice and data lines, once a reliable option for businesses, now offer insufficient speed (45 Mbps) for modern demands, which often exceed 100 Mbps. Businesses today require significantly faster connections, with some even seeking speeds beyond 10 Gbps. If you&amp;rsquo;re still using a T3 line, you might find better bandwidth options at a similar or lower cost.
What is a T3 Line?
Developed by Bell Labs, the T3 line was designed to carry numerous simultaneous phone conversations, a function it still serves in certain settings.</description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals.</description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network.</description></item></channel></rss>