<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Horizontal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/horizontal/</link><description>Recent content in Horizontal on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:23:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/horizontal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Lubricating and Adjusting the Solenoid to Tonearm Linkages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</guid><description>Following the solenoid replacement and removal of the faulty voltage regulator on my Beogram 4000 restoration project, the arm mechanism remained sluggish. This indicated a need to lubricate the connection between the damper and tonearm lift. Additionally, the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s horizontal alignment was significantly off. While attempting to adjust this with the set screw on the tonearm counterweight&amp;rsquo;s connecting arm, I discovered it was glued in place with epoxy, preventing screwdriver access - likely another consequence of a previous repair attempt.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Keypad Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with LEDs. This enhances the unit&amp;rsquo;s lifespan and prevents issues that incandescent bulbs, susceptible to vibration, can experience during shipping.
The top two bulbs illuminate the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s unique position indicator, while the vertical bulbs light the RPM trimmers. I recently designed SMD LED-based PCB replacements for the position indicator bulbs (available via email).
Standard red LEDs with current-limiting resistors can replace the RPM trimmer bulbs.</description></item></channel></rss>