<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Knowledge on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/knowledge/</link><description>Recent content in Knowledge on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/knowledge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China.</description></item><item><title>Winners of the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Awards are influential figures in promoting knowledge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 01:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. A representative from the MiSK Foundation receives the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award.
The Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award recipients, celebrated on November 21st, share a common goal: shaping the future. This award acknowledges those who significantly contribute to the creation and dissemination of knowledge globally.
Among the winners, Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s MiSK Foundation focuses on developing educational institutions and bolstering scientific research.</description></item></channel></rss>