<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Global on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/global/</link><description>Recent content in Global on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:37:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/global/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement was initiated in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: GEM Facebook page.
The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) launched officially in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia today. This non-governmental organization (NGO) aims to create a platform for entrepreneurs from various sectors like social entrepreneurship, technology, and halal to connect.
“This NGO brings together community leaders from different networks who will cultivate strong partnerships for Malaysia and our entrepreneurs,&amp;quot; shared YBhg. Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah, GEM patron and Secretary General Treasury, Ministry of Finance.</description></item><item><title>Switch to organic bath and shower products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</guid><description>According to research firm Technavio, consumers are increasingly interested in bath and shower products that offer both organic ingredients and convenience. The company&amp;rsquo;s report on the global bath and shower products market highlights that rising living standards and disposable income are driving consumers towards higher-priced, aesthetically pleasing products with unique fragrances and effective ingredients. This trend is projected to propel the market to a value of at least US$15 billion by 2019, reflecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of approximately 4% from 2015 to 2019.</description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule.</description></item><item><title>According to the Brand Finance Global 500 2016 report, Disney is recognized as the most influential brand in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</guid><description>· Out of the top 10 fastest growing brands, four are Chinese.
· Disney is the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential brand due to the immense success of Star Wars.
· Despite experiencing a decline in sales, Apple&amp;rsquo;s brand value increased by 14% to US$145.9 billion, making it the most valuable brand globally.
· Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s brand value experienced a decline of US$12 billion as a consequence of the emissions controversy.
· Leading brands are outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500 average in terms of share performance.</description></item><item><title>Schroders predicts that the second half of 2016 will be challenging, but still an improvement over the first half</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</guid><description>Schroders Investment Management believes the global economy will improve after weak growth in the first half of 2016.
Keith Wade, Chief Economist &amp;amp; Strategist at Schroders, states that there are indicators of increasing growth in the next two quarters of 2016, with previous economic obstacles diminishing. Consumer spending is also rising due to renewed credit growth. However, Wade cautions that 2016 will likely not see robust global growth.
Wade attributes much of the sluggishness to the aftermath of the global financial crisis, with various economic actors still adapting.</description></item><item><title>The popularity of cosmetic surgery is increasing globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-cosmetic-surgery-is-increasing-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-cosmetic-surgery-is-increasing-globally/</guid><description>Cosmetic surgery is becoming increasingly popular. Over 23 million cosmetic procedures, both surgical and non-surgical, were performed globally in 2013, as reported by the International Society of Aesthetic Plastic Surgery (ISAPS). This international society comprises over 2,700 board-certified aesthetic plastic surgeons across 95 countries.
Botulinum toxin (Botox) injections were the most common cosmetic procedure performed.
Dr. Carlos Uebel, ISAPS President, highlighted the improved data collection strategy for the report, stating that the society aimed to enhance the comprehensiveness and statistical soundness of the survey methodology.</description></item><item><title>The goal of the BTSE Debit Card is to provide worldwide access to funds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</guid><description>Source: BTSE. The BTSE Debit Card.
There&amp;rsquo;s a new player in the crypto debit card arena. Accepted at over 53 million MasterCard merchants and compatible with over a million ATMs globally, the BTSE Debit Card sets itself apart by allowing users to fund it with various fiat and cryptocurrencies without needing a traditional bank account.
BTSE, a fintech company focused on financial freedom, designed this card to give users more control over their money.</description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region.</description></item><item><title>Benetton will concentrate on empowering women through their new collection, A Collection of Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</guid><description>The idea that women sharing their experiences and learning from each other is crucial for creating a brighter future is the driving force behind A Collection Of Us. This new United Colors of Benetton collection, launching in four parts throughout October 2015, December 2015, February 2016, and April 2016, embodies this philosophy.
Each capsule within the collection reimagines a core aspect of Benetton&amp;rsquo;s brand identity—heritage, technique, color, and performance—giving it a fresh and modern significance.</description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors.</description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year.</description></item><item><title>More than half of the worldwide facial aesthetics market is made up of Botox</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</guid><description>The global demand for facial aesthetic procedures is growing, driven by consumers who are increasingly interested in their appearance and prefer less invasive treatments, according to a report on the Facial Aesthetics Market from 2016-2020 by Technavio.
Technavio&amp;rsquo;s research shows that Botox holds the largest share of the facial aesthetics market, making up roughly 52% of the total. They attribute this dominance to changing cultural perceptions of beauty, higher disposable incomes, and the growing popularity of the brand.</description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www.</description></item><item><title>Hilton guests will enjoy Live Nation experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and Live Nation, a live entertainment company, have launched a new five-year marketing partnership. This collaboration will provide unique experiences, including artist connections and concerts, to Hilton HHonors members, guests, and employees across Hilton&amp;rsquo;s global network of over 4,250 hotels.
Source: Hilton Worldwide. Hilton
aims to motivate a new,
healthier way of thinking - urging
individuals to embrace the unfamiliar,
gain perspective, and learn from daily
life and travel.</description></item><item><title>Berkeley Earth raises concerns about air pollution in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</guid><description>Source: Berkeley Earth website.
A recent study published in PLOS ONE by Berkeley Earth reveals that air pollution causes approximately 4,000 deaths per day in China, representing 17% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total deaths. This non-profit organization, established to investigate concerns raised by global warming skeptics, determined that the air quality for 38% of China&amp;rsquo;s population would be deemed &amp;ldquo;unhealthy&amp;rdquo; by United States standards.
Berkeley Earth&amp;rsquo;s analysis of hourly measurements from 1,500 ground stations over a four-month period indicated coal as the most likely source of PM2.</description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions.</description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031.</description></item><item><title>Australia, Singapore, and the UAE are among the top 10 destinations on people's relocation wishlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</guid><description>A recent report by Hydrogen Group, a global recruitment firm, reveals a growing trend of professionals seeking international work opportunities. The study found that the number of individuals open to working abroad doubled over a five-year period, rising from 16% in 2010 to 35% in 2014. Furthermore, 40% of respondents believe there are no obstacles to relocating for work.
While the US and UK were the most popular destinations, followed by Australia, Singapore ranked as the most preferred Asian country at seventh place.</description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders.</description></item><item><title>We are all increasing the frequency of washing our hair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</guid><description>The increasing prevalence of hair problems and pollution has led people to shampoo their hair more often, either daily or every other day. This trend has fueled the growth of the shampoo industry, as noted in Technavio&amp;rsquo;s report on the global hair shampoo market from 2015 to 2019. The report highlights that shampoos held over 40% of the global hair care market share in 2014.
Source: Technavio.
The global shampoo market is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 4.</description></item><item><title>Vertiv declares utilities as the most crucial industry globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vertiv-declares-utilities-as-the-most-crucial-industry-globally/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vertiv-declares-utilities-as-the-most-crucial-industry-globally/</guid><description>A new study from Vertiv, formerly Emerson Network Power, has found that utilities, including electricity, gas, nuclear power, and water treatment, are the world&amp;rsquo;s most critical industries.
Vertiv assembled a group of international experts in critical infrastructure to develop a system for quantifying and ranking the criticality of various industries based on 15 criteria. Public transportation, particularly rail and air travel, came in second place, followed by telecommunications, upstream oil and gas operations, and cloud and colocation services.</description></item><item><title>The World Economic Forum introduces its inaugural online leadership module for professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</guid><description>Professionals can now register for the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s first online leadership program, Global Information Technology Outlook. This six-week module, created for senior executives and fast-track leadership programs, offers a comprehensive overview of important new technologies transforming industries and society.
Professor Klaus Schwab, Founder and Executive Chairman of the World Economic Forum, highlighted the challenges leaders face understanding the increasingly complex and unpredictable world, largely due to rapid technological advancements. He stated that the Forum Academy module addresses this by giving leaders a better grasp of ongoing information technology transformations.</description></item><item><title>Investors are increasingly optimistic about placing foreign direct investment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore achieved a top-ten ranking in the 2016 AT Kearney Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) Confidence Index. The city-state climbed five positions, representing the most significant advancement in the rankings, securing the 10th spot.
This index provides a future-oriented assessment of how political, economic, and regulatory shifts are likely to influence FDI inflows into various countries in the coming years. Since its inception in 1998, the study has consistently identified the preferred global destinations for FDI, with the index rankings closely mirroring actual global FDI inflows.</description></item><item><title>Singapore ranks second in global competitiveness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</guid><description>The World Economic Forum (WEF) recently published its Global Competitiveness Report for 2016.
The report determined that a global trend of decreasing openness in countries is negatively impacting growth and prosperity. Financial stimuli like quantitative easing are insufficient for sustained growth and must be paired with reforms that bolster competitiveness. For emerging markets, modernizing business practices and investing in innovation are now just as crucial as infrastructure, skilled workforces, and efficient markets.</description></item><item><title>Workers value recognition more than money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</guid><description>Source: ACCA report. Tone at the top influences corporate behaviour the most, according to 61% of respondents.
A recent report by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) titled &amp;ldquo;Culture and channelling corporate behaviour: ACCA member survey&amp;rdquo; found that workplace recognition is the most significant motivator for employees across all ages, industries, and locations. Notably, this recognition even outweighs monetary rewards.
The survey, conducted with support from the Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC), gathered insights from nearly 2,000 ACCA finance professionals globally.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>Consumers are now blending their physical and digital experiences. How should companies respond?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</guid><description>A new study emphasizes the importance of personalization in merging online and offline shopping experiences for &amp;ldquo;phy-gital&amp;rdquo; consumers. The study found that while companies are embracing digital technologies, they are lagging in implementing personalization strategies that consumers desire.
The study revealed that personalized promotions significantly influence purchasing decisions, encouraging consumers to buy familiar products and explore new ones. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between consumer expectations and company investments. While consumers value enhanced search and comparison features, companies prioritize features like shopping lists and social elements.</description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market.</description></item><item><title>The top 10 global consumer trends for 2015 focus on multitasking and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor.
Market research firm Euromonitor International recently published their findings on the top 10 global consumer trends for 2015.
Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Global Consumer Trends 2015 report states that consumers, pressed for time, are seeking convenience, diverse options, global product availability, and instant satisfaction. They aim to get the most out of their time and money, looking for products and services that meet multiple needs. As an illustration, a Swedish taxi service provides in-car therapists for their stressed and busy clients at a rate of US$165 per hour.</description></item><item><title>Today is the day for the landrush of .global, .website, and .press domain names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</guid><description>Starting August 27th, Singapore time, several top-level domain names will be up for grabs in a &amp;ldquo;landrush&amp;rdquo; phase, according to online brand specialist IP Mirror.
The &amp;ldquo;sunrise&amp;rdquo; phase, reserved for trademark holders to register their brands, precedes this period. During the landrush phase, anyone can secure remaining domain names at a premium price.
IP Mirror highlights &amp;ldquo;.global&amp;rdquo; as a particularly appealing option, signifying a broad international reach. This domain&amp;rsquo;s landrush phase lasts from August 27th to September 4th.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals.</description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 provides a boost to talented young entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: GES 2016. President Obama waves as he walks off the stage with Mark Zuckerberg, Chairman, CEO, and co-founder of Facebook with successful young entrepreneurs from Africa and South America after a panel discussion that he moderated. This is the occasion where he famously said he still had some time to go before he could wear a t-shirt like Zuckerberg, but could at least remove his jacket.
Former US President Barack Obama believes entrepreneurship is a driving force for economic growth.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today.</description></item><item><title>AIN has added English and Chinese websites for those interested in fashion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</guid><description>Source: AIN English website.
A Korean women&amp;rsquo;s fashion brand is aiming to become a global name, focusing particularly on mainland China, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
AIN has seen positive results selling on international e-commerce platforms. To further expand its reach, the company has launched English and Chinese websites through cafe24, a leading Korean e-commerce platform. AIN&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Park A-In, shared that customers appreciate the brand&amp;rsquo;s distinct, contemporary designs and overall aesthetic.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>The acceptance of UnionPay is expanding globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 19:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</guid><description>UnionPay has successfully expanded its network, brand, and products globally, advancing the international use of Chinese financial technology standards. UnionPay International is now present in over 50 markets involved in the Belt and Road Initiative.
Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International, emphasized their strategy of adapting to each local market, fostering personnel exchange between China and other regions, and supporting the globalization of Chinese financial standards.
In Kazakhstan, over 1.3 million UnionPay cards have been issued.</description></item><item><title>LBS and Fudan have collaborated to introduce a new Global Masters in Management program with a double business degree</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</guid><description>London Business School (LBS) and Fudan University&amp;rsquo;s School of Management (FDSM) have partnered to create a dual-degree Global Masters in Management (MiM) program.
Sir Andrew Likierman, Dean of London Business School, emphasized the increasing need for skilled professionals who can navigate the business landscape in both Eastern and Western contexts. He highlighted that this collaboration reflects their dedication to close partnerships with Chinese corporations. The program aims to equip graduates with a global perspective through direct engagement with both China and the West.</description></item><item><title>16% of the top 100 MBAs from the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Business schools in Asia may be overlooking the potential of online MBAs. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s first ever Online MBA Rankings for 2014, which came out in March, contained no Asian business schools in its list of the top 15 programs.
However, the region performs better in the traditional MBA format. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s Global MBA Rankings for 2014, published in January 2014, features a number of Asian schools within its top 50.</description></item><item><title>CEOs anticipate a deceleration in economic growth in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</guid><description>Global CEOs are expressing unprecedented pessimism regarding the economic outlook for 2020, according to PwC&amp;rsquo;s 23rd Annual Global CEO Survey. 53% of CEOs anticipate a decline in economic growth, a significant increase from 29% in 2019 and a stark contrast to the mere 5% who held this view in 2018. This marks the highest level of pessimism since the survey began in 2012, with only 22% of CEOs predicting economic growth in 2020, down from 42% in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Sony has introduced the Picture This Festival for the Planet competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</guid><description>Sony Pictures Television Networks (SPTN), working with the United Nations Foundation, has launched the Picture This Festival for the Planet. The short-film competition encourages emerging filmmakers, storytellers, and changemakers globally to share their visions for a positive future for the planet.
Representing over 70 countries, participants are invited to submit videos inspired by the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The SDGs are a collection of global goals adopted by the United Nations to address poverty, protect the planet, and promote prosperity for everyone.</description></item><item><title>The Global Day of Discovery at Renaissance Hotels worldwide is celebrated on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 04:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Renaissance Hotels is hosting its third annual Global Day of Discovery on June 26th at over 150 locations. On this day, almost every hotel will offer guests and community members the opportunity to explore something new. These events, designed by hotel Navigators, include musical performances, culinary experiences, art displays, cultural activities, and unique local excursions.
This day marks the start of the Renaissance Hotels&amp;rsquo; Summer of Discovery calendar, a summer-long series of exclusive events at all 157 hotels worldwide.</description></item><item><title>The Top 25 Multinational Workplaces consist of widely recognized brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</guid><description>Great Place to Work, a global firm that assists organizations in developing positive workplace cultures, has announced its yearly ranking of the top 25 multinational workplaces worldwide. This list is derived from an extensive study of workplace environments and recognizes companies with exceptional work cultures.
To be eligible for this list, companies must meet specific requirements: placement on at least five national &amp;ldquo;Best Workplaces&amp;rdquo; lists, a minimum of 5,000 employees, and a workforce comprised of at least 40% employees based outside of the company&amp;rsquo;s home country.</description></item><item><title>Singapore emerges victorious at the Culinary Olympics 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</guid><description>Source: the Singapore National Culinary Team. The Singapore National Culinary Team outperformed over 30 countries to become the champions of the Culinary Olympics 2016. The team achieved gold medals in both the Cold Display and Hot Cooking categories, proving the country&amp;rsquo;s chefs are world-class. From left: Teo Yeow Siang, team captain, from Lavish Catering; Triston Fang, team member, from Ocean Restaurant by Cat Cora, Resorts World Sentosa; Alan Wong, team member, from Lavish Catering; team manager Louis Tay from Swissotel Merchant Court; Roy Lim, team member, from Unilever FoodSolutions; and Alex Chong, team member, from The Regent Singapore.</description></item><item><title>KPMG has identified gaps in global corporate responsibility reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</guid><description>A 2015 KPMG study reveals inconsistencies in how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies report their carbon emissions, making it challenging to compare their performance. While 80% of the top 250 companies address carbon in their reports, the information provided varies significantly. For instance, only half declare carbon reduction goals, and among those, two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t explain their rationale.
The reported emissions types also differ. Most companies (84%) report emissions from their operations and purchased power (79%), but only half include supply chain emissions.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay International introduces a new cross-border marketing campaign with global promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</guid><description>Source: UnionPay International. Ge Huayong, Chairman of China UnionPay (sixth from the right), Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International (fifth from the right), and representatives from initial partners were present at the ceremony.
UnionPay International, in collaboration with Bank of China, China Merchants Bank, CYTS, Ctrip, Spring Airlines, SaSa Hong Kong, Prince Jewellery &amp;amp; Watch, LUKFOOK JEWELLERY, and ISA, has introduced 优计划 (Youjihua), translating to &amp;lsquo;a beneficial strategy&amp;rsquo; and playing on the &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; in UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s Chinese name.</description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization has declared the Ebola outbreak a global public health emergency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) declared the West African Ebola outbreak a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) on August 8th.
As of August 4, 2014, there were 1,711 cases (1,070 confirmed, 436 probable, and 205 suspected) of Ebola virus disease (EVD), resulting in 932 deaths. Between August 5th and 6th, 2014, 68 new EVD cases (including confirmed, probable, and suspected) and 29 deaths were reported across Guinea, Liberia, Nigeria, and Sierra Leone.</description></item><item><title>The average increase in deal values due to M&amp;A deal leaks is US$21 million</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-average-increase-in-deal-values-due-to-m-a-deal-leaks-is-us-21-million/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:22:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-average-increase-in-deal-values-due-to-m-a-deal-leaks-is-us-21-million/</guid><description>A new study by Intralinks and Cass Business School revealed that confidential information leaks about mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) before an official announcement added an average of US$21 million to the value of disclosed deals in 2016.
The report found that 8.6% of global M&amp;amp;A deals experienced leaks in 2016, a figure consistent with 2015 and exceeding the six-year low of 6% observed in 2014. Despite efforts by financial regulators to limit deal leaks through regulations and enforcement actions, the trend of leaked deals has seen an increase in 2015 and 2016.</description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations.</description></item><item><title>Ipsos: More than half of Singaporeans are feeling positive about 2022, but have mixed emotions about 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</guid><description>A recent worldwide survey conducted by Ipsos explored global citizens&amp;rsquo; opinions on the past year and their outlook for the future. The survey revealed that 73% of respondents believe their country had a challenging year, marking a slight improvement compared to the previous year (2021).
The Ipsos Global Predictions for 2023 report, which included data from 36 countries, indicated that over half (56%) of respondents globally considered 2022 a difficult year personally.</description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing.</description></item><item><title>The popularity of home remedies for teeth whitening is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 05:27:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</guid><description>Technavio, a research company specializing in technology, found that self-applied teeth whitening products have significantly changed the global oral care market. Consumers are increasingly choosing at-home treatments over professional ones. The firm attributes this shift to the affordability and convenience of oral care products like whitening strips, pens, and trays, which have become popular alternatives to professional whitening procedures.
According to a new Technavio report on the global teeth whitening product market, the industry is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 4% between 2015 and 2019.</description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks.</description></item><item><title>Aramex is constructing private parcel lockers to meet the demands of the expanding e-commerce industry in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:04:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Aramex, a leading provider of global logistics and transportation solutions, has partnered with InPost, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest parcel locker network. This collaboration aims to provide consumers in the Middle East with convenient access to private, automated parcel lockers for all their e-commerce needs by the end of 2014.
Aramex attributes the significant growth of the e-commerce sector in the region to several factors. These include a growing affluent urban population, increased interest in and demand for online products and services, and a rise in new online retailers entering the market.</description></item><item><title>The APAC region is strongly featured in Warc's list of the top 100 marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Warc, a provider of marketing intelligence, has introduced the Warc 100, a new ranking of the top marketing campaigns globally based on their effectiveness and strategic impact.
The Asia Pacific region contributed over 30 entries, including one from the UAE, with Australia having the second-highest representation after the US with 11 entries.
Among the top 10 campaigns from the Asia Pacific are: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s More Fun in the Philippines&amp;rdquo; by the Philippines Department of Tourism and BBDO Guerrero (ranked 3rd), &amp;ldquo;Overstay Checkout&amp;rdquo; by Art Series Hotels and Naked Communications (5th), &amp;ldquo;Smoking Kid&amp;rdquo; by Thai Health Promotion Foundation and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (7th), &amp;ldquo;Old Parts for New&amp;rdquo; by ORBIS International and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (8th), and &amp;ldquo;Car Creation&amp;rdquo; by NRMA Insurance and Whybin\TBWA (10th).</description></item><item><title>Apple is recalling Beats speakers and offering refunds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</guid><description>Apple initiated a voluntary recall of Beats Pill XL speakers due to a potential fire safety risk. The company determined that in rare cases, the battery in these speakers may overheat.
This recall only affects the specific Beats Pill XL speaker model shown in the images and no other Beats or Apple products.
Apple prioritizes customer safety and urges all Beats Pill XL users to stop using their devices.
To return their speakers and receive a refund of US$325 (or equivalent in local currency) as Apple Store credit or electronic payment, owners can visit www.</description></item></channel></rss>