<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Point of Presence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/point-of-presence/</link><description>Recent content in Point of Presence on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/point-of-presence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cross-Border Private Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</guid><description>When considering private line services for business locations, we often focus on domestic connections. However, international business operations necessitate cross-border line services, which not all carriers provide.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/international/PrivateLines/international_private_lines.php)
International connectivity involves navigating varying regulations, practices, and technical requirements. For example, the US and Europe employ slightly different companding standards for digitized phone calls. While both use the G.711 CODEC for PCM, the US and others utilize Mu-law compression, while Europe and most of the world use A-law.</description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in.</description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Point of Presence Locator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting more bandwidth for your money, and finding an Ethernet Point of Presence (POP) Locator can help. But what is a POP and how can it save you money?
Essentially, a POP is a carrier&amp;rsquo;s service location, such as a central office with termination equipment for their fiber optic network. Think of it as a station for accessing high-speed data and voice services. POPs aren&amp;rsquo;t always in carrier offices; they can be in colocation centers, shared facilities housing servers and offering resources like bandwidth, security, and backup power.</description></item></channel></rss>