<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Customer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/customer/</link><description>Recent content in Customer on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:19:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/customer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vizury monitors users on various screens to gain a better understanding of them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vizury-monitors-users-on-various-screens-to-gain-a-better-understanding-of-them/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vizury-monitors-users-on-various-screens-to-gain-a-better-understanding-of-them/</guid><description>For marketers aiming to cultivate customer relationships, providing a consistent and tailored experience is crucial. In anticipation of ad:tech Tokyo, Vizury, a digital CRM company, has presented insights into developing a comprehensive cross-device targeting strategy.
Understanding a user completely requires gathering data from various touchpoints such as desktop browsers, mobile websites, and apps. Vizury emphasizes that a successful cross-device strategy hinges on accurately identifying users across different devices. This allows marketers to track the customer journey from initial product view to the final purchase.</description></item><item><title>Jin Jiang International Hotels and Hanwha Hotels &amp; Resorts have officially merged their loyalty programs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</guid><description>Jin Jiang International Hotels from China and Hanwha Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts from Korea have joined their loyalty programs.
Starting September 1st, members of Jin Jiang&amp;rsquo;s J-Club and Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s THE PLUS will share membership benefits. This includes perks like discounts on rooms, food, and beverages, as well as late check-outs and room upgrades at both hotel groups. J-Club&amp;rsquo;s over 14 million members will also have access to Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s resorts and golf courses across Korea.</description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading.</description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever.</description></item><item><title>Criteo provides three suggestions for increasing sales conversions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 23:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance display advertising, offers advice based on its collaborations within the travel industry on converting leads into customers. This guidance is relevant across all sectors.
Tip #1: Strategically Time Your User Acquisition
Travel app downloads peak during summer (June-September), providing a window before peak season to engage a larger active user base*. Capitalize on your customers&amp;rsquo; planning and buying cycles by aligning download promotions for optimal new customer acquisition, Criteo recommends.</description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering.</description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features.</description></item><item><title>Companies that experience data breaches in the Asia Pacific region are unlikely to be forgiven</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 02:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</guid><description>New research from SafeNet reveals that data breaches significantly influence customer trust. The global study, including participants from Japan and Australia, found that 65% wouldn&amp;rsquo;t patronize a business that experienced a financial data breach, compromising credit card details, bank accounts, or login credentials.
SafeNet&amp;rsquo;s Q2 Breach Level Index reported 237 data breaches from April to June 2014, exposing over 175 million records globally. These findings highlight the impact of data breaches on customer loyalty and revenue.</description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question.</description></item><item><title>A Singapore retailer utilizes Qlik and Deloitte Digital solution to monitor customer narratives over time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</guid><description>Inverted Edge, a Singapore-based online retailer, is enhancing the customer experience at its Scotts Square location. Using technology from Qlik, a visual analytics company, and design by Deloitte Digital, the store provides a unique and interactive digital shopping experience.
Source: Inverted Edge website.
In addition to its selection of high-quality, modern luxury clothing, the store features a dynamic display of customer photos and stories from social media. This constantly updated feed showcases how customers style their purchases and shares their experiences.</description></item><item><title>In 2024, 80% of service professionals in Singapore anticipate that customer service will play a larger role in generating revenue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</guid><description>A recent Salesforce report highlights the growing expectation for customer service to become a significant revenue driver in 2024. The report suggests that AI-powered personalized customer experiences empower service teams to capitalize on upselling, cross-selling, and customer retention to boost revenue.
This new &amp;ldquo;State of Service&amp;rdquo; report is based on insights from over 5,500 service professionals globally, including 100 from Singapore. It examines current trends, challenges, and strategies shaping the customer service landscape, emphasizing how service teams utilize AI and data to enhance revenue, efficiency, and customer satisfaction amidst rising customer expectations.</description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is dedicated to improving its services and is now providing Better Thursdays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 03:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. The new logo at Singtel headquarters in Singapore.
Singtel recently introduced a refreshed brand identity, the first update in 16 years, with the tagline &amp;ldquo;Let’s make everyday better&amp;rdquo;. This signifies a new chapter in Singtel’s evolution beyond traditional telecommunications, expanding into multimedia and ICT services.
Chua Sock Koong, Singtel Group CEO, stated: “Singtel is a familiar name for many generations in Singapore. We are seen as a dependable and trusted brand at the forefront of technology.</description></item><item><title>The key to e-commerce success according to Akamai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</guid><description>Akamai, a content delivery network (CDN) provider, emphasizes the importance of speed in e-commerce, stating that slow loading times can lead to customer loss. They suggest two key ways online retailers can improve their businesses: by understanding modern customer behavior and by prioritizing speed, intelligence, and security in their online operations.
Mobile shopping is a growing trend. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s data shows that mobile and tablet shoppers make purchases 20% more often and spend US$500 more than desktop users in the same timeframe, highlighting the need for strong mobile optimization.</description></item></channel></rss>