<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ICCPR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iccpr/</link><description>Recent content in ICCPR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iccpr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Evaluation of the updated EU Council Guidelines on Freedom of Expression in both digital and physical spaces.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods from the University of Essex, and co-author of Steiner and Woods, EU Law, discusses new EU guidelines on freedom of expression.
The European Union Council recently established guidelines for freedom of expression. These guidelines, falling under the Foreign Affairs Council, are designed for application within the framework of the Union’s Common Foreign and Security Policy, similar to previous guidelines addressing issues like torture, capital punishment, and human rights advocates.</description></item><item><title>A Story of Two Institutions: Regulation of Hate Speech in Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</guid><description>Clotilde Pégorier, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The regulation of hate speech has recently resurfaced as a crucial legal and political topic in Europe. While the complexity of this issue and the varying views on balancing legislation with rights protection are well-known, the contrasting approaches of the EU and the Council of Europe, two closely linked entities, is notable. This difference raises questions about its underlying reasons and broader legislative ramifications in Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>