<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modem Banks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/modem-banks/</link><description>Recent content in Modem Banks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:16:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/modem-banks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ISDN's Primary Rate Interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</guid><description>The Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) is a digital telephone standard that provided widespread voice and data services before Enterprise VoIP and MPLS networks. Notably, ISDN&amp;rsquo;s Primary Rate Interface remains in high demand due to its seamless integration with existing telephone trunk lines, which are nearly ubiquitous.
The development of ISDN was driven by the increasing use of modems on analog telephone lines for long-distance data transmission. Analog telephone networks, designed for limited voice bandwidth, only allowed for data speeds up to 56 Kbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is a PRI Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</guid><description>Businesses frequently use PRI lines to obtain multiple phone lines. But what exactly are PRI lines, and what choices are there?
PRI is a component of ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network), a telecommunications standard. Its goal was to replace analog phone lines with digital ones for both residential and commercial customers. When ISDN was first introduced, dial-up connections using 56 Kbps modems were the norm for internet connectivity. Many of these modems only achieved speeds of 30 to 40 Kbps due to phone line limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>