<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hosted Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Hosted Communications on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:49:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Virtual Office Hosted Telecommunications at Half Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</guid><description>Upgrading your business phone system can be pricey, but hosted telecommunications, like Packet8&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Office, offers a more affordable solution. For a limited time, they&amp;rsquo;re offering a 50% discount, making it even more budget-friendly.
Instead of buying and managing your own phone system, hosted telecommunications lets a specialized company handle the equipment and services. You simply plug in your phones wherever you need them. Packet8&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Office utilizes an internet-based PBX system, eliminating the need for on-site equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>