<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>5G Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5g-wireless/</link><description>Recent content in 5G Wireless on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:13:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5g-wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit WiFi For Video Streaming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</guid><description>WiFi has become the standard wireless connection due to its widespread availability, outpacing technologies like Bluetooth and WiMax. While cellular data is useful in the absence of WiFi, its limited bandwidth and potential for overage charges make it a secondary choice. In fact, data shows that most tablet users don&amp;rsquo;t even utilize their device&amp;rsquo;s cellular capabilities. WiFi&amp;rsquo;s strength is evident in its ability to not only replace cellular broadband but also wired connections.</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs.</description></item></channel></rss>