<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Verizon Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/verizon-wireless/</link><description>Recent content in Verizon Wireless on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 01:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/verizon-wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Sweet Touch of LG Chocolate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sweet-touch-of-lg-chocolate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 01:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sweet-touch-of-lg-chocolate/</guid><description>The LG Chocolate Touch phone is a must-have, offering a delightful blend of style and functionality.
Verizon has a hit with the LG Chocolate Touch, a phone that combines sleek design with powerful multimedia features.
True to its name, the Chocolate Touch features a 3-inch touchscreen display with a sharp resolution of 400x240 pixels. It also boasts a 3.2-megapixel camera equipped with intelligent shot, panorama, facial makeover, and more. The camera captures stunning photos suitable for printing or instant sharing online and through multimedia messages.</description></item><item><title>RAZR Reincarnation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/razr-reincarnation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 08:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/razr-reincarnation/</guid><description>The original Motorola RAZR was a groundbreaking phone that redefined the industry, much like the iPhone did in its own time. Unlike the bulky phones available then, the RAZR stood out with its incredibly slim half-inch profile, all encased in a revolutionary aircraft-grade aluminum body.
The new RAZR takes this legacy further with even more advanced technology and a thinner 0.3-inch (7.1 mm) design. The iconic aluminum case is replaced by laser-cut KEVLAR with Corning Gorilla Glass for screen protection and a splash-guard coating for water resistance.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday Cell Phone Deals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</guid><description>The best deals on cell phones can be found online, especially during sales like Cyber Monday. These limited-time offers on free and discounted phones are valid until midnight today, Monday.
For a limited time, get a free BlackBerry Bold 9700 for AT&amp;amp;T after an instant online discount. This offer includes a bonus of free activation for up to five lines, making it perfect for family plans.
Prefer a different BlackBerry? The BlackBerry Curve in Titanium or silver is also available.</description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>The BlackBerry Storm Just Blew In at a Lower Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:51:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on getting a BlackBerry Storm in stores. You can buy one online from Cell Phone Plans Finder with free shipping.
Although I can&amp;rsquo;t disclose the price here, you can easily find it on the cellphone special offers page. You can then order the phone with your preferred Verizon Wireless service package, all delivered directly to you without shipping fees.
The BlackBerry Storm 9530 Black, the first BlackBerry with a touch keyboard, offers a unique experience for those accustomed to physical keys.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry 8830 is World Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</guid><description>Verizon Wireless has engineered a BlackBerry that functions domestically and internationally. This is notable because Verizon uses the CDMA network in the US, while the rest of the world primarily uses GSM.
Previously, this difference prevented Verizon phones from roaming internationally. To solve this, Verizon created a device with both CDMA and GSM capabilities. In the US, the CDMA component accesses the 800 and 1900 MHz bands, including EV-DO broadband. Outside the US, the GSM component accesses the 900 and 1800 MHz bands, including GPRS broadband.</description></item><item><title>LG enV Envy Touch Phone Messaging Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</guid><description>Do you find yourself desiring a modern touchscreen phone but also require a physical QWERTY keyboard? The new LG enV Touch eliminates this dilemma by offering both!
When closed, the &amp;ldquo;enV Touch&amp;rdquo; resembles a typical touchscreen smartphone. The exterior features a 3-inch, 800x480 pixel color TFT touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable shortcuts. However, a hidden surprise awaits inside: a second 3-inch, 800x400 pixel color display. This internal screen, paired with a spacious QWERTY keyboard, prioritizes efficient typing over touch input.</description></item><item><title>DROID is the Woid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</guid><description>Motorola and Verizon have partnered to challenge the dominant Apple iPhone with their highly anticipated DROID phone. Powered by the Google Android 2.0 operating system, the DROID promises exceptional functionality. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore its features.
A key distinction between the iPhone and most other smartphones, aside from the BlackBerry Storm, is the inclusion of a physical keyboard. For those accustomed to texting on physical keys, transitioning to a touchscreen keyboard can be challenging.</description></item><item><title>The Incredible DROID INCREDIBLE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-incredible-droid-incredible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 07:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-incredible-droid-incredible/</guid><description>Android phones are constantly improving, aiming to surpass the leading Apple iPhone. The newest contender in the Google versus Apple battle is the impressive DROID INCREDIBLE.
This HTC phone, available through Verizon Wireless, runs on the Android 2.1 operating system and offers customization with numerous apps and widgets from the Android marketplace. Its internal features are equally remarkable.
One standout feature is the 8-megapixel digital camera and camcorder, with resolution comparable to standalone digital cameras.</description></item><item><title>Backing Down In The Face of Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</guid><description>At the end of 2011, major companies like GoDaddy and Verizon Wireless faced significant public backlash that caused them to reverse recently announced decisions. GoDaddy quickly backpedaled on their support for SOPA after online outrage, while Verizon abandoned their plan to charge a $2 payment fee due to public outcry and potential FCC involvement. These incidents, while seemingly isolated, point to a larger pattern found in other events from the past year.</description></item><item><title>An Android Phone to Devour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</guid><description>Interested in getting a Google Android smartphone? The Motorola DEVOUR Silver might be the one for you. This Android 1.6 smartphone features a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and a 3.1-inch touchscreen, all within a sleek silver design.
The DEVOUR uses MOTOBLUR, a service that seamlessly syncs your messages, status updates, and contacts directly to your customizable home screens. This eliminates the need to log in or open individual apps, giving you instant access to your information.</description></item><item><title>Going Rogue But Not Rouge With Samsung</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a go-getter in need of a powerful cell phone that won&amp;rsquo;t let you down, the Samsung Rogue U960 Black for Verizon Wireless is a top contender among smartphones.
Does your current phone offer easy access to social media apps like Facebook and MySpace? How about web browsing, YouTube videos, and photo editing on a bright screen, even in sunlight? Can you stream music wirelessly, get directions, or message easily with a physical QWERTY keyboard?</description></item><item><title>Your Ally In The Android vs iPhone Battle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 20:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s initial Android offering, the LG Ally for Verizon Wireless, is a remarkable device. It boasts a range of features and access to a vast library of apps on the Android Market.
If you prioritize texting and email, you&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the tactile feedback of real keys. The LG Ally features a 3.2-inch touchscreen and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with well-sized keys. With five customizable home screens, you can personalize it with numerous Android apps.</description></item><item><title>Media Flos to Mobile TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 12:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</guid><description>Television is everywhere. While it started with over-the-air broadcasts, it quickly spread to cable, satellite, and the internet through platforms like YouTube and IPTV. Now, mobile devices like cell phones are the new frontier for watching TV on the go.
Early mobile video relied on downloadable clips using cellular broadband networks like EV-DO. However, these networks struggle with bandwidth limitations, making it difficult to deliver high-quality real-time video without overloading the system.</description></item></channel></rss>