<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Taxi on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/taxi/</link><description>Recent content in Taxi on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/taxi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the ability to hail a cab using Hailo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</guid><description>Hailo, a highly-rated taxi app boasting more five-star reviews than any other similar service, launched in Singapore on October 29th. With a global network of over 60,000 drivers and a strong user base exceeding 1.4 million, Hailo reports a ride request every two seconds somewhere in the world.
Source: Hailo. From left: Benny Lim, Managing Director, SMRT Road Holdings; Ron Zeghibe, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Executive Chairman, Hailo Global, and Yu Hsiang Wong, General Manager, Hailo Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi cab booking app is now available in Kuala Lumpur and will soon be expanding to more countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a cab booking app, has expanded its reach to Malaysia and will be pre-installed on Celkon phones in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal.
Developed by India-based On Time Technologies, TaxiPixi launched in Malaysia this week. Celkon, a mobile phone manufacturer, will pre-install the app on its devices in several countries. Pradeep Yerraguntla, Celkon&amp;rsquo;s Head of Digital, stated that Celkon will promote the app through its app store and website, targeting consumers in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotels.com provides exclusive information on transportation options to and from the airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</guid><description>Hotels.com, a website for booking accommodations online, has put together an insider&amp;rsquo;s guide on the top transportation choices from 29 major airports globally. This guide, called the Hotels.com Airport Transportation Insider, compares taxis, private cars, and public transportation in popular international and domestic destinations using data from the recent Hotel Price Index™. Although it&amp;rsquo;s geared towards US travelers, the infographic provides helpful information for cities like Bangkok, Beijing, Singapore, and Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Makani numbers in Dubai assist taxi drivers in locating their customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</guid><description>Source: RTA. Dubai taxis are now connected to the city through the Makani system.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) Public Transport Agency has successfully connected 4,500 taxis operated by franchise companies to the Dubai Municipality&amp;rsquo;s Makani System. This system utilizes unique coordinates, known as Makani numbers, for precise building location.
Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems at RTA&amp;rsquo;s Public Transport Agency, highlighted the significant role of the Makani System...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can book Mwasalat taxis without using the mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Mwasalat. Taxi Butler devices will offer taxi booking
services.
Mwasalat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Taxi Butlers,&amp;rdquo; kiosks that streamline taxi bookings. This initiative is part of the public transportation company&amp;rsquo;s ongoing plan to modernize Oman&amp;rsquo;s taxi services.
Taxi Butlers eliminate the hassle of individual driver contact by allowing users to pre-book taxis. The kiosks offer the convenience of booking multiple taxis and provide passengers with real-time updates on arrival times, driver information, and vehicle arrival alerts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA has entered into a partnership with Careem for ride-hailing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</guid><description>Source: RTA. HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of RTA and Mudassir Sheikha, Founder and Managing Director of Careem, signed the agreement on behalf of the two respective entities. RTA executives attending the signing included Mohammed Obaid Al Mulla, Member of Board of Executive Directors, Abdullah Yousef Al Ali, CEO of Public Transport Agency, and Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems. Bassel Al Nahlaoui, VP of Business Development &amp;amp; Government Relations attended on behalf of Careem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>