<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Competition Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competition-law/</link><description>Recent content in Competition Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competition-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Don't waste a valuable opportunity: the importance and methods of reforming the governance of European football following the collapse of the 'SuperLeague'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 05:07:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</guid><description>Professor Stephen Weatherill, Faculty of Law and Somerville College, University of Oxford, analyzes the attempted formation of a European SuperLeague and what it reveals about the weaknesses in European football governance and legal frameworks. He argues that while the SuperLeague ultimately failed, the desire for such a league persists and requires proactive legal and structural reforms to safeguard the European model of sport.
A Persistent Threat
The proposed SuperLeague, driven by wealthy and commercially successful clubs, posed a significant challenge to UEFA, the governing body of European football...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Prime Minister hinting at a potential shift in Brexit stance with his unexpected mention of competition policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</guid><description>Andreas Stephan, Professor of Competition Law &amp;amp; Head of UEA Law School, University of East Anglia*
In a speech delivered on March 2, 2018, Prime Minister Theresa May aimed to clarify the UK&amp;rsquo;s Brexit objectives. She proposed aligning UK State Aid and Competition rules with those of the EU, while allowing UK courts to consider European Court of Justice (ECJ) judgments. However, she emphasized that the ECJ would not have jurisdiction over the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finally achieving greater coherence for the Ne Bis in Idem Principle: Analysis of the Bpost Judgment (C-117/20)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-achieving-greater-coherence-for-the-ne-bis-in-idem-principle-analysis-of-the-bpost-judgment-c-117-20/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 01:55:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-achieving-greater-coherence-for-the-ne-bis-in-idem-principle-analysis-of-the-bpost-judgment-c-117-20/</guid><description>Towards Greater Coherence on Ne Bis in Idem: The bpost Case Victor Davio and Ilaria Gambardella*
*Victor is a PhD Researcher at the Institute for European Law, KU Leuven and Assistant in Constitutional Law at University Saint-Louis Brussels and Ilaria is Teaching Assistant and Research Associate at the Institute for European Law, KU Leuven. They are part of the RESHUFFLE research project hosted by KU Leuven under the direction of Prof...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-achieving-greater-coherence-for-the-ne-bis-in-idem-principle-analysis-of-the-bpost-judgment-c-117-20/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-achieving-greater-coherence-for-the-ne-bis-in-idem-principle-analysis-of-the-bpost-judgment-c-117-20/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is a Title Sufficient to Override Constitutional Rules and Fundamental Rule-of-Law Principles? A Paper on Enforcement Priorities for Article 102 TFEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</guid><description>Konstantinos Sidiropoulos
DPhil Candidate at University of Oxford – Prof Steve Weatherill
Foundation for Education and European culture scholar
Introduction
The best way to regulate abuse of dominance in the EU has been a subject of much discussion. In the early 2000s, aiming to address criticisms of its approach to unilateral conduct control, the European Commission started reviewing the relevant law, including how it was being applied (see the EAGCP Report and the Discussion Paper)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maxima Latvija: Non-compete clauses in commercial lease agreements are considered competition restrictions by their nature.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxima-latvija-non-compete-clauses-in-commercial-lease-agreements-are-considered-competition-restrictions-by-their-nature/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxima-latvija-non-compete-clauses-in-commercial-lease-agreements-are-considered-competition-restrictions-by-their-nature/</guid><description>Michele Giannino (Italian qualified lawyer: LL.M. Leicester, Ph.D London)
A recent judgment from the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) concerning the Maxima Latvija case determined that commercial lease agreements containing clauses granting tenants the right to approve leases with third parties are not inherently anti-competitive. This means a full analysis of the agreements&amp;rsquo; economic effects is required to ascertain if they violate competition laws. The CJEU outlined the criteria for evaluating the agreements&amp;rsquo; competition impact...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxima-latvija-non-compete-clauses-in-commercial-lease-agreements-are-considered-competition-restrictions-by-their-nature/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxima-latvija-non-compete-clauses-in-commercial-lease-agreements-are-considered-competition-restrictions-by-their-nature/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing Health and Trade: The Scotch Whisky Association ruling on finding the right equilibrium.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School The Court of Justice has issued its judgment regarding the legality of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s minimum alcohol pricing (MUP) measure in Case C-333/14. Both the Scottish Government and the Scotch Whisky Association (SWA), which initiated the legal challenge, have expressed satisfaction with the ruling, although the SWA might be more content as the case now returns to Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Inner House of the Court of Session, which had referred it to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where are EU Consumers' Actions for Damages Headed?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/</guid><description>By Sonsoles Prieto, EU competition law practitioner, London*
EU Member States are nearing the deadline to implement the EU Damages Directive. This directive aims to empower consumers and small businesses to seek damages from parties who violate competition law.
Although the need for such a directive was questioned in the past, the current perspective has significantly shifted. Nevertheless, adapting to this new approach presents ongoing challenges.
Background
Adopted in December 2014, the Directive mandates that all EU and EEA member states ensure individuals and entities impacted by competition law violations can claim and receive full compensation for their losses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How do the Court's rulings on December 21, 2023 impact UEFA's position as a 'gatekeeper' in the Football Revolution?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</guid><description>Steve Weatherill, Somerville College and Faculty of Law, University of Oxford
Photo credit: Werner100359, via Wikimedia Commons
Summary
Recent Court of Justice rulings on December 21, 2023, determined that practices requiring prior approval for new sporting competitions created by external entities clash with EU law. This decision primarily stemmed from the lack of clear, unbiased, and transparent criteria and procedures. While governing bodies, particularly in football, are obligated to adjust their practices, the extent of their authority as gatekeepers remains unclear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Attorney General considers the intersection of public health, trade, and competition in setting minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School Background to the Opinion Advocate General (AG) Bot provided his opinion on September 3rd, 2015, regarding Case C-333/14, which involved the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to establish a minimum price per unit (£0.50) on alcohol sales. This Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) faced legal challenges from the Scotch Whisky Association, leading to the case reaching the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The CJEU was asked to determine whether the MUP aligned with the single Common Market Organisation (CMO) and the free movement principles of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>