<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Broadband on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both.</description></item><item><title>Cricket Offers Advantages For Urban Dwellers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</guid><description>Are you constantly on your cell phone, talking or texting? Do you live in or around a city and use the internet frequently outside your home or work? If so, Cricket Wireless has cellular service deals that might be perfect for you.
Cricket Wireless operates differently than traditional cell phone providers. First, there are no contracts. Second, most services are unlimited with one exception. Plans range from $30 to $60 per month, all offering unlimited service.</description></item><item><title>HP has launched a new mobile broadband service called DataPass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</guid><description>HP has introduced new technology designed for business travelers in the Asia Pacific region called HP DataPass.
&amp;ldquo;In today&amp;rsquo;s constantly connected, fast-moving, and virtual business world, new opportunities are emerging for businesses and individuals,&amp;rdquo; said Nick Lazaridis, Senior VP, Printing and Personal Systems, and Managing Director of HP Asia Pacific and Japan. &amp;ldquo;At HP, our focus is on developing innovations that provide the best possible customer experience while creating opportunities for our customers to transition to the New Style of IT.</description></item></channel></rss>