<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Goodwood Park on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/goodwood-park/</link><description>Recent content in Goodwood Park on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/goodwood-park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park introduces new fruit-infused mooncake flavors to its 2017 lineup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 21:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</guid><description>This mid-autumn, Goodwood Park Hotel is excited to present a selection of new and unique snowskin mooncake flavors. Among the new offerings is the blush pink prickly pear with bergamot snowskin mooncake. This confection features the sweet and succulent fruit of a cactus, complemented by a citrusy bergamot flavor and the crunch of diced pears.
Goodwood Park Hotel will also be bringing back popular snowskin favorites. These include premium durian and tropical fruit varieties alongside traditional baked mooncakes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an unexpected Christmas at Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel in Singapore has designed a Christmas menu featuring new versions of classic dishes, playful food presentations, and delightful surprises. These festive meals and unique takeaway options aim to make holiday celebrations even more memorable.
This year&amp;rsquo;s new gourmet takeaway options center around turkey with unique Asian flavors for savory dishes and chocolate-focused sweet treats.
Source: Goodwood Park Hotel. The 12 Treasures turkey is available for takeaways.
12 Treasures Turkey | S$268, serves eight to 10 people - New for 2017..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>