<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1980ODBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1980odbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 1980ODBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1980odbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Brand New Hood Fatally Damaged Due to Bent Hood Hinges! - Straightening Hinges Out and Installation of Another Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) for a Florida-based client and installed a new dust cover purchased from beoparts-shop in Denmark. These dust covers are remarkable replicas, made with the same die-cast process as the originals, resulting in a seamless finish.
However, a problem arose with this particular dust cover. When closing it, there was slight friction on the hinge approximately halfway through its movement. While I initially dismissed it as an insignificant tolerance issue common in older manufacturing, the issue escalated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a Brand New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</guid><description>Before returning the recently restored Beogram 4002 (5513) to its owner, one final detail needed attention: the original dust cover showed early signs of cracking around the hinges.
The owner opted for a brand new replacement dust cover from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These reproduction dust covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, resulting in a seamless look, unlike previous versions made by fusing laser-cut panels. The result is indistinguishable from the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): A New Arrival from Florida - First Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-florida-first-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 01:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-florida-first-assessment/</guid><description>A local customer brought me a Beogram 4002 (5513) for restoration last year, opting for the safety of personal delivery. The unit is in decent condition, as seen upon arrival.
[Image]
The dust cover is nearly flawless, with one common hinge crack just starting to form.
[Image]
This makes it a perfect candidate for Beolover hinge patches to reinforce the area, especially since the crack hasn&amp;rsquo;t fully developed. Of course, new hoods are an option now as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Complete Functional Restoration and a Spin with the Cal Tjader Quartet!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The restoration began with addressing the motor, a common procedure for these models. After removing and disassembling the motor, the Oilite bearings were submerged in oil and placed under a vacuum for several days to replenish lubrication.
Next, the carriage and arm mechanisms were disassembled, cleaned, and re-lubricated. This included taking apart and servicing the damper. The main PCB was removed, and both power transistors were replaced.</description></item></channel></rss>