<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Seoul on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/seoul/</link><description>Recent content in Seoul on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/seoul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>The Business Plan package at The Shilla Seoul includes access to The Executive Lounge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. The Executive Lounge.
Through June 30, 2019, The Shilla Seoul is offering its Business Plan package, which gives guests the opportunity to experience The Executive Lounge.
Guests selecting the Executive Business Deluxe option receive exclusive access to The Executive Lounge, complimentary breakfast at The Parkview, and access to both the gym and indoor swimming pool.
The Executive Lounge at The Shilla Seoul, situated on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s top floor, is designed as a luxurious penthouse.</description></item><item><title>Le Meridien Seoul combines traditional Korean elements with French sophistication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 07:40:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</guid><description>Source: Le Meridien, Seoul website. Hub lobby.
The Le Meridien, Seoul, the first of its brand in Korea, introduces the renowned London-based David Collins Studio to the country. Conveniently located in the upscale Gangnam district, the hotel is a short walk from the Sinnonhyeon and Gangnam subway stations and easily accessible from both Gimpo (GMP) and Incheon (ICN) International Airports.
Tasked with designing the hotel&amp;rsquo;s public spaces and rooms, the studio has crafted a sophisticated blend of Parisian elegance with mid-century modern influences.</description></item><item><title>The Urban Island promotion has been introduced by The Shilla Seoul</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</guid><description>With the arrival of summer, The Shilla Seoul presents Urban Island, a luxurious outdoor escape for guests. This all-inclusive retreat offers relaxation, a connection with nature, and delightful poolside service.
Reopened for the season, Urban Island welcomes guests to heated outdoor pools, a jacuzzi, and a rooftop garden against a scenic backdrop of Namsan Mountain and the Seoul skyline. Intimate cabanas nestled among lush greenery provide secluded havens.
The Urban Days room rate, available until June 30, 2019, starts from KRW 320,000 per night, excluding taxes and service charges, based on double occupancy.</description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon, the Korean fine-dining restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, has been awarded three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. Nine delicacies at La Yeon.
During the first-ever Michelin Guide Seoul launch in 2017, held at The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Dynasty Hall, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s traditional Korean fine-dining establishment, La Yeon, was granted a coveted three-star Michelin rating. Recognized for its authentic flavors, exceptional service, inviting atmosphere, and well-paired drinks, La Yeon stands as the sole Seoul restaurant within a hospitality group to achieve this three-star distinction.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy delicious autumn treats at The Shilla Seoul and The Shilla Jeju</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-delicious-autumn-treats-at-the-shilla-seoul-and-the-shilla-jeju/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 19:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-delicious-autumn-treats-at-the-shilla-seoul-and-the-shilla-jeju/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul.
Both the Shilla Seoul and Shilla Jeju hotels are celebrating autumn with a variety of special promotions and activities.
The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s upscale Korean restaurant, La Yeon, will offer a special autumn menu featuring seasonal ingredients like pine nuts, sweet potatoes, and seafood in keeping with traditional culinary practices. La Yeon made its debut on the list of Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants in 2015 at position 38 and received the coveted One To Watch award.</description></item></channel></rss>