<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get Ready For The Recovery With Bandwidth on Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>The economy is recovering, benefiting some businesses while others struggle. Maintaining earnings through cost-cutting instead of increased sales won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable. When the economy fully recovers, rapid adaptation will be crucial, but increased expenses are only justifiable with increased revenue. Bandwidth on demand offers a solution.
Bandwidth on demand allows businesses to access and pay for only the bandwidth they currently need, scaling usage up or down as required. This differs from the traditional approach of installing full capacity in advance, which poses financial risks if projected growth doesn&amp;rsquo;t materialize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes a Great MAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</guid><description>Access to Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs), previously limited to large corporations, is now feasible for small and medium-sized businesses. If your company requires communication between multiple locations within a city, a metro network might be beneficial.
Metro Ethernet is the modern solution for data connections in major cities and surrounding areas. There are two main types: E-Line and E-LAN. E-Line provides a direct Ethernet connection between two points, such as a business and its data center, warehouse, factory, or branch office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheaper DS3 Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</guid><description>Your business needs more bandwidth, but the price of a DS3 connection might seem daunting. While upgrading from a T1 line to a DS3 might have seemed expensive in the past, prices have gone down. Even with the current economic climate, a DS3 connection could now be within your budget.
DS3, or Data Service level 3, is a digital telecommunications standard initially designed for telephone systems. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the T-Carrier system and works seamlessly with SONET fiber optic networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Build Wide Area Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:05:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Imagine offering your clients network installations that stretch across the city or even the entire country! You might think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible, but it&amp;rsquo;s more achievable than you think.
You won&amp;rsquo;t need massive spools of wire or heavy equipment. Everything is taken care of, allowing you to focus on expanding your business and profits.
This is possible due to two key advancements: the rise of Metro and Carrier Ethernet services from competitive carriers and a business model that lets you integrate these Ethernet WAN services into your network designs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Fiber Diet for Business Not Expensive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</guid><description>With business picking up, many companies are hitting a wall – their internet connections can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the increased data flow. The solution? A high-fiber diet for their network.
Fiber optic cables are incredibly efficient. A single strand can handle massive amounts of voice, data, and video simultaneously, far exceeding the needs of most businesses. This capacity can be further multiplied by splitting the light into different wavelengths, each carrying gigabits per second...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contract Expiration Means Opportunity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</guid><description>Business telecom services often come with fixed-price contracts lasting 1 to 3 years, providing price stability but limited cost-saving opportunities. However, the fear of potential price increases upon contract renewal is often overstated. In many cases, businesses can find better deals by exploring alternative providers.
The misconception about limited options arises from a perceived lack of competition. While you may have negotiated what seemed like the best price at the time, there are often numerous competitive service providers not listed in traditional directories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is 1 Tbps The Next Optical Network Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</guid><description>While everyday users are getting used to 100 Mbps speeds, network providers are already looking ahead to Terabit per second speeds, debating whether 400 Gbps or 1 Tbps will be the next standard.
This push for higher speeds is a natural progression, similar to the advancement from Kbps to Mbps and Gbps. Just like previous upgrades, the proposed standards represent a tenfold increase.
This speed increase mirrors Moore&amp;rsquo;s Law, which predicted the doubling of transistors on integrated circuits yearly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Communications Nears Tbps National Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 01:23:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</guid><description>Any lingering doubts about the supposed overabundance of bandwidth in the late &amp;rsquo;90s telecom boom should be dispelled by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; recent announcement. Despite upgrading their national backbone just last year, XO is increasing its capacity again. This upgrade will boost major coast-to-coast network routes from 400 Gbps to a staggering 800 Gbps, putting them within reach of terabit-per-second speeds.
This massive capacity increase is driven by a fivefold surge in demand for high-capacity inter-city network services over the past year, according to XO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Offers Lower Cost Carrier Grade Fiber Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</guid><description>Large bandwidth consumers, including major corporations, healthcare systems, independent phone companies, video production companies, and internet service providers, now have an affordable alternative for obtaining the reliable bandwidth they require. This shift is thanks to Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet provides metropolitan and long-distance bandwidth services using Ethernet technology rather than conventional telephone company methods. This service is often called Metro Ethernet within a single metropolitan area. These services deliver professional-grade bandwidth solutions characterized by high reliability and dedicated bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Covad Lets T1 Lines Go Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 03:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</guid><description>While T1 lines are currently the standard for dedicated internet and business phone service for small and medium businesses, their future might be wireless. Similar to how wireless technology changed phone service, it is now impacting broadband data delivery.
Covad, a national provider of T1 and related services, is at the forefront of this change. While they offer traditional wired T1 service in most areas, they&amp;rsquo;ve deployed &amp;ldquo;T1-class wireless broadband&amp;rdquo; in some major cities using pre-WiMAX technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Thrives In The 21st Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</guid><description>For over a century, copper wire has been the backbone of telecommunications, connecting homes and businesses. While fiber optic technology has advanced, copper remains dominant, even in the 21st century.
Despite the rise of fiber optics, copper persists due to its widespread availability and established infrastructure. Connecting to existing copper is often more cost-effective than installing new fiber optic lines.
While copper-based systems were designed for analog signals, they can still handle today’s high-speed digital demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Get To The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing and storage are becoming increasingly popular, and many believe they will soon be the standard for computer use. There are many benefits to using the cloud, such as not needing to buy or maintain software, having data automatically backed up, accessing tools and data from anywhere on any device, and being able to use smaller, more portable computers, like netbooks, cellphones, and tablets. However, one concern remains: reliable access to the cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth is Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Business bandwidth solutions are significantly more expensive than residential options like DSL or Cable. While this is partly due to their guaranteed reliability and dedicated lines, another factor is the complex infrastructure involved. Providing business-grade services often requires collaboration between a long-haul carrier and the local phone company for the final connection.
Despite recent price drops in dedicated T1 connections, high-bandwidth services remain costly, potentially hindering smaller companies needing to transmit large amounts of data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Offers Synchronous Service Transport For Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>Need to move massive amounts of data quickly and reliably? Within a building or campus, fiber optic cables provide sufficient speed and capacity. However, for longer distances, you need robust carrier services. Quest&amp;rsquo;s Synchronous Service Transport (SST) offers a solution.
SST utilizes fiber optics and SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) to provide high-speed, point-to-point data transfer. SONET, a dependable carrier service based on Time Division Multiplexing (TDM), was initially designed for telephone companies and later adopted by large organizations requiring extensive bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Wavelengths to Serve You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</guid><description>When your network reaches its maximum capacity, you typically need to upgrade to a faster network with faster components. Upgrading your entire network infrastructure can be extremely expensive. However, with fiber optic networks, you can significantly increase bandwidth within the same cables using a technique called Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM).
WDM allows multiple light beams to transmit data simultaneously over a single fiber optic cable. Each beam operates on a different wavelength, increasing capacity proportionally to the number of beams...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul is Backing Things Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</guid><description>While it may seem like the world operates solely on wireless connections, especially if you rely on cell phones and mobile internet, this is only true for the link between your device and the nearest cell tower or access point. Beyond that point lies the backhaul, a crucial but often overlooked component that bridges the wireless and wired worlds. As wireless connections become faster, the limitations of traditional backhaul solutions are becoming increasingly apparent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aggressive Passive Optical Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 02:09:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</guid><description>Passive Optical Networking (PON) is becoming a budget-friendly way to bring fiber optic connections directly to homes and businesses. This technology is advancing so rapidly that new PON standards are being surpassed almost as quickly as they are established. For instance, Ericsson is currently showcasing 10 Gbps GPON. Will we soon see speeds of 100 Gbps or even terabits per second?
While it&amp;rsquo;s not happening overnight, bandwidth requirements are definitely increasing for both home and business wide area networks (WANs)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Real Estate Developers Need to Know About Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-real-estate-developers-need-to-know-about-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 23:03:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-real-estate-developers-need-to-know-about-ethernet/</guid><description>High-speed internet is becoming as essential as other utilities like electricity, water, and phone services. Businesses rely on it, and those working from home expect it. Developers of office spaces, industrial parks, and new housing divisions should incorporate broadband internet into their plans, rather than making it the responsibility of buyers or renters. Broadband access is not just a desirable feature, but a potential revenue source, and Ethernet is the best technology for the job...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-real-estate-developers-need-to-know-about-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-real-estate-developers-need-to-know-about-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Covad Ethernet Now Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>Prepare to be surprised! Covad is now offering Ethernet bandwidth at prices even lower than T1 solutions of comparable speeds. That&amp;rsquo;s right, the tide has turned, and Ethernet is now a more budget-friendly option.
While this is an initial launch in 12 markets across California, Michigan, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, and Texas, it could be a sign of a nationwide shift in telecommunication pricing. To see if your location qualifies, you can check Ethernet availability online...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</guid><description>Global telecommunication companies are updating their networks from circuit-based to packet-based systems. With the growth of internet-based networks, Ethernet WAN services have become more accessible and affordable. However, businesses often still rely on older technologies like T1, DS3, or SONET for connecting to these services and cloud networks.
While these older technologies are reliable and getting cheaper, using Ethernet for the initial connection, known as the &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; offers several benefits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantage of Dedicated Cloud Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</guid><description>Companies of all sizes are increasingly adopting cloud services due to their cost-effectiveness. However, the assumption that a basic internet connection is sufficient for accessing these services is proving to be inaccurate in many situations.
While the internet&amp;rsquo;s widespread availability and affordability make it appealing for WAN services, its security concerns led to the development of VPNs. These secure tunnels encrypt data, allowing remote workers and branch offices to connect securely to corporate networks and transfer sensitive information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of Bandwidth for Wide Area Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 23:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) connect your business to the outside world, encompassing private networks across various locations. These connections, often called &amp;ldquo;long haul circuits&amp;rdquo;, form the foundation of wide area networking.
Connecting your local area network (LAN) to a WAN usually involves a router and a specialized interface corresponding to the WAN circuit type.
A common WAN connection is a T1 line, terminating at a &amp;ldquo;smart jack&amp;rdquo; in your telecom closet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ciena Takes New Bandwidth Technologies On The Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</guid><description>Today, June 29th, those in Waltham, MA can experience cutting-edge carrier bandwidth technology firsthand. Visit the Ciena Innovation Lab to see live demonstrations of their latest optical, Ethernet, and software solutions. The lab will move to its next location in White Marsh, MD on July 15th.
What exactly is the Ciena Innovation Lab? It&amp;rsquo;s a mobile showcase housed in a semi-trailer, packed with the most recent advancements in telecom and networking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Better Than a T3 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 voice and data lines, once a reliable option for businesses, now offer insufficient speed (45 Mbps) for modern demands, which often exceed 100 Mbps. Businesses today require significantly faster connections, with some even seeking speeds beyond 10 Gbps. If you&amp;rsquo;re still using a T3 line, you might find better bandwidth options at a similar or lower cost.
What is a T3 Line?
Developed by Bell Labs, the T3 line was designed to carry numerous simultaneous phone conversations, a function it still serves in certain settings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telarus, the New Face of Telecom Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a massive transformation thanks to disruptive technology. Wireless technology is shaking up the century-old wireline business, VoIP is changing the landscape of the digital voice trunking business, competitive fiber optic carriers are challenging the dominance of established phone companies, and Ethernet and IP networks are blurring the lines between local and wide area networks.
Despite these technological advancements, the sales and marketing processes for business telecommunications services have remained largely unchanged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100, 1000, 10000 Mbps Internet Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As technology progresses, businesses require significantly faster internet speeds. Our Wide Area Networks (WANs) are now crucial for operations. Today, internet connections of 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps, and even 10,000 Mbps are standard and essential. Fortunately, pricing has decreased as speeds have increased, making these bandwidth levels attainable.
100 Mbps Fast Ethernet
100 Mbps is the current standard bandwidth, replacing the older 45 Mbps DS3 bandwidth. DS3, an upgrade from slower T1 lines, is part of the TDM telecom standard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs SONET Throw Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SONET and Carrier Ethernet, two contenders for the top spot in high-speed business bandwidth.
SONET, or Synchronous Optical NETwork, is a fiber optic transmission system using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). Primarily used by telephone companies to boost their digital trunk capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s known for its redundant data rings over fiber optic cables, which create an automatic failover mechanism in case of a network disruption. While perfect for carrier-grade digitized phone calls, SONET can also handle packetized data including voice, video, and standard T1 or T3 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic ISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</guid><description>Internet service used to rely on dial-up connections, but it has advanced significantly since then. Today, medium-sized businesses are now transitioning to fiber optic internet service providers, a technology already embraced by larger corporations.
Residential fiber optic internet, like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS, offers high speeds, with Google soon to introduce even faster Gigabit service. Business broadband connections, however, have already surpassed Gigabit speeds, with 10 Gbps becoming increasingly common. The technology is well-established, leaving businesses to determine their bandwidth needs and locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cure The Bulging T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</guid><description>Not too long ago, you got your first T1 line. It was impressive with its 1.5 Mbps speed for both uploading and downloading. The connection was reliable, and there was a guarantee for quick assistance if any issues arose. Though a bit pricey, it was worth it, and you believed it would last forever. However, lately, that once-speedy connection has slowed to a crawl. So, what now?
Many businesses are facing the issue of overloaded T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TW Telecom's Extensive Service Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</guid><description>tw telecom is a full-service communications provider with a privately owned, nationwide fiber optic network. They provide service in 75 major markets and over 8,800 commercial buildings. Their network spans more than 26,000 route miles and features a 10 Gbps IP backbone. They offer a wide array of services, from affordable T1 lines to high-speed Carrier Ethernet services ranging from 2 Mbps to 10 Gbps.
You might recognize the name tw telecom from its previous iterations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tired of Flaky Internet Connections?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</guid><description>Running a business is challenging when your tools are unreliable. You would think technology would make things easier, but it often has the opposite effect. As processes become more complex and interconnected, they seem to become less dependable. A simple cash transaction can turn into an e-commerce nightmare. Why can&amp;rsquo;t things just work flawlessly all the time?
While expecting perfection might be unrealistic, your business systems should function seamlessly most of the time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN to Complement Your LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your company&amp;rsquo;s Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at blazing speeds of 1 Gbps or more, making internal network operations seem almost instantaneous. However, accessing resources outside your physical location can feel painstakingly slow. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be convenient if your LAN could extend across cities or even to remote offices? You might be surprised to learn that this is a possibility.
Yes, The WAN is Ethernet Networks can be broadly categorized as either owned or leased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying Out of the Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 19:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</guid><description>While the use of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is widespread in information technology, understanding its complexities is crucial. The cloud often represents large, intricate networks that users may not fully comprehend.
Although many users are content with the cloud&amp;rsquo;s seemingly magical abilities, David G. Rusin, CEO of American Fiber Systems, argues against perceiving internet clouds as uniform entities. He emphasizes the differences in integrity, reliability, and delivery among cloud providers, highlighting the importance of scrutinizing these aspects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Audio Interview With Adam Edwards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</guid><description>Telarus, Inc. is considered a leading innovator in telecommunications marketing since the major telecom expansion of the 1990s. The company has transformed how businesses purchase services like T1, Ethernet, and other high-speed internet options.
I recently spoke with Adam Edwards, Telarus&amp;rsquo;s president, to understand the company&amp;rsquo;s success as a top master agency. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share an MP3 recording of our conversation so you can hear directly from Adam instead of reading a transcript...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet is Cheaper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</guid><description>You probably know that T1 and DS3 lines have become much cheaper in recent years. But for those who need bandwidth of 10 Mbps or more, there&amp;rsquo;s an even better deal: Ethernet.
While you might know Ethernet as a local area network protocol, it&amp;rsquo;s now a wide area network protocol too. This means your carrier can provide an Ethernet connection that plugs directly into your existing network router or switch. You might see it called Ethernet WAN, Metro Ethernet, Carrier Ethernet, or Ethernet Transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new network switches designed specifically for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Dell has improved its networking solutions designed for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs). Their new X-series smart managed switches and expanded N-series family provide cost-effective, enterprise-grade network control with user-friendly simplicity.
The Dell Networking X-Series includes web-managed 1 Gigabit Ethernet (GbE) and 10GbE switches with flexible configuration options. SMBs can benefit from advanced network management without specialized IT staff using step-by-step wizards and customizable dashboards. These features allow for quick and accurate configuration, calibration, and troubleshooting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick Way to Cut the Corporate Phone Bill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 03:33:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/</guid><description>As the cost of goods and fuel continues to rise, many businesses find themselves caught between escalating expenses and a limited ability to increase prices. The situation is changing so rapidly that overhauling or even reconsidering business strategies is challenging. The most practical solution for maintaining profits becomes straightforward cost reduction.
At this juncture, attention often turns to the phone bill. Are all those calls truly essential?
Reviewing telecommunications invoices is a wise practice, even when business operations are running smoothly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five Years Of The Explainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 21:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</guid><description>T1 Rex’s Business Telecom Explainer turned five this month, with more than 800 posts published since its 2004 launch. Our initial goal was to clarify complex telecommunications services and provide businesses with competitive options. Over time, we&amp;rsquo;ve broadened our scope to encompass a wide range of products, services, and topics relevant to our audience. As we approach our second decade, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the &amp;ldquo;aughts&amp;rdquo; and explore potential future trends.
This explainer blog, as the name suggests, was launched alongside T1Rex...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ethernet Next Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</guid><description>Feeling constrained by your internet speed? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While your business might be struggling with a slow T1 line, your competitors may have a secret weapon: a new, affordable broadband service called Carrier Ethernet.
This service, rapidly being deployed across the nation, is an extension of the familiar Ethernet standard used in local area networks (LANs). Instead of converting data to different protocols for external connections, businesses can now use Ethernet for seamless, high-speed access to the internet and connections with other facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LAN WAN Connection Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 18:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</guid><description>Local area networks (LANs) are standardized and consistent, making them easy to understand and work with. However, connecting to a wide area network (WAN) introduces a new set of telephone company standards that can be challenging for network professionals familiar with LAN technologies.
In the past, connecting to a WAN required specialized knowledge of complex technologies like DS channels and SONET multiplexing. This often involved significant effort to bridge the gap between LAN and WAN environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>