<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Labour Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/labour-law/</link><description>Recent content in Labour Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/labour-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK.</description></item><item><title>Brexit and Labour Standards during COVID-19: Will they Align or Separate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</guid><description>Jeff Kenner, Professor of European Law, University of Nottingham*
The COVID-19 pandemic has taken center stage, demanding an urgent worldwide response that is yet to materialize. In light of this global crisis, the issue of Brexit, particularly its self-serving nature and political maneuvering, has understandably faded from the minds of both policymakers and the public. However, despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s onset in mid-March 2020, which coincided with the start of negotiations for a new EU-UK partnership and led to widespread lockdowns across Europe, the UK government remains steadfast in its refusal to extend the post-Brexit transition period beyond the December 31, 2020, deadline established in the October 2019 EU-UK Withdrawal Agreement.</description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period.</description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones.</description></item></channel></rss>