<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platter Motor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/platter-motor/</link><description>Recent content in Platter Motor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/platter-motor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Floating Suspension, Reservoir Capacitor &amp; Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</guid><description>This project is nearing completion. This post details the remounting of the floating chassis within the cabinet, replacing the reservoir capacitor, and installing the refurbished platter motor.
Here are the parts needed for mounting the floating suspension system back into the cabinet.
The threaded pin&amp;rsquo;s longer section is positioned at the bottom. When attaching the wing-nut, ensure it sits at the very beginning of the thread. I personally position it to allow enough thread for securing the nut while keeping the nut&amp;rsquo;s outer edge aligned with the topmost thread.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reinstalling the Floating Chassis Components</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</guid><description>All the necessary restoration parts for the Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable are now available, marking the start of the reassembly process.
The reinstallation begins with securing the floating chassis, equipped with the tangential arm assembly, back into the Beogram 4002 cabinet. The process starts by fitting the Beolover replacement suspension lock bushings onto the floating chassis. Subsequently, the suspension locks are positioned within the cabinet base. The floating chassis is then carefully lowered onto these locking bolts, and the remaining locking mechanisms are put in place.</description></item><item><title> Beogram 4004 Type 5526: Platter Motor, Detector Arm Adjustment and Solenoid Repair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-4004-type-5526-platter-motor-detector-arm-adjustment-and-solenoid-repair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-4004-type-5526-platter-motor-detector-arm-adjustment-and-solenoid-repair/</guid><description>During today&amp;rsquo;s work, I installed the Beogram 4004 platter motor, fine-tuned the position sensor&amp;rsquo;s voltage, calibrated the detector arm sensor, and addressed an issue with the arm lowering solenoid.
My previous checks indicated adjustments would be needed after installing new parts, which is typical.
I also observed that the Beogram 4004&amp;rsquo;s arm solenoid, responsible for lowering the tonearm, was not raising it correctly. There was a lag between the signal to raise the tonearm and the solenoid disengaging.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Upgrade with SyncDrive Platter Motor, Commander Remote Control and Internal RIAA Pre-Amplifier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</guid><description>A customer from Kentucky requested a full upgrade for their Beogram 4002 turntable, including three modifications: a SyncDrive motor for enhanced speed stability, a Commander remote control system for convenient operation and keypad protection, and a Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier for direct connection to modern audio equipment.
All upgrades were installed without soldering. The SyncDrive replaced the original DC motor, connecting to existing mounting points and the main circuit board. The Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier replaced the output board, using compatible connectors for easy installation.</description></item></channel></rss>