<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HTC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/htc/</link><description>Recent content in HTC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/htc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the 'Butterfly' smartphone in specific Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 to the Japanese market through KDDI. This phone, also known as the HTC Butterfly 2, will be available from various carriers, including Chunghwa Telecom in Taiwan, CSL in Hong Kong, and others in South Asia.
Source: HTC.
The new HTC Butterfly 2 simplifies daily tasks with features like HTC Sense 6, an HTC Duo Camera, and the Motion Launch sensor.
Using au carrier aggregation*, the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 offers download speeds up to 150Mbps and supports WiMAX2+.</description></item><item><title>A Plethora of Free Android Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</guid><description>This Christmas, give the gift of a cutting-edge Android phone without breaking the bank. Although these devices boast advanced technology and typically come with a high price tag (often $500-$600), it&amp;rsquo;s possible to get one for free.
Android smartphones are essentially pocket computers, running on 3G and 4G networks and offering similar functionality to desktops and laptops. They&amp;rsquo;re capable of web browsing, social networking, email, video streaming, and more. While $500-$600 might be reasonable for such a device, why pay when you can get one for free?</description></item><item><title>HTC has unveiled the Desire 620 and 620G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC Desire 620 dual sim, the successor to the HTC Desire 610.
Source: HTC. The 620G in Milkyway gray.
Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia, stated that the new HTC Desire model provides a balance of modern design, strong processing, and fast connectivity, making it a suitable option for budget-conscious entertainment enthusiasts.
The Desire 620 dual sim is equipped with a Snapdragon 410 Qualcomm processor, Android 4.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 210, an entry-level dual SIM phone, is priced at less than S$160</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</guid><description>HTC will launch its budget-friendly smartphone, the HTC Desire 210, in Singapore on Wednesday, September 3, 2014. The phone will be sold through various retailers in two colors: Stealth Black and Polar White. A notable feature of the Desire 210 is its dual SIM card support, allowing users to manage personal and work profiles easily from a single device.
Source: HTC.
“The HTC Desire 210 brings impressive technology and design to the entry-level smartphone market,” stated Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia.</description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>HTC unveils its latest flagship smartphone, the HTC 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-unveils-its-latest-flagship-smartphone-the-htc-10/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-unveils-its-latest-flagship-smartphone-the-htc-10/</guid><description>Source: HTC. HTC Themes allows users to personalize their phones with thousands of professionally designed themes, each featuring unique icons, backgrounds, and sounds.
HTC has introduced its newest flagship smartphone, the HTC 10. Representing &amp;ldquo;the Power of 10&amp;rdquo; - signifying greatness and independence - this latest addition to the HTC phone lineup combines what HTC claims is the best smartphone camera available, the first-ever stereo 24-bit high-resolution audio recording capability in a smartphone, and exceptional performance.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography.</description></item><item><title>The HTC One E9+ dual sim will be available in Singapore starting August 29th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-one-e9-dual-sim-will-be-available-in-singapore-starting-august-29th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:40:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-one-e9-dual-sim-will-be-available-in-singapore-starting-august-29th/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The HTC One E9+ dual sim in rose gold.
HTC has introduced the HTC One E9+ dual sim in Singapore. This lightweight smartphone boasts a sizable 2K display and injects vibrant colors into the signature flagship design.
&amp;ldquo;This latest addition to our HTC One E series capitalizes on the success of our flagship phones, offering both sophistication and style,&amp;rdquo; stated Faisal Siddiqui, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;The HTC One E9+ dual sim represents a continuation of HTC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and design, showcasing a large 5.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 510 provides budget-friendly LTE capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 22:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</guid><description>HTC&amp;rsquo;s most budget-friendly LTE smartphone is hitting the shelves just days after the company launched the Desire 210 in Singapore. Starting September 6, 2014, you can find the HTC Desire 510 at mobile carriers and major retailers across Singapore. This device boasts a quad-core LTE processor, a 4.7” display, and runs on Android 4.4.
Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;While the industry has been buzzing about the impact of 4G, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook that only a handful of high-end devices truly utilize this technology,&amp;rdquo; says HTC CEO, Peter Chou.</description></item><item><title>HTC revolutionizes photography with the RE camera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</guid><description>HTC is launching a new camera called the RE, aiming to change how people take pictures. This waterproof handheld device can capture time-lapse photos and even act as a remote viewfinder for smartphones.
Source: HTC blog.
HTC CEO Peter Chou emphasizes their dedication to innovation, stating that the RE camera will allow people to experience photography in a new way. The RE&amp;rsquo;s grip sensor activates upon pickup, removing the need for a power button.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the Desire 616 dual SIM smartphone for entry-level users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</guid><description>HTC, a company known for mobile innovation and design, has introduced the HTC Desire 616 dual sim phone. This new phone offers high-end features at an affordable price. Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;The HTC Desire 616 dual sim is a powerful phone with a great price tag,&amp;rdquo; says Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;This new phone in the popular HTC Desire line offers an eight-core processor, fast processing speeds, and top-tier features at an accessible price, giving users a best-in-class experience.</description></item><item><title>HTC has launched the HTC Desire 826 dual sim, promising an exceptional mobile audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The Blue Lagoon version.
HTC is enhancing the mobile audio experience with its Desire 826 dual sim phone, featuring HTC BoomSound and Dolby Audio surround sound. This makes HTC the first smartphone manufacturer to integrate dual front-facing stereo speakers, a precisely adjusted sound profile, and Dolby&amp;rsquo;s decoding technology for a comprehensive multi-channel audio solution.
This combination provides listeners with a level of audio depth and range not typically found in mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>HTC reveals the new HTC One M9</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-reveals-the-new-htc-one-m9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-reveals-the-new-htc-one-m9/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The HTC One M9 will be available globally in dual-tone silver and rose gold¹ , single-tone gunmetal grey, single-tone gold and dual-tone gold and pink from mid-March. The silver and rose gold model is pictured.
HTC has launched its latest flagship phone, the HTC One M9. This new addition to the HTC One line combines the best features of the award-winning HTC One M7 and HTC One M8.</description></item><item><title>HTC has released the Android-powered Nexus 9, with pre-orders starting on October 17th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-released-the-android-powered-nexus-9-with-pre-orders-starting-on-october-17th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 13:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-released-the-android-powered-nexus-9-with-pre-orders-starting-on-october-17th/</guid><description>HTC teamed up with Google to create the Nexus 9, the first tablet to launch with Android Lollipop*. This premium tablet is designed for an exceptional user experience.
The Nexus 9 allows for extensive customization and features a suite of secure login functions for enhanced security. Multi-tasking is made easy with this device.
The tablet boasts an 8.9-inch display with a 4:3 aspect ratio, all within a sleek brushed aluminum frame.</description></item></channel></rss>