<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Phone Systems on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-phone-systems/</link><description>Recent content in Business Phone Systems on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-phone-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TDM vs VoIP - Why Not Both?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</guid><description>Feeling stuck between choosing a traditional phone system or a modern one? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses hesitate between sticking with their reliable but potentially outdated PBX system and switching to a VoIP system, unsure of the financial implications. The good news is that you have more choices than you might realize. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit to one system completely. You can have a mix of analog, digital, or IP phones at each desk, and you can choose between TDM or VoIP for outside calls.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item></channel></rss>