<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Forecast on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-forecast/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Forecast on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-forecast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tech Upheavals in 2009</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</guid><description>The world of technology is about to undergo another major shift, particularly in telecommunications and computing. While these changes have been in motion throughout 2008, 2009 looks to be the year they truly make their mark. Here are a few potential game-changers:
Wireless Broadband Takes the Lead: Traditional DSL and cable internet services are facing stiff competition from wireless providers. Cell towers, now equipped with broadband capabilities, offer comparable speeds to wired connections, often at slightly higher prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 07:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</guid><description>In the previous discussion, we explored how AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon are aggressively acquiring bandwidth for their LTE networks. Now, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the consequences of this insatiable demand for bandwidth as we transition into the 4G era.
While UHF and microwave bandwidth transactions are currently active, this surge won&amp;rsquo;t last indefinitely. The high prices will incentivize existing bandwidth holders to sell to major players heavily investing in 4G deployment. What happens once this bandwidth is depleted?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>