<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure as a Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infrastructure-as-a-service/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure as a Service on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:56:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infrastructure-as-a-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Capital Starved Companies Upgrade Technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</guid><description>Even with the economy recovering, securing funds for new technology can be challenging for businesses. Instead of traditional financing, consider &amp;ldquo;hosted solutions&amp;rdquo; or renting technology. This approach avoids large capital investments, allowing businesses to upgrade their systems affordably.
Website hosting is a prime example. Initially, hosting your website on your servers made sense. However, with increased competition, affordable hosting services have become widely available, making it more practical to outsource this function...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Helion offers enterprise-level cloud services tailored for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Helion Managed Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Lean, a service designed to support cloud-based applications for medium and large businesses. This service is suitable for purposes like application development and testing, as well as collaborative work environments.
This managed infrastructure solution allows smaller companies to adopt cloud technology swiftly and scale their usage as needed, all at a lower price point than previous HP Helion managed services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>