<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cartridge on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cartridge/</link><description>Recent content in Cartridge on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cartridge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000 Arrives From UK! Solenoid Oscillates!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</guid><description>I recently acquired another Beogram 4000 from the UK. The unit is in fair shape; importantly, the MMC cartridge mount is undamaged and the sensor arm insert is present. The control panel for the cueing and tonearm lift detached during shipping, highlighting the wisdom of securing such parts. Thankfully, the seller had protected the turntable with a durable plastic sheet, preventing any damage. Reattaching the panel should be simple.
Internally, all parts appear to be present:</description></item><item><title>Bang &amp; Olufsen MMC Cartridge Protector: Dimensionally True Reproduction with Stereolithography</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 05:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</guid><description>I recently decided to test out the clear resin (sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;maker juice&amp;rdquo;) on my Formlabs Form 1 printer. I chose to design a replica of a Multi Media Card (MMC) cartridge protector, as they always seem to go missing. While I own multiple MMC cartridges, I only had one remaining protector.
As you can see in the images, the finished product is pretty good! The term &amp;ldquo;transparent&amp;rdquo; might be subjective, as the 3D-printed clear material doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite match the real thing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new business printer capable of printing up to 75,000 pages in a single run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</guid><description>Epson helps businesses reduce printing expenses with its Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS). RIPS utilizes high-capacity ink packs that hold significantly more ink than traditional cartridges. This system combines the convenience of cartridges with the high-volume output of ink tanks.
Source: Epson.
The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-R8591 is the first printer in Southeast Asia to offer this technology. Using a complete set of ink packs, the WF-R8591 can print approximately 75,000 pages* before replacements are needed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:</description></item><item><title>Bang&amp;Olufsen MMC20EN Vintage Cartridge Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</guid><description>The MMC20EN cartridge that came with my recently restored Beogram 4004 parts was tested using my evolving cartridge testing methodology.
My approach involves evaluating the frequency range and trackability of a cartridge. For this, I utilize three test records: the Analogue Audio Ultimate Test LP for checking frequency response up to 20kHz, the Fisher Test &amp;amp; Performance Standard Quadradisc to observe 30kHz carrier frequency reproduction, and the Clearaudio Trackability Test Record to assess the cantilever suspension&amp;rsquo;s condition at different groove amplitudes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Arrives! First Impressions!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-first-impressions-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 07:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-first-impressions-/</guid><description>I was lucky enough to get a Beogram 4000 turntable today! It needs a little work, but it came with a perfect MMC20EN cartridge – I&amp;rsquo;m listening to Miles Davis on it right now and it sounds incredible!
The outside and dust cover are in great shape, and the platter looks really good too. Here are my initial thoughts:
The control panel is nice (ignore the Sharpie marks under the position indicator for now&amp;hellip;):</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Signal Path between DIN5 Plug and Cartridge, Plug Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</guid><description>I recently decided to update my Beogram 4002 turntable for the 21st century. While it was functional, the DIN 5 plug was noticeably worn and corroded. To address this, I swapped it out with a modern, high-quality Neutrik AG Rean NYS 322G plug featuring gold-plated pins, aiming for a reliable, long-lasting connection with my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s auxiliary input. The old plug was in rough shape, leaving me curious about its past.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame.</description></item></channel></rss>