<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Northern Ireland Protocol on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/northern-ireland-protocol/</link><description>Recent content in Northern Ireland Protocol on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:35:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/northern-ireland-protocol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Windsor Framework Relaunch receives general acclaim with little said.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: en:User:Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
The opportunity to finalize the Windsor Framework and ensure its acceptance was limited. The challenging task of establishing trade rules for goods moving between Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK had been largely settled almost a year prior. The objective was to minimize trade friction within the UK while upholding the EU Single Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Violating International Law on a Broad Scale: The Northern Ireland Protocol Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Reader in Public Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
In 2020, Brandon Lewis acknowledged that the UK&amp;rsquo;s Internal Market Bill would contravene the Withdrawal Agreement, albeit in a limited capacity. However, regarding the recent Northern Ireland Protocol Bill, Lewis insists that it will not violate international law. This assertion is debatable, as the Bill&amp;rsquo;s implications are vast.
The Protocol and Brexit
The UK government argues that the Protocol lacks cross-community support within Northern Ireland and cannot continue as is...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dillon Judgment, Exemption of Laws, and Article 2 of the Northern Ireland Protocol/Windsor Framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD researcher, Queens University Belfast, and Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Aaronward, via Wikicommons media
In a landmark decision, a UK court has disapplied portions of a UK Act of Parliament for the first time since Brexit due to conflicts with the Withdrawal Agreement, specifically highlighting the ongoing connection between UK and EU legal systems. This unexpected development, though previously argued for, underscores the UK government&amp;rsquo;s consistent underestimation of Article 2&amp;rsquo;s impact on rights-related cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simply Refuse? The latest 'Stormont Brake' within the Windsor Framework (part 2 of the framework analysis)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</guid><description>The Stormont Brake: A Closer Look at its Potential Impact Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons Introduction
This analysis delves into the &amp;lsquo;Stormont Brake&amp;rsquo;, a new mechanism within the Windsor Framework designed to address concerns about how EU law applies to Northern Ireland. This analysis explores the text and interpretation of this &amp;lsquo;brake&amp;rsquo; on changes to EU law under the protocol. While it might never be used, understanding the mechanics of the Stormont Brake is crucial to grasp its potential implications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Allister: the impact of the EU Withdrawal Act</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-the-impact-of-the-eu-withdrawal-act/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-the-impact-of-the-eu-withdrawal-act/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, a PhD researcher at Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, explores the legal implications of Brexit on Northern Ireland, particularly focusing on the impact of the EU Withdrawal Act 2018 and the subsequent amendments made by the EU Withdrawal Agreement Act 2020. He argues that the 2020 Act didn&amp;rsquo;t simply maintain the legal status quo as one might expect, but instead partially reversed the intended purpose of the 2018 Act.
This reversal is most evident in Section 7A of the 2018 Act, which incorporates the EU Withdrawal Agreement (including the Northern Ireland Protocol) into UK law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-the-impact-of-the-eu-withdrawal-act/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-the-impact-of-the-eu-withdrawal-act/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Allister Round 2: Exploring the depths of UK constitutional law in the Mariana Trench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD student, Queen’s University Belfast School of Law
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikicommons
Introduction
It&amp;rsquo;s a common observation in UK constitutional law that complex issues rarely have simple solutions. Instead, they often result in multiple, overlapping interpretations. This is certainly the case with the recent Allister and others v Prime Minister and others [2022] NICA 15 ruling from the Northern Ireland Court of Appeal (NICA). It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this case is headed to the UK Supreme Court on appeal, ensuring further analysis and discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Perhaps we are drawn to the suffering: The conclusion of the legal battle over the Northern Ireland Protocol.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Law Professor, University of Newcastle
Photo credit: ChrisVTG photography, via Wikicommons media
In October 2019, the UK government, led by Boris Johnson, reached a Withdrawal Agreement with the EU. This agreement encompassed a Northern Ireland Protocol iteration based on closely aligned rules governing goods between Northern Ireland and the EU. Notably, no comparable provisions addressed goods regulations for Great Britain. In January 2020, Westminster passed legislation to enact this agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>