<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bicycle on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bicycle/</link><description>Recent content in Bicycle on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:18:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bicycle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discover Clark by participating in the CLARK BIKE TOUR this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</guid><description>Source: PDOT.
The Philippines Department of Tourism (PDOT), alongside the Clark Development Corporation, announced the upcoming CLARK BIKE TOUR happening in July. This bike tour aims to raise awareness about the significance of health and wellness as a way of life while promoting travel and tourism. It also seeks to highlight Clark as a bike-friendly area.
The event, scheduled for July 30 at the parade ground, anticipates around 400 road bikers, forming 100 teams of four members each, to engage in a non-competitive day-long tour of different attractions within the freeport zone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CruCycle brings a fresh perspective to the fitness scene in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</guid><description>Krewfit recently introduced CruCycle, a new spin studio concept in Singapore, to fitness and fun enthusiasts. The studio&amp;rsquo;s classes operate on the principle of &amp;ldquo;Riding with the Pack,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing group workouts, teamwork, and camaraderie. This makes CruCycle&amp;rsquo;s workouts perfect for corporate team-building events.
Source: Crucycle.
The Ding siblings – Valerie, Calvin, and Beatrice – founded, own, and operate CruCycle. The inspiration for the studio came from their upbringing in Los Angeles, California...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coast Cycles introduces the new Coast Cycles Ruckus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coast-cycles-introduces-the-new-coast-cycles-ruckus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coast-cycles-introduces-the-new-coast-cycles-ruckus/</guid><description>Source: Coast Cycles. The Coast Cycles Ruckus.
Coast Cycles, a Singaporean lifestyle bicycle company, has launched its newest model: the Coast Cycles Ruckus. Described as a more compact version of a tandem bicycle, the Ruckus was awarded the 2016 Taipei Cycle d&amp;amp;i Award.
The Coast Cycles Ruckus features a vintage-inspired chromoly parallelogram frame, wide tires, and an extended seat, providing a comfortable ride for both the cyclist and a passenger...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coast-cycles-introduces-the-new-coast-cycles-ruckus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coast-cycles-introduces-the-new-coast-cycles-ruckus/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>