<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fortinet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fortinet/</link><description>Recent content in Fortinet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fortinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Home networks must be made more secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 06:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</guid><description>The increasing availability of faster and cheaper internet in Southeast Asia is driving a surge in home users adopting internet-connected devices. This trend is happening alongside more employees working remotely, often from home. While these connected devices offer convenience and improve communication, Fortinet, a global cybersecurity leader, warns that &amp;ldquo;home networks&amp;rdquo; are becoming attractive targets for cybercriminals.
Peerapong Jongvibool, Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s VP for Southeast Asia and Hong Kong, points out the vulnerability of internet-connected devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible that your computer is generating wealth for someone else?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</guid><description>Fortinet, a leading cybersecurity company, is warning users to be alert if their computers drastically slow down, as it could be a sign of &amp;ldquo;browser cryptojacking.&amp;rdquo; This new cybercrime involves hackers secretly using victims&amp;rsquo; computers to mine Monero, a type of cryptocurrency.
This is how it works: a malicious script is secretly embedded into a website. When a user visits the site, the script uses their computer&amp;rsquo;s processing power to mine Monero for the cybercriminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>