<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Channel Bank on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/channel-bank/</link><description>Recent content in Channel Bank on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/channel-bank/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>Converting From Regular Phone Lines to T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</guid><description>Your business is thriving, and your team is expanding, but your phone system isn&amp;rsquo;t keeping pace. The limited lines, tangled mess of wires, and sky-high bills are holding you back. There&amp;rsquo;s a better solution than relying on outdated analog lines.
T1 lines are the answer for businesses ready for a professional phone system. This technology allows multiple calls on a single line using your existing copper wiring. It&amp;rsquo;s like consolidating numerous lines into one connection for your phone system.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Trunk Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines often benefit from trunk lines. But with various trunk services available, choosing the right one can be tricky. While VoIP phone systems might make SIP trunking seem like the obvious choice, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to evaluate all options before deciding.
The concept of telephone trunking originated with telephone companies. Initially, individual phone lines connected users to the local phone company. As phone usage surged, businesses adopted switchboards to manage multiple lines, leading to a tangled mess of overhead wires.</description></item></channel></rss>