<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Taiwan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/taiwan/</link><description>Recent content in Taiwan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/taiwan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces the 'Butterfly' smartphone in specific Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 to the Japanese market through KDDI. This phone, also known as the HTC Butterfly 2, will be available from various carriers, including Chunghwa Telecom in Taiwan, CSL in Hong Kong, and others in South Asia.
Source: HTC.
The new HTC Butterfly 2 simplifies daily tasks with features like HTC Sense 6, an HTC Duo Camera, and the Motion Launch sensor.
Using au carrier aggregation*, the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 offers download speeds up to 150Mbps and supports WiMAX2+.</description></item><item><title>KKday has launched in Singapore and is introducing the #taiwantrippin promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</guid><description>Source: KKday. Ming Chen, CEO of Asia’s leading travel experience e-commerce platform KKday celebrates Singapore launch, and the #taiwantrippin digital campaign.
KKday, an Asian e-commerce platform specializing in travel experiences, has launched in Singapore. Based in Taiwan, KKday links users with local tours globally. Following its 2014 debut, KKday expanded to Hong Kong, Korea, and Japan, with Singapore as its fourth market.
“Establishing a presence in Singapore was a logical step.</description></item><item><title>Miramar Hotel Group offer now available with Asia Miles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</guid><description>Source: Miramar Hotel Taipei website.
Miramar Hotel Group is now part of the Asia Miles rewards program. This means members can earn 250 Asia Miles for every qualifying stay at either the Miramar Garden Taipei or Miramar Hotel Hsinchu.
To earn miles, members should provide their membership number during booking and show their card upon arrival. Note that this offer applies to deluxe room reservations.
For reference, the Miramar Garden Taipei first opened its doors in 2006, followed by the Miramar Hotel Hsinchu in 2013.</description></item><item><title>Experience the street food of Taiwan at Tea Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</guid><description>Tea Valley: Bringing Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Street Food Flavors to Singapore [Image of Tea Valley Downtown East outlet]
Tea Valley (茶食坊), a casual Taiwanese dining chain in Singapore, has ambitious plans for expansion. At a tasting event held at their first location in Downtown East, Director Lawrence Lim shared his vision for growing the brand beyond just new locations, but also in the variety of services they offer.
[Image of Lawrence Lim, Director of Tea Valley]</description></item><item><title>Citizens of Thailand holding ordinary passports can travel to Taiwan without a visa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 07:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</guid><description>Holders of regular Thai passports can now travel without a visa to 26 countries, along with Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau. Beginning August 1st, Taiwan initiated a year-long trial program waiving visa requirements for Thai citizens with regular passports visiting for tourism purposes.
This program permits eligible travelers to stay in Taiwan for a maximum of 30 days. To qualify, Thai nationals must possess a valid regular passport with at least six months of validity remaining, hold a return or onward ticket to another destination, and meet Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s entry requirements.</description></item><item><title>DHL introduces new freight service from Taiwan to Austria for shipments smaller than a full container</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding has introduced a new weekly Less-than-Container-Load (LCL) service originating in Taiwan and arriving in Vienna, Austria, by way of Koper, Slovenia. This service, departing every Monday from Keelung or Kaohsiung, allows Taiwanese exporters to ship cargo with a 35-day transit time to Vienna.
Kelvin Leung, CEO, Asia Pacific at DHL Global Forwarding, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to understanding industry trends and supporting exporters. He highlighted the increasing demand for Asian products in Eastern Europe and positioned the new service as a way to strengthen trade partnerships and improve the speed and efficiency of services for Taiwanese businesses.</description></item><item><title>The 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards are now accepting submissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</guid><description>Source: GCSA organizers. GCSA winners for 2019 at the GCSF in 2019.
If your company demonstrates a strong dedication to sustainability, we encourage you to apply for the 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards (GCSA).
The Alliance for Sustainable Development Goals (A•SDGs) is hosting the 2020 GCSA in collaboration with the Taiwan Academy of Corporate Sustainability (TACS), the Taiwan Institute for Sustainable Energy (TAISE), and the Center for Corporate Sustainability (CCS).</description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers.</description></item><item><title>BERI considers Taiwan to be a top candidate for establishing its Asia Pacific headquarters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 09:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</guid><description>Is your business searching for a new Asia-Pacific regional headquarters? Taiwan might be the ideal location.
Business Environment Risk Intelligence (BERI) released its third &amp;ldquo;Report on the Evaluation of Environmental Risks of Investment&amp;rdquo; for 2013 in December 2013. The report ranks 50 countries and territories based on their &amp;ldquo;Profit Opportunity Recommendation&amp;rdquo; metric. Switzerland secured the top position, followed by Singapore and then Taiwan.
Taiwan holds the second position globally, just behind Singapore, for operational risk.</description></item><item><title>Asia Miles has launched a new Facebook travel game specifically designed for travelers in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Asia Miles members in Hong Kong have the opportunity to win 100,000 miles this month. To participate, visit the Asia Miles Facebook page and find the post featuring travel tips for Taipei from social media influencer Ming Jai (Ming 仔).
Participants are asked to identify two Asia Miles categories that apply to Ming Jai&amp;rsquo;s itinerary. Then, they need to design an additional day of travel in Taipei with a budget of HK$5,000 or less, incorporating at least three categories for earning miles.</description></item><item><title>Cebu Pacific has been approved for more international routes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</guid><description>The Philippine Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB) has granted Cebu Pacific (CEB) additional flight entitlements for international routes. These include flights from Manila to the UAE and routes connecting various Philippine cities to Taipei and Kaohsiung in Taiwan.
CEB received approval to operate seven more weekly flights between Manila and the UAE. This allows the airline to offer service to any destination within the UAE, expanding upon its current daily flights between Manila and Dubai.</description></item></channel></rss>