<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS).</description></item><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors.</description></item><item><title>Hitachi drives are endorsed with a vote of confidence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</guid><description>In a January 2014 blog post, cloud storage company Backblaze reported that Hitachi and Western Digital hard drives have been the most reliable in their data centers.
Backblaze engineer Brian Beach revealed that Seagate&amp;rsquo;s 1.5TB drives had an annual failure rate of about 14%, significantly higher than Hitachi&amp;rsquo;s 2TB drives at approximately 1% and Western Digital&amp;rsquo;s 1TB drives at 3%. For 3TB drives, Seagate again had the highest failure rate at around 9%, while Western Digital stood at about 3% and Hitachi at roughly 1%.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website.</description></item><item><title>Canon has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Canon Singapore has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution providing businesses with real-time delivery tracking and automated scheduling. Designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) that rely on scheduling, delivery, and documentation for their core operations, FleetnexG offers a way to optimize resources and boost efficiency.
Vincent Low, Director &amp;amp; General Manager of Business Imaging Solutions at Canon Singapore, highlights the need for SMEs to go beyond timely order fulfillment. He emphasizes that optimizing resources for greater efficiency and productivity is crucial for success in today&amp;rsquo;s business landscape.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste</description></item><item><title>Box Zones provides customers with increased flexibility in choosing the locations for storing their data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</guid><description>The enterprise content management platform Box has introduced Box Zones, enabling companies to store their data regionally in Europe and Asia. Utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) and IBM Cloud, Box Zones will allow content to be stored in Germany, Ireland, Singapore, and Japan, based on customer requirements.
Box CEO and co-founder Aaron Levie highlighted that businesses are increasingly interconnected, collaborative, and global due to cloud technology. However, local regulations often compel companies to make technological compromises that hinder their growth and reduce employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean companies are prioritizing cloud technology to gain a competitive edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</guid><description>Source: VMware infographic.
VMware, a leading company in virtualization and cloud infrastructure, recently shared the results of their vForum Singapore Business Survey. The survey shows a positive attitude toward hybrid cloud solutions, which combine public cloud services with internal cloud technology, as a method of driving growth, efficiency, and innovation. Almost every business surveyed (90%) believes that the cloud can facilitate innovation, and nearly half (44%) prefer a hybrid cloud model for their IT infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in Singapore are increasingly transitioning to cloud services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</guid><description>Parallels, a company specializing in hosting and cloud services, has released an updated report on the Singaporean cloud market for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), called Parallels SMB Cloud Insights. This 2014 report predicts significant growth for the SMB cloud services market in Singapore, projecting it to reach S$916 million by 2017. This represents a strong three-year compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 21%.
Source: Parallels. Zanni.
John Zanni, Chief Marketing Officer for Service Providers at Parallels, observed that the Asia Pacific region is poised to outpace the rest of the world in cloud adoption due to its later start.</description></item><item><title>Digi has teamed up with Telenor to provide its subscribers with a complimentary image storage service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</guid><description>Telenor, through Digi, has launched Capture, a free mobile app and cloud storage service for backing up images and videos.
Capture allows users to automatically save and back up photos and videos from their devices, safeguarding memories if their phone is lost or needs to be replaced. It also provides additional storage, especially useful for entry-level devices with limited capacity.
Non-Digi customers can download and utilize Capture with 2GB of free storage space.</description></item><item><title>Intel Security is turning to the cloud to enhance consumer security protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-is-turning-to-the-cloud-to-enhance-consumer-security-protection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-is-turning-to-the-cloud-to-enhance-consumer-security-protection/</guid><description>Intel Security has released its 2017 consumer security product line, aiming to provide better protection for everyday devices. The main feature is a new anti-malware engine that increases efficiency and effectiveness by performing analysis in the cloud. Enhancements for multiple devices are also included in McAfee AntiVirus Plus, McAfee Internet Security, McAfee Total Protection, and McAfee LiveSafe.
The McAfee Labs Threats Report: June 2016 revealed a 120% rise in new ransomware since Q1 2015 and over 4.</description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it.</description></item><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding.</description></item><item><title>HP has released the HP Helion OpenStack Community Edition for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 09:24:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</guid><description>As part of its new HP Helion portfolio, HP is launching cloud products and services. These include:
HP Helion OpenStack Community Edition: This commercially available OpenStack product line is delivered, tested, and supported by HP. This free edition, available now, is perfect for proofs of concept, pilot projects, and basic production workloads. HP&amp;rsquo;s OpenStack Technology Indemnification Program: This safeguards eligible customers who use HP Helion OpenStack code from claims of patent, copyright, and trade secret infringement by third parties.</description></item><item><title>Xero creates cloud-based accounting software specifically tailored for business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-creates-cloud-based-accounting-software-specifically-tailored-for-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 14:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-creates-cloud-based-accounting-software-specifically-tailored-for-business-owners/</guid><description>Fitzgerald.
Despite the significant benefits, small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs) are slow to embrace cloud computing.
Kevin Fitzgerald, FCCA, Regional Director for Asia at cloud accounting software provider Xero, noted that cloud adoption remains a hurdle, particularly in accounting. Speaking at the recent Accounting &amp;amp; Finance Show Asia 2018 in Singapore, Fitzgerald shared that Xero&amp;rsquo;s potential clients often express concerns about security and privacy.
He pointed out the irony, stating, &amp;ldquo;They don&amp;rsquo;t realize they are already in the cloud if they use a banking app or an email server.</description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?</description></item><item><title>Readsoft Online version 9 has been released by Kofax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</guid><description>Kofax, a company that produces software to streamline and transform the initial stages of business operations, has introduced the 9th release of ReadSoft Online, a cloud-based solution for capturing and processing invoices.
ReadSoft Online provides small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) with a cost-effective and adaptable way to automate their accounts payable procedures. The solution captures invoices, extracts invoice data, and exports verified data to enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems, accounting software, and other applications.</description></item><item><title>SMU and Alibaba Cloud introduce groundbreaking upskilling program beyond China for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>Singapore Management University (SMU) and Alibaba Cloud have teamed up to introduce a series of courses designed to enhance the skills of over 1,000 working professionals in Singapore.
This joint initiative, known as the SMU-Alibaba Series, marks Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s first professional continuing education program outside of China. Set to commence in March 2019, the program will be delivered through SMU Academy, the university&amp;rsquo;s professional training division.
With a specific focus on empowering small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), the Series aims to equip businesses with the necessary competencies to navigate the challenges posed by rapid technological advancements and evolving consumer behavior.</description></item><item><title>Acronis has released updated versions of Acronis True Image Cloud and True Image 2016 for backup purposes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 06:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</guid><description>Source: Acronis.
Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, has released updates for its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 software. These comprehensive backup solutions, designed for individuals, families, and home offices, incorporate user feedback. Key improvements include simplified cloud storage options to address limited device space, a redesigned user interface for ease of use, and enhanced features for managing backups across multiple devices like PCs, Macs, smartphones, and tablets.</description></item><item><title>HP Stream notebooks include a complimentary one-year subscription to Office 365 and OneDrive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new notebook PCs to its HP Stream line of lightweight, cloud-based Windows devices. HP emphasizes affordability, offering these thin and light notebooks at a lower price point than typically seen.
Source: HP. The HP Stream notebooks come in horizon blue and orchid magenta.
“Consumers today want mobile devices that reflect their style and empower them to work and play from anywhere,” says Serena Yong, General Manager for Printing &amp;amp; Personal Systems at HP Singapore and Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>Colliers presents the concept of the Internet of the Workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colliers-presents-the-concept-of-the-internet-of-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 18:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colliers-presents-the-concept-of-the-internet-of-the-workplace/</guid><description>Colliers International, a leading global real estate services firm, has published a new report titled &amp;ldquo;Flex, Core and the Cloud: A Blueprint for the Future Asia Pacific Workplace.&amp;rdquo; The report examines how businesses, particularly those in technology, financial services, and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG), are incorporating cloud technology into their operations and the effects this has on employee productivity and well-being.
The report highlights that cloud computing, driven by the Internet of Things (IoT), is creating new opportunities for businesses in the Asia Pacific region to change how and where their employees work.</description></item><item><title>Adobe Sign simplifies the process of creating digital signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</guid><description>Adobe has introduced new cloud-based digital signature solutions, Adobe Document Cloud and Adobe Sign, built on an open standard developed with the Cloud Signature Consortium. This new technology, announced following the Consortium&amp;rsquo;s formation last June, allows digital signatures on any browser or mobile device.
Adobe Sign works with over 200 providers from the European Union Trust List (EUTL) and Adobe Approved Trust List (AATL), offering users a wide selection of trusted digital IDs.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud will assist companies in accelerating their entry into the Chinese market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud recently introduced its China Gateway Program alongside eight local partners: the Info-communications Media Development Authority (IMDA), Enterprise Singapore, DBS SME Banking, Singapore Chinese Chamber of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (SCCCI), SMU Academy, SGTech, Action Community for Entrepreneurship (ACE), and TechNode.
Alibaba Cloud, the data intelligence branch of the Alibaba Group, recently hosted its second Alibaba Cloud APAC Summit in Singapore, showcasing its dedication to serving Asia.
During the summit, the company announced the China Gateway Program in collaboration with IMDA, Enterprise Singapore, DBS SME Banking, SCCCI, SMU Academy, SGTech, ACE, and TechNode.</description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?</description></item><item><title>IBM reports that early adopters of cloud-based software are experiencing tangible benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 18:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</guid><description>IBM has revealed that nearly half of the businesses utilizing Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) are gaining a competitive edge, rather than just reducing expenses. This insight comes from a recent global survey conducted by the IBM Center for Applied Insights, involving over 800 IT and business decision-makers.
The study confirms that SaaS offers a wide range of advantages beyond lowering overall costs. It demonstrates that organizations strategically and collaboratively implementing SaaS are better equipped to execute programs that drive business growth compared to those slower to adopt SaaS.</description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces an improved True Image family and guarantees regular updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</guid><description>Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, recently launched its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 products in Singapore.
During the launch event, Acronis Co-Founder and CEO, Serguei Beloussov, emphasized the increasing importance of data protection, stating that it will soon be as essential as basic necessities. He believes that data represents a comprehensive record of our lives and preserving it should be a top priority, with the goal of eventually retaining all data indefinitely.</description></item><item><title>For the initial six months, HP Touchpoint Manager is being offered at a discounted rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Touchpoint Manager, a cloud-based IT management solution specifically designed for small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs).
Managing IT systems has become more challenging due to the increasing variety of devices and operating systems used in business, from company-provided equipment to personal devices.
HP Touchpoint Manager simplifies IT management for SMBs, helping them ensure device functionality, data security, and IT staff effectiveness. Its adaptability allows it to manage a wide array of devices and operating systems, including iOS, Android, and Windows.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud introduces the Create@Alibaba Cloud startup program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing branch of Alibaba Group, has launched its first international startup program, Create@Alibaba Cloud. The program was announced in Singapore, home to Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s international headquarters, which will also serve as the regional hub for the initiative.
Singapore was selected as the regional hub due to its strong ties and access to other ASEAN markets, such as Thailand, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The company explained that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s robust connectivity and reputation as Asia&amp;rsquo;s most entrepreneurial economy enable participating startups to easily connect within Singapore and expand into neighboring markets.</description></item><item><title>Dropmysite has undergone a rebranding and is now known as Dropsuite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</guid><description>Dropmysite, a cloud-based backup provider for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), has been renamed Dropsuite. This rebranding reflects a new global vision, business strategy, and ambition focused on business continuity, data recovery, and protection.
Dropsuite now offers a comprehensive suite of backup, recovery, and archiving solutions, consolidating its previous standalone brands: Dropmysite (website and database backup), Dropmyemail (email backup), and Dropmymobile (mobile data backup).
Furthermore, Dropsuite has introduced DSE Server Backup, a new file-based server backup solution.</description></item><item><title>The IBM Kenexa Talent Suite leverages big data to benefit HR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</guid><description>IBM has introduced a new software-as-a-service (SaaS) product designed to provide Chief Human Resources Officers (CHROs) and other executives with valuable insights from employee data.
The cloud-based IBM Kenexa Talent Suite helps organizations enhance the efficiency and accuracy of their hiring processes, boost workforce productivity, and foster employee connections in ways that positively influence business outcomes.
This software empowers HR teams to analyze extensive employee data, encompassing work history, social interactions, skills development, and individual interests.</description></item><item><title>The Important Contribution of Small Business [Infographic]</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 23:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</guid><description/></item><item><title>CloudGuard SaaS from Check Point is now accessible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudguard-saas-from-check-point-is-now-accessible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 21:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudguard-saas-from-check-point-is-now-accessible/</guid><description>Check Point Software Technologies, a leading global cybersecurity provider, has launched CloudGuard SaaS, a new cloud-based security suite.
As part of Check Point&amp;rsquo;s CloudGuard product line, CloudGuard SaaS is designed to safeguard businesses against advanced threats targeting software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications.
This solution protects companies using SaaS applications and cloud-based email, such as Office 365, GSuite, and OneDrive, from targeted attacks aimed at stealing sensitive information. It detects unauthorized SaaS application use, prevents data breaches, and provides immediate threat visibility.</description></item><item><title>HP Helion offers enterprise-level cloud services tailored for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Helion Managed Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Lean, a service designed to support cloud-based applications for medium and large businesses. This service is suitable for purposes like application development and testing, as well as collaborative work environments.
This managed infrastructure solution allows smaller companies to adopt cloud technology swiftly and scale their usage as needed, all at a lower price point than previous HP Helion managed services.</description></item><item><title>DocuWorks 9 is compatible with cloud and mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docuworks-9-is-compatible-with-cloud-and-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 19:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docuworks-9-is-compatible-with-cloud-and-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Fuji Xerox Asia Pacific has introduced DocuWorks 9, a document management software now enhanced with cloud integration for seamless mobile workflows.
DocuWorks allows users to interact with electronic documents, such as office files and images, as if they were physical copies. The latest mobile features empower users to pick up their work anytime, anywhere.
A new feature called Task Space lets users gather work-related documents and sync them to Fuji Xerox&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based Working Folder with a simple click.</description></item></channel></rss>