<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fashion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fashion/</link><description>Recent content in Fashion on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fashion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Four fashion trends from New York Fashion Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</guid><description>Milanoo.com, an online retailer for apparel and other goods, has recently highlighted the major trends observed during February&amp;rsquo;s New York Fashion Week.
Source: Milanoo website.
One trend was wrapped skirts that sit above the knee. This is a departure from the more revealing styles seen in past fashion events, which Milanoo refers to as &amp;ldquo;the consistent sexy style.&amp;rdquo; The company observed, &amp;ldquo;Skirts have been very popular these years. But things are changing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Styletag is known for identifying the latest fashion trends globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</guid><description>Want to stay stylish at work? South Korea&amp;rsquo;s SK Planet has refreshed its Styletag mobile app using trends from New York Fashion Week, which wrapped up on February 13th.
Source: Styletag page at the Play Store
Styletag gathers and organizes user-submitted fashion content worldwide, offering both style inspiration and shopping details. The app includes contributions from professional photographers, amateur enthusiasts, and invited fashion experts.
This free app is compatible with iOS 7 (iPad, iPhone, and iPod) via iTunes and Android devices through the Google Play store...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas Originals is reintroducing the Superstar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</guid><description>Source: adidas.
This year, adidas Originals launches a campaign exploring the meaning of being a superstar, coinciding with the anniversary of the iconic Superstar shoe, first released in 1969.
A short film by adidas Originals, directed by Karim Huu Do, examines what it means to be a superstar in 2015. Footballer David Beckham states, &amp;ldquo;It’s not about trying to be the next big thing.&amp;rdquo; Entertainer Pharrell Williams believes &amp;ldquo;It’s not about the number of views, likes or shares...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TINKR combines fashion, design, and 3D printing technology in a unique way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</guid><description>TINKR, a company from Singapore, has transitioned its business model from solely offering 3D printing services. They now focus on merging fashion, design, and technology to produce unique corporate gifts.
In a recent announcement, company founders Xiaohui and Freda expressed their passion for blending craftsmanship with technology. They are excited to introduce their latest venture: high-quality, locally and regionally designed prints. They plan to collaborate with various artisans and designers in the upcoming months to create fresh, unique prints with a distinctive style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benetton will concentrate on empowering women through their new collection, A Collection of Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</guid><description>The idea that women sharing their experiences and learning from each other is crucial for creating a brighter future is the driving force behind A Collection Of Us. This new United Colors of Benetton collection, launching in four parts throughout October 2015, December 2015, February 2016, and April 2016, embodies this philosophy.
Each capsule within the collection reimagines a core aspect of Benetton&amp;rsquo;s brand identity—heritage, technique, color, and performance—giving it a fresh and modern significance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Blum &amp; Co transforms the cheongsam into stylish workwear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 03:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</guid><description>Blum, a Singaporean fashion brand, has launched a new line of workwear inspired by the traditional cheongsam.
Source: Blum &amp;amp; Co.
Emerging in the 1920s as a symbol of women&amp;rsquo;s liberation, the cheongsam has undergone stylistic changes throughout the years. Originally a loose-fitting, full-sleeved dress, it evolved to feature a slimmer silhouette with shorter hemlines and a side slit. Despite being prohibited in mainland China following the communist revolution, the cheongsam remained popular in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore welcomes the arrival of Japanese fashion retail concepts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</guid><description>Source: WMH Group. Kafuku.
World Mode Holdings Group (WMH Group) aims to improve the Singapore fashion retail sector by establishing its first international branch, iDA Singapore (iDA’SG).
WMH Group is a Japanese fashion retail consultancy firm known for strengthening its clients&amp;rsquo; brands. As Japan&amp;rsquo;s top recruiter for beauty and fashion sales professionals, their Singapore branch will offer expert guidance and support to enhance retail staff skills.
“As Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader in retail job placements, we&amp;rsquo;ve placed 100,000 retail staff with approximately 1,000 clients, primarily in fashion and luxury...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JWT has identified 100 trends for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Source: JWT website.
The renowned marketing communications company, JWT, has unveiled &amp;ldquo;The Future 100,&amp;rdquo; a report that offers unique perspectives and analyses of 100 significant trends and cultural shifts to monitor in the coming year.
Lucie Greene, JWTIntelligence&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Director, emphasizes the importance of understanding the direction and implications of change for brands today. She points out that the rapid evolution of the digital world, readily available information, globalization, and social media have significantly accelerated the pace of trends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singapore retailer utilizes Qlik and Deloitte Digital solution to monitor customer narratives over time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</guid><description>Inverted Edge, a Singapore-based online retailer, is enhancing the customer experience at its Scotts Square location. Using technology from Qlik, a visual analytics company, and design by Deloitte Digital, the store provides a unique and interactive digital shopping experience.
Source: Inverted Edge website.
In addition to its selection of high-quality, modern luxury clothing, the store features a dynamic display of customer photos and stories from social media. This constantly updated feed showcases how customers style their purchases and shares their experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AIN has added English and Chinese websites for those interested in fashion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</guid><description>Source: AIN English website.
A Korean women&amp;rsquo;s fashion brand is aiming to become a global name, focusing particularly on mainland China, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
AIN has seen positive results selling on international e-commerce platforms. To further expand its reach, the company has launched English and Chinese websites through cafe24, a leading Korean e-commerce platform. AIN&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Park A-In, shared that customers appreciate the brand&amp;rsquo;s distinct, contemporary designs and overall aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become a leading global e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Aladdinstreet.com.sg, a global e-marketplace specializing in premium and halal products, has officially launched. Catering to both businesses and individual consumers, the platform offers a range of halal-certified products alongside premium items that don&amp;rsquo;t require certification.
Since its initial announcement in July 2016, Aladdinstreet.com.sg has carefully selected 200 merchants for inclusion on the site, formalizing agreements with nearly 60. Approximately half of these merchants provide halal-friendly or halal-certified products, encompassing diverse categories such as food, beverages, vitamins, cosmetics, pharmaceuticals, fashion, and more...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Men's cufflinks that can be customized are now offered on Indiegogo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</guid><description>CuffloCs, customizable cufflinks designed for men, are seeking funding on Indiegogo. These unique cufflinks feature a secure compartment for holding small items. According to creator Josh Jablonski, CuffloCs can accommodate a variety of small objects, such as jewelry charms, pebbles, or even photographs.
Source: Indiegogo.
&amp;ldquo;The screw/on off design ensures the security of your items within the double-sided glass, and the cufflink can be effortlessly disassembled to switch up the design,&amp;rdquo; explains Jablonski on his Indiegogo page...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean fashion designers are displaying their collections that have been digitally printed by Epson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. Display, Wai Yang.
Epson, a printing technology company, partnered with designers based in Singapore for FashionisTech, a showcase at the recent FUZE Fashion Technology 2017 event in Singapore. The designers used Epson&amp;rsquo;s digital printing technology to create their collections.
Organized by Textile and Fashion Federation (TAFF), the summit was the first of its kind in Singapore. It promoted advancements in materials and highlighted creative uses of technology by Singaporean fashion brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The last adidas Originals = PHARRELL WILLIAMS collection of 2014 will be released on November 28th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</guid><description>The last adidas Originals and Pharrell Williams collaboration of 2014 features a playful use of polka dots. More releases are planned for 2015. The bold and cheerful polka dot motif symbolizes energy and happiness.
Source: adidas Originals. The Polka Dot Pack includes Stan Smith sneakers.
Launching in Southeast Asia on November 28th, the Polka Dot Pack features leather Stan Smith sneakers. This collection embodies the profound joy of love. The youthful and optimistic designs aim for a relatable and authentic feel, representing the collaboration&amp;rsquo;s core value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: Customizable, reusable clothing in an instant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 13:33:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</guid><description>SiDi Huang, the creator behind ZipSeam, has developed an innovative solution for achieving a tailored look without the need for traditional sewing. ZipSeam offers a quick and easy way to create secure, temporary seams in loose clothing, providing a better fit for the wearer.
This invention has a wide range of applications, from the modeling industry and hand-me-downs to simply adjusting the fit of clothes you love. It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that this project has garnered significant attention and support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASICS introduces the versatile fuzeX TR, an all-in-one fitness solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 08:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The fuzeX TR training shoe.
ASICS has introduced the fuzeX TR, a training shoe designed for greater workout efficiency with its lightweight cushioning and versatile design. This all-in-one shoe supports athletes of all backgrounds and experience levels, accommodating activities from high-intensity interval training (HIIT) and weightlifting to treadmill running.
The fuzeX TR launch is part of ASICS&amp;rsquo;s larger expansion into the training category, a market expected to exceed US$55 billion globally by 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Belstaff has opened its flagship store in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Belstaff.
The renowned British heritage brand, Belstaff, recently celebrated the grand opening of its flagship store in Tokyo, Japan. Situated within the expansive Ginza Six retail complex, the new store occupies a prime location within this 47,000 square meter shopping destination. This strategic move underscores Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s growing presence in the Japanese market and its commitment to global retail expansion.
Upon its debut, the Tokyo flagship presents a curated selection of Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s offerings, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s complete menswear collection and, for the first time in Tokyo, its womenswear line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>