<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Premium on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/premium/</link><description>Recent content in Premium on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/premium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bookmate has teamed up with StarHub for its initial launch in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Bookmate. Pictured at the December 17 launch of Bookmate in Singapore are (from left): Simon Dunlop, Bookmate Founder, Andrew Baev, Bookmate Managing Director, and Michael Sim, StarHub Lead Futurist, i3 (Innovation, Investment, Incubation).
Bookmate, a social platform for reading e-books, has launched in Singapore, its initial entry point into the Southeast Asian market. The service offers subscribers unlimited reading for a fixed monthly price, drawing from a library of over half a million e-books provided by 600 publishers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rasel offers artisanal catering services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</guid><description>Rasel Catering Singapore, a top-tier halal catering service, has enhanced its offerings to become a leader in the industry.
Alan Tan, Co-Founder and Managing Director of Rasel Catering Singapore, highlighted the company’s focus on meeting the evolving needs of a global clientele. He stated, “Rasel caters to international events and weddings, recognizing the sophisticated tastes of today’s customers and their demand for high-quality halal food. Our service goes beyond just the food itself—we leverage our expertise to elevate the entire experience for our customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Come to Singapore Gifts Show 2015 for a wide selection of corporate gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</guid><description>The upcoming Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015 is the ideal event to discover this year&amp;rsquo;s corporate gift trends. Taking place from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, Halls 401 to 403, this international trade event offers free admission. It showcases innovative gifts, premiums, and lifestyle products and services, catering to trade buyers and corporate attendees.
Celebrating its 10th anniversary, SGS 2015 will host 160 booths featuring exhibitors from the Philippines, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vietjet's SkyBoss enhances the premium customer experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet.
Vietjet now offers SkyBoss, a premium travel class. SkyBoss passengers receive priority check-in, a 20kg checked baggage allowance, priority seat selection, airport lounge access, in-flight meals, extra legroom, and flexible flight date and time changes.
Established in 2011, Vietjet Air is Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s first privately held airline. Since its inception, Vietjet has served over 12 million passengers across 32 domestic and international routes. The airline currently operates two daily flights between Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi International Airport and Ho Chi Minh City&amp;rsquo;s Tan Son Nhat International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Foodpanda has introduced a high-end delivery service in the Central Business District of Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</guid><description>Source: foodpanda website.
In celebration of its third anniversary in Singapore, foodpanda Singapore has introduced a premium delivery service. This service includes approximately 50 restaurants and covers the central business district. It aims to serve busy professionals who want diverse food choices delivered directly to their workplaces.
Launched a month after securing US$110 million in funding, this new service reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing user experience and customer service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Avex Group introduces high-quality hemp fabric as part of the majotae brand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</guid><description>Avex Group Holdings, a Japanese entertainment company, has introduced &amp;ldquo;majotae,&amp;rdquo; a fabric brand reviving taima-fu, a traditional natural hemp fabric.
The photo above features (from left) Shigekazu Takeuchi, Representative Director of Avex Group Holdings; Masato Matsuura, CEO of Avex Group Holdings; Shinichiro Yoshida, natural fabric expert; Genbei Yamaguchi, obi artisan; and Hiroshi Onishi, CEO of Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings. They were attending the opening reception for the &amp;ldquo;majotae: The Forgotten Fabric&amp;rdquo; exhibition at Daikanyama Hillside Forum on October 22, 2014, in Tokyo, Japan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new Medium Roast Freeze-Dried instant coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect.
Cafédirect, a British beverage company, has introduced a new premium instant coffee in Singapore. This medium roast, freeze-dried coffee offers a convenient solution for those seeking a flavorful cup on the go, featuring a smooth, vibrant taste with hints of caramel.
Interestingly, a growing number of Singaporean coffee drinkers who typically prefer milk in their coffee are developing a taste for black coffee. This shift is attributed to Cafédirect&amp;rsquo;s master blender, who has crafted a unique blend using sweet and chocolatey Arabica beans from South America, well-rounded beans from Central America, and robust Robusta beans from East Africa (60%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fujifilm has launched the X100T premium compact camera in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Fujifilm has introduced the X100T, a high-end compact camera succeeding the successful X100S, to the Middle East market.
Source: Fujifilm. The X100T is available
in black and silver.
&amp;ldquo;The X100, launched in March 2011, established a new market for premium compact cameras. A year later, the second-generation X100S was released, featuring an updated sensor, processor, and an advanced Hybrid Viewfinder,&amp;rdquo; stated Yuta Kawamura, Marketing Manager for the electronic imaging division at Fujifilm Middle East &amp;amp; Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Sydney ICC Hotel will now be referred to as the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Artist&amp;rsquo;s rendition of the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
Accor, the leading hotel group in Australia, will manage the new International Convention Centre (ICC) Hotel in Sydney under its luxury Sofitel brand. The hotel will be called Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
This Sofitel hotel is part of the New South Wales government&amp;rsquo;s A$2.5 billion project to transform Darling Harbour, creating a new hub for conventions, exhibitions, and entertainment in Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Journeyful has revamped its website, incorporating additional listings and enhancing rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</guid><description>Source: Journeyful. The Journeyful 2.0 website.
Journeyful, a company located in Singapore, has relaunched an updated website for its rewards-based online travel agency, Journeyful.com. The new and improved &amp;ldquo;Journeyful 2.0&amp;rdquo; website features a selection of over 200,000 hotels globally, a price-match guarantee, and Facebook integration.
The redesigned website includes Journeyful MICE, which offers comprehensive solutions for business conferences, corporate events, and incentive trips. A Journeyful representative explained that once an online inquiry is submitted, MICE consultants collaborate offline with the organization to personalize solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LAVISH is bringing a new standard of high-end catering to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</guid><description>The renowned catering company, LAVISH, celebrated its 18th anniversary with a gala in late January. The event served as a platform for the brand&amp;rsquo;s revitalization and showcased their forward-thinking approach to catering, blending culinary arts with technology and science. LAVISH is well-regarded for its expertise in catering a variety of events, from large-scale conferences and corporate gatherings to intimate private dinners and celebratory functions.
Source: LAVISH. The gala dinner was held..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preview of Singapore Gifts Show 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015, held from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, presented a diverse selection of uniquely Singaporean gifts.
A sample pack from organizer TTG Events included the NYP Postcard Set, SG50 Tattoos, Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig, Miniature Tea Book – Volume II, and a Suction Mug.
Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig (Graceland Gifts, Booth B21)
These personalized LEGO figures demonstrate the potential for designing and 3D printing unique minifigures, as they are known by LEGO enthusiasts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Presidential Villa is now available at Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:01:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort.
The Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort is located near Dujiangyan, a UNESCO World Heritage &amp;amp; Natural Cultural site known as the home of giant pandas.
Inspired by the region&amp;rsquo;s history as the birthplace of Taoism, Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain introduces a new Presidential Villa. This villa embodies Taoist principles of living in harmony with nature, offering a space for reconnection and self-discovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>