<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Readmission on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/readmission/</link><description>Recent content in Readmission on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/readmission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What potential issues could arise with the EU, Turkey, and the Refugee Crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers* and Emanuela Roman, University of Palermo and Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam**
*Emanuela Roman wrote the sections on ‘safe third country’, ‘super-safe third country’ and ‘first country of asylum’. Steve Peers wrote the rest of the main text and the annexes.
Turkey plays a pivotal role in the EU&amp;rsquo;s current refugee crisis, hosting over two million Syrian refugees and serving as a transit point for many asylum seekers. A growing number of these individuals travel from Turkey to the Greek islands, contributing to a notable increase in asylum seekers within the EU in recent times.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals.</description></item><item><title>Updating the visa policy of the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
In 2014, the European Commission put forward a proposal to update the EU&amp;rsquo;s visa policy for short-term visits by revising the existing Visa Code. This proposal ultimately stalled due to disagreements between the European Parliament and the Council on whether or not to incorporate &amp;ldquo;safe passage&amp;rdquo; visas for individuals requiring protection. Currently, the Commission is revisiting this issue, this time prioritizing security concerns rather than economic benefits.</description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter.</description></item></channel></rss>