<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Signaling on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/signaling/</link><description>Recent content in Signaling on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/signaling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 Telephony Has Many Flavors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</guid><description>Initially designed for high-volume call transfer between telephone exchanges, T1 technology has evolved into a leading digital phone solution for businesses. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering T1, understanding the available options is crucial.
T1 is a digital standard supporting voice, data, video, or a combination thereof. Originally, it carried 24 separate calls on individual channels called DS0s, collectively forming a T1 line or DS1. Each DS0 transmits digitized voice, call control, and signaling information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So, What Does ISDN Stand For?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</guid><description>If your business uses telephone systems, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the term ISDN. This piece explains what ISDN is and how it can benefit your company.
ISDN, or Integrated Services Digital Network, is a digital telephone standard initially intended to replace analog lines for both residential and business users. While DSL, cable broadband, and VoIP surpassed ISDN in the residential market with their higher bandwidths and lower costs, ISDN found its niche as a popular trunking service for business PBX telephone systems and a few specialized applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>