<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YouTube on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/youtube/</link><description>Recent content in YouTube on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Divergence in regulations after Brexit: Copyright law as a preview of future changes.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</guid><description>Martin Kretschmer, Professor of Intellectual Property Law (CREATe Centre, University of Glasgow)
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the European Union has resulted in the first instance of regulatory divergence. As the UK exits the single market, existing regulations are starting to show cracks.
In response to a question from MP Jo Stevens, former Intellectual Property Minister Chris Skidmore indicated the UK would not implement the latest EU Copyright Directive, despite the UK&amp;rsquo;s prior support for it in the EU Council.</description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after.</description></item><item><title>Update of the Directive on Audiovisual Media Services – Platforms for Sharing Videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-of-the-directive-on-audiovisual-media-services-platforms-for-sharing-videos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:26:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-of-the-directive-on-audiovisual-media-services-platforms-for-sharing-videos/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
The Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) has been undergoing revisions since 2016, sparking debate about how to update it for the digital age. While the Council and European Parliament generally agree that video-sharing platforms (VSPs) need some regulation, they differ significantly on the specifics. This disagreement is evident in the ongoing trilogue negotiations, where even accessing agreed-upon positions has proven difficult due to the influence of interest groups concerned about advertising regulations.</description></item><item><title>Understand your social media presence with Socialbakers' Social Health Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</guid><description>Socialbakers, a company specializing in social media analytics and optimization, has launched its Social Health Index, a tool created in collaboration with Lenovo. This industry benchmark offers brands a single metric to assess their social marketing performance across multiple platforms. It allows them to effortlessly measure their overall social media presence and compare it to their competitors over a period of time.
Jan Rezab, CEO and Co-Founder of Socialbakers, stated that the Social Health Index is the first benchmark of its kind, providing context to brands&amp;rsquo; social marketing efforts.</description></item><item><title>A democratic option to the Digital Services Act's collaboration between governments and online platforms in addressing disinformation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 09:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</guid><description>By Paul De Hert* and Andrés Chomczyk Penedo**
* Professor at Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium) and associate professor at Tilburg University (The Netherlands)
** PhD Researcher at the Law, Science, Technology and Society Research Group, Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium). Marie Skłodowska-Curie fellow at the PROTECT ITN. The author has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No 813497</description></item><item><title>The guidelines for using YouTube have been published by the UAE's Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</guid><description>The Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA) of the UAE has introduced guidelines for using YouTube as part of its UAE Social Media White Papers series.
The TRA highlights the immense popularity of YouTube, with over a billion unique monthly users and over 100 hours of video uploaded every minute. They emphasize that UAE law forbids publishing content that violates public morals, Islamic principles, and the social and moral well-being of the UAE.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadhan, digital marketing methods need to be adapted in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Think with Google website. Changes in statistics for Musalsalat, a platform for Ramadhan TV series, during the month.
The Think with Google blog highlights the need for specialized digital marketing strategies in the Middle East and North Africa during Ramadhan. Google Analytical Consultants Vrinda Singh and Younis Maqousi, along with YouTube Specialist David Lacklen, observed a significant increase in mobile internet usage, YouTube viewership, and search engine activity throughout the month.</description></item><item><title>The most popular videos on YouTube in Hong Kong for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</guid><description>Content related to local news, tutorials, and parodies were the most popular on YouTube in Hong Kong this year.
A wider variety of music genres are gaining traction.
YouTube Hong Kong Rewind 2019 highlights this year&amp;rsquo;s trending videos, showcasing categories like the Top 10 Trending Videos, Top 10 Trending Local Music Videos, Top 10 Trending International Music Videos, and Top 10 Emerging Channels.
Music, in various forms like music videos, live shows, remixes, and covers, remains a favorite among Hong Kong viewers.</description></item><item><title>Take a look at the lineup for YouTube FanFest Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: YouTube. Poster for YouTube FanFest Hong
Kong 2018.
The Manulife-sponsored YouTube FanFest returns to Hong Kong on August 3 at the Kowloonbay International Trade &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre (KITEC).
This live event bridges the gap between prominent YouTube creators from Hong Kong and around the globe, offering a platform for fan engagement. YouTube FanFest Hong Kong will feature:
- Matt Steffanina, a US-based dancer, YouTuber, and social media figure known for his dance-centric content</description></item><item><title>An innovative social media project, fueled by the power of crowdsourcing, is revolutionizing Korean brand marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 01:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Bitter, Sweet, Seoul,&amp;rdquo; a feature-length film directed by Park Chan-wook, is the culmination of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s first international crowdsourced film project.
Source: PR Newswire
The Seoul Metropolitan Government, as part of a global brand marketing campaign to showcase the diverse experiences and emotions Seoul has to offer, invited individuals worldwide to submit short video clips about the city through YouTube and a dedicated microsite.
The initiative generated almost 12,000 submissions, totaling an impressive 159 hours, 35 minutes, and 4 seconds of footage from around the globe.</description></item></channel></rss>