<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wellbeing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wellbeing/</link><description>Recent content in Wellbeing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wellbeing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>60% of employed Singaporeans report feeling burned out</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic has led 49% of Singaporeans to reevaluate their priorities, with their careers no longer holding the same level of importance. A new study by Employment Hero highlights the significant role employers can play in employee well-being to attract and keep talent, particularly given that 62% of Singaporean employees report experiencing burnout and 57% feel they have an inadequate work-life balance.
Employment Hero, a company specializing in payroll, HR, and people management solutions, suggests that burnout stems from multiple factors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IHH Healthcare, NUS, Otis, and PSA set new standards for leadership and workplace mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</guid><description>WorkWell Leaders (WWL), a Singapore-based non-profit focused on workplace wellbeing and mental health, has revealed the winners of the WorkWell Leaders Awards 2024. These awards acknowledge exemplary practices in promoting positive change within workplaces. WWL emphasized that these awards are unique in their recognition of specific elements of workplace wellbeing that drive business results, as well as leadership behaviors that foster cultural transformation within organizations.
Anthea Ong, Founder and Chairperson of WorkWell Leaders, stressed the importance of addressing mental health proactively in the workplace, stating, &amp;ldquo;With 70% of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s population employed and spending a significant portion of their day at work, workplaces must serve as catalysts to support employees and their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The beauty industry acknowledges the growing demand in Asia for products that promote relaxation and stress relief</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</guid><description>A recent report by market intelligence agency Mintel reveals that the Asia-Pacific region produced one-third of all new beauty and personal care products aimed at relaxation and stress relief in the first nine months of 2018. This represents a significant increase from 2015 when the region accounted for only 26% of similar global product launches.
Sharon Kwek, Senior Innovation and Insights Analyst, Beauty and Personal Care at Mintel, addressed the in-cosmetics Asia event stating that today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, demanding world has normalized stress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>