<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pool on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pool/</link><description>Recent content in Pool on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Urban Island promotion has been introduced by The Shilla Seoul</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</guid><description>With the arrival of summer, The Shilla Seoul presents Urban Island, a luxurious outdoor escape for guests. This all-inclusive retreat offers relaxation, a connection with nature, and delightful poolside service.
Reopened for the season, Urban Island welcomes guests to heated outdoor pools, a jacuzzi, and a rooftop garden against a scenic backdrop of Namsan Mountain and the Seoul skyline. Intimate cabanas nestled among lush greenery provide secluded havens.
The Urban Days room rate, available until June 30, 2019, starts from KRW 320,000 per night, excluding taxes and service charges, based on double occupancy.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life.</description></item></channel></rss>