<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Treaty of Lisbon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/treaty-of-lisbon/</link><description>Recent content in Treaty of Lisbon on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/treaty-of-lisbon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Farewell and gratitude for the fish: CJEU provides clarity on international law and institutional matters related to fisheries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s fisheries policy generates disagreement both within and outside the EU because of its effects on fish populations and the economic well-being of fishing communities. Prior to the Treaty of Lisbon, its implementation was essentially under the sole authority of the Council. Although the European Parliament (EP) attempted to gain shared control over some of the policy&amp;rsquo;s external aspects by asserting its consent was required for international fisheries agreements that significantly impacted the EU budget, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) dismissed this claim...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The argument for the UK to remain in the European Arrest Warrant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Maria Fletcher, Senior Lecturer in Law at the University of Glasgow, and Steve Peers, Professor of Law at the University of Essex, collaborated on this piece.
As of December 1, 2014, the UK government will have to decide which pre-December 2009 EU laws on criminal law and policing to potentially rejoin. One of the most contentious issues is whether to opt back into the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. This article presents the argument for rejoining this legal framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>