<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EY on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ey/</link><description>Recent content in EY on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EY identifies obstacles that are impeding the effectiveness of the AEC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</guid><description>Political, legal, and organizational difficulties, regulatory burdens, and a lack of standardized trade regulations among ASEAN nations are hindering the progress of the 2007 ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) Blueprint. This plan aims to achieve regional economic integration by 2015, according to EY.
A recent EY report, &amp;ldquo;Trade Secrets: ASEAN economic community and inward investment,&amp;rdquo; examines the AEC&amp;rsquo;s development from a business standpoint, specifically focusing on obstacles to conducting business within ASEAN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EY introduces the Entrepreneur of the Year 2016 award in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, EY has announced the launch of the Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) 2016 award in Saudi Arabia. This year, the EOY will center on medium-sized enterprises, emphasizing their successes and the significance of their expansion and prosperity. The event has been conducted internationally for 29 years in 150 cities across 60 countries.
Ahmed I. Reda, Office Managing Partner at EY, Jeddah, and Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader at EY, states, “As we celebrate the 30th anniversary of the EOY program globally, we are excited to host the Saudi Arabia EOY program again this year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean CFOs are struggling to manage an overwhelming amount of data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 10:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chief Financial Officers (CFOs) face difficulties due to evolving stakeholder expectations and reporting timelines. CFOs anticipate changes in how reporting operates. CFOs are finding it difficult to provide boards with timely and accurate insights due to the increasing amount and speed of data. This issue is highlighted in a new report by EY Financial Accounting and Advisory Services (FAAS): 66% of global respondents say this significantly impacts corporate reporting effectiveness, up from 57% in 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>