<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lock on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lock/</link><description>Recent content in Lock on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Deteriorated Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002, deteriorated transport lock bushings, evidenced by small orange plastic pieces within the unit, were discovered. To address this, 3D-printed replacement bushings were designed for convenient installation without major disassembly. These bushings are comprised of two halves, insertable from above and below the sub-chassis.
The replacement bushings are available for purchase, with each bushing requiring two of the 3D-printed parts. A video detailing the installation process is accessible online.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings with 3D Printed Replacement Parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5523) arm lowering mechanism, I removed the circuit boards for refurbishment. This presented an ideal opportunity to swap the deteriorated transport lock bushings with 3D-printed replacements. The old bushings tend to break down, scattering fragments within the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s casing, often lodging beneath the floating chassis. These fragments can obstruct the chassis&amp;rsquo;s movement, hindering its ability to isolate the turntable and tonearm from the enclosure.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Missing Leaf Spring on a Plate Lock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</guid><description>During the rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5513), I encountered an issue while adjusting the sub-chassis, platter, and tonearm. The large aluminum plate wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly against the plinth when it was pushed back, making it impossible to align the platter flush with the plate.
The problem originated from one of the locking mechanisms in the back left corner. These locks, equipped with leaf springs, are designed to secure the plate to the frame when the plinth is moved back.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Transport Lock Bushings and cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>Many Beogram 4002 (5513) turntables, including the one I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring, require replacement of the transport lock bushings and cabinet guidance washers. These components are crucial for proper platter and arm alignment. Without them, alignment is unreliable and won&amp;rsquo;t hold during transport.
This image shows the front transport lock missing its bushing:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the disassembled mechanism with the lower part of the new bushings installed:
The top part of the bushing is added next:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A Broken Off Solenoid Plunger and New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, recently serviced and returned to a customer, unexpectedly came back with a faulty tonearm. The culprit was a broken solenoid plunger, a part responsible for lowering the tonearm. This unusual breakage was likely due to material fatigue.
To fix the issue, the solenoid was replaced with one from a donor Beogram 4002. During the repair, it was discovered that the transport lock bushings had also deteriorated and needed replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings and Missing Cabinet Guiding Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration involved addressing the common issue of fragile orange transport lock bushings and missing cabinet guiding washers. Many Beograms used plastic washers, which are prone to cracking and falling apart. This was evident in the restoration project, as some washers were missing entirely.
To rectify this, five new 3D-printed washers were installed. For aesthetic purposes, using a black washer for the front-center position is recommended to avoid visibility through the gap between the aluminum panel and the plinth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit.</description></item></channel></rss>