<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Greenhouse Gas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/greenhouse-gas/</link><description>Recent content in Greenhouse Gas on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:52:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/greenhouse-gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Advocate General's Opinion in Grupa Azoty once again exposes a significant deficiency in EU judicial protection, but fails to address the issue.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-grupa-azoty-once-again-exposes-a-significant-deficiency-in-eu-judicial-protection-but-fails-to-address-the-issue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-grupa-azoty-once-again-exposes-a-significant-deficiency-in-eu-judicial-protection-but-fails-to-address-the-issue/</guid><description>Professor Geert van Calster, University of Leuven
Photo credit: Wojciech Antosz, via Wikimedia Commons
Executive summary: In early March, Advocate General Pikamäe issued an opinion in the case of Grupa Azoty S.A. et al v European Commission (Joined Cases C 73/22P and C 77/22 P). This case is an appeal concerning the ability to partially overturn the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2020 &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on certain State aid measures in the context of the system for greenhouse gas emission allowance trading post-2021.</description></item><item><title>Implementing the European Green Deal and Making the EU Maritime Transport Sector "Fit for 55": Is Pain Necessary for Gain?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</guid><description>Killian O’Brien, DAAD Lecturer (Fachlektor), University College London
To achieve its European Green Deal objectives, the EU aims to cut greenhouse gas emissions by at least 55% of 1990 levels by 2030. As part of this goal, the European Commission introduced the “Fit for 55” legislative package on July 14, 2021. This collection of measures aims to rapidly decarbonize the EU economy by significantly altering the trajectory of emissions and aligning EU policies and legislation across 12 sectors.</description></item></channel></rss>