<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crowdsource on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crowdsource/</link><description>Recent content in Crowdsource on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:39:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crowdsource/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ImageCrowd has identified a market opportunity for an Asian stock photography marketplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imagecrowd-has-identified-a-market-opportunity-for-an-asian-stock-photography-marketplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imagecrowd-has-identified-a-market-opportunity-for-an-asian-stock-photography-marketplace/</guid><description>ImageCrowd, a new multilingual platform, wants to make it easier to find Asian photography. They connect international buyers with Asian photographers in their native languages. Buyers can make specific image requests, and ImageCrowd will crowdsource photographers to find the perfect match. Both professional and amateur photographers can submit photos. Any photos not purchased are added to a stock photography database.
&amp;ldquo;These days, visual campaigns need to be highly targeted,&amp;rdquo; says Gijs Waverijn, CEO of ImageCrowd.</description></item><item><title>Avast Wi-Fi Finder helps you find trustworthy Wi-Fi connections globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</guid><description>Avast has released Avast Wi-Fi Finder, an Android app that helps users locate trustworthy, fast, and secure Wi-Fi connections no matter where they are. The app uses a map interface to display recommended and crowdsourced hotspots.
&amp;ldquo;Many of us, whether traveling or working remotely, have struggled to find dependable and secure Wi-Fi,&amp;rdquo; said Gagan Singh, President of mobile at Avast. &amp;ldquo;With Avast Wi-Fi Finder, consumers can now easily locate a safe and fast Wi-Fi connection at the gym, hotel, airport, bus station, library, or café.</description></item><item><title>CrowdsUnite offers convenient crowdsourcing updates all in one location</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 22:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</guid><description>CrowdsUnite (crowdsunite.com) aims to be the &amp;ldquo;Yelp&amp;rdquo; for crowdfunding, featuring over 800 platforms in its database. The website provides guidance on crowdfunding and helps startups find the best platforms for their needs.
Alex Feldman, CEO of CrowdsUnite, points out that crowdfunding sites vary in features, customer support, and transparency. He emphasizes the risk of fraudulent campaigns that disappear with investors&amp;rsquo; money.
Source: CrowdsUnite blog. Feldman presents crowdfunding at a July 2014 talk in New York, US.</description></item><item><title>An innovative social media project, fueled by the power of crowdsourcing, is revolutionizing Korean brand marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 01:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Bitter, Sweet, Seoul,&amp;rdquo; a feature-length film directed by Park Chan-wook, is the culmination of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s first international crowdsourced film project.
Source: PR Newswire
The Seoul Metropolitan Government, as part of a global brand marketing campaign to showcase the diverse experiences and emotions Seoul has to offer, invited individuals worldwide to submit short video clips about the city through YouTube and a dedicated microsite.
The initiative generated almost 12,000 submissions, totaling an impressive 159 hours, 35 minutes, and 4 seconds of footage from around the globe.</description></item></channel></rss>