<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-ethernet-port/</link><description>Recent content in Gigabit Ethernet Port on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-ethernet-port/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dual Core, Quad Core, Up to 64 Core Managed Dedicated Servers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</guid><description>The race for faster processors has shifted its focus. Instead of increasing clock speeds, the industry is now prioritizing multi-core and multi-processor designs to improve performance.
The good news is that there are affordable options for powerful processing, including managed dedicated servers with excellent support.
Entry-level systems typically feature dual-core processors. For increased power, users can opt for quad-core or hexa-core (6 cores) configurations. For even greater performance, dual or quad-processor dedicated servers are available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>