<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>File Transfers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/file-transfers/</link><description>Recent content in File Transfers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:39:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/file-transfers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Bandwidth Can Affect Productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</guid><description>Businesses are grappling with decisions about bandwidth allocation, often facing costs calculated per Megabit per second (Mbps). While strategies exist to maximize Mbps per dollar, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to first understand the correlation between network bandwidth and employee productivity.
If your bandwidth is primarily used for non-work activities, reducing it might seem like a productivity booster. However, most businesses rely heavily on internal and external network connectivity for operations. So, how do you determine the appropriate bandwidth level?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 04:11:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</guid><description>There are two main types of broadband internet: shared and dedicated. While you might be familiar with terms like wireless, landline, satellite, or fiber optic, these refer to delivery methods that impact price and availability. Your primary choice lies in deciding between shared and dedicated internet access.
What sets them apart? The names are quite descriptive. Shared internet access resembles a buffet where you might eye a large roast, hoping for a full plate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>