<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CSR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/csr/</link><description>Recent content in CSR on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/csr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customize SPD paper and electronic greeting cards with your own branding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</guid><description>Source: SPD website.
The SPD, a Singaporean organization supporting individuals with disabilities, operates a supported employment facility that creates physical and digital greeting cards. These cards are suitable for various events like birthdays and holidays such as Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, and Chinese New Year.
Customization options are available for these cards, including adding company branding, personalized notes, or designs for other special events.
Interested parties can explore the complete selection of cards on the SPD e-shop...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover the most environmentally friendly hotels worldwide with GreenHotelWorld</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</guid><description>Source: GreenHotelWorld website.
GreenHotelWorld, in collaboration with TripAdvisor, now boasts the largest selection of verified eco-friendly hotels on a single platform. This was achieved by incorporating hotels from TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s GreenLeaders Program.
With a global reach, GreenHotelWorld curates over 8,000 hotels recognized for their demonstrably sustainable practices. Their categorization process utilizes standards from the Global Sustainable Tourism Council (GSTC), a respected international body that sets benchmarks for sustainable tourism and accredits green hotel certifications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore is sponsoring limited edition prints for The Schooling Effect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. From left: Tan May Lin, Epson Singapore’s GM (Sales, Marketing &amp;amp; Customer Service Division) and Tay Kay Chin, one of the collaborators for the photo book, with one of the prints available for sale as part of the collaboration.
Epson Singapore, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, is supporting The Schooling Effect. This community project is inspired by the victory of Singaporean Olympian Joseph Schooling at the 2016 Olympic Games...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benetton will concentrate on empowering women through their new collection, A Collection of Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</guid><description>The idea that women sharing their experiences and learning from each other is crucial for creating a brighter future is the driving force behind A Collection Of Us. This new United Colors of Benetton collection, launching in four parts throughout October 2015, December 2015, February 2016, and April 2016, embodies this philosophy.
Each capsule within the collection reimagines a core aspect of Benetton&amp;rsquo;s brand identity—heritage, technique, color, and performance—giving it a fresh and modern significance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 5th annual PCCW Global Charity Run will be held in Singapore this June</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</guid><description>Source: PCCW Global Charity Run web page. A picture from the same event in 2017.
The 5th yearly PCCW Global Charity Run will happen this June, and both PCCW employees and the general public can participate.
This run is organized by PCCW Global, a telecommunications company operating in Asia, Africa, Latin America, and the Middle East.
All funds raised from this year&amp;rsquo;s run will be donated to Make-A-Wish Singapore, an organization that grants wishes for children facing life-threatening illnesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Someline Apple Tree app will produce apples for charity as long as you refrain from using your phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</guid><description>Source: Google Play.
Libern Lin, a student entrepreneur attending Republic Polytechnic in Singapore, has expanded his app, Someline Apple Tree, with financial support from the Singapore Computer Society (SCS).
The app incentivizes real-life interactions by rewarding users with digital apples for reducing phone usage. Lin, the app&amp;rsquo;s creator, explained that they wanted to use the app&amp;rsquo;s concept for a good cause. So, they used the S$30,000 grant from SCS to add a charitable component to the app in line with IDA&amp;rsquo;s Code for Charity*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is extending its Change for Good program to additional flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Hainan Airlines flight attendants distributing Change for Good donation bags to passengers.
Hainan Airlines is significantly expanding its successful in-flight donation program, Change for Good, to include 16 more routes. The program, which supports UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s initiatives for children, was initially introduced in September 2013 on the Beijing-Haikou route.
As the first mainland China-based airline to partner with UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s Change for Good alliance, Hainan Airlines aims to raise a minimum of RMB 10 million over five years, starting from September 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bloem marks 4th anniversary with introduction of new services and partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Sukri Kadola and Ivy Tan cut a cake during Bloem&amp;rsquo;s anniversary celebration.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s custom floral design company, Bloem, recently commemorated its fourth anniversary. The company marked this occasion by announcing new partnerships and the launch of its Concierge service.
&amp;ldquo;While many believe the economy has presented difficulties for businesses, success is subjective,&amp;rdquo; says Sukri Kadola, Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO. Eighty percent of Bloem&amp;rsquo;s revenue is generated through corporate projects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Businesses have the opportunity to take part in the For a Golden Home charity campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</guid><description>Cromly.com, a design portal and social media platform, has launched &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home.&amp;rdquo; This online charity campaign aims to improve the lives of needy elderly individuals in Singapore this Chinese New Year. The platform allows organizations to create their own fundraising projects in support of this shared goal.
Source: Cromly.com. Participating companies can create a pledge project to raise funds. Eunice Olsen and Paul Foster are ambassadors for the &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home&amp;rdquo; campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pi1M Training Programme offered by Digi provides benefits to small business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Participants of the Pi1M Training Programme gathered for a group photo.
Digi Telecommunications recently conducted a training program for community members residing near the company-managed Pusat Internet 1 Malaysia (Pi1M) centers. This tailored program reflects Digi&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering online entrepreneurship within its Pi1M communities. Currently, Digi manages 34 Pi1Ms across Pahang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Johor, Melaka, and Sarawak, with plans to establish 70 more centers by year&amp;rsquo;s end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi is sponsoring customers to participate in the Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</guid><description>Source: Digi Telecommunications.
Digi Telecommunications is sponsoring 200 customers to join the WWF-Malaysia Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk in Penang and Sunway Pyramid. This event coincides with the Earth Hour 2015 celebration on March 28, 2015.
As the Night Walk@Sunway&amp;rsquo;s corporate sponsor, Digi has donated RM35,000 to support WWF-Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s environmental conservation efforts.
Digi is sponsoring 200 walk packs, costing RM60 each, for its customers. 100 packs are designated for Night Walk@Sunway and 100 for Night Walk@Penang...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sydney's Christmas programme has been officially launched by the City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</guid><description>Source: City of Sydney. Lord Mayor Clover Moore launched the Sydney Christmas program at Martin Place.
Sydney has officially begun its Christmas celebrations, featuring an array of decorations, carols, light displays, concerts, Christmas trees, and special retail events.
Lord Mayor Clover Moore expressed her enthusiasm for the festivities, stating, &amp;ldquo;Each year, we warmly welcome thousands of people from all over Sydney to the city center for our Christmas celebrations. With live concerts, vibrant light projections, excellent shopping opportunities, and the chance for kids to meet Santa, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone - visitors, shoppers, and locals alike...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CruCycle brings a fresh perspective to the fitness scene in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</guid><description>Krewfit recently introduced CruCycle, a new spin studio concept in Singapore, to fitness and fun enthusiasts. The studio&amp;rsquo;s classes operate on the principle of &amp;ldquo;Riding with the Pack,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing group workouts, teamwork, and camaraderie. This makes CruCycle&amp;rsquo;s workouts perfect for corporate team-building events.
Source: Crucycle.
The Ding siblings – Valerie, Calvin, and Beatrice – founded, own, and operate CruCycle. The inspiration for the studio came from their upbringing in Los Angeles, California...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KPMG has identified gaps in global corporate responsibility reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</guid><description>A 2015 KPMG study reveals inconsistencies in how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies report their carbon emissions, making it challenging to compare their performance. While 80% of the top 250 companies address carbon in their reports, the information provided varies significantly. For instance, only half declare carbon reduction goals, and among those, two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t explain their rationale.
The reported emissions types also differ. Most companies (84%) report emissions from their operations and purchased power (79%), but only half include supply chain emissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beautiful.me is inviting shoppers in Singapore to donate rice to those in need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 20:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</guid><description>Source: Beautiful.me. Beautiful.me partners with Community Chest. From left: Elise Wong, CRM Executive, Beautiful.me; Mae Kng, Senior Associate Director, Community Chest; Olive Tai, MD, Beautiful.me; Wileen Chen, Manager of Relations &amp;amp; Engagement, Community Chest.
Beautiful.me, in partnership with rice importer and distributor Hak Yong Company and the Singapore Community Chest, has initiated the Giving Is Beautiful campaign. This project encourages Singapore&amp;rsquo;s online shoppers to contribute funds to provide rice to those in need...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During the holiday season, Transamerica Life Bermuda and the World Wide Fund for Nature are advocating for the conservation of forests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 08:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/</guid><description>Source: TLB/WWF. A booth for the Rewrap Project.
Transamerica Life Bermuda (TLB), a life insurance provider for high-net-worth individuals, has teamed up with the World Wide Fund for Nature (WWF) in Singapore to launch the Rewrap Project.
The campaign, which will run until December 24, 2019, aims to raise awareness about the dangers of deforestation and the importance of forest conservation. All proceeds will support WWF&amp;rsquo;s conservation initiatives.
In 2018 alone, Singapore generated about 1 million tonnes of paper waste...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Registration is now open for the Bare Your Sole walkathon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/</guid><description>Source: Habitat for Humanity.
Habitat for Humanity Singapore&amp;rsquo;s yearly walkathon, Bare Your Sole, is back for its seventh year on May 30th.
This event unites individuals from all backgrounds to highlight the challenges faced by those living in poverty who lack access to basic necessities like shelter and shoes.
The funds gathered from the 2km and 4km barefoot walkathon will support Habitat for Humanity Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Project HomeWorks program. This local initiative focuses on enhancing the living situations of seniors, individuals with illnesses, and those with physical disabilities residing in one-room apartments in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson hosts its first charity event of the year-end</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</guid><description>Source: Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson. The poolside.
Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson will host its first charity event with the Friends of The Disabled Society (FDS) as part of their year-end festivities.
The public can purchase various handicrafts and accessories on November 17, 2016, at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s lounge area and poolside. All proceeds will go to FDS. The hotel will also host a dinner for FDS on December 3, 2016, as part of the holiday celebrations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The AirAsia Foundation is investigating the concept of social enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia Foundation website.
The AirAsia Foundation is hosting a conference and marketplace focused on social enterprise on November 7th at Nexus Bangsar South in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. This event, Destination: Good – ASEAN Social Enterprise 2015, is the first public event organized by the AirAsia Foundation, the philanthropic branch of the AirAsia Group. Its goal is to initiate a discussion on the role large companies and social enterprises can play in fostering fair, sustainable, and inclusive economies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Singaporeans are aware of human trafficking but underestimate its prevalence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</guid><description>The International Organization for Migration’s X Campaign (IOM X), in collaboration with USAID, the US Embassy in Singapore, and Microsoft, recently released findings from their pilot outreach program, IOM X Connect Singapore. This initiative sought to increase awareness about human trafficking in Singapore.
During the project, students from the National University of Singapore (NUS) and Singapore Management University (SMU) utilized the newly developed IOM X Learn, Act and Share App. They tested the knowledge of 100 Singaporean residents on the topic of human trafficking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>