<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Africa on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/africa/</link><description>Recent content in Africa on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/africa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Last Minute Online Gifts For Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</guid><description>_On Christmas Eve, instead of the typical peaceful house,
your home is filled with stress as you realize you forgot a gift.
Despite your best efforts, you overlooked someone on your list.
The pressure is on to find a solution quickly.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that can save your holiday!
Search online and find the K.I.N.D site for the perfect gift.
You&amp;rsquo;ll not only deliver a thoughtful present but also make a difference.</description></item><item><title>The Marauding Elephant Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marauding-elephant-network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marauding-elephant-network/</guid><description>Farmers near Mount Kenya Forest in Africa are constantly on edge due to the threat of elephant attacks. These attacks can happen unexpectedly, putting crops, livestock, and even human lives at risk.
This conflict stems from the age-old struggle between humans and nature. Humanity&amp;rsquo;s relentless pursuit of expansion has pushed many species to the brink of extinction. As a result, we are only now beginning to grasp the understanding that destroying nature ultimately harms us all.</description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join.</description></item><item><title>Foul Odor of Decaying Prepaid Calling Cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are a popular choice for international calls due to their incredibly low advertised rates. The cards often boast incredibly low per-minute rates, but these rates don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story. Like perishable food, prepaid calling cards have a limited lifespan once you start using them.
Hidden in the fine print on the back of these cards are details about connection fees, minimum call durations, and weekly service fees.</description></item></channel></rss>