<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-access/</link><description>Recent content in Internet Access on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables.</description></item><item><title>Telnes Broadband for T1 Dedicated Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 23:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</guid><description>Reliable, always-on internet connectivity has transitioned from a convenient business tool to a necessity. Companies of all types rely on consistent bandwidth for communication with customers, suppliers, and even phone services. Dedicated connections, like T1 data lines, offer the highest reliability with guaranteed uptime.
Telnes Broadband is an Internet Service Provider (ISP) catering specifically to businesses and government entities, constituting over 99% of their clientele. Their reputation for dependable WAN connections, especially for businesses with multiple locations, has made them a popular choice.</description></item><item><title>Business Broadband Options in Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses located in bustling city centers have a wide array of broadband Internet options, unlike their rural counterparts. While the lack of service providers in less populated areas might make it seem like broadband is a luxury they can&amp;rsquo;t afford, there are actually several options available, depending on the location.
Rural businesses might feel limited in their connectivity choices. Unlike their city counterparts, they don&amp;rsquo;t have numerous service providers vying for their business.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Bandwidth Suits the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), despite being independently owned, are no longer isolated entities. They rely heavily on the internet, from small insurance offices to quick-service restaurants (QSRs). This reliance stems from the cost-effectiveness of internet-based solutions.
The T1 line is widely used by SMBs for digital communication. This business-grade telecommunication service has become more affordable in recent years due to increased competition and demand. Costs for T1 services have been cut by more than half in some instances.</description></item><item><title>Secure Any Public WiFi Hotspot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: you&amp;rsquo;re away from your secure office network or home WiFi, relying on public WiFi that makes you uneasy. While convenient, unsecured WiFi hotspots present a security risk. How can you be sure someone isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring your activity with malicious software when you send private emails or sensitive data?
](http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-1726600-11129503)
It&amp;rsquo;s a valid concern. Cybercrime is rampant, and tools for intercepting data on public WiFi are readily available.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion.</description></item><item><title>Why You Need Dedicated Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume all high-speed internet connections are equal, but this isn&amp;rsquo;t true. Unfortunately, businesses may only discover this reality after missing out on sales and losing valuable customers.
While the core of the internet is quite reliable, with issues like packet loss, latency, and bandwidth rarely impacting crucial applications, the most significant difference between internet services lies in the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection – the link between your router and the provider.</description></item><item><title>Dynamically Allocate T1 Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a reliable choice for transmitting voice and data for many years. Traditionally, it was believed that the purpose of the line (voice or data) needed to be determined before installation. For voice communication, a channelized T1 line or ISDN PRI configuration was used, with each of the 23 or 24 channels dedicated to a single phone call. Conversely, a clear channel T1 line was used for point-to-point data transmission or dedicated internet access, allowing for the full 1.</description></item><item><title>Fight For Your Right to Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fight-for-your-right-to-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fight-for-your-right-to-broadband/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with slow internet speeds that interrupt your work and entertainment? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Despite being a global leader, the United States lags behind in internet access, ranking 16th globally in broadband subscriptions per capita.
While South Korea boasts 24.9 subscriptions per 100 people, the US has only 11.4. Furthermore, South Korea enjoys speeds of 45.50 Mbps, while Japan leads with 61 Mbps. In contrast, the US averages a mere 1.</description></item><item><title>What Is a PRI Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</guid><description>Businesses frequently use PRI lines to obtain multiple phone lines. But what exactly are PRI lines, and what choices are there?
PRI is a component of ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network), a telecommunications standard. Its goal was to replace analog phone lines with digital ones for both residential and commercial customers. When ISDN was first introduced, dial-up connections using 56 Kbps modems were the norm for internet connectivity. Many of these modems only achieved speeds of 30 to 40 Kbps due to phone line limitations.</description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications.</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>3G Fixed Wireless For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</guid><description>The same 3G technology that revolutionized mobile phones is also available as a fixed wireless service, offering a cost-effective solution for businesses in areas with limited internet options. Cellular networks have established a wide infrastructure of base stations, effectively blanketing the country with both voice and data coverage. These familiar cell towers transmit signals using microwave radio equipment.
Essentially, the 3G wireless broadband service functions as a network of interconnected Wi-Fi hotspots with a significantly larger coverage area.</description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance.</description></item></channel></rss>