<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Line Bonding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-line-bonding/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Line Bonding on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:13:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-line-bonding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DS3 Over Copper Avoids Fiber Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</guid><description>Businesses desire fiber optic connections for their high bandwidth capabilities, but the installation costs can be prohibitive, ranging from tens of thousands to even hundreds of thousands of dollars. However, there&amp;rsquo;s an alternative solution worth considering: DS3 over Copper.
Although DS3 is often associated with fiber optic lines, it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a 45 Mbps TDM protocol that can operate on various carriers. Originally, DS3 was delivered using T3 coaxial copper lines, waveguides, or microwave transmissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>