<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Divorce on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/divorce/</link><description>Recent content in Divorce on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:10:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/divorce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU's judgment on divorce and free movement law poses a problem.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Singh case tackles a crucial question: what happens to a non-EU spouse&amp;rsquo;s residency rights when their EU citizen partner, who moved to another EU country, leaves that country after their marriage ends? This case highlights a conflict within the EU Citizens’ Directive, where rules concerning divorce and departure clash. Unfortunately, the court chose a simplistic interpretation, aligning with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s prior suggestion.</description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach.</description></item></channel></rss>