<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Breach on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/breach/</link><description>Recent content in Breach on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/breach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Be cautious of insiders when it comes to protecting data privacy: Infowatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</guid><description>The most significant danger to data privacy in Southeast Asia comes from internal actors. Cybersecurity firm InfoWatch Group&amp;rsquo;s recent study reveals that careless top executives and employees with access to sensitive data are the primary cause of data leaks in ASEAN nations.
The company states that executives, employees, IT administrators, and other authorized personnel caused slightly more than 56% of compromised data incidents in Southeast Asia. External attacks and former employees were responsible for the remaining 44%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET advocates for the use of two-factor authentication to enhance security for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, cautions that small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) are frequently targeted by cybercriminals due to the vulnerability of their data. Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research&amp;rsquo;s study reveals that stolen personal data fuels a multi-billion dollar industry.
Lukas Raska, COO of ESET Asia, emphasizes the evolution of cybercrime from viruses to the current threat of identity theft, highlighting its potential to cripple businesses and compromise customer trust.
Parvinder Walia, Director at ESET APAC, explains that SMBs are attractive targets because they often lack the robust cybersecurity budgets and dedicated personnel of larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>