<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellular on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular/</link><description>Recent content in Cellular on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>Why Business Needs Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There was a time when the only way to communicate electronically was with that clunky black phone on your desk. While that phone might still be there, modern technology has made it lighter and brought a wealth of new communication methods. Email, text messages, mobile phone calls, and video chats are now commonplace across various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, smartphones, and even watches.
A significant challenge, particularly in business, is that these platforms and applications don&amp;rsquo;t always work well together.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs.</description></item><item><title>Verizon Goes After Blue Collar Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</guid><description>When picturing someone in a hard hat using a cell phone, most people think of a Nextel phone, known for their walkie-talkie feature and durability. However, Verizon is now entering this market, aiming to capture the construction and outdoor enthusiast demographics.
Verizon has the advantage of being a larger company with a wider customer base and a broader phone selection. They have leveled the playing field by adding push-to-talk (PTT) functionality and introducing tougher phones.</description></item><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology.</description></item><item><title>It's a Sidekick and a Running Mate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-a-sidekick-and-a-running-mate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-a-sidekick-and-a-running-mate/</guid><description>The T-Mobile Sidekick Slide is perfect for those who love to stay connected. Its compact design easily fits into your pocket, keeping you in touch even during a workout. While it functions as a cell phone, its primary use lies in its messaging capabilities.
Accessing the full QWERTY keyboard is as simple as sliding the phone open, transforming it into a miniature computer. The large, vibrant display and physical keys enhance the user experience.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Internet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, businesses depend heavily on infrastructure like electricity, telephone lines, and internet connectivity, often delivered through copper cables. While electricity and landline phones are widely accessible due to national initiatives, internet availability, particularly broadband via copper or fiber optic cables, diminishes as you move away from city centers. Rural areas often lack wired internet infrastructure entirely, leaving businesses with limited choices.
One option for these areas is wireless internet.</description></item><item><title>Lonliness of the Long Distance Landline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</guid><description>Recent data shows people are rapidly ditching landlines. If Alexander Graham Bell were alive today, he&amp;rsquo;d have trouble reaching anyone on his original invention. Instead, he&amp;rsquo;d have much better luck using a cell phone, just like everyone else.
It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that most people own a cell phone, or even multiple old ones. People want to be constantly connected, even when they perhaps shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be. Observe drivers at a stoplight, and you&amp;rsquo;ll likely spot several talking on their phones.</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process.</description></item><item><title>International Cell Phone Calls for Pennies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</guid><description>Imagine making international calls for as little as two cents a minute! It might sound impossible, but with a new service, you can make calls from the US and Canada to other countries at incredibly low rates.
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about rates like 2.36 cents per minute to China. Yes, you read that right. Still paying exorbitant rates? Get with the times and switch to the TEL3AdvantageMobile Plan before you make another call!</description></item><item><title>Sell Your Free Cell Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You were wise to get your new, top-of-the-line smartphone for free when you signed up for service. You understand that service plan costs are consistent, and it&amp;rsquo;s the phone&amp;rsquo;s price that fluctuates.
Now that your contract is up, it&amp;rsquo;s a great opportunity to upgrade. As you search for another discounted or free phone, you might wonder what to do with your old one.
Many people keep their old phones, thinking they might be helpful someday.</description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population.</description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>LG enV Envy Touch Phone Messaging Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</guid><description>Do you find yourself desiring a modern touchscreen phone but also require a physical QWERTY keyboard? The new LG enV Touch eliminates this dilemma by offering both!
When closed, the &amp;ldquo;enV Touch&amp;rdquo; resembles a typical touchscreen smartphone. The exterior features a 3-inch, 800x480 pixel color TFT touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable shortcuts. However, a hidden surprise awaits inside: a second 3-inch, 800x400 pixel color display. This internal screen, paired with a spacious QWERTY keyboard, prioritizes efficient typing over touch input.</description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP).</description></item><item><title>A Vu to an iPhone Kill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</guid><description>The Apple iPhone 3G is the current target for every cell phone company, indicating its leading position in the market. While iPhone enthusiasts might find alternatives underwhelming, the LG Vu smartphone offers a compelling option with unique features.
One standout feature is live TV. The LG Vu CU920 supports AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s MEdia FLO, a subscription-based digital TV service delivered through a dedicated over-the-air broadcasting system, requiring specific hardware in compatible phones.</description></item><item><title>Craving the Motorola ZN4 Krave</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</guid><description>The Motorola Krave ZN4&amp;rsquo;s unique design, reminiscent of futuristic helmets, features a protective visor. This &amp;ldquo;touch cover&amp;rdquo; can be lifted to interact with the full touchscreen or closed to shield the display while still allowing access to essential functions like the camera, media, and messages. This design combines the appeal of both flip phones and touchscreen devices, offering a large screen ideal for media consumption and showcasing the capabilities of the phone&amp;rsquo;s 2.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Old RAZR Getting Dull?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-old-razr-getting-dull/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-old-razr-getting-dull/</guid><description>The Motorola RAZR V3, known for its slim profile, is a highly sought-after mobile phone. Its popularity is evident across various carriers, even prepaid services like AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s GoPhone. While the original RAZR remains desirable, those considering an upgrade will find that the RAZR design has evolved. Newer models offer the classic RAZR aesthetic with enhanced features.
One notable upgrade is the Motorola RAZR 2 V8 with myFaves, available for T-Mobile. Also called the MOTORAZR, this model boasts a slimmer and more tapered design than its boxy V3 predecessor.</description></item><item><title>The Motorola ROKR Rocks On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</guid><description>The first iTunes phone, the Motorola ROKR, was a huge success. But instead of fading away, it has evolved into the modern ROKR E8 for T-Mobile. Is it still a great phone? You be the judge.
The sleek black design with red accents makes the Motorola ROKR E8 a striking multimedia phone. It&amp;rsquo;s actually three devices in one: a cell phone, music player, and digital camera. The touch-sensitive keypad adapts to the function you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?</description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable.</description></item><item><title>Have SIM, Will Travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</guid><description>SIM Simminy, SIM Simminy, SIM SIM Siree
Having the right phone is essential for international travel.
Traveling to a foreign country can be exciting, but discovering your cell phone is unusable can put a damper on your trip. Without a working phone, you&amp;rsquo;ll be stuck using expensive hotel phones to stay in touch.
Fortunately, with a little planning, you can avoid this problem. The key is to ensure your cell phone is compatible with the network used in your destination country.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry's Bold Move to HSDPA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</guid><description>BlackBerry, the company known for its wireless devices, is launching a new model called &amp;ldquo;Bold&amp;rdquo; with enhanced features like a sharper display, increased storage, a faster processor, and a 2-megapixel camera. However, the most significant advancement lies in its connectivity. The Bold surpasses standard EDGE data services by incorporating tri-band HSDPA and Wi-Fi, catering to the growing demand for desktop-like web browsing and video streaming among professionals.
Adding to the excitement, rumors are circulating about Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone selling out in anticipation of a new model featuring HSDPA technology.</description></item><item><title>Do You Have The Instinct For Covert Ops?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</guid><description>Ever imagine yourself as a secret agent like Jack Bauer from the show &amp;ldquo;24&amp;rdquo;? The Samsung Instinct phone, especially in sleek black, is your gateway to that world. Packed with features, it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate device for any aspiring operative.
The large, high-resolution touchscreen provides crystal-clear visuals and even vibrates slightly when you touch it, ensuring precise navigation. Its powerful 2.0 Megapixel camera captures high-quality photos and videos suitable for sharing or printing.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages.</description></item><item><title>Unlimited International Landline Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-international-landline-calls/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 19:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-international-landline-calls/</guid><description>We all know international calls can be pricey, making internet calls very appealing. As long as it&amp;rsquo;s computer-to-computer, you only pay for your internet service. But what if you want to use your regular phone line or cell phone? Is unlimited calling for a low fixed price even possible?
Now it is. IBNtel Unlimited Long Distance is a new service that works with your existing phones – no computer needed. It offers unlimited international long distance calling.</description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business.</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>For Free Phone Aficionados Only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</guid><description>Looking for a free cell phone? Look no further than Cell Phone Plan Finder&amp;rsquo;s free phones section. This site is completely dedicated to showcasing free phones available when you sign up for a service contract.
This screenshot only displays a limited selection. As of today, there are 23 free phone models from leading carriers such as Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, AT&amp;amp;T, and Sprint.
The selection includes various BlackBerry models like the Bold, Curve, Storm, and Tour.</description></item><item><title>Your Ally In The Android vs iPhone Battle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 20:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s initial Android offering, the LG Ally for Verizon Wireless, is a remarkable device. It boasts a range of features and access to a vast library of apps on the Android Market.
If you prioritize texting and email, you&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the tactile feedback of real keys. The LG Ally features a 3.2-inch touchscreen and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with well-sized keys. With five customizable home screens, you can personalize it with numerous Android apps.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel NumberShare service is compatible with the Apple Watch Series 3, which comes with built-in cellular capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</guid><description>Singtel is the first in Singapore to offer Apple Watch Series 3 (GPS + Cellular), allowing users to stay connected without their iPhones. The watch has been available in Singapore since September 2017 and works with compatible plans.
Apple Watch Series 3 with cellular enables users to stay in touch, make calls, and send and receive texts without needing their iPhones nearby, as long as their carrier provides a compatible plan.</description></item></channel></rss>