<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4G LTE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g-lte/</link><description>Recent content in 4G LTE on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 08:42:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g-lte/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RAZR Reincarnation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/razr-reincarnation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 08:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/razr-reincarnation/</guid><description>The original Motorola RAZR was a groundbreaking phone that redefined the industry, much like the iPhone did in its own time. Unlike the bulky phones available then, the RAZR stood out with its incredibly slim half-inch profile, all encased in a revolutionary aircraft-grade aluminum body.
The new RAZR takes this legacy further with even more advanced technology and a thinner 0.3-inch (7.1 mm) design. The iconic aluminum case is replaced by laser-cut KEVLAR with Corning Gorilla Glass for screen protection and a splash-guard coating for water resistance.</description></item><item><title>Alternative Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>For those living and working in rural areas, limited internet options can be a major problem. While major providers often only service cities, there are ways to stay connected without spending a fortune or waiting years for expanded infrastructure.
Forget DSL or cable – those are rare finds outside city limits. While universal telephone service guarantees basic phone lines (and thus, very slow dial-up internet), there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for fast, affordable internet: the existing cell phone network.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations.</description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business.</description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service.</description></item></channel></rss>