<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2018JL05BG4002-2 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2018jl05bg4002-2/</link><description>Recent content in 2018JL05BG4002-2 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2018jl05bg4002-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Service Manual Adjustments &amp; Preparing for Use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</guid><description>In the previous post, I finished cleaning and deoxidizing the keypad and RPM panel. The keypad is now responsive, but the cueing up and down button is overly sensitive and needs further attention.
The RPM panel re-installation was put on hold because the plastic mounting fixtures were cracked, a common issue with Beogram 4002 turntables. I was fortunate that the cracks weren&amp;rsquo;t severe and the fixtures were still usable. To repair them, I used acrylic repair fluid while pressing the pieces together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 02:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>Slow response times from the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control panel buttons pointed to potential oxidation on the keypad contacts. This was confirmed upon opening the keypad assembly, revealing dull key contacts.
The contact pads were unsoldered and removed for a closer look. While they seemed okay, the leaf contacts engaged by the actuators showed signs of oxidation.
To address the oxidation, a fiberglass brush and Deoxit were used, restoring the contacts to a shiny and clean condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Tangential Arm Assembly Oil Cleanup and Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-tangential-arm-assembly-oil-cleanup-and-restoration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-tangential-arm-assembly-oil-cleanup-and-restoration/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 restoration project continued with a thorough cleaning of the cabinet&amp;rsquo;s interior, focusing on removing oil residue. The tangential arm assembly was detached to access and clean the oil contamination found throughout the unit.
The oil had spread extensively, affecting various components from the arm&amp;rsquo;s mechanics to the switch contacts. The tangential arm position sensor assembly was entirely disassembled for cleaning.
With the old oil removed, the arm assembly restoration and adjustments could begin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Second Unit From Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-second-unit-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-second-unit-from-houston/</guid><description>A few weeks back, I completed the first of two Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable restorations for a client in Houston. I&amp;rsquo;m now starting work on the second one. Both turntable platters had their motors removed before being sent to Beolover for refurbishment. He has since finished these and documented the process on his blog.
I believe that refurbishing the platter motor is an essential step in any Beogram 400x restoration project.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Floating Suspension, Reservoir Capacitor &amp; Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</guid><description>This project is nearing completion. This post details the remounting of the floating chassis within the cabinet, replacing the reservoir capacitor, and installing the refurbished platter motor.
Here are the parts needed for mounting the floating suspension system back into the cabinet.
The threaded pin&amp;rsquo;s longer section is positioned at the bottom. When attaching the wing-nut, ensure it sits at the very beginning of the thread. I personally position it to allow enough thread for securing the nut while keeping the nut&amp;rsquo;s outer edge aligned with the topmost thread.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Electrical Work and Initial Tracking Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-electrical-work-and-initial-tracking-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-electrical-work-and-initial-tracking-adjustment/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s begin restoring the electronic boards. The main control board needs its capacitors replaced and the RPM relay (along with the RPM trimmers) need attention. Additionally, the output board requires inspection of its phono muting circuit. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that aside from wiring, the muting relay is the sole electrical part interacting with the phono audio signal. The turntable&amp;rsquo;s electronics mainly manage the platter motor, tangential arm, indicator lamps, and user controls, none of which are part of the audio pathway.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some additions for a previous Beogram project from Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-additions-for-a-previous-beogram-project-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-additions-for-a-previous-beogram-project-from-houston/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 Type 5513 turntable I previously restored in 2018 was returned for a sensor lamp replacement. This turntable had also visited in 2020 for a broken tonearm cartridge mount.
During both prior repairs, the owner opted to retain some original, functioning components, including the sensor lamp, tracking sensor lamp, and output phono muting switch. Since the sensor lamp has now burned out, it will be replaced with a modern Beolover LED assembly.</description></item></channel></rss>