<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Incandescent on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/incandescent/</link><description>Recent content in Incandescent on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/incandescent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the Incandescent Indicator Light Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, two indicator lights presented problems. One had a typical issue with a broken lead, while the other had become dim due to a deteriorating filament.
To address this, I opted to use SMD LEDs as replacements, similar to a method I&amp;rsquo;ve used for Beomaster 8000 units, documented on my blog. This provides lasting stability and safeguards against potential shipping damage. However, the Beocord 9000 has more compact reflector housings compared to the Beomaster 8000, necessitating a redesign of the PCBs for the LEDs.</description></item></channel></rss>