<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NGO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ngo/</link><description>Recent content in NGO on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ngo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement was initiated in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: GEM Facebook page.
The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) launched officially in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia today. This non-governmental organization (NGO) aims to create a platform for entrepreneurs from various sectors like social entrepreneurship, technology, and halal to connect.
“This NGO brings together community leaders from different networks who will cultivate strong partnerships for Malaysia and our entrepreneurs,&amp;quot; shared YBhg. Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah, GEM patron and Secretary General Treasury, Ministry of Finance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>