<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social Policy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social-policy/</link><description>Recent content in Social Policy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse.</description></item><item><title>Looking beyond austerity: the future of employment law in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Catherine Barnard, Trinity College Cambridge
Contrary to critics, the EU social model (ESM) is not dead, argues Professor Barnard. Although facing significant challenges, the ESM has historically demonstrated a capacity for renewal. This post explores potential future directions for the model.
While some believe a Social Union is necessary for Europe, this post focuses on a potentially more agreeable agenda for the EU-28, particularly in the area of employment law.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the European Labour Authority: A New EU Agency Based in Bratislava</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</guid><description>Bartłomiej Bednarowicz, PhD Researcher at the Faculty of Law of the University of Antwerp
Background
Bratislava was chosen by the Council to host the headquarters of the newly established European Labour Authority (ELA). Initially proposed by President Juncker in 2017, the ELA&amp;rsquo;s primary goal is to simplify and enhance the fairness of EU labor mobility within the internal market. This initiative stemmed from the European Pillar of Social Rights (EPSR) and was introduced alongside other measures aimed at promoting social fairness within the EU.</description></item><item><title>Should there be increased use of majority voting in EU social policy decisions? Evaluating the Commission's suggestion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, PhD Candidate, University of Antwerp
In April 2019, the European Commission initiated a discussion on streamlining the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making in social policy. The goal was to enhance efficiency by utilizing &amp;ldquo;passerelle&amp;rdquo; clauses, which permit a shift from unanimous voting to qualified majority voting (QMV) and from special to ordinary legislative procedures. This change, while requiring unanimous approval from Member States, aims to bypass the complexities of Treaty revisions.</description></item><item><title>Returning from Austerity to Legitimacy: An Overview of the European Pillar of Social Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</guid><description>This piece explores how Juncker can use ‘The European Pillar of Social Rights’ to convey a strong message: that the EU champions dignity, autonomy, and social justice.
Claire Kilpatrick (EUI), Elise Muir (Veni Fellow, Maastricht) and Sacha Garben (College of Europe, Bruges)
The EU has faced skepticism from its citizens about its commitment to prosperity and better living and working conditions, especially since the financial crisis and the subsequent implementation of austerity measures in various countries.</description></item></channel></rss>