<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Equality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/equality/</link><description>Recent content in Equality on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/equality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Most Singaporean women believe they are compensated fairly and that their employers value their opinions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</guid><description>Milieu Insight, a Southeast Asian consumer research firm, recently surveyed women in Singapore, Indonesia, and the Philippines to gauge their perceptions of workplace support, opportunities, and rewards.
Concept art featuring a woman
generated by dream by WOMBO.
Some key takeaways include:
While 67% of Singaporean women feel adequately compensated for their work, only half believe they are appropriately rewarded for exceeding expectations.
Although 65% believe their employers welcome their input, only 50% feel that feedback is acted upon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that self-employed workers are protected from discrimination, including on the basis of sexual orientation, under anti-discrimination and labor rights laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</guid><description>A Closer Look at Worker Protections: Analyzing the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in Case C-356/21 By Chiara De Capitani, linguist agent at the European Commission and PhD candidate and honorary fellow in European law at the University of Naples “L&amp;rsquo;Orientale”. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Photo credit: Silar, via Wikimedia Commons..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on discrimination against EU citizen workers just a futile effort?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</guid><description>Despite public debate regarding EU citizens working in different Member States (&amp;ldquo;EU workers&amp;rdquo;), the Council and European Parliament have agreed on new legislation concerning this topic. Recently approved by the European Parliament, the new Directive focuses on enforcing existing rules against discrimination toward EU workers and will likely be adopted by the Council soon. Member States are given two years to implement this Directive.
The Directive itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t modify existing rights related to EU worker free movement, but instead, clarifies the enforcement and application of rights granted by Article 45 TFEU and Regulation 492/2011...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it legal to terminate employees for religious reasons related to divorce?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-legal-to-terminate-employees-for-religious-reasons-related-to-divorce/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-legal-to-terminate-employees-for-religious-reasons-related-to-divorce/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law at University College London
Despite coming into effect in 2003, the Framework Directive on Discrimination in Employment&amp;rsquo;s impact on religion-related matters remained unclear for 14 years until a series of landmark decisions by the Court of Justice. These rulings have clarified the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance on religious expression in the workplace.
It is now established that a consistently applied workplace neutrality policy prohibiting religious symbols is considered indirectly, not directly, discriminatory (the Achbita case)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-legal-to-terminate-employees-for-religious-reasons-related-to-divorce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-legal-to-terminate-employees-for-religious-reasons-related-to-divorce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Commission's reflections on the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities focus more on praise than introspection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:44:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</guid><description>Dr. Charlotte O’Brien, Lecturer in Law, York Law School, University of York
Over seven years after signing the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities (UNCRPD) and over three years after its conclusion, how effectively is the EU safeguarding the disability rights outlined within it? The European Commission claims it is doing very well. In fact, it suggests the UNCRPD was hardly necessary, as the EU was already on the right track...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dr. David L. Parris v. Trinity College Dublin and Others represents yet another missed chance to effectively protect LGB rights under EU law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>By Dr. Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Introduction
The recent ruling in the Parris case represents a missed chance for the European Court of Justice (ECJ) to provide meaningful protection to LGB individuals and same-sex couples under EU law. While recent cases like Asociaţia Accept and Hay suggested a shift towards stronger protection of LGB rights, the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s judgment in Parris, similar to the Léger case preceding it, reveals a hesitancy to address matters considered sensitive by Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Explaining the European Court of Justice's decisions on headscarf bans in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued rulings on whether employers can prohibit employees from wearing headscarves at work. These rulings have garnered significant attention, although some of it stems from misunderstandings. This post aims to provide a clear explanation of the rulings.
Background
The EU has established laws against discrimination based on sex, nationality, race, disability, age, sexual orientation, and religion. While the ECJ has frequently addressed cases related to the first three grounds, the recent judgments in G4S v Achbita and Bougnaoui mark the first instance where the court has been asked to interpret workplace discrimination based on religious grounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ipsos provides insights on fatigue regarding equal rights in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-provides-insights-on-fatigue-regarding-equal-rights-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-provides-insights-on-fatigue-regarding-equal-rights-in-singapore/</guid><description>A recent study by market research firm Ipsos reveals that 62% of Singaporeans believe that sufficient progress has been made in achieving equal rights for women in Singapore. This sentiment is more pronounced among men (68%) compared to women (55%).
This data is drawn from a larger global study conducted by Ipsos in partnership with the Global Institute for Women’s Leadership at King’s College London for International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day 2024. The survey encompassed approximately 24,000 individuals across 31 countries, with 500 respondents from Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-provides-insights-on-fatigue-regarding-equal-rights-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-provides-insights-on-fatigue-regarding-equal-rights-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protection for fixed-term workers against unfair dismissal and mistreatment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union (EU) has increasingly addressed the rise of non-standard employment through measures like agreements on part-time and fixed-term work, and a Directive on agency work. The fixed-term work rules, in particular, have spurred many legal cases in the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). However, until recently, the court had not fully considered the connection between these rules and national laws on unfair dismissal, particularly for university researchers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Further information regarding the horizontal direct impact of the principle of age nondiscrimination can be found in the case of Dansk Industries (DI).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 08:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano The Court of Justice, in the recent DI case, further defined the differences in applying rights derived from Directive 2000/78/EC, which prohibits employment discrimination based on religion, disability, sexual orientation, and age, and the general principle of non-discrimination based on age in employment matters.
This builds upon previous landmark cases like Mangold and Kucukdeveci. In these cases, the Court addressed the obligation to prevent age discrimination in employment when challenged by national laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU judgment in NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford has erased the blurry line between employment discrimination and the right to freedom of expression.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Ph.D. Researcher in International Studies at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case C‑507/18, NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford, centers around the balance between freedom of expression and the harmful impact of discriminatory language. Advocate General Eleanor Sharpston aptly used bird metaphors in her opinion, likening discriminatory statements to volatile birds that can quickly spread their harmful effects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions on cases involving obesity and discrimination laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 03:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</guid><description>Katharina O Cathaoir
The European Court of Justice, in its decision on Kaltoft, determined that obesity itself is not a protected characteristic under EU employment law, nor is it automatically a disability. However, the Court acknowledged that the EU Directive prohibiting workplace discrimination based on disability might apply in certain situations. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this ruling specifically pertains to employment disputes, as EU law does not address disability discrimination outside of the workplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides clarification on when employers can prohibit headscarves in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Ronan McCrea, University College London
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s initial significant decisions concerning workplace policies limiting religious symbols were issued four years ago in the G4S and Micropole cases. These rulings addressed the compatibility of these policies with the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment (Directive 2000/78).
In these decisions, the Court&amp;rsquo;s Grand Chamber determined that requiring employees to maintain visible religious neutrality constituted indirect rather than direct discrimination, provided this policy was uniformly applied to all religions or beliefs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>