<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sleep on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sleep/</link><description>Recent content in Sleep on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:15:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sleep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bose's sleepbuds are specifically created to improve our sleep quality by masking noise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</guid><description>Bose has introduced noise-masking sleepbuds — wireless earbuds designed to combat common sleep-disrupting noises with a blend of comfortable design and soothing sounds.
Source: Bose. Bose sleepbuds offer noise
masking, not noise cancellation.
These sleepbuds, the most compact product Bose has developed, come equipped with 10 preloaded &amp;ldquo;sleeptracks.&amp;rdquo; These tracks are designed to mimic the frequencies of common noises like snoring, neighbors, dogs, and traffic, effectively masking them with calming audio.</description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality is introducing an upgraded hotel sleep experience for travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality
SilverNeedle Hospitality, a company focused on hospitality investment, management, and development, is launching the SilverNeedle DreamWeave Sleep System to enhance the sleep quality of its guests. This system will be implemented in all new hotels joining their network across midscale to luxury categories and will be gradually introduced to existing properties in those segments over time.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director and Group CEO of SilverNeedle Hospitality, emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving business travel by acknowledging the importance of sleep for their guests.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans struggle with getting a good night's sleep</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-struggle-with-getting-a-good-night-s-sleep/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-struggle-with-getting-a-good-night-s-sleep/</guid><description>Singaporeans are some of the world&amp;rsquo;s worst sleepers, averaging 6.3 hours of sleep on weekdays and 6.7 hours on weekends. These figures fall short of the global averages of 6.8 and 7.8 hours, respectively, and the recommended eight hours per night. This information comes from the report &amp;ldquo;The Global Pursuit of Better Sleep Health,&amp;rdquo; published by Royal Philips, a global leader in health technology.
Philips conducts an annual global sleep survey in conjunction with World Sleep Day (March 15).</description></item><item><title>Travel insomnia tips from Accor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-insomnia-tips-from-accor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 06:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-insomnia-tips-from-accor/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. Raffles Dubai – calming amenities help to welcome a restful night’s sleep.
In honor of World Sleep Day on March 15th, Accor Hotels has put together advice for getting a good night&amp;rsquo;s sleep while traveling.
Warm mood lighting
For travelers, lighting plays a crucial role in achieving quality sleep. Swissôtel&amp;rsquo;s Vitality Rooms are equipped with circadian lighting technology. This technology adapts to individual preferences and habits, ultimately enhancing well-being and overall health.</description></item><item><title>Improve your sleep with the Sleep with Six Senses program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Better sleep with the new Sleep with Six Senses programme.
Six Senses partnered with Sleep Doctor Dr. Michael Breus to launch its improved sleep standard called Sleep With Six Senses. Currently, five resorts offer this standard, with complete implementation across all locations expected by mid-2017. All future resorts will feature this program from their opening day.
The experience begins with a pre-arrival online questionnaire. This allows a designated Sleep Ambassador to understand the guest&amp;rsquo;s relationship with sleep and tailor the room accordingly.</description></item></channel></rss>