<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Human Rights Act on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/human-rights-act/</link><description>Recent content in Human Rights Act on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 03:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/human-rights-act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Impact of Brexit on Human Rights Law in the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-brexit-on-human-rights-law-in-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 03:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-brexit-on-human-rights-law-in-the-uk/</guid><description>Steve Peers
*Adapted from comments made at the launch of Conor Gearty’s book On Fantasy Island: Britain, Europe and Human Rights
The future of human rights law in a post-Brexit UK starts with the fate of the Human Rights Act, the subject of Professor Gearty&amp;rsquo;s new book. On Fantasy Island provides a detailed analysis of the Act within its social, political, and historical context. It emphasizes both the legal intricacies and the human impact of human rights cases.</description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law.</description></item><item><title>Does repealing the Human Rights Act comply with EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK&amp;rsquo;s new government plans to revoke its Human Rights Act (HRA), a move with legal and political ramifications. While the overlap with EU law is complex, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to examine the potential conflicts and consequences.
Assuming the UK remains part of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and doesn&amp;rsquo;t intend to disapply the EU Charter of Rights domestically, the government&amp;rsquo;s objective seems to be weakening domestic human rights protection and separating it from the ECHR, potentially impacting groups considered undesirable.</description></item></channel></rss>