<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>D3 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/d3/</link><description>Recent content in D3 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/d3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your 50 Mbps WAN Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The need for 50 Mbps bandwidth has increased due to businesses needing to use cloud services, access remote data centers, transfer large data files, run e-commerce platforms, send high-resolution images, and distribute video content. There are various ways to get 50 Mbps bandwidth connectivity, each with its own benefits and drawbacks.
DS3 &amp;amp; T3
DS3, or T3, is a traditional telecom service designed for transmitting many calls simultaneously between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>