<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/quality/</link><description>Recent content in Quality on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:06:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/quality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Berkeley Earth raises concerns about air pollution in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</guid><description>Source: Berkeley Earth website.
A recent study published in PLOS ONE by Berkeley Earth reveals that air pollution causes approximately 4,000 deaths per day in China, representing 17% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total deaths. This non-profit organization, established to investigate concerns raised by global warming skeptics, determined that the air quality for 38% of China&amp;rsquo;s population would be deemed &amp;ldquo;unhealthy&amp;rdquo; by United States standards.
Berkeley Earth&amp;rsquo;s analysis of hourly measurements from 1,500 ground stations over a four-month period indicated coal as the most likely source of PM2.</description></item><item><title>SPRING Singapore fully supports the enhancement of quality and standards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-fully-supports-the-enhancement-of-quality-and-standards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-fully-supports-the-enhancement-of-quality-and-standards/</guid><description>SPRING Singapore has increased its grant budget by S$10 million to assist local businesses in enhancing quality and utilizing standards as key business strategies. Enterprises can leverage this funding to create and implement new standards.
Quality and standards can make businesses more efficient, minimize waste, produce safer and higher-quality environmentally friendly products, and create stronger product and service differentiation.
SPRING will also provide funding to establish new standards development organizations that will manage the creation and promotion of standards in emerging sectors.</description></item></channel></rss>