<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Managed Routers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-routers/</link><description>Recent content in Managed Routers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-routers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Combine T1 Lines For Higher Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a popular choice for small and medium-sized businesses for many years due to their reliability, security, dedicated bandwidth, and accessibility. While their affordability has increased in recent years, their speed has remained a limitation. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution to overcome this without sacrificing the benefits of T1 technology: bonding.
Bonding is a standard industry technique that allows you to combine the bandwidth of multiple T1 lines. This effectively merges them into a single, faster connection.</description></item><item><title>Covad Ethernet Now Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>Prepare to be surprised! Covad is now offering Ethernet bandwidth at prices even lower than T1 solutions of comparable speeds. That&amp;rsquo;s right, the tide has turned, and Ethernet is now a more budget-friendly option.
While this is an initial launch in 12 markets across California, Michigan, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, and Texas, it could be a sign of a nationwide shift in telecommunication pricing. To see if your location qualifies, you can check Ethernet availability online.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Router Included With Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</guid><description>Considering upgrading your voice or data bandwidth? DS3 service offers 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads, suitable for demanding tasks like video transfer, medical imaging, or call centers. But finding the right DS3 router for your network can feel like an added burden.
Rest assured, DS3 is a well-established technology with readily available equipment and decreasing prices. As more companies switch from T1 lines to DS3 bandwidth, implementation is becoming increasingly straightforward.</description></item></channel></rss>