<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Productivity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/productivity/</link><description>Recent content in Productivity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Don't Layoff Employees, Evict Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/</guid><description>The work-life balance for many employees today feels unbalanced. They often face excessive workloads, whether the company is thriving or facing difficulties, and the constant threat of layoffs creates a stressful environment. However, what if instead of layoffs, companies considered &amp;ldquo;evicting&amp;rdquo; employees from their offices?
This doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean losing their homes, but rather transitioning to a telecommuting model. The concept is that many employees, especially in information-driven fields, can be just as productive, if not more so, working remotely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</guid><description>The current focus on infrastructure often overlooks a critical element: fiber optic broadband. While roads, bridges, and utilities are essential, fiber optic networks are the backbone of the 21st-century economy. Just as electricity revolutionized the 20th century, fiber optics will define this one.
We&amp;rsquo;ve outgrown the limitations of traditional wireline systems. Fiber optic technology, with its capacity for high bandwidth, is the only way to meet the growing demand for data-intensive applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KODAK CapturePro Software v5.0 has been released by Kodak Alaris</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</guid><description>Large businesses are constantly looking for ways to manage information more efficiently and productively. Extracting data from documents for business processes and getting information into digital storage can slow things down, impacting expenses and customer happiness.
Source: Kodak Alaris.
&amp;ldquo;As organizations rely more on online platforms for profit, it&amp;rsquo;s critical to manage remaining paper documents effectively,&amp;rdquo; says Harvey Spencer, President of leading capture software analyst firm Harvey Spencer Associates. &amp;ldquo;The best approach is quickly converting paper into usable electronic data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increase your productivity by installing a treadmill at your desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</guid><description>A recent study featured in the journal Plos One found that using a treadmill desk could lead to higher productivity compared to a traditional desk setup.
[Image of a treadmill desk]
Source: Plos One
This study, titled &amp;ldquo;Treadmill Workstations: The Effects of Walking while Working on Physical Activity and Work Performance&amp;rdquo;, was conducted by researchers from the University of Minnesota-Twin Cities, University of Texas-Arlington, Mayo Clinic, and Arizona State University. Over 12 months, they observed the impact of treadmill desks on physical activity and work output at a financial services company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simplify your computing experience with Parallels Toolbox 3.5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplify-your-computing-experience-with-parallels-toolbox-3-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 10:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplify-your-computing-experience-with-parallels-toolbox-3-5/</guid><description>Parallels has released Parallels Toolbox 3.5 for Windows and Mac. This suite of over 30 tools is designed to make using PCs and Macs easier.
“We&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to PC and Mac users who want new tools that can simplify their lives,” said Nick Dobrovolskiy, Senior VP of Engineering and Support at Parallels.
“We&amp;rsquo;ve added Break Time, Energy Saver, Hide Menu Icons, Clipboard History, and Sleep Timer to the dozens of other one-click solutions already available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplify-your-computing-experience-with-parallels-toolbox-3-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplify-your-computing-experience-with-parallels-toolbox-3-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telepresence as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</guid><description>Think of telepresence as the next step beyond the telephone and television: instead of sending your voice or an image, you&amp;rsquo;re projecting your presence across distances. While not as futuristic as Star Trek&amp;rsquo;s transporter, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool for businesses, especially now that companies like Cisco and AT&amp;amp;T offer it as a more accessible service. This shift could mark a significant increase in the use of virtual meetings.
Telepresence evolved from video conferencing, which a decade ago was clunky and unreliable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most effective productivity hacks for Microsoft Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</guid><description>Microsoft Office 2013 offers several improvements over previous versions, but long-time users may not be aware of these useful additions. At the Singapore launch of Office 365 Personal, Elsie Chong, Marketing Manager for Microsoft Singapore, highlighted her favorite new features:
PDF Reflow in Word 2013 allows users to open PDF files as editable Word documents, retaining the original formatting as much as possible. The modified document can be saved as a PDF or a Word file...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rural Broadband Stimulus Hopes To One-Up Dial-up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 12:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</guid><description>Right before the 4th of July holiday, the much-awaited government funding plan for expanding rural broadband access was officially announced through a &amp;ldquo;Notice of Funds Availability (NOFA)&amp;rdquo; and a call for applications.
The application window is short, running from July 14th to August 14th, 2009, so interested parties need to act fast.
Don&amp;rsquo;t expect to see immediate changes if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to use these new broadband services rather than provide them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox unveils new tools to enhance productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</guid><description>Source: Dropbox website.
Dropbox aims to simplify content creation, sharing, and teamwork through its new features.
Users can now create new Microsoft Office files, upload photos, or scan documents directly through the Dropbox iPhone app using the plus button.
A Dropbox badge shows who is currently working on the same Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, or Excel files, preventing work duplication or loss. Microsoft co-authoring enables real-time collaboration on Microsoft Office files online, eliminating email exchanges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Bandwidth Can Affect Productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</guid><description>Businesses are grappling with decisions about bandwidth allocation, often facing costs calculated per Megabit per second (Mbps). While strategies exist to maximize Mbps per dollar, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to first understand the correlation between network bandwidth and employee productivity.
If your bandwidth is primarily used for non-work activities, reducing it might seem like a productivity booster. However, most businesses rely heavily on internal and external network connectivity for operations. So, how do you determine the appropriate bandwidth level?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra discusses the obstacles of maintaining productivity in a workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</guid><description>Source: Jabra research report.
According to audio and communications company Jabra, modern workplaces face difficulties in fostering productivity due to common hurdles employees experience daily. These include distractions, poorly structured meetings, and technology that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work as intended.
Jabra&amp;rsquo;s 2015 research report, Productivity at the Office – Challenges, highlights that while companies invest in resources and tools to help office workers collaborate and focus, employees still encounter obstacles. These include constant distractions, unproductive meetings, and challenges utilizing technology meant to enhance their output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bonded T1 Solution Increases Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</guid><description>A 1.5 Mbps T1 bandwidth has long been a standard for small businesses, often proving sufficient for their needs. Some businesses even utilize an Integrated T1 solution for combined internet and telephone services. However, as bandwidth demands increase, many find T1 bandwidth limiting their productivity.
A simple solution to increase bandwidth is adding a second T1 line, doubling it to 3 Mbps. However, for these lines to function as a single, larger line, they should be ordered from the same provider with a &amp;ldquo;bonded T1 solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A survey on employee productivity has discovered that productivity is higher in the early part of the day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-survey-on-employee-productivity-has-discovered-that-productivity-is-higher-in-the-early-part-of-the-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-survey-on-employee-productivity-has-discovered-that-productivity-is-higher-in-the-early-part-of-the-day/</guid><description>A recent study by Milieu Insight, a consumer data and analytics firm, revealed that employees are typically most productive for five to six hours daily, especially in the morning. This conclusion comes from surveying 500 full-time employees in Thailand, Singapore, Indonesia, the Philippines, and Vietnam.
The study found that 45% of respondents felt most productive for five to six hours daily. A significant 72% identified the period between 8 am and 12:59 pm as their most productive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-survey-on-employee-productivity-has-discovered-that-productivity-is-higher-in-the-early-part-of-the-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-survey-on-employee-productivity-has-discovered-that-productivity-is-higher-in-the-early-part-of-the-day/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>