<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brand on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brand/</link><description>Recent content in Brand on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarivate Analytics states that global innovation is shifting its focus from quantity to quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 07:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</guid><description>Source: Clarivate Analytics infographic.
Clarivate Analytics, previously known as the Intellectual Property &amp;amp; Science division of Thomson Reuters, has announced its 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators. Utilizing unique proprietary data analysis, the report recognizes the world&amp;rsquo;s most innovative companies and institutions.
Now in its sixth year, the 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators report highlights a significant change in approach among leading global innovators, according to Clarivate Analytics. The report shows a decline in patent filings coupled with an increase in grant rates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The flag-carrier airline of Dubai is the most popular brand among women in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. 2019 Women&amp;rsquo;s Choice Rankings, top 10 for the UAE.
For the third consecutive year, Emirates secured the top spot in the UAE YouGov BrandIndex Women&amp;rsquo;s Rankings. The airline achieved the highest positive &amp;ldquo;Impression&amp;rdquo; score, reaching +70.0 among women in the UAE. WhatsApp maintained its second-place position, while Carrefour climbed to third place, surpassing Apple, which descended to fourth.
These rankings were determined using data from YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex, a daily brand tracker...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Brand Finance Global 500 2016 report, Disney is recognized as the most influential brand in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</guid><description>· Out of the top 10 fastest growing brands, four are Chinese.
· Disney is the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential brand due to the immense success of Star Wars.
· Despite experiencing a decline in sales, Apple&amp;rsquo;s brand value increased by 14% to US$145.9 billion, making it the most valuable brand globally.
· Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s brand value experienced a decline of US$12 billion as a consequence of the emissions controversy.
· Leading brands are outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500 average in terms of share performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google is ranked first in the Brandindex Australia rankings for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</guid><description>Source: YouGov BrandIndex. Overall brand rankings for 2016 in Australia.
YouGov BrandIndex has released its 2016 rankings for Australia. Having monitored brands in Australia since mid-2015, BrandIndex currently tracks over 260 brands. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Google secured the top position, followed by YouTube, another Alphabet subsidiary, and then ALDI, the discount retailer.
Here are some other notable findings:
In the automotive sector, Toyota, Mazda, and Mercedes-Benz secured the top three spots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FMCG brands are well-regarded in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. Brandindex 2016 rankings for the Philippines are heavy on toiletry brands.
The YouGov BrandIndex rankings from 2016 show that personal care products are very popular in the Philippines. The top 10 includes Colgate dental care, Cream Silk hair products, Dove soaps and hair care, Safeguard soaps and washes, and Olay skin care. Bench, primarily a clothing retailer, also has a presence with their bath and body products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance reveals the top influential brands in Asia for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Brand Alliance. The brand gallery at Marina Bay Sands is open until August 21st.
Brand Alliance, using its brand leadership platform Influential Brands, has announced the 2015 Asia’s Top Influential Brands. This announcement leverages consumer insights gathered from 2013 to 2015.
This year, the Asia’s Top Influential Brands awards expanded to include over 100 categories. These categories span various sectors, ranging from food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) to financial services and property development...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia loves food and communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Top ranked-brands for KSA in 2016.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 illustrate the diverse brands consumers love. Rankings were determined by BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which asks respondents about their recent exposure to a brand through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth and whether their perception was positive or negative.
The Buzz Rankings chart highlights the brands that achieved the highest average Buzz scores from January to December 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indonesia has the highest number of brand advocates for Garuda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia, the national airline, has earned the highest level of brand advocacy among Indonesian consumers, according to a YouGov BrandIndex analysis.
With a score of 87.5, Garuda secured the top position, surpassing Singapore Airlines (77.2) and Bank Central Asia (76.5).
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s rankings utilize a net promoter score methodology to determine which brands have the highest percentage of current and former customers who would recommend them to family or friends. The top 10 list includes several automotive brands, with Toyota ranking 4th (75...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to BrandZ, Tencent is currently the most valuable brand in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</guid><description>Tencent, a Chinese company, has become the most valuable brand in Asia and the fastest growing brand globally, achieving a brand value of US$54 billion in the 2014 BrandZ Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands ranking. This success propelled Tencent to the 14th spot globally, surpassing China Mobile.
Source: Millward Brown website.
Deepender Rana, Managing Director of Millward Brown Greater China, emphasized the significance of a market-driven Chinese brand like Tencent taking the lead over state-owned enterprises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If apps don't offer speed, simplicity, and security, consumers will not hesitate to abandon them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</guid><description>Source: CA Technologies infographic.
People are pickier than ever about the apps they use, so businesses that don&amp;rsquo;t offer a good app experience could lose a significant portion of their customers. A regional study* sponsored by CA Technologies shows that mobile and desktop applications in the Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) region have become key to earning customer loyalty.
Software: the New Battleground for Brand Loyalty – A survey of 1,449 consumers and 259 business decision-makers across five APJ nations pinpointed three major factors influencing the customer experience: Source: CA Technologies infographic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance is set to release a new book highlighting the achievements of influential brands in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 18:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</guid><description>Brand Alliance, a brand consulting firm, is releasing its inaugural book, &amp;ldquo;Influential Brands: A documentary of their heroic rise.&amp;rdquo; This book launch coincides with the firm&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;2014 Influential Brands&amp;rdquo; conference, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes&amp;rdquo;, taking place on November 7, 2014, at the Suntec City Convention Centre.
Source: Brand Alliance. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s brand story is in the book.
The book offers never-before-seen insights into the development of well-known brands, particularly those from Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is heavily involved in digital communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. This data represents the Brandindex rankings for brands in Thailand in 2016.
According to the YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016, digital brands were highly favored in Thailand. Facebook, Line, and 7-Eleven secured the top three spots, while YouTube and Google were among the top 10. Other notable tech brands included Apple iPhone and the e-commerce platform Lazada.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents whether their exposure to the brand, whether through advertising, news, or word of mouth, in the past two weeks has been positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>YouGov's ranking of the top brands in Hong Kong for the first half of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</guid><description>In the first half of 2016, Mannings was the most talked-about brand among Hong Kong respondents, according to YouGov&amp;rsquo;s 2016 Mid-Year Best Brand Ranking for Hong Kong. Nike and Adidas secured the second and third positions, respectively. This ranking, drawn from YouGov BrandIndex data, reflects the brands generating the most positive buzz.
The leading brands across various industries in Hong Kong are:
Source: YouGov. The top 10 brands by buzz...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is dedicated to improving its services and is now providing Better Thursdays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 03:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. The new logo at Singtel headquarters in Singapore.
Singtel recently introduced a refreshed brand identity, the first update in 16 years, with the tagline &amp;ldquo;Let’s make everyday better&amp;rdquo;. This signifies a new chapter in Singtel’s evolution beyond traditional telecommunications, expanding into multimedia and ICT services.
Chua Sock Koong, Singtel Group CEO, stated: “Singtel is a familiar name for many generations in Singapore. We are seen as a dependable and trusted brand at the forefront of technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Women in Saudi Arabia prefer Apple over Almarai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</guid><description>In 2019, Apple surpassed Almarai to secure the top position in YouGov MENA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Women’s Choice Brand Rankings&amp;rdquo; for Saudi Arabia. YouGov attributes Apple&amp;rsquo;s success to the buzz surrounding their new iPhones and Apple Watches, which resonated strongly with women.
Almarai&amp;rsquo;s decision to increase milk prices last year sparked consumer backlash, including calls for boycotts on social media. This negatively impacted the brand&amp;rsquo;s perception among women in Saudi Arabia, causing them to drop from first to fifth place in the rankings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Japanese consumers prefer domestic brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Japan.
YouGov Brandindex&amp;rsquo;s 2016 rankings reveal that Japanese brands are the most popular in Japan. Rakuten and Rakuten Card secured the top two spots, followed by clothing retailer Uniqlo in third place.
These brands were assessed using BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents if their exposure to the brand through advertising, news, or word of mouth in the past two weeks was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Singapore welcomed technology and locally-made brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Brand rankings for 2016.
The 2016 YouGov Brandindex rankings show that Singaporeans have a strong preference for both local and digital brands. Singapore Airlines, DBS bank, The Straits Times newspaper, WhatsApp, and the Apple iPhone (in the top three) all made the list. Other popular tech brands included Facebook, Google, e-commerce platform Qoo10, and YouTube.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score, which asks respondents whether their exposure to the brand in the previous two weeks, through advertising, news, or word of mouth, was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's Influential Brands are identified by Gen X</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Leading Brands Chosen by Generation X
A consumer-driven award program spearheaded by Brand Alliance has identified the top Influential Brands in Singapore, as determined by the upwardly mobile Generation X (Gen X) demographic.
Source: Brand Alliance. Brand Alliance presented the 2013 Influential Brands awards in November 2013. The 2014 Influential Brands conference is scheduled for November 10, 2014.
The survey highlighted over 100 prominent brands resonating with consumers in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines is the top-ranked brand in terms of recognition in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 02:01:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</guid><description>YouGov, a polling and research company, has released its mid-year rankings of the best brands in Singapore for 2015. Singapore Airlines secured the top spot, while Apple appeared twice on the list. Technology brands dominated the top 10, with WhatsApp, e-marketplace Qoo10, Facebook, and Google all making appearances.
Source: YouGov.
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex is a daily metric of public brand perception that monitors numerous brands across various sectors. The company compiles its data every six months and publishes the Best Brand Rankings globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BrandZ reports that the value of Indian brands has increased by 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 03:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/</guid><description>The combined value of India&amp;rsquo;s top brands has seen a significant increase of 33% over the past year, as reported by the second yearly BrandZ Top 50 Most Valuable Indian Brands ranking from WPP and Millward Brown. This growth rate is the most substantial among all BrandZ rankings in the past decade, surpassing the Global Top 100, China, Latin America, and Indonesia.
The current total worth of India&amp;rsquo;s Top 50 brands is US$92...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indonesian brands are at the top of the Brandindex 2016 rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 08:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Indonesia.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 reveal a diverse range of popular brands in Indonesia. Garuda, the national airline, claims the top spot, followed by tech giant Samsung and Danone&amp;rsquo;s mineral water brand, Aqua.
These brands were evaluated based on BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which gauges public perception by asking respondents whether their exposure to a brand in the past two weeks, whether through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth, was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>