<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Qatar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qatar/</link><description>Recent content in Qatar on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:42:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qatar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enjoy a complimentary stay at a luxurious hotel in Doha when you transit overnight with Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:42:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Doha skyline.
Qatar Airways has teamed up with Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA) to launch a stopover package, aiming to highlight Qatar as a top destination for travelers.
The package allows transit passengers to explore Doha with complimentary luxury hotel stays and transit visas. This unique deal is part of their larger &amp;ldquo;+Qatar&amp;rdquo; campaign, encouraging those passing through to consider extending their trip.
The promotion invites all Qatar Airways transit passengers to include Doha in their travel plans by offering a free one-night stay at some of the country’s top four- and five-star hotels in the capital...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways introduces more flights on the Abu Dhabi to Doha route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is commemorating a decade of service to Qatar this year by adding nine weekly flights to its Abu Dhabi-Doha route, strengthening its dedication to this important Gulf market.
Starting August 1, 2016, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s national airline will boost its weekly service to Qatar&amp;rsquo;s capital to 37 flights. These new daily morning and early evening departures on Thursdays and Saturdays offer more flexibility and convenience, catering to business travelers in both Abu Dhabi and Doha...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hamad International Airport introduces two innovative dining experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 13:07:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Spizzico is one of two new dining establishments in the North Node at Hamad International Airport.
Qatar Duty Free (QDF), working with global travel dining provider HMSHost International, has revealed two new dining options in the North Node of Hamad International Airport (HIA) in Doha.
Burger Federation, a relaxed dining spot, has opened in the North Node of HIA&amp;rsquo;s main terminal. This restaurant presents elevated burgers made with gourmet ingredients...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bahrain becomes a member of the Cruise Arabia Alliance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</guid><description>Bahrain has joined the Cruise Arabia Alliance, solidifying the organization&amp;rsquo;s presence in the region. Other members include Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Sharjah, Qatar, and Oman. The alliance promotes collaboration among its members to maintain high standards of service for cruise lines and their passengers.
This announcement took place at the Seatrade Middle East Cruise Forum in Doha, Qatar, hosted by the Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA). Alongside this news, Bahrain also shared that the 2015/2016 cruise season will include 68,000 passengers and 32 visits from major cruise lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ViaVii is providing assistance with travel arrangements in Qatar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viavii-is-providing-assistance-with-travel-arrangements-in-qatar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 06:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viavii-is-providing-assistance-with-travel-arrangements-in-qatar/</guid><description>Travelers visiting Qatar for leisure or major events can now create personalized itineraries through ViaVii, a platform for booking unique travel experiences.
ViaVii connects visitors with local experiences, such as Qatari cooking classes, art scene exploration, cultural storytelling, desert overnight stays, and heritage walks.
Rola Fayyad, founder and CEO of ViaVii, recognized that travelers to the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region often struggle to find experiences that allow for cultural immersion and personal connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viavii-is-providing-assistance-with-travel-arrangements-in-qatar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viavii-is-providing-assistance-with-travel-arrangements-in-qatar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Meliá Hotels opened at least 11 new locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</guid><description>Meliá Hotels International is adding at least 11 new hotels to its portfolio in 2015, including the Sol House Kuta Bali in Indonesia.
Source: Meliá Hotels website.
The recently opened 317-room Meliá Doha, which began welcoming guests in January, is the first Spanish hotel in Qatar. Located within Bin Samikh Tower, a prominent skyscraper in Doha&amp;rsquo;s West Bay district, the hotel enjoys a prime position on the Qatari coast.
The urban German brand, Innside by Meliá, is expanding its Middle Eastern presence with the upcoming Innside Dubai, a 125-room hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flights to Doha canceled by airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 10:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/</guid><description>The diplomatic break between several countries and Qatar on June 5th has resulted in canceled flights for airlines based in the involved nations. These countries, including Bahrain, Saudi Arabia, and the UAE, have severed air, land, and sea connections with Qatar.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, halted daily flights between Bahrain and Doha as of 11:59 PM local time on June 5, 2017, until further notice.
The final Gulf Air departure from Bahrain to Doha (GF530) left at 8:55 PM on June 5th, while the last flight from Doha to Bahrain (GF531) departed at 10:40 PM that same day (all times local)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enjoy the first 15 minutes of free Wi-Fi on Qatar Airways, courtesy of Ooredoo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo. The MoU was signed by (from left) Waleed Al Sayed, CEO, Ooredoo Qatar and Qatar Airways Group Chief Executive, His Excellency Akbar Al Baker.
Ooredoo and Qatar Airways have established a partnership where Ooredoo will sponsor Qatar Airways&amp;rsquo; in-flight Wi-Fi for the next three years. This agreement will make Ooredoo the sole sponsor for Wi-Fi on all Qatar Airways flights equipped with the service.
This sponsorship allows passengers to use their personal electronic devices to connect to the internet, check emails, and send SMS/MMS messages once the service is active during their flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>