<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Rate on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-rate/</link><description>Recent content in E-Rate on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-rate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>E-Rate Discounted Broadband Internet for Schools and Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</guid><description>Educational institutions and libraries are demanding high-speed internet, which has become essential for business, personal growth, and various types of learning. While most public resources have some internet access, there is increasing pressure to enhance speed for more users and advanced applications. The main obstacle is the cost.
Discounted Service is Available A government program offers discounts of 20% to 90% on broadband internet upgrades for most K-12 schools and libraries.</description></item></channel></rss>