<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Air China on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/air-china/</link><description>Recent content in Air China on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/air-china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Air China provides flights from Beijing to Vienna and Barcelona four days a week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:07:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</guid><description>As a prominent member of Star Alliance, the largest global airline network, Air China is actively expanding its flight schedule in Europe. The airline aims to bridge the gap in nonstop flights between East Asia and Barcelona and increase flight frequency between Beijing and Vienna.
Source: Air China
This new Beijing-Vienna-Barcelona route will be Air China&amp;rsquo;s 23rd European route, creating a direct link between East Asia and Central and Southern Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China have partnered on a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China, China&amp;rsquo;s national airline, have partnered to provide travelers with expanded options and easier connections. This agreement comes after Hawaiian launched its new non-stop service to Beijing, operating three times a week.
&amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to collaborate with Air China to expand our reach beyond Beijing, allowing our customers to conveniently explore more Chinese cities with a single ticket from Honolulu,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Dunkerley, Hawaiian Airlines President and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China and Kunming Airlines have initiated a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Source: Air China. The image shows representatives from Air China and Kunming Airlines at a signing ceremony for a codeshare agreement on September 3.
Air China and Kunming Airlines launched a codeshare partnership on September 15, 2014.
This agreement allows the airlines to link their respective networks through the city of Kunming. Air China will place its &amp;ldquo;CA&amp;rdquo; code on 26 Kunming Airlines routes, encompassing nearly 500 weekly flights. This expands Air China&amp;rsquo;s reach to various cities within Yunnan province and its neighboring areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China is providing a 50% discount on excess baggage fees to North America if paid in advance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</guid><description>Air China is the first Chinese airline to offer a prepaid excess baggage fee service for flights to North America. Travelers on Air China flights between Beijing and North America who anticipate exceeding their baggage allowance can now pay a discounted fee in advance. This service can be accessed through Air China ticketing offices globally or by calling their Member Services hotline.
Passengers who prepay for excess baggage will save 50% compared to airport rates, paying RMB 650 per piece or the equivalent in local currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>