<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lit Buildings on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lit-buildings/</link><description>Recent content in Lit Buildings on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lit-buildings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light.</description></item><item><title>1,000,000 Miles of Metro Ethernet Fiber And Growing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t assume Metro Ethernet is a small, insignificant service. XO Communications alone has a vast network of metro fiber, connecting thousands of buildings. And that&amp;rsquo;s just one provider, not even counting Ethernet over Copper options.
Metro Ethernet and its long-distance counterpart, Carrier Ethernet, are the future of telecommunications. The world is shifting from traditional circuit-based communication to packet-based IP networks. While your current internet might be a T1 line, your data likely transitions to an IP-based backbone at your provider&amp;rsquo;s location.</description></item><item><title>Choosing Dark Fiber vs Lit Fiber Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</guid><description>When applications require the bandwidth of fiber optic transmission, businesses face a choice: use existing &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber services or establish their own transport services using purchased or leased &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; fiber.
Deciding between these options involves weighing performance, cost, and installation time. Focusing solely on cost can lead to extended installation delays, potentially impacting operational needs. While a cost-effective solution might be suitable with ample planning time, immediate bandwidth demands may necessitate prioritizing availability over cost.</description></item><item><title>EoC and EoTDM Complement Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:35:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a significant disparity in bandwidth offered by traditional telecom services, particularly between smaller businesses and large corporations. Smaller businesses often rely on slower T1 lines (1.5 Mbps), while larger corporations enjoy significantly faster speeds (100-1000 times faster) through fiber optic connections.
However, technologies like Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and Ethernet over TDM (EoTDM) are bridging this gap by enabling a broader range of bandwidths on existing copper infrastructure. This allows for a smoother transition between T1 speeds and gigabit or even higher speeds.</description></item><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768).</description></item><item><title>Fiber Plus Copper Equals High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 03:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Our appetite for bandwidth is insatiable, growing daily. Businesses and consumers alike are hampered by insufficient bandwidth, preventing them from fully utilizing the latest technologies. Content providers and productivity vendors face similar hurdles, unable to deliver their full potential due to inadequate transport and last-mile bandwidth.
This scenario mirrors the early days of personal computers. For decades, limitations in processor speed, RAM, and hard disk capacity were constant challenges. While advancements in these areas have significantly minimized these bottlenecks, they haven&amp;rsquo;t entirely vanished.</description></item><item><title>100 Business Locations and 1 Bandwidth Bill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-business-locations-and-1-bandwidth-bill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 19:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-business-locations-and-1-bandwidth-bill/</guid><description>As businesses expand nationally or even globally, their network connections often develop haphazardly. Managing numerous individual contracts becomes a significant burden, and costs can spiral out of control. It&amp;rsquo;s highly likely that a more streamlined solution could save money.
Instead of tackling this challenge alone, seeking assistance from a specialized company is recommended. Trying to find the optimal combination of providers and service levels on your own is likely to result in an inefficient and costly setup.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Point of Presence Locator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting more bandwidth for your money, and finding an Ethernet Point of Presence (POP) Locator can help. But what is a POP and how can it save you money?
Essentially, a POP is a carrier&amp;rsquo;s service location, such as a central office with termination equipment for their fiber optic network. Think of it as a station for accessing high-speed data and voice services. POPs aren&amp;rsquo;t always in carrier offices; they can be in colocation centers, shared facilities housing servers and offering resources like bandwidth, security, and backup power.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Steal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</guid><description>Everyone appreciates a bargain, especially for telecommunications services. The current prices for Ethernet might even make you wonder if they&amp;rsquo;re legitimate. To see just how competitive these prices are, take a moment to compare Ethernet costs for your business locations.
The reason Ethernet services are so affordable now is due to rapid technological advancements. Until recently, traditional telephone company services were the only option. Today, competition has introduced alternatives that have completely changed the landscape.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Maps At Your Fingertips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</guid><description>You might want to upgrade to a faster internet service, but the cost of installing fiber optic cables might seem scary. How can you figure out if upgrading from copper to fiber is affordable?
The easiest way is to compare quotes from different providers in your area. A telecom broker, like Telarus, Inc., can gather these quotes for you quickly and easily. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a report with pricing from all major providers in your area.</description></item></channel></rss>