<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Payroll on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payroll/</link><description>Recent content in Payroll on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payroll/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Merchant Account Credit Card Processing Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</guid><description>Even the smallest businesses need a way to process credit card payments. Instead of making it a difficult process, choose a reliable credit card processing company to simplify things. Elite Processing Systems handles the complexities of electronic payments, allowing you to concentrate on your customers and what you offer. They provide a full range of financial services for small businesses, going above and beyond traditional credit card processing.
You might have heard of Elite Processing Systems (EPS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Solving the Mystery of the Missing Payroll 941 Table</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-mystery-of-the-missing-payroll-941-table/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-mystery-of-the-missing-payroll-941-table/</guid><description>The most crucial advice for payroll professionals is to prioritize backups before finalizing and issuing payroll. Recovering from payroll errors becomes significantly less painful with a readily available backup.
Beyond backups, two additional recommendations are:
Avoid posting payroll if printing or processing issues arise. Instead, cancel the process. The transactions can be included in a new run, eliminating the need to address a partial posting.
When using manual checks for adjustments or corrections, meticulous review of taxable wages and employer FICA taxes is critical...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-mystery-of-the-missing-payroll-941-table/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-mystery-of-the-missing-payroll-941-table/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TXSHANTY and Tax Sheltered Deductions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/txshanty-and-tax-sheltered-deductions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/txshanty-and-tax-sheltered-deductions/</guid><description>Coming back from vacation and jumping right into a busy week, I encountered a strange issue with a client&amp;rsquo;s FUTA and SUTA taxable wages in their system. Here&amp;rsquo;s the situation:
We had a deduction set up initially as non-tax-sheltered. Later, this was changed to be tax-sheltered with specific tax boxes checked. While the general setup reflected this change, the existing deduction records for employees did not automatically update to reflect the new tax-sheltered status...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/txshanty-and-tax-sheltered-deductions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/txshanty-and-tax-sheltered-deductions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Did you forget about FUTA? Falling behind on SUTA? Take care of it immediately!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find payroll errors, particularly with FUTA and SUTA taxes, even with careful planning. Issues arise when pay codes aren&amp;rsquo;t correctly classified for these taxes at setup or when employee payroll details are changed. Unlike other taxes, FUTA and SUTA discrepancies aren&amp;rsquo;t immediately obvious because they are calculated during period-end processing.
Manual correction of such errors, especially across multiple payrolls or employees, is tedious and error-prone. It involves reversing incorrect entries and re-entering them with the correct FUTA and SUTA classifications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tax-Free Holiday!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 01:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</guid><description>Last week, a client reached out because their employees&amp;rsquo; state taxes weren&amp;rsquo;t being calculated correctly, despite seemingly accurate setup in the system.
Everything appeared properly configured: state tax assignments, default state codes, pay codes subject to state tax, and transaction entries. However, upon examining the build and calculate reports, the state tax was present in the build report but missing from the calculation. The culprit? The default filing status for that state&amp;rsquo;s tax code was set to 0%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Remember to bring your keys (and report your taxable wages)!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 08:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, there have been some recurring support cases related to taxable wages on the manual payroll checks window, particularly when starting with initial balances. Here are a few common issues:
Federal taxes are accurate, but Federal wages are incorrect. FICA/S and/or FICA/M are accurate, but the corresponding wages are incorrect. Federal wages don&amp;rsquo;t match FICA/M or FICA/S wages, and the reason is unclear. Let&amp;rsquo;s break down how these issues occur:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I may not be Sherlock Holmes, but I can help you find missing deductions and benefits.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-may-not-be-sherlock-holmes-but-i-can-help-you-find-missing-deductions-and-benefits/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-may-not-be-sherlock-holmes-but-i-can-help-you-find-missing-deductions-and-benefits/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m in Denver this week providing training on reporting tools for Microsoft Dynamics GP, such as Report Writer, SmartList Builder, and SQL Reporting Services. A client asked for a report to identify employees not set up for Denver&amp;rsquo;s occupational tax. We use a specific benefit and deduction code in the system (&amp;ldquo;head tax&amp;rdquo;) instead of the standard local tax functionality.
Finding employees who are set up is simple. The challenge is identifying those who aren&amp;rsquo;t, especially when they have other benefits and deductions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-may-not-be-sherlock-holmes-but-i-can-help-you-find-missing-deductions-and-benefits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-may-not-be-sherlock-holmes-but-i-can-help-you-find-missing-deductions-and-benefits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Summary of Payroll Audit SmartList POW!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/</guid><description>Last week, I was asked to create a report that summarized payroll amounts and hours by pay code. This report would be used as a final check before printing paychecks, ensuring accuracy after payroll calculation.
Using SmartList Builder, we created the report in minutes! Here&amp;rsquo;s how:
Navigate to the SmartList Builder: Microsoft Dynamics GP &amp;raquo; Tools &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder. Input a SmartList ID, Name, and Item Name. Select Product: Microsoft Dynamics GP, Series: Payroll...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Incorporating Employer Tax Fields into Payroll Check Register</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incorporating-employer-tax-fields-into-payroll-check-register/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incorporating-employer-tax-fields-into-payroll-check-register/</guid><description>This month, we encountered a strange issue. A client reported a discrepancy between the payroll Check Register printed immediately after payroll posting and the same report reprinted later using Reports-Payroll-Reprint Journals-Check Register.
Both the standard and reprinted Check Register reports usually combine Employer FICA taxes into a single &amp;ldquo;Employer FICA Owed&amp;rdquo; field. However, the client&amp;rsquo;s reports displayed this amount split into two additional fields: &amp;ldquo;Employer FICA/Social Security&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Employer FICA/Medicare.&amp;rdquo; Since these fields aren&amp;rsquo;t standard, we knew the reports were customized, which we verified through Microsoft Dynamics GP customization tools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incorporating-employer-tax-fields-into-payroll-check-register/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incorporating-employer-tax-fields-into-payroll-check-register/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Basic: Arrears Deductions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/basic-arrears-deductions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 20:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/basic-arrears-deductions/</guid><description>When new software features are released, they are often overlooked or considered too complex for users to implement. One valuable feature that deserves attention is Deductions in Arrears (DIA), introduced in Payroll Extensions for GP 10.0. This feature simplifies payroll processing when dealing with part-time or seasonal employees whose earnings may not cover their deductions.
DIA automatically tracks any deductions that are not fully paid due to insufficient wages. It then recovers these arrears in subsequent payrolls until the obligation is settled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/basic-arrears-deductions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/basic-arrears-deductions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enjoy the Payroll FICA Fun!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 01:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sharing Michael Lupro&amp;rsquo;s recent blog post about the changes to FICA rates. The post highlights the different rates for employees and employers, which may require manual adjustments in Great Plains until a system update is available to address this discrepancy.
http://btosteam.blogspot.com/2011/01/manual-employer-fica-tax-calculations.html..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avoid Payroll and Tips at all costs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of handling payroll, tips, sales tax, and analytical accounting, I recently discovered something interesting in Dynamics GP. Tax-sheltered deductions (TSAs) can affect how tips are taxed. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at an example:
We have Adam Smith, an employee paid hourly with a rate of $15/hr. He also earns tips and has a tax-sheltered health deduction of $10 per pay period, exempt from federal and FICA taxes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Articles on Payroll Support that I Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/articles-on-payroll-support-that-i-love/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/articles-on-payroll-support-that-i-love/</guid><description>Most payroll problems stem from tax setup within the payroll module. Here are two helpful articles about taxability in payroll:
Resolving Payroll Tax Overwithholding http://support.microsoft.com/kb/858712
This valuable resource outlines three steps to fix over-withheld taxes:
Issue refunds for the over-withheld amount. Rectify the tax summary information by adjusting total taxes and taxable wages. Modify the pay code used for reimbursing the taxes. Reconciling Federal Wage Discrepancies Between Form 941 and the Payroll Summary Report http://support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/articles-on-payroll-support-that-i-love/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/articles-on-payroll-support-that-i-love/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing the minimum amount for garnishments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-the-minimum-amount-for-garnishments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 06:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-the-minimum-amount-for-garnishments/</guid><description>It can feel overwhelming trying to understand the numerous ways to calculate garnishments across different agencies. While the standard garnishment feature in Dynamics GP works well for single garnishments, more complex scenarios with multiple garnishments often necessitate the use of the Greenshades Garnishments module.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what Dynamics GP can handle independently. A recent example involved these requirements:
The initial $150 of the employee&amp;rsquo;s eligible earnings are exempt from garnishment. If earnings fall between $150 and $200, only the amount exceeding $150 is subject to garnishment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-the-minimum-amount-for-garnishments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-the-minimum-amount-for-garnishments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions About Year-End Payroll</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 23:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</guid><description>This information comes from a Microsoft and Terry Heley webinar and addresses common questions about FICA rate changes:
Q: I already applied the 2011 tax tables before creating the year-end wage file. What should I do? A: Change the FICA/Social Security tax rate back to 6.2% in the Payroll Tax setup. Then, create the year-end wage file and reset the rate to the 2011 value of 4.2%.
Q: Can I rebuild the year-end wage file using the above method if I already processed 2011 payrolls?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick Payroll Data Entry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-payroll-data-entry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 02:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-payroll-data-entry/</guid><description>During a recent payroll implementation and training, I was inspired to share some of my favorite tips for quicker payroll entry in Dynamics GP.
#1: Utilizing Payroll Mass Transaction Entry Many users overlook the Mass Entry window in Dynamics GP (Transactions&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Mass Entry), but it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly useful. Begin by choosing or creating a Batch ID for the transactions. Then, select a pay code, deduction, or benefit, and specify the date range and employee range using criteria like employee ID, class, department, or position...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-payroll-data-entry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-payroll-data-entry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exciting Updates Ahead for HR and PR in Dynamics GP 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic to hear about the exciting updates coming to the Human Resources and Payroll modules in Dynamics GP 2013, as shared by Terry Heley from Microsoft. Here are a few highlights:
A significant improvement is the direct integration of tools for managing deductions, benefits, and pay code modifiers. This user-friendly approach will make it much easier to modify pay codes, deduction codes, and benefit codes, enhancing user satisfaction.
Another valuable enhancement for users is the ability to choose whether or not to print alignments on checks and earnings statements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Excelity Global will be providing HR and payroll services in Indonesia through Cekindo Bisnis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 07:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</guid><description>Excelity Global Solutions, the largest payroll service provider in Asia, has partnered with Cekindo Bisnis Grup to offer its services in Indonesia. Excelity Global, which operates in 19 countries across Asia Pacific, provides payroll outsourcing and human capital management cloud services.
Indonesia, with a large SME market, presents a significant opportunity for Excelity. SMEs make up over 98% of companies in Indonesia and contribute significantly to the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP.
By collaborating with Cekindo, a provider of market-entry and corporate secretarial services, Excelity aims to simplify HR and payroll processes for businesses in Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Directly depositing direct deposit information</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/directly-depositing-direct-deposit-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/directly-depositing-direct-deposit-information/</guid><description>When implementing payroll for smaller companies (fewer than 250 employees), manual data entry might be acceptable and even beneficial for data accuracy. However, with larger implementations, like my current project involving over 1500 employees across three companies, manual entry isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible.
While integration tools help import most payroll data, direct deposit information requires extra caution. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to avoid errors in account and routing numbers, making manual entry risky. Therefore, I use table imports for this specific data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/directly-depositing-direct-deposit-information/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/directly-depositing-direct-deposit-information/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where oh where could my overtime be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-oh-where-could-my-overtime-be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-oh-where-could-my-overtime-be/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m seeking advice on a specific overtime calculation issue in Dynamics GP. While GP can calculate overtime based on exceeding a set number of hours within a pay period, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t consider daily or weekly overtime rules common in many locations.
For example, with biweekly pay and an 80-hour overtime threshold, exceeding 80 hours triggers overtime. However, GP doesn&amp;rsquo;t recognize situations where an employee works a 14-hour day within an 80-hour pay period, which could still qualify for overtime pay in many jurisdictions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-oh-where-could-my-overtime-be/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-oh-where-could-my-overtime-be/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Payroll System Continues to Grow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 11:48:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</guid><description>Over the last few months, many clients have asked me about additional modules for Payroll in Dynamics GP. While the base payroll module works well, companies seeking better efficiency and streamlined processes are looking for ways to expand its capabilities. For example, they might need to automate a previously manual process or switch from paper-based delivery to electronic methods like email or portals.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to share some options for improving payroll processing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>