<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EYE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eye/</link><description>Recent content in EYE on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eye/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography.</description></item><item><title>Bourjois eyeshadows are available in matte, pearl, and shimmer finishes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bourjois-eyeshadows-are-available-in-matte-pearl-and-shimmer-finishes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bourjois-eyeshadows-are-available-in-matte-pearl-and-shimmer-finishes/</guid><description>Launched in 1912, Bourjois makeup is recognized for its signature small round compacts. The brand&amp;rsquo;s newest eyeshadows come in these iconic compacts and are offered in a range of matte, pearl, and shimmer finishes.
The eight new eyeshadows glide onto eyelids smoothly when applied dry. If applied damp, the eyeshadows can be used to create precise lines, similar to eyeliner.
01 INGENUDE
This shade is a delicate, slightly pearly off-white. It can be used to even out the look of eyelids.</description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM.</description></item></channel></rss>