<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet WAN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-wan/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet WAN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-wan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lock In Telecom Cost Savings For Next Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</guid><description>As we wrap up the year and analyze our performance, it&amp;rsquo;s common to wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re overspending on business operations, especially networking and telecom. A thorough market analysis often reveals opportunities to secure better rates for the same services. By doing this now, you can lock in savings for the entire next year.
Why are such savings possible? Primarily, increased competition and technological advancements. Previously, businesses were limited to local telephone companies for their communication needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit to 10 Gigabit to 100 Gigabit WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business operations transition to the cloud and remote work becomes increasingly common, the demand for robust Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth has surged. Fortunately, providers offer excellent solutions for establishing high-bandwidth connections between locations and to the internet.
Fiber Optic Ethernet WAN
Fiber optic connectivity has become the leading choice for business bandwidth. Businesses still relying on older technologies like T1 lines, ISDN PRI, or DS3 bandwidth may be facing limitations and nearing obsolescence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Better Than a T3 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 voice and data lines, once a reliable option for businesses, now offer insufficient speed (45 Mbps) for modern demands, which often exceed 100 Mbps. Businesses today require significantly faster connections, with some even seeking speeds beyond 10 Gbps. If you&amp;rsquo;re still using a T3 line, you might find better bandwidth options at a similar or lower cost.
What is a T3 Line?
Developed by Bell Labs, the T3 line was designed to carry numerous simultaneous phone conversations, a function it still serves in certain settings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How MPLS Network Bursting Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 19:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>The standard method of ordering bandwidth for last-mile connections or MPLS networks involves committing to a specific rate or line speed. For instance, a T1 line provides a constant 1.5 Mbps, while a 10 Mbps Ethernet service delivers precisely that speed. In multi-tenant networks like MPLS VPNs, you purchase a committed information rate representing the maximum speed your connection will achieve. However, what happens if business needs change or your initial estimate is inaccurate?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Will Light Your Building</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</guid><description>Ethernet has become the preferred option for WAN (Wide Area Networking), moving beyond its established role in LAN networks. It makes sense to extend your LAN using the same standards both internally and for connecting to remote locations or the internet.
A key advantage is cost-effectiveness as bandwidth needs grow. While a 1.54 Mbps T1 line might cost around $450 per month ($292.20 per Mbps), a 45 Mbps DS3 connection could cost $5,000 per month ($111...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber WAN is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that your business needs the speed of fiber optic WAN service to ensure cloud-based applications are responsive and your team stays productive. However, you may have struggled to find this service in the past. It&amp;rsquo;s time to try again.
Why Is Fiber More Accessible Now?
Fiber optic used to be a rare and costly option limited to large corporations. You had to rely on the telephone company and hope they serviced your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>