<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Road Warriors on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/road-warriors/</link><description>Recent content in Road Warriors on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:56:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/road-warriors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FAX On The Run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fax-on-the-run/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fax-on-the-run/</guid><description>Fax machines have long been the go-to for urgent business documents, with large companies utilizing massive machines and smaller offices relying on all-in-one devices. However, these machines share a common limitation: they are tethered to a physical location.
This restriction is eliminated with internet faxing, which allows sending and receiving faxes from any location with internet access, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a cafe, hotel, airport, or even using mobile broadband. This technology is readily accessible at an affordable price.</description></item><item><title>Take Your Office PC With You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</guid><description>Mobile professionals often rely on their laptops but might find themselves needing files left on their office desktops. Traveling long distances back for these files isn&amp;rsquo;t always feasible.
Imagine accessing your office desktop from anywhere, anytime. This eliminates the worry of having the right files and removes the need for duplicates. Your laptop and a special application are all you need to make any computer your office computer.
GoToMyPC is a remote access software, or KVM application, that allows this.</description></item><item><title>Your Cell Phone IS Your Business Phone System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-your-business-phone-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-your-business-phone-system/</guid><description>Why invest in a large, expensive office phone system when you&amp;rsquo;re an independent professional constantly on the move? If your work revolves around sales or consulting, your mobile phone might be the only phone system you need.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense for clients to call your office if you&amp;rsquo;re rarely there. When they call your mobile number, you&amp;rsquo;re reachable regardless of location. You can always let calls go to voicemail, eliminating the need to rush back to the office just to check messages.</description></item></channel></rss>