<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Remain on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remain/</link><description>Recent content in Remain on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 05:40:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>If you are a voter who is undecided or uncertain, here is why you should consider remaining in the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 05:40:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
As the referendum campaign concludes, undecided voters should consider the arguments for remaining in the European Union. This piece outlines the reasons for staying, addressing counter-arguments from the Leave campaign.
Why Remain?
Staying in the EU offers several advantages: economic benefits, security, improved workers&amp;rsquo; rights, and environmental protection. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine each.
Economic Benefits
EU membership grants the UK access to the world&amp;rsquo;s largest market, along with trade deals with 50 additional countries.</description></item><item><title>Briefing 3: Is there a lack of democracy in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, Middlesex University
Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The European Union is frequently criticized for being undemocratic or suffering from a &amp;ldquo;democratic deficit.&amp;rdquo; One common assertion is that all EU decisions are made by the unelected bureaucrats of the European Commission. This post will demonstrate why this criticism is fundamentally flawed. It stems from a misunderstanding of both the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s actual powers within the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes and how the European Commission is appointed.</description></item></channel></rss>