<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KPMG on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kpmg/</link><description>Recent content in KPMG on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kpmg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asian venture capital investments have remained stable in the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Venture capital (VC) investment experienced a global decline in 2016, following a strong 2015, according to the Venture Pulse Q4 2016 report by KPMG Enterprise.
Global VC investment decreased by 24% year-over-year, totaling US$127.4 billion. Despite a promising start to the year, investor confidence waned in the latter half of 2016 due to uncertainties in the market. Events like Brexit and the US presidential election furthered this uncertainty.
Chia Tek Yew, Head of Financial Services Advisory at KPMG in Singapore, noted that this period of uncertainty allowed VCs to refine their portfolios, focus on high-potential deals, and guide their portfolio companies towards further growth.</description></item><item><title>KPMG has identified gaps in global corporate responsibility reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</guid><description>A 2015 KPMG study reveals inconsistencies in how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies report their carbon emissions, making it challenging to compare their performance. While 80% of the top 250 companies address carbon in their reports, the information provided varies significantly. For instance, only half declare carbon reduction goals, and among those, two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t explain their rationale.
The reported emissions types also differ. Most companies (84%) report emissions from their operations and purchased power (79%), but only half include supply chain emissions.</description></item><item><title>The KPMG index assesses the capacity of 140 countries to adapt to change</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</guid><description>According to the 2019 KPMG Change Readiness Index (CRI), countries in the Asia Pacific region are generally showing improvement in their approaches to climate change. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose two spots to number 2, while Taiwan jumped 18 places.
Published twice a year, the CRI is now in its fourth year. It ranks 140 countries* based on their preparedness for and response to major change events. This edition focuses on the capabilities countries need to effectively combat climate change and minimize related risks.</description></item></channel></rss>