<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hotspot on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hotspot/</link><description>Recent content in Hotspot on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hotspot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Happn shows that the east is the ideal location for social gatherings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happn-shows-that-the-east-is-the-ideal-location-for-social-gatherings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happn-shows-that-the-east-is-the-ideal-location-for-social-gatherings/</guid><description>Source: Happn. The top 10 Happn hotspots.
For those seeking romantic connections in Singapore, heading east might be the key. Happn, a dating app that connects individuals who have crossed paths, has identified the top ten locations in Singapore where users are most likely to find potential matches. With a presence in over 40 major cities globally, including Hong Kong, Happn boasts more than 22.5 million users.
The app utilizes real-time geolocation technology to show users individuals they&amp;rsquo;ve been near, within a 250-meter radius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happn-shows-that-the-east-is-the-ideal-location-for-social-gatherings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happn-shows-that-the-east-is-the-ideal-location-for-social-gatherings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transfer files from your phone without using up your mobile data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</guid><description>Xender, a Chinese app, simplifies phone-based file sharing without incurring mobile data costs using peer-to-peer technology.
For device-to-device transfers, Xender creates a local Wi-Fi hotspot that nearby users can join. This allows for the seamless sharing of photos, music, files, and apps between phones, proving particularly useful when upgrading to a new device. Xender boasts unlimited file sizes, cross-platform compatibility, and transfer speeds up to 50 times faster than Bluetooth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transfer-files-from-your-phone-without-using-up-your-mobile-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>