<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Trade on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-trade/</link><description>Recent content in Free Trade on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-trade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Negotiating the future relationship between the UK and EU: the EU's mandate for negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Thanks to Georgina Wright, of the Institute for Government, for a &amp;rsquo;track changes&amp;rsquo; version of the negotiation mandate. The usual disclaimer applies.
This week, the UK-EU future relationship negotiation process progressed. The EU Council approved the negotiation mandate, differing from the initial proposal. This post provides an updated analysis, comparing the final mandate to the political declaration, highlighting differences between the EU and UK&amp;rsquo;s positions that are expected to make negotiations difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>