<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Allister on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/allister/</link><description>Recent content in Allister on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/allister/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Allister Round 2: Exploring the depths of UK constitutional law in the Mariana Trench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD student, Queen’s University Belfast School of Law
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikicommons
Introduction
It&amp;rsquo;s a common observation in UK constitutional law that complex issues rarely have simple solutions. Instead, they often result in multiple, overlapping interpretations. This is certainly the case with the recent Allister and others v Prime Minister and others [2022] NICA 15 ruling from the Northern Ireland Court of Appeal (NICA). It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this case is headed to the UK Supreme Court on appeal, ensuring further analysis and discussion.</description></item><item><title>Perhaps we are drawn to the suffering: The conclusion of the legal battle over the Northern Ireland Protocol.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Law Professor, University of Newcastle
Photo credit: ChrisVTG photography, via Wikicommons media
In October 2019, the UK government, led by Boris Johnson, reached a Withdrawal Agreement with the EU. This agreement encompassed a Northern Ireland Protocol iteration based on closely aligned rules governing goods between Northern Ireland and the EU. Notably, no comparable provisions addressed goods regulations for Great Britain. In January 2020, Westminster passed legislation to enact this agreement.</description></item></channel></rss>