<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MENA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mena/</link><description>Recent content in MENA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mena/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Watching 100 trends in the MENA region for 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:22:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: JWT website. Cover for the report.
J. Walter Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Middle East and Africa Innovation Group recently published their sixth yearly consumer trends report, focusing on the MENA region for 2018. Future 100 Trends and Change to Watch in MENA highlights the significant themes that are changing how consumers in Egypt, North Africa, Lebanon, Jordan, the Gulf, and Saudi Arabia live and consume.
A key takeaway from the Future 100 MENA Report is that Middle Eastern consumers are seeing themselves more as global citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fujifilm has launched the X100T premium compact camera in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Fujifilm has introduced the X100T, a high-end compact camera succeeding the successful X100S, to the Middle East market.
Source: Fujifilm. The X100T is available
in black and silver.
&amp;ldquo;The X100, launched in March 2011, established a new market for premium compact cameras. A year later, the second-generation X100S was released, featuring an updated sensor, processor, and an advanced Hybrid Viewfinder,&amp;rdquo; stated Yuta Kawamura, Marketing Manager for the electronic imaging division at Fujifilm Middle East &amp;amp; Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai hotels are at the top of the list of top meeting hotels according to Cvent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 03:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</guid><description>Dubai, UAE, boasts seven out of the top 10 hotels in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region for Meetings, Incentives, Conferences, and Exhibitions (MICE), according to a new ranking. The list was released by Cvent, a leading technology provider for meetings, events, and hospitality.
These rankings are based on data from the Cvent Supplier Network (CSN), a comprehensive database with information on over 260,000 hotels, resorts, and event spaces in more than 175 countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>