<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Palm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/palm/</link><description>Recent content in Palm on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 11:59:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/palm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Atlantis Dubai offers a diverse selection of options for iftar dining</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</guid><description>This Ramadan, Atlantis is offering three unique dining experiences for iftar and suhoor: Asateer, Nobu, and Kaleidoscope, each providing a taste of Arabian culture.
Asateer, meaning &amp;ldquo;legends&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, provides a traditional tent setting overlooking the Arabian Sea, accommodating up to 900 guests. A customary iftar buffet is available at sunset for AED195, featuring Ramadan juices and followed by an à la carte suhoor menu starting at 9:30 pm.
During iftar, guests can enjoy classic dishes like foul moudammas and balila, complemented by a variety of Ramadan beverages such as jallab, laban, kamr al deen, and karkadeh.</description></item><item><title>Cirque de Cuisine: The Festive Edition returns to Atlantis, The Palm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</guid><description>Source: Atlantis, The Palm. Cirque de Cuisine.
The Cirque de Cuisine event will launch Dubai&amp;rsquo;s holiday season with a Winter Wonderland theme. Held on December 6th at The Avenues in Atlantis, The Palm, this all-you-can-eat-and-drink event offers early bird tickets starting at AED495 for four hours of holiday festivities.
Cirque de Cuisine gives diners the opportunity to sample signature dishes, live cooking stations, buffets, drinks, and live entertainment at a variety of restaurants.</description></item></channel></rss>