<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Non-Discrimination on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/non-discrimination/</link><description>Recent content in Non-Discrimination on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/non-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the special status of minority religious groups, stating "You are all individuals!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law, University College London
The Court of Justice recently issued five significant decisions regarding Directive 2000/78&amp;rsquo;s provisions on religious discrimination, a topic it hadn&amp;rsquo;t addressed in many years. This surge in rulings signifies the Court&amp;rsquo;s renewed focus on this area.
The latest case originated from Austria&amp;rsquo;s Supreme Court and concerned a law granting paid holidays on Good Friday to members of three minor Christian denominations, excluding others.</description></item><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church).</description></item><item><title>The European Commission's reflections on the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities focus more on praise than introspection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:44:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-reflections-on-the-un-convention-on-the-rights-of-persons-with-disabilities-focus-more-on-praise-than-introspection/</guid><description>Dr. Charlotte O’Brien, Lecturer in Law, York Law School, University of York
Over seven years after signing the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities (UNCRPD) and over three years after its conclusion, how effectively is the EU safeguarding the disability rights outlined within it? The European Commission claims it is doing very well. In fact, it suggests the UNCRPD was hardly necessary, as the EU was already on the right track.</description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions on cases involving obesity and discrimination laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 03:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</guid><description>Katharina O Cathaoir
The European Court of Justice, in its decision on Kaltoft, determined that obesity itself is not a protected characteristic under EU employment law, nor is it automatically a disability. However, the Court acknowledged that the EU Directive prohibiting workplace discrimination based on disability might apply in certain situations. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this ruling specifically pertains to employment disputes, as EU law does not address disability discrimination outside of the workplace.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides clarification on when employers can prohibit headscarves in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Ronan McCrea, University College London
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s initial significant decisions concerning workplace policies limiting religious symbols were issued four years ago in the G4S and Micropole cases. These rulings addressed the compatibility of these policies with the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment (Directive 2000/78).
In these decisions, the Court&amp;rsquo;s Grand Chamber determined that requiring employees to maintain visible religious neutrality constituted indirect rather than direct discrimination, provided this policy was uniformly applied to all religions or beliefs.</description></item></channel></rss>