<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-NNI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-nni/</link><description>Recent content in E-NNI on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-nni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards.</description></item><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Networks Interconnect in Arizona</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</guid><description>Ethernet is quickly gaining popularity as the preferred protocol for metropolitan and wide area networks. It&amp;rsquo;s predicted that IP networks using standard Ethernet services will eventually replace the outdated Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). The main obstacle to this is the fragmented nature of Ethernet service providers, comprising a mix of established and newer carriers with limited service areas. However, E-NNI technology is emerging as the solution to connect these disparate networks.</description></item><item><title>GTT Expands Ethernet Footprint With PacketExchange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</guid><description>GTT, a global telecommunications company, is expanding its Ethernet services globally by acquiring PacketExchange, an Ethernet provider. PacketExchange, based in London, boasts a substantial 10 Gigabit fiber optic IP network spanning Europe, the United States, and Asia, largely acquired through its acquisition of MZIMA Networks in 2010. This combined infrastructure offers private line services, MPLS, VPLS networking, and peering capabilities.
This acquisition highlights the growing dominance of Carrier Ethernet in telecommunications.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Business-grade Carrier Ethernet services are gaining popularity. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about Ethernet and its potential benefits, read on.
Ethernet dominates as a LAN protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable how quickly it outpaced competitors. Switched Ethernet is nearly ubiquitous. A similar shift is happening with telecom services, moving from traditional circuit-switched technologies to packet-switched networks that align better with modern devices. Ethernet is poised to become the standard for both metropolitan and long-distance networks.</description></item><item><title>Extending Ethernet over MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Ethernet has transitioned from a local network protocol to a preferred choice for metropolitan area networks. Its benefits include easy integration with wired and wireless networks, scalable bandwidth without equipment upgrades, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom options. This begs the question: can Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s success in LAN and MAN be replicated in WAN?
Ethernet WAN is gaining popularity, particularly among businesses with geographically dispersed sites. Dedicated point-to-point Ethernet connections are possible, but Ethernet over MPLS presents a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item></channel></rss>