<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tokyo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tokyo/</link><description>Recent content in Tokyo on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tokyo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach.</description></item><item><title>Aeromexico introduces an additional flight connecting Shanghai and Mexico City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Aeromexico will expand its service between Shanghai and Mexico City to include a third weekly flight on Sundays. This increase will bring the total number of seats available on the route to over 1,500 each week. The flights, operated by Boeing 777 aircraft, accommodate 277 passengers with 49 business class seats and 228 economy seats.
Each Aeromexico flight features personal entertainment systems, increased passenger space, and lie-flat seats in Clase Premier, its business class section.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has identified Tokyo, Singapore, and Dubai as some of the top choices in its Cities Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</guid><description>Singapore at night.
The travel website TripAdvisor recently published its second annual Cities Survey, which collected data from over 54,000 user reviews. The survey evaluated cities worldwide based on traveler feedback.
Tokyo received the highest ranking for providing the best overall travel experience. It also earned top scores for its helpful residents, taxi services, public transportation, and clean streets. Tokyo ranked among the top ten cities in 13 out of 16 survey categories.</description></item><item><title>The KOGEI Future Forward exhibition at Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store showcases the work of 15 artists</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</guid><description>The Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a contemporary art exhibition, KOGEI Future Forward, from February 15 to 20, 2017. The exhibition showcases the work of 15 Japanese artists, highlighting kogei as a unique form of Japanese fine art.
Kogei, meaning &amp;ldquo;craft,&amp;rdquo; emerged during the Meiji Period (1868-1912) and has evolved over time to gain recognition as fine art. This exhibition offers a fresh perspective on kogei, curated by Yuji Akimoto, a renowned art professor and museum director.</description></item><item><title>The Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo has officially opened its doors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-marunouchi-tokyo-has-officially-opened-its-doors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-marunouchi-tokyo-has-officially-opened-its-doors/</guid><description>Source: The Ascott Limited. The lobby, Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo.
CapitaLand&amp;rsquo;s serviced residence branch, The Ascott Limited, opened its first high-end serviced residence in Japan on March 30, 2017, under its top brand, Ascott The Residence.
The 130-unit Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo is in the desirable Marunouchi-Otemachi district. It&amp;rsquo;s part of a mixed-use development with offices and close to notable attractions like the Imperial Palace East Gardens and the Ginza area. The residence provides convenient access to Otemachi Station, a major Tokyo subway hub served by five lines, with connections to the Shinkansen bullet train available from nearby Tokyo Station.</description></item><item><title>Belstaff has opened its flagship store in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Belstaff.
The renowned British heritage brand, Belstaff, recently celebrated the grand opening of its flagship store in Tokyo, Japan. Situated within the expansive Ginza Six retail complex, the new store occupies a prime location within this 47,000 square meter shopping destination. This strategic move underscores Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s growing presence in the Japanese market and its commitment to global retail expansion.
Upon its debut, the Tokyo flagship presents a curated selection of Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s offerings, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s complete menswear collection and, for the first time in Tokyo, its womenswear line.</description></item></channel></rss>