<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CA Technologies on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ca-technologies/</link><description>Recent content in CA Technologies on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ca-technologies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CA Technologies is offering a free migration tool for Windows XP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</guid><description>If you need to upgrade from Windows XP, there&amp;rsquo;s a free tool that can help. Developed by CA Technologies, CA Desktop Migration Manager (CA DMM) is a software solution designed to manage, upgrade, and maintain laptops and desktops. It can also migrate a Windows XP computer to a more secure operating system.
&amp;ldquo;Since Microsoft is no longer providing ongoing technical support and security updates for Windows XP, our customers are exposed to vulnerabilities and significant risks,&amp;rdquo; says Vic Mankotia, VP of Solution Strategy for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IIJ Global Solutions Singapore is now providing cloud monitoring services using CA Nimsoft Monitor for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 15:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>IIJ Global Solutions Singapore, a subsidiary of a major Japanese internet and network solutions company, Internet Initiative Japan (IIJ) Group, has incorporated CA Nimsoft Monitor from CA Technologies into its cloud solutions for small and medium-sized businesses.
This addition allows IIJ Global Solutions Singapore to offer its clients extensive 24/7 monitoring and reporting services. Using this unified monitoring platform from CA Nimsoft Monitor, users can optimize resources, improve planning and investments, and reduce time spent on troubleshooting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CA Technologies believes that Asia has the potential to become a central hub of global innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</guid><description>Lionel Lim, President for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies, believes the significant data exchange happening within Asia indicates the region&amp;rsquo;s potential to become a leading force in innovation.
During a Chinese New Year event in Singapore, Lim stated that Asia is capable of matching Europe and the US in driving innovation. He emphasized that the focus is shifting from cost reduction to accelerating innovation.
Lim highlighted four key areas for innovation and differentiation: improving user experience, ensuring convenient, fast, and secure data access, utilizing technologies that boost business growth, and strengthening IT skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If apps don't offer speed, simplicity, and security, consumers will not hesitate to abandon them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</guid><description>Source: CA Technologies infographic.
People are pickier than ever about the apps they use, so businesses that don&amp;rsquo;t offer a good app experience could lose a significant portion of their customers. A regional study* sponsored by CA Technologies shows that mobile and desktop applications in the Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) region have become key to earning customer loyalty.
Software: the New Battleground for Brand Loyalty – A survey of 1,449 consumers and 259 business decision-makers across five APJ nations pinpointed three major factors influencing the customer experience: Source: CA Technologies infographic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CA Technologies reports that CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has been successful in its first 100 days</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:46:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</guid><description>CA Technologies, a provider of IT management solutions for securing and managing complex IT environments, has released a new version of its freemium product, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap. This solution helps businesses support agile business services.
Since its release 100 days ago, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has seen 5,000 downloads from SMBs, Fortune 1000 companies, and IT service providers across 147 countries. The full-featured version of CA Nimsoft Monitor shares the same codebase and proactively monitors servers, networks, storage, databases, and applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>