<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Display on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/display/</link><description>Recent content in Display on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:30:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/display/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LG will be showcasing its newest Ultra monitors at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</guid><description>At CES, LG Electronics (LG) will showcase its newest Ultra monitors, featuring UltraWide models for productivity and UltraGear monitors designed for gaming.
2019 LG UltraWide Monitor
Source: LG. The new 49&amp;quot; UltraWide monitor.
Known for its innovation in the UltraWide monitor market, LG&amp;rsquo;s latest 49-inch model (49WL95) offers a 32:9 aspect ratio curved screen designed to enhance productivity. Its size is equivalent to two 27-inch Quad High Definition displays combined, with a resolution of 5,120 x 1,440 and 108 pixels per inch for clarity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BenQ interactive flat panel simplifies education and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</guid><description>BenQ, a well-known name in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, introduces the RP750K, a new interactive flat panel (IFP). This innovative IFP offers a comprehensive solution by combining a 4K Ultra HD whiteboard with annotation and collaboration tools.
The RP750K excels in dynamic classroom or corporate training settings. Its Germ-Resistant Screen, infused with a safe and robust nano-ionic silver coating, effectively eliminates most surface germs, reducing cross-infection risks. This antimicrobial protection persists even with regular cleaning and extended use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (I)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m waiting for a part for a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, I&amp;rsquo;ve started restoring another one with faulty displays. It seems cassettes are making a comeback! I&amp;rsquo;m even hoping for new tapes and maybe even a revival of the Sony Walkman II.
This particular Beocord 9000 has a very dim display:
[Image of dim display]
The &amp;ldquo;Time Cal&amp;rdquo; bulb is also weak, a common issue. I began with the VU meter (or Peak Program Meter), as I haven&amp;rsquo;t refurbished this type before...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (III)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</guid><description>This article, the third in a series about restoring a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s peak program meters (PPM), focuses on installing and calibrating the rebuilt PPM.
The initial step involved switching the original current limiting resistors with values suitable for modern SMD LEDs. These LEDs are more efficient and brighter, requiring significantly larger resistors to match the original brightness. Testing showed that 470 Ohm and 330 Ohm resistors for red and green LEDs, respectively, produced slightly brighter output compared to the original 180 Ohm and 120 Ohm resistors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the Incandescent Indicator Light Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, two indicator lights presented problems. One had a typical issue with a broken lead, while the other had become dim due to a deteriorating filament.
To address this, I opted to use SMD LEDs as replacements, similar to a method I&amp;rsquo;ve used for Beomaster 8000 units, documented on my blog. This provides lasting stability and safeguards against potential shipping damage. However, the Beocord 9000 has more compact reflector housings compared to the Beomaster 8000, necessitating a redesign of the PCBs for the LEDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoring the Peak Program Meters with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s Peak Program Meter (PPM), even though it was fully functional. This decision stemmed from my success in restoring a different Beocord&amp;rsquo;s PPM that had several broken segments.
Since the technology behind these PPMs is similar to that of a 7-segment display, I realized that the segments in this unit were also susceptible to future breakage. Therefore, I chose to preemptively address the issue while I had the opportunity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Display Restoration with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:28:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 being restored has a common issue: a faulty 7-segment display. While only one segment was out, these large, early LED displays are a key design element, making repair essential.
This display resembles the Beomaster 8000&amp;rsquo;s frequency display, but they are not interchangeable. The repair process, however, is the same as documented in previous posts.
To begin, PCB #11 and the bezel are removed to access the display for desoldering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (II)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s rebuilt Peak Program Meters (PPM) display passed a 24-hour test, confirming its functionality.
To reattach the red-green covers, I secured the display to ensure a tight seal, preventing light leakage. Using a soldering iron, I melted the plastic posts of the covers, replicating the original attachment method.
During cleaning, the glue holding the light guide dissolved, indicating it was likely polyvinyl ester-based. I used &amp;lsquo;Aleene&amp;rsquo;s Original Tacky Glue&amp;rsquo; as a substitute, providing a clear and durable bond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Apple introduces the iMac featuring the Retina 5K display, the most advanced display resolution to date</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-introduces-the-imac-featuring-the-retina-5k-display-the-most-advanced-display-resolution-to-date/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-introduces-the-imac-featuring-the-retina-5k-display-the-most-advanced-display-resolution-to-date/</guid><description>Forget 4K, Apple has jumped ahead with 5K resolution.
Source: Apple.
Apple introduces the 27-inch iMac with a Retina 5K display, boasting the world’s highest resolution display with 14.7 million pixels. This advancement results in sharper text, more realistic videos, and an unprecedented level of detail in photographs.
“Thirty years after the first Mac revolutionized technology, the new iMac with Retina 5K display and OS X Yosemite is the most impressive Mac we&amp;rsquo;ve created,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s Senior VP of Worldwide Marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-introduces-the-imac-featuring-the-retina-5k-display-the-most-advanced-display-resolution-to-date/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-introduces-the-imac-featuring-the-retina-5k-display-the-most-advanced-display-resolution-to-date/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination with a Red/Green LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, the light bulb illuminating the peak program meter&amp;rsquo;s dB scale malfunctioned. This common issue stems from the age of the bulbs, as their leads tend to oxidize and break under pressure.
The initial state of the display, lacking illumination for the numbers on the dB scale, is shown below:
The bulb is inserted into a waveguide that distributes light across the scale, with a textured surface behind the numbers for diffusion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination-with-a-redgreen-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asus introduces a portable LED projector with a 4K display</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</guid><description>The PB287Q is a 28-inch monitor with 4K ultra high definition.
At CES last week, Asus, known for its consumer notebooks and motherboards, introduced new products designed for content creators and mobile professionals seeking enhanced performance and affordability. The company emphasized delivering bigger, better, and faster solutions. Among their offerings is the PB287Q, a 28-inch display with 4K ultra high definition (UHD) resolution. This slim-profile monitor features a full range of adjustments including swivel, tilt, pivot, and height, along with Splendid Plus video intelligence technology for optimal viewing comfort...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Rebuilding the Pinch (Rubber) Roller</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 22:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/</guid><description>The last step in restoring my Beocord 9000 is fixing the worn-out pinch roller, a common problem in these decks given their age. These decks are over 30 years old, surpassing the lifespan of most rubber components. For optimal performance, a pinch roller rebuild is essential.
Fortunately, Terry Witt of Terry&amp;rsquo;s Rubber Rollers &amp;amp; Wheels is an expert in restoring tape rollers. He is highly regarded in the field, as evidenced by his reputation on online forums...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-rebuilding-the-pinch-rubber-roller/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Stability Test and an Updated Display on the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>I dedicated time to program the compact display integrated into my BeoloverRPM device. This enhancement enables precise RPM adjustments and long-term RPM stability analysis. The display now includes minimum and maximum values, along with the total measurement duration. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the display:
The display boasts high resolution and excellent contrast. However, those of us who are getting older might need reading glasses to decipher the small font. Is perfection ever attainable?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>