<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MPLS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls/</link><description>Recent content in MPLS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VPLS Is The Ethernet Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re all familiar with cloud networks, but wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have a private cloud connecting all your business locations?
Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS) offers a solution. While not a fully private cloud, it comes close.
VPLS allows you to share a private multipoint network built on technology like Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS). MPLS networks can handle various traffic types, including Ethernet, making it ideal for diverse needs.</description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives.</description></item><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services.</description></item><item><title>Low Latency WAN Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</guid><description>Businesses are increasingly demanding low latency in their WAN connections. But why is latency suddenly so important, and how can you achieve it?
Latency is the time it takes for data packets to travel between two points. While insignificant on local networks, latency can pose major problems on long-distance WAN connections, especially for applications where speed is critical.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that latency and bandwidth are not directly related. You can have slow connections with minimal latency and blazing-fast connections with terrible latency.</description></item><item><title>Last Mile Connections That Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</guid><description>The US is covered in a network of competing telecom companies, reaching into every major city. Businesses of all sizes are drawn to their advanced IP networks, fiber optic infrastructure, and significantly lower prices. But how can businesses connect to these networks?
The final connection to a customer&amp;rsquo;s location, often called the &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; is frequently the most critical, expensive, and limiting part of a wide area network. It gets its name from the typical distance between a business and the nearest carrier Point of Presence (POP).</description></item><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location.</description></item><item><title>Even Lower Latency Connections To Chicago</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</guid><description>The significance of network latency is evident in AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s efforts to establish faster fiber optic connections, even within a metropolitan area like Chicago, set to launch by the middle of next year. This begs the question: will other cities follow suit?
Latency is the new frontier, surpassing even bandwidth in importance. It represents the critical factor when exceptional computing performance is non-negotiable. This need is especially acute in the financial sector, where companies engaged in stock and commodity trading demand minimal delays.</description></item><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging.</description></item><item><title>From LAN to MAN to WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</guid><description>The world is currently experiencing a revolution in network technology. While computer networks have historically relied on various communication protocols, some adapted from the telephone industry, there’s a growing trend towards adopting IP as a universal networking standard. This shift towards IP encompasses all network types, from local area networks (LANs) to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and wide area networks (WANs).
This standardization trend originated in LANs. Today, most LANs utilize Ethernet network interfaces due to economies of scale rather than inherent superiority.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices.</description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times.</description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers.</description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Vyvx Connects The Super Bowl</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-vyvx-connects-the-super-bowl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-vyvx-connects-the-super-bowl/</guid><description>Super Bowl Sunday is a time for celebration, but behind the scenes, technology ensures a seamless broadcast experience for millions. Level 3 Vyvx VenueNet+ plays a crucial role in delivering high-quality broadcasts from stadiums like Indianapolis&amp;rsquo;s Lucas Oil Stadium, where their technology is pre-installed and managed by experts.
Remote broadcasting, whether for radio or TV, can be unpredictable. Traditional methods often involve cumbersome equipment and potential signal disruptions. The demand for high-definition broadcasts further complicates matters, requiring substantial bandwidth to maintain picture clarity during fast-paced action.</description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line as an On Ramp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</guid><description>You might know about T1 lines as dedicated connections for digital data or PBX phone lines, but they also serve as excellent access points for various other services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Most businesses maintain a Local Area Network (LAN) and a Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect with the wider world. Your WAN connection often acts as an entry point to larger public or private networks.
A prime example is &amp;ldquo;T1 dedicated Internet.</description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?</description></item><item><title>Advantage of Dedicated Cloud Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</guid><description>Companies of all sizes are increasingly adopting cloud services due to their cost-effectiveness. However, the assumption that a basic internet connection is sufficient for accessing these services is proving to be inaccurate in many situations.
While the internet&amp;rsquo;s widespread availability and affordability make it appealing for WAN services, its security concerns led to the development of VPNs. These secure tunnels encrypt data, allowing remote workers and branch offices to connect securely to corporate networks and transfer sensitive information.</description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps).</description></item><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Frame Relay, Hello MPLS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</guid><description>Managing communication across multiple business locations can be challenging. While private lines offer a solution, their cost increases with the number of locations. Frame Relay, a private network solution, gained popularity for its reliability, security, and affordability. However, MPLS networks have emerged as a newer technology offering higher bandwidth and lower costs.
Frame Relay bridges the gap between public switched telephone networks and dedicated private lines. It replaces physical wires with virtual circuits, eliminating the need for dedicated circuits that incur costs regardless of usage.</description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>XO Launches SIP for Multi-Location Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</guid><description>XO Communications, a large telecommunications company, has introduced a new solution that allows businesses with numerous locations to take advantage of enterprise VoIP technology.
Connecting business locations to a phone service provider through SIP trunking is a well-established method for improving network performance and saving money. XO is building on this concept with a multi-site SIP trunking solution. Instead of requiring each location to connect to a remote service provider separately, branch offices, warehouses, and other locations can now use their existing Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect SIP phones back to a central IP-PBX system at the main office.</description></item><item><title>100 Business Locations and 1 Bandwidth Bill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-business-locations-and-1-bandwidth-bill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 19:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-business-locations-and-1-bandwidth-bill/</guid><description>As businesses expand nationally or even globally, their network connections often develop haphazardly. Managing numerous individual contracts becomes a significant burden, and costs can spiral out of control. It&amp;rsquo;s highly likely that a more streamlined solution could save money.
Instead of tackling this challenge alone, seeking assistance from a specialized company is recommended. Trying to find the optimal combination of providers and service levels on your own is likely to result in an inefficient and costly setup.</description></item><item><title>Branching Out With MPLS and VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</guid><description>Is secure communication between multiple locations critical for your business? As businesses increasingly rely on electronic forms and transactions, traditional methods like fax machines, overnight mail, and dial-up connections are no longer sufficient. To stay competitive, businesses need real-time access to sales and inventory data, rapid transfer of large files like medical images and CAD drawings, and instant delivery of important documents. A broadband connection linking all your key locations is essential.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points.</description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices.</description></item><item><title>Two Routes to Virtual Private Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</guid><description>VPNs have become the go-to solution for connecting multiple business locations due to their cost-effectiveness and ease of maintenance. Managed service providers allow businesses to enjoy secure multipoint communication without the burden of extensive staffing or high monthly line lease fees.
Virtual private networking is now cloud-based, but the choice of cloud type remains. You can opt for a VPN solution using the public internet or choose a completely private network for enhanced performance.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach.</description></item><item><title>Verizon enhances e-business capabilities with increased support for private IP services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</guid><description>Verizon Communications is expanding its Private IP services network, offering businesses a secure way to deliver e-business applications and conduct business-to-business e-commerce. The expansion includes 10 additional countries across the Middle East, Africa, and Asia-Pacific regions.
Verizon business and wholesale customers in the Middle East and Asia Pacific now have expanded access to Private IP Multiprotocol Private Label Switching (MPLS) services in Bangladesh, Cambodia, Laos, Nepal, Iraq, Lebanon, and Yemen. Chennai, India, gains an additional location, offering customers enhanced network resiliency and reach through increased access to MPLS services.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>Private Point to Point Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Secure and transparent data transfer is crucial. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some popular methods to achieve this.
What Are Dedicated Private Lines?
Imagine a dedicated private line as a secure connection between two points facilitated by a carrier. It&amp;rsquo;s like having your own wiring, but provided by a third party, spanning across cities or even globally.
T1 Dedicated Lines
T1 lines are the digital version of old-school &amp;ldquo;dry loops&amp;rdquo; used by radio stations and alarm systems.</description></item><item><title>VPLS Connects Your Many LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-connects-your-many-lans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-connects-your-many-lans/</guid><description>Do you have multiple offices in your company? It&amp;rsquo;s likely that each office has its own local network for computers and potentially even internet-based phone systems. The question then becomes, how do you link these separate networks together?
The solution, unfortunately, is often complex and costly.
However, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to simplify this process and potentially save money compared to your current individual connections: VPLS, or Virtual Private LAN Service. This service is provided by companies like Layer2 Communications and other competitive network providers.</description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Network For Orange County</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a rising demand for high-bandwidth, low-latency internet connectivity from businesses, particularly in sectors like finance, automation, cloud computing, and medical imaging. This surge is driving the expansion of fiber optic networks, with a prime example being the ongoing development in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
AboveNet, a prominent fiber optic network provider in the US and Europe, is constructing a major &amp;ldquo;feeder ring&amp;rdquo; in Orange County, California. This ring will connect various business locations, including office buildings, data centers, and carrier hotels, to an existing fiber optic backbone already serving the Irvine and Costa Mesa business districts.</description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning.</description></item><item><title>Transparent LAN Service for WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transparent-lan-service-for-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transparent-lan-service-for-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>With the increasing trend of businesses expanding beyond a single location, the demand for reliable wide-area connectivity is on the rise. This is particularly relevant for companies with branches across the country and medical facilities spread over large regions. While traditional telecommunications services have connected multiple locations, newer solutions now allow your local area network (LAN) to cover an entire metropolitan area or even span multiple states.
One such solution is known as transparent LAN service, which effectively combines multiple separate LANs into a single, unified network.</description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>WAN Topology Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</guid><description>Businesses have various choices for connecting their branch offices, franchisees, suppliers, customers, and remote employees. The ideal network structure depends on the specific goals, whether it&amp;rsquo;s basic off-site backups or creating a virtual company spanning multiple states. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some prevalent WAN topologies used today.
The most widespread WAN is the Internet, connecting almost everyone everywhere. It&amp;rsquo;s a massive mesh network with affordable connections available through various methods like wireline, wireless, and fiber optic.</description></item></channel></rss>