<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Floating Chassis on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/floating-chassis/</link><description>Recent content in Floating Chassis on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/floating-chassis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Floating Suspension, Reservoir Capacitor &amp; Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</guid><description>This project is nearing completion. This post details the remounting of the floating chassis within the cabinet, replacing the reservoir capacitor, and installing the refurbished platter motor.
Here are the parts needed for mounting the floating suspension system back into the cabinet.
The threaded pin&amp;rsquo;s longer section is positioned at the bottom. When attaching the wing-nut, ensure it sits at the very beginning of the thread. I personally position it to allow enough thread for securing the nut while keeping the nut&amp;rsquo;s outer edge aligned with the topmost thread...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Floating Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 18:29:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</guid><description>This short post will illustrate an intriguing difference in the suspension systems of two Beogram 4002 Type 5513 turntables.
The first Beogram 4002 Type 5513, serial number 1312615, used a stack of concave washers to secure the floating suspension to the top plate. These washers were also present on the bottom lock.
The second Beogram 4002 Type 5513, serial number 1311076, features a slightly different suspension mechanism. This earlier production model employs a single, concave metal piece between the suspension lock and the top plate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Inside Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-inside-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-inside-work/</guid><description>My work on restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable from Houston continues, focusing on the internal components this time. This update covers the refurbishment of the tangential arm assembly and the replacement of the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s reservoir capacitor.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a current picture of the Beogram 4002 with its chassis and tangential arm assembly removed.
The tangential arm assembly components on this Beogram 4002 are in great condition. My work mainly involved cleaning and lubricating the Beogram chassis parts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-inside-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-inside-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reinstalling the Floating Chassis Components</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</guid><description>All the necessary restoration parts for the Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable are now available, marking the start of the reassembly process.
The reinstallation begins with securing the floating chassis, equipped with the tangential arm assembly, back into the Beogram 4002 cabinet. The process starts by fitting the Beolover replacement suspension lock bushings onto the floating chassis. Subsequently, the suspension locks are positioned within the cabinet base. The floating chassis is then carefully lowered onto these locking bolts, and the remaining locking mechanisms are put in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reassembly of the Floating Chassis and Some Initial Checks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</guid><description>After completing the tangential arm assembly checks and cleaning the Beogram 4002 cabinet, it was time to reinstall the floating chassis.
The reassembly began with cleaning and lubricating the three suspension lock down screws, then reinstalling them in the Beogram cabinet.
With all three suspension locks back in place, the platter motor and output board, which had been previously restored, were reinstalled.
The control panel, RPM indicator panel, and arm position scale were then put back in their respective places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</a></p></description></item><item><title> Beogram 8000 Type 5613: Finishing the floating chassis components, transformer C1 replacement &amp; cleaning the control panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</guid><description>Last night, I completed work on the floating chassis parts.
I reassembled the cleaned tangential drive parts, including the spindle, spindle nut, rails, and new bracket, and installed them on the floating chassis.
Following the service manual&amp;rsquo;s instructions, I lubricated the spindle. The lubricants are very similar to those used in the Beogram 400x, which is logical given that both turntable series have comparable tangential drive systems. The Beogram 8000 lubrication chart had one intriguing item that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t previously considered: an entry for lid damping grease...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going over the chassis and mechanical parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</guid><description>The two circuit boards that needed component updates are finished. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s cabinet and its mechanical parts.
I prefer working on the floating chassis with it removed, which is easier since I&amp;rsquo;ll disassemble most of the tangential arm.
This revealed some hidden issues.
Initially, I believed the three chassis lock bushings were okay because they looked fine. However, examining the locking mechanism showed otherwise.
This was the first indication of the bushings&amp;rsquo; poor condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>