<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Statistics on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/statistics/</link><description>Recent content in Statistics on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong government confirms the schedule for releasing statistics from March to May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</guid><description>Companies interested in monitoring the Hong Kong economy can stay informed through press release schedules published by the Hong Kong government. These releases provide insights into various economic indicators.
A schedule of upcoming releases for March to May 2014 is provided below, starting with March 3rd.
March 2014
3rd: January 2014 Retail Sales Statistics
7th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Statistics on Vessels, Port Cargo, and Containers
10th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Quarterly Business Receipts Indices for Service Industries..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Switch to organic bath and shower products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</guid><description>According to research firm Technavio, consumers are increasingly interested in bath and shower products that offer both organic ingredients and convenience. The company&amp;rsquo;s report on the global bath and shower products market highlights that rising living standards and disposable income are driving consumers towards higher-priced, aesthetically pleasing products with unique fragrances and effective ingredients. This trend is projected to propel the market to a value of at least US$15 billion by 2019, reflecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of approximately 4% from 2015 to 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Today is World Backup Day. Have you ensured the safety of your data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</guid><description>A recent worldwide study funded by Acronis, a prominent name in hybrid cloud data protection, highlights a rising awareness of the importance of safeguarding personal data on computers, mobile phones, and tablets.
Almost half of the surveyed individuals possess more than four devices per household requiring protection, and 45% are most afraid of misplacing photos and videos. Security and privacy were identified as crucial factors in data backup.
Evolving Concerns in Personal Data Security The traditional worries of hardware malfunctions and accidental deletions are no longer the sole reasons for data loss apprehension...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Economic Community has the potential to be a goldmine for B2C businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, has published a white paper outlining a strategic framework for marketing to ASEAN consumers.
The establishment of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in December 2015 will unify the ten ASEAN member states into a single market and production hub. This development is anticipated to draw significant attention from multinational corporations that have traditionally focused on China and India. Euromonitor suggests that the AEC is on track to become a global economic powerhouse due to its projected robust economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Determining the Impact of the Advocate General on the European Union Court of Justice: Is it Correlation or Causation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</guid><description>Carlos Arrebola and Ana Julia Mauricio (PhD students at the University of Cambridge)
It is widely claimed, especially in publications like The Guardian, that Advocate Generals significantly influence the European Court of Justice (ECJ)&amp;rsquo;s decisions. This belief is also prevalent among legal professionals specializing in EU law. However, there is limited empirical evidence to support this assumption. Our research investigates whether this perceived influence is accurate or merely a misconception...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is your company using mobile for recruiting?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</guid><description>Mobile interaction is crucial for successful recruitment in India. In 2014-15, almost half of companies surveyed by TimesJobs reported receiving 10-20% of job applications via mobile phones, significantly up from the previous year.
With mobile phones widespread, 65% of organizations in India now have mobile recruitment strategies, a 10% increase from the previous year, according to a TimesJobs.com survey.
Jobseeker behavior has shifted dramatically, with 85% of online job searching now done on smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mergers and acquisitions in the early stages are decelerating in Southeast Asia and Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 11:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</guid><description>Announcements for early-stage mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in Q4 2016 are predicted to be similar to the same period last year. This is attributed to reduced early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity in Southeast Asia and South Korea, as per the latest Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor (DFP) report released by Intralinks Holdings. Intralinks provides software and services, including virtual data rooms (VDRs), for managing M&amp;amp;A transactions.
Southeast Asia, encompassing Singapore, Malaysia, and Indonesia, is experiencing a significant 47...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TechSci Research believes that the organic dairy market has significant potential</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</guid><description>A recent report by TechSci Research, a global management consulting firm, predicts significant growth in the global organic dairy products market. Driven by factors like increased health consciousness, a growing urban population, and rising spending on organic foods, the market is expected to achieve a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of over 11% between 2016 and 2021.
The report, titled Global Organic Dairy Products Market By Product Type, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, identifies expanding product lines, readily available organic dairy products, strong distribution networks, increasing internet access, and proactive marketing strategies from key players as contributing factors to this projected growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Casual dining is becoming more popular globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</guid><description>A global market research firm, Euromonitor International, determined that consumer food service sales increased by 5.7% worldwide in 2015, a rise from the previous year&amp;rsquo;s growth rate of 5.3%. Fast casual dining experienced the most significant growth within the industry at 10.4%, generating an extra US$3.4 billion in revenue between 2014 and 2015.
Elizabeth Friend, a Consumer Foodservice Strategy Analyst at Euromonitor International, observed, &amp;ldquo;Consumers are changing their dining habits, especially in developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If apps don't offer speed, simplicity, and security, consumers will not hesitate to abandon them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</guid><description>Source: CA Technologies infographic.
People are pickier than ever about the apps they use, so businesses that don&amp;rsquo;t offer a good app experience could lose a significant portion of their customers. A regional study* sponsored by CA Technologies shows that mobile and desktop applications in the Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) region have become key to earning customer loyalty.
Software: the New Battleground for Brand Loyalty – A survey of 1,449 consumers and 259 business decision-makers across five APJ nations pinpointed three major factors influencing the customer experience: Source: CA Technologies infographic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Alibaba truly the top player in the e-commerce industry?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</guid><description>While Alibaba Group Holding is often called the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest e-commerce company, a new report from yStats.com suggests that this depends on how you interpret the data. The report, which ranks companies based on official revenue figures, found that Amazon was the actual leader in 2013.
Amazon&amp;rsquo;s impressive $74 billion in product and service sales surpasses the combined revenue of the next nine companies on the list. Chinese B2C retailer JD...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>80% of Singaporeans living abroad are interested in returning to work in their home country</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 07:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</guid><description>A new report from Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, suggests that competition for skilled workers in Singapore will increase in 2016. This demand will likely lead to more attempts to recruit Singaporeans working abroad. Hiring managers believe that these experienced professionals could help alleviate the tight labor market, benefiting both companies and the &amp;ldquo;Fair Consideration Framework,&amp;rdquo; which promotes local hiring.
Returning Singaporeans are desirable candidates because they often have international experience and a broader range of skills compared to their counterparts who haven&amp;rsquo;t worked overseas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, ASEAN received the highest amount of foreign direct investment (FDI) among developing countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The latest ASEAN Investment Report examines the growth of foreign direct investment (FDI) into the ASEAN region, particularly the influence of corporations on infrastructure expansion and regional integration.
In 2014, ASEAN emerged as the top recipient of FDI among developing nations. FDI inflows to the region experienced a third consecutive year of growth, reaching US$136.2 billion, a rise from US$117.7 billion in 2013. This achievement occurred despite a 16% global decline in FDI and inconsistent global economic progress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is a growing trend of adults purchasing toys and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</guid><description>In 2016, games and puzzles experienced an 8% surge in the global market, surpassing construction toys as the fastest-growing toy category, according to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm. This impressive growth also marks the highest for the category since 2002.
Although construction toys saw a growth of 7.8% in 2016, a dip compared to the double-digit growth of 2015, they still dominated the traditional toys and games market with a value of US$10 billion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Number of Human Trafficking Victims in the EU: A Statistical Puzzle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</guid><description>Dr. Vladislava Stoyanova
Postdoctoral Fellow, Faculty of Law, Lund University; Author of Human Trafficking and Slavery Reconsidered. Conceptual Limits and States’ Positive Obligations in Europe (Cambridge University Press, 2017)
In May 2016, the European Commission presented its initial findings on the progress made in combating human trafficking. This report, mandated by the 2011 EU Trafficking Directive, examines advancements in prosecuting traffickers, safeguarding victims, and preventative measures. It highlights trafficking patterns, incorporating statistical data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports that skincare is a popular trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has reported that the global beauty industry is experiencing growth, particularly in emerging markets, as consumers increasingly adopt more comprehensive beauty routines and upgrade to premium products.
Skincare stands out as the dominant segment in most markets, with global sales projected to exceed US$130 billion by 2019. &amp;ldquo;Consumers are allocating a significant portion of their beauty spending on skincare, averaging US$15 per person annually,&amp;rdquo; notes Irina Barbalova, Head of Beauty and Personal Care at Euromonitor International...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2015 Vuclip Global Video Insights reveals that Malaysian consumers are seeking uncomplicated entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Vuclip, a leading mobile video-on-demand (VOD) service in emerging markets, has published its Global Video Insights (GVI) 2015 Survey. The study examines video consumption trends and device preferences among Malaysian consumers.
Source: Vuclip. Prakash.
Malaysian consumers value several features in an over-the-top (OTT) content player. The most important are a seamless user interface (61%), uninterrupted viewing experience (58%), high-definition video quality (56%), and access to the newest videos (54%). Other desirable features include adjustable streaming quality (47%), video downloads (46%), and simultaneous multiple video downloads (45%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Childcare centers are emerging in Chinese workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</guid><description>Government policy changes are fueling the growth of the preschool or childcare market in China. Technavio forecasts a CAGR exceeding 6% for this market between 2016 and 2020. This growth is largely attributed to recent policy adjustments, notably the 2015 amendment to the one-child policy, now permitting couples to have two children. This shift aims to balance population development and, coupled with rising disposable incomes among middle-class families, is driving increased preschool enrollment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Malaysia election, #GE14, generated more than 7.3 million tweets on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 22:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</guid><description>During the short Malaysian election campaign period, over 7.3 million tweets using the hashtags #GE14 and #MalaysiaElection established Twitter as a key platform for political discourse.
On May 9th, election day discussions dominated Twitter in Malaysia, exceeding all other topics. Over 4.2 million #GE14 tweets were sent globally in just 24 hours. The hashtag topped Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s trending list, joined by other politically charged terms like #MalaysiaMemilih and #PakatanHarapan in the top ten...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangkok is the top tourist destination in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Mastercard. Report cover.
Although Bangkok, Thailand remains the top spot for visitors in the Asia Pacific, the latest Mastercard Asia Pacific Destinations Index 2017* shows that Singapore outpaces the Thai capital in total tourist spending.
Singapore experienced an 18% increase in visitor spending between 2015 and 2016. As one of just five destinations in the top 20 for overall expenditure to hit a minimum daily spend of US$200, Singapore drew in the biggest spenders at US$254 per day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Viu, a service provided by Vuclip, delivers an average of 20 videos per month to viewers in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:44:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Vuclip, a PCCW Media company, has released key engagement data for its OTT service, Viu, based on an analysis of app and desktop viewership.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOh1EZVWoEhfM9h_KB5E2oDQtVX9NIYnObrOM6oWpK6xB_fWBVmqMwQv5MQtoq5jTe338bKg_10JMMP4wDeSWDCbwHwC8jKXx1VMXkYHCYTrGVSsm8QO-dG0eKaUelNE4fQSA8esO5InKk/s1600/image.png)
Source: Viu Malaysia website.
In the two months since its launch in Malaysia, Viu has seen average user engagement of 20 videos per month. Peak viewing times are after work hours, with Wednesday to Sunday being the most popular days.
Korean dramas, Bollywood films, and Malaysian TV series rank among the top ten most-watched content, highlighting the strong demand for Asian entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A study conducted by Abbott reveals concerning patterns among diabetics in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 22:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</guid><description>Special thosai set.
A recent study, the Abbott Food, Spikes and Diabetes Survey, suggests that 70% of individuals managing diabetes in urban India may not be carefully managing their food intake. This survey, conducted by Ipsos India on behalf of Abbott, involved over 4,100 participants aged 36 to 65 with Type 2 diabetes (diagnosed for over 18 months) from various socioeconomic backgrounds across eight major cities. The study aimed to understand their eating habits, the impact of meals on blood sugar fluctuations, and its effect on diabetes management...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Supplying office pantries with items from FoodAsia2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</guid><description>The recent Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016) trade event showcased a diverse selection of office pantry-friendly foods at the FoodAsia halls and Halal Supermarket zone.
One notable display was by Camel, a company known for snacks like nuts and dried fruit. A camel statue stood atop a mound of their products, greeting attendees. Competitor Tong Garden was also present at the event.
Another highlight was Nuhoney, a sparkling honey drink made in Singapore using Australian honey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kaspersky provides solutions to combat ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</guid><description>Ransomware is increasingly targeting businesses, encrypting files and demanding payment for decryption keys.
A Kaspersky Lab report reveals a six-fold increase in ransomware attacks against businesses from 2015 to 2016, affecting one in ten business users.
Cybercriminals are focusing on businesses, particularly small and medium-sized companies. A Kaspersky Lab and B2B International study found that 42% of respondents from these businesses considered ransomware a major threat.
Even brief data unavailability can severely impact small businesses, potentially halting operations entirely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>