<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mutual Recognition on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mutual-recognition/</link><description>Recent content in Mutual Recognition on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mutual-recognition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition.</description></item><item><title>Dear Colleague, Do You Possess Sufficient Independence? The Impact of Systemic Deficiencies in a Member State's Justice System on the Principle of Mutual Trust</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah*
*Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund For Scientific Research (F.R.S.-FNRS). The author wishes to thank Pr. S. Van Drooghenbroeck. The usual disclaimer applies.
Advocate General Tanchev recently presented his opinion on case C-216/18 PPU. This case involves multiple European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) issued by Polish authorities against an individual, LM, suspected of drug trafficking. The case, brought before the European Court of Justice (ECJ) by the Irish High Court, questions whether an EAW is enforceable if the issuing Member State&amp;rsquo;s conditions contradict the fundamental right to a fair trial due to systemic rule of law issues within its justice system.</description></item><item><title>Recognition of Professional Qualifications after Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 23:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</guid><description>Dáire McCormack-George*
*The author, a Ph.D. Candidate in Law and Scholar of Trinity College Dublin, the University of Dublin, based this blog post on his presentation at the third Radboud University Economic Law Conference, ‘Upgrading Trade and Services in EU and International Economic Law’, on June 15, 2018. He thanks the conference participants and attendees for their engaging questions. All errors are his own.
Introduction
The current draft withdrawal agreement between the UK and the EU proposes the temporary application of Directive 2005/36/EC (the Recognition Directive) until the transition period ends, ensuring continued recognition of qualifications recognized beforehand.</description></item><item><title>How committed are Member States to safeguarding fundamental rights through the EU's common rules on detention?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</guid><description>By Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
In early February 2014, the Commission released a concerning report regarding &amp;ldquo;common rules on detention.&amp;rdquo; The report revealed that a mere 18 out of 28 EU member states had implemented any of the intended instruments. This study was purely quantitative and did not assess the effectiveness of the rules or their impact on individuals.
The inadequate implementation of these fundamental commitments to enhance detainee rights is worrisome.</description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state.</description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles.</description></item><item><title>Is the CJEU judgment in LM a new era for mutual trust and independence of the judiciary, or just business as usual?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</guid><description>Dr. Agnieszka Frąckowiak-Adamska, Faculty of Law, University of Wroclaw
In the case of C-216/18 PPU LM, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was asked by an Irish court to consider a significant legal issue facing the EU: how restrictions on judicial independence in one member state impact other EU member states. A series of laws enacted in Poland from 2015 to 2018 has been widely criticized by numerous institutions, both within and outside Poland, for enabling legislative and executive branches to significantly interfere with the judicial process.</description></item></channel></rss>