<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ecofriendly on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ecofriendly/</link><description>Recent content in Ecofriendly on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ecofriendly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visa Eco Benefits promote sustainability in every transaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</guid><description>Visa, a digital payment company, has introduced Visa Eco Benefits in the Asia Pacific region. This suite of sustainability solutions aims to help Visa cardholders understand the environmental effects of their everyday spending. They can track their carbon footprint from Visa transactions and explore options for offsetting their impact through carbon offsets or charitable donations via their bank&amp;rsquo;s app or website.
Banks in the Asia Pacific region that adopt Eco Benefits can offer these solutions to their Visa cardholders, addressing the increasing demand for environmentally conscious financial services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover the most environmentally friendly hotels worldwide with GreenHotelWorld</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</guid><description>Source: GreenHotelWorld website.
GreenHotelWorld, in collaboration with TripAdvisor, now boasts the largest selection of verified eco-friendly hotels on a single platform. This was achieved by incorporating hotels from TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s GreenLeaders Program.
With a global reach, GreenHotelWorld curates over 8,000 hotels recognized for their demonstrably sustainable practices. Their categorization process utilizes standards from the Global Sustainable Tourism Council (GSTC), a respected international body that sets benchmarks for sustainable tourism and accredits green hotel certifications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses becomes a part of the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</guid><description>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is among the first to sign the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative. This initiative, spearheaded by the UN Environment Programme and UN World Tourism Organization with the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, aims to tackle plastic waste in the tourism sector.
By signing the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative, Six Senses reinforces its commitment to eliminate, innovate, and circulate its plastic use by 2025, aiming to be plastic-free as early as 2022...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience sustainable dining at Avani properties in Indochina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</guid><description>Image Credit: Avani. Plant-based coconut acai bowls are available at the Avani+ Samui Resort.
To create a healthier planet and promote sustainability, Avani Hotels has introduced a variety of eco-friendly and wellness-focused programs.
Avani&amp;rsquo;s flagship hotels in Thailand, Cambodia, and Laos are increasing their efforts to support nearby communities. They are accomplishing this by showcasing regional specialties and advocating for a decrease in reliance on imported goods. They have also implemented zero-waste programs, which include composting systems to handle all organic waste and on-site organic gardens to encourage self-sufficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The beauty industry is increasingly prioritizing sustainability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</guid><description>The beauty industry needs a complete overhaul in its approach to sustainability and zero waste, focusing on every part of the process, according to market intelligence agency Mintel. The company highlights &amp;ldquo;Sub-Zero Waste&amp;rdquo; as a major trend that will shape the global beauty and personal care markets in the years to come.
The zero-waste movement is picking up speed as consumers become increasingly affected by environmental problems like natural disasters and water scarcity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>