<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WISP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wisp/</link><description>Recent content in WISP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wisp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is 4G and Why Do You Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re constantly bombarded with ads for 3G phones and wireless aircards, and now 4G is emerging. But what does this new technology mean and why should you care?
2G, 3G, 4G—these &amp;ldquo;Gs&amp;rdquo; represent different generations of wireless broadband. This technology evolves so rapidly that various generations often coexist in the same region. This is intentional. If you&amp;rsquo;re in an area with weak 3G coverage, your device automatically connects to slower 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Internet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, businesses depend heavily on infrastructure like electricity, telephone lines, and internet connectivity, often delivered through copper cables. While electricity and landline phones are widely accessible due to national initiatives, internet availability, particularly broadband via copper or fiber optic cables, diminishes as you move away from city centers. Rural areas often lack wired internet infrastructure entirely, leaving businesses with limited choices.
One option for these areas is wireless internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Many T1 Lines Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</guid><description>For small businesses dissatisfied with DSL or Cable broadband, a professional T1 line might seem like the ideal solution. The superior reliability and dedicated bandwidth make T1 lines the popular choice for business voice and data services. However, as your business expands, you might encounter the bandwidth limitations of your once-sufficient T1 line. What then?
Similarly, high-tech businesses, such as Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) or video production companies, might find the 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul is Backing Things Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</guid><description>While it may seem like the world operates solely on wireless connections, especially if you rely on cell phones and mobile internet, this is only true for the link between your device and the nearest cell tower or access point. Beyond that point lies the backhaul, a crucial but often overlooked component that bridges the wireless and wired worlds. As wireless connections become faster, the limitations of traditional backhaul solutions are becoming increasingly apparent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bonded T1 Solution Increases Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</guid><description>A 1.5 Mbps T1 bandwidth has long been a standard for small businesses, often proving sufficient for their needs. Some businesses even utilize an Integrated T1 solution for combined internet and telephone services. However, as bandwidth demands increase, many find T1 bandwidth limiting their productivity.
A simple solution to increase bandwidth is adding a second T1 line, doubling it to 3 Mbps. However, for these lines to function as a single, larger line, they should be ordered from the same provider with a &amp;ldquo;bonded T1 solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, There IS Rural Broadband For Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</guid><description>Many people are excited about the economic stimulus plan&amp;rsquo;s promise of expanded rural broadband access. However, you might already be able to get the internet speeds your rural business needs.
Most major internet providers have overlooked rural areas, not because rural businesses are less important, but because the cost of installing infrastructure like coaxial cables or fiber optic cables is difficult to recoup when there are fewer customers. This is why cable and DSL internet services are less common in the countryside...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>