<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecommunications Act on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecommunications-act/</link><description>Recent content in Telecommunications Act on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:05:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecommunications-act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Right to Competitive T1 Prices Protected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) recently upheld your right to benefit from competition among wireline telecommunication services. The FCC unanimously rejected a request from Verizon Telephone Companies to be released from regulations requiring them to provide competitive access to their lines in six Northeastern cities.
This regulation, part of the Telecommunications Act of 1996, aims to level the playing field between established phone companies and newer competitors. Historically, these incumbent companies, descendants of the Bell System monopoly, operated without competition for a century...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Buying Ernest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations often struggle to manage their telecommunications across the board. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t a single, national provider that understands local needs be ideal? While that might seem contradictory, Ernest Communications offers precisely that solution.
Ernest specializes in serving businesses with widespread locations, such as chain stores, hotels, and restaurants, by providing phone lines, data connections, and wireless services. Essentially, any company with franchises, branches, or service centers across various regions fits their model...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>