<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Right to Property on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-property/</link><description>Recent content in Right to Property on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-property/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules.</description></item><item><title>After the Steinhoff case, the ECB has an increased responsibility to uphold and advocate for the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Diane Fromage, Maastricht University*
* I am grateful to Menelaos Markakis for his insightful feedback.
On March 12, 2020, the Court of Justice dismissed an appeal concerning the Steinhoff case (T-107/17), previously decided by the General Court in May 2019. This case, though not widely discussed, holds significant weight as it clarifies and broadens the European Central Bank (ECB)&amp;rsquo;s obligation to &amp;lsquo;respect the rights [of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (ECFR)], [to] observe the principles and [to] promote the application thereof&amp;rsquo; as stated in Article 51 ECFR, specifically concerning its advisory role.</description></item><item><title>The politicization of treaty obligations in private schools.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-politicization-of-treaty-obligations-in-private-schools/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-politicization-of-treaty-obligations-in-private-schools/</guid><description>Dr Kasey McCall-Smith, Senior Lecturer in Public International Law, University of Edinburgh
The Labour Party&amp;rsquo;s 2019 Annual Conference has drawn significant attention, particularly for its resolution to eliminate private schools in the UK. This highlights the need to examine politicians&amp;rsquo; passionate pronouncements in light of legal realities, especially international and human rights law. Similar situations arose earlier this year when Theresa May presented a unilateral statement on the UK&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the Withdrawal Agreement Protocol on Ireland/Northern Ireland and when Geoffrey Cox MP incorrectly suggested that the Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties (VCLT) offered a simple solution to the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the backstop.</description></item></channel></rss>