<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Singtel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/singtel/</link><description>Recent content in Singtel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/singtel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel provides leasing options for high-end smartphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first mobile phone leasing program to make high-end devices more accessible.
Subscribers with SIM Only plans can choose to pay a low monthly fee to use premium Apple and Samsung handsets instead of buying them outright. They can lease the newest Apple iPhone and Samsung Galaxy models for two years and have the option to upgrade in the twelfth month for a S$200 fee.
With prices starting at S$35 per month for a Samsung Galaxy S9 (64 GB), customers can save up to S$578 off the regular retail price if they lease the phone for a year or S$358 if they keep it for two years.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has released its annual festive film about a lost phone just before Christmas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest holiday film centers around the importance of family connection during the Christmas season, particularly in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s tech-savvy environment.
The film, titled The Gift, portrays a teenager excessively focused on her digital life and how this affects her family&amp;rsquo;s Christmas traditions. The creators were inspired by research indicating that people of all ages, across demographics, are spending a significant amount of time on their phones, even more so than quality time with their families.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp.</description></item><item><title>Singtel will be providing the option to share up to 50GB of mobile data at the PC Show 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</guid><description>Singtel is increasing its mobile data offerings with the launch of &amp;ldquo;DataMore,&amp;rdquo; a new plan featuring larger data bundles. This launch comes less than a month after Circles.Life entered the market with a focus on data options. DataMore is designed for users who need a lot of data and is shareable with multiple users, making it perfect for families.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Mobile Marketing, highlights that this plan caters to customer demand for larger data packages at affordable prices.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with TVB programming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</guid><description>Singtel TV is adding Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s TVB Jade and TVB Xing He channels to its lineup. From September 9th to October 8th, 2019, viewers can enjoy a free preview.
Singtel customers will have access to the same TVB Jade as Hong Kong viewers, featuring Cantonese dramas, variety shows, and infotainment programs.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CEO of Consumer Singapore, shared that the company is fulfilling customer requests by introducing these channels, broadening their comprehensive TV offerings and solidifying their position as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading pay-TV provider.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases its offering of free content as the circuit-breaker in Singapore is extended</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</guid><description>Singtel TV is expanding its free preview by adding 10 more channels while the circuit breaker period is extended. This is in addition to the 95,000 hours of programming already offered for free on Singtel TV and Singtel CAST, which was launched last month to help entertain people stuck at home.
From May 1st to 31st, Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO will offer a free preview with more entertainment, factual, news, and other programming from popular channels including National Geographic and FOX Family Movies.</description></item><item><title>Singtel expands ReadyRoam data roaming service to include additional destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</guid><description>Singtel has improved its ReadyRoam 1GB for 30 days service, making it the first to provide comprehensive multi-destination data roaming across Asia, Europe, the US, and Canada. This enhanced service, which covers 26 countries for S$35 and 11 countries for S$20, offers travelers a convenient way to stay connected.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, highlights that this enhancement caters to the holiday season when many customers travel.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has declared the champions of Season 1 for the PVP Esports Corporate Championship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</guid><description>Teams from Singapore and Indonesia emerged victorious in the corporate category of Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 2020 PVP Esports Community Championships (Season 1).
Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s team, DeloitteOne, and DBS&amp;rsquo;s team, TurretHeist, secured the top spots in the Dota 2 and Mobile Legends: Bang Bang Corporate Championships, respectively. The Indonesian team, HZL Legion (RM Djamiah Putra), claimed victory in PlayerUnknown&amp;rsquo;s Battlegrounds (PUBG): Mobile.
Each winning team received over S$5,000 in cash and prizes. The grand finals, held online from September 5th to 6th due to the COVID-19 pandemic, saw teams competing remotely.</description></item><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):</description></item><item><title>Starting today, Singtel will be accepting preorders for the Google Pixel 2 XL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</guid><description>Singtel announced a partnership with Google to become the official telecommunications provider for the highly anticipated Google Pixel 2 XL in Singapore. Starting November 15th, Singtel customers will have the exclusive opportunity to be the first in Southeast Asia to purchase this new device.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, expressed excitement about bringing the Pixel 2 XL to Singapore, highlighting its innovative features that have been eagerly awaited by Android fans.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and Great Eastern have launched a new home and contents insurance offering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-great-eastern-have-launched-a-new-home-and-contents-insurance-offering/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 03:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-great-eastern-have-launched-a-new-home-and-contents-insurance-offering/</guid><description>Singtel and Great Eastern have partnered to introduce Singtel Home Protect Flexi, a home and contents insurance plan that offers flexibility and convenience. The plan is directly connected to a customer&amp;rsquo;s Singtel broadband subscription, automatically updating with their new address if they move. This feature ensures continuous coverage without any gaps or the need for manual updates. The plan operates on a no-contract basis, allowing customers to cancel at their convenience.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash and UOB Asset Management have collaborated to provide a mobile robo-adviser that includes an ESG option</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for UOBAM Robo-Invest.
Singtel has introduced a new digital advisor, developed by UOB Asset Management (UOBAM), on its Dash e-wallet platform. This launch expands Dash’s selection of financial services, which already encompasses payments, international money transfers, insurance, savings, and investments.
UOBAM Robo-Invest is the first robo-advisor in Singapore available on a mobile wallet and stands out by offering sustainable investing options created by UOBAM specifically for Dash users.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's 2022 Chinese New Year film features the Angs and the Huangs facing off on Sentosa with the addition of 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 23:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chinese New Year festive film for 2022.
To celebrate the Year of the Tiger and the values of family and community central to the holiday, Singtel has released its annual Chinese New Year short film. The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger is the third installment in a series of films by Singtel featuring the amusing rivalry between two families.</description></item><item><title>Dash, the mobile payment service by Singtel, introduces a new rewards program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 22:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</guid><description>Singtel Dash users now have a new incentive to use the app – the Dash Rewards program. This program allows users to earn points for various transactions, including payments and overseas remittances. These points can then be redeemed for rewards such as Singtel mobile services, grocery vouchers, dining options, retail discounts, and lifestyle benefits.
Source: Singtel website. Dash Rewards incentivizes Dash users for making transactions.
Dash Rewards aims to provide more value to users by awarding points for every dollar spent.</description></item><item><title>Song Seung Heon is in Singapore to promote Saimdang</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon spent time with fans and Singtel TV subscribers during a Singapore trip sponsored by Singtel and Oh!K.
Two hundred Singtel TV subscribers in Singapore enjoyed an exclusive meeting with Korean actor Song Seung Heon, hosted by Singtel and Oh!K.
Song&amp;rsquo;s visit was to promote his K-drama Saimdang (师任堂). Before a large public event at The Cathay, Singtel TV subscribers could take pictures with Song and chat with him.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces music services that do not use data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</guid><description>Singtel debuted its Singtel Music service, a first-of-its-kind offering in Singapore. For a fixed monthly price, subscribers gain access to music from Spotify, KKBOX, AMPed, and MeRadio without incurring data charges.
Representatives from Singtel Music at the launch event.
Singtel Music provides premium accounts from Spotify, KKBOX, or AMPed, enabling users to stream an extensive library of songs without data usage concerns. Additionally, they can enjoy 13 MeRadio stations without impacting their data allowance.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a new prepaid SIM card that also functions as a travel card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced the hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card, a first in Asia, which combines a prepaid SIM card with a stored value travel card usable for Singapore&amp;rsquo;s public transportation.
Source: Singtel. The hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card is the first in Asia to combine travel and phone services.
Priced at S$18, this SIM card provides 100 GB of 4G data, unlimited access to social media and messaging apps, and 1 GB of roaming data for select countries in the region.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has announced that the iPad Pro is now available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-announced-that-the-ipad-pro-is-now-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-announced-that-the-ipad-pro-is-now-available/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Singtel now offers the new iPad Pro with Wi-Fi + Cellular. This tablet boasts a 12.9-inch Retina display, packing 5.6 million pixels for exceptional resolution, and its size rivals some laptops. Customers can also purchase smart cases and silicone covers.
According to a Singtel representative, &amp;ldquo;Singtel will offer iPad Pro with a variety of attractive data plans that will allow customers to connect to its tri-band 4G network.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides an explanation of mobile performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</guid><description>Singtel contributed to the Infocomm Development Authority&amp;rsquo;s (IDA) MyConnection SG study, highlighting connectivity, speed, and coverage as crucial aspects of user experience.
Singtel emphasized that, based on study feedback, users prioritize network coverage, call stability, customer service, and reliable data connections over pure speed. Consistent speed across a broad coverage area is key for a positive user experience. This feedback helps Singtel pinpoint areas for service enhancement.
Connectivity, as defined by Singtel, is the server connection response time, measured in milliseconds.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils National Day film for 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest National Day film celebrates the resilience of Singaporeans as they face the challenges of COVID-19. Titled This is the year, the film is available on Singtel TV and social media platforms.
This is the year highlights the difficulties brought on by the pandemic and pays homage to the spirit of progress that drives Singaporeans forward.
Source: Singtel video. This is the year we will not have the F1 race.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a special upgrade offer for owners of 2G phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced a special offer as they prepare to discontinue 2G services in Singapore, starting in April 2017.
Source: Singtel.
The Alcatel Onetouch 2052x is available for S$48, and the Onetouch Pop D3 is priced at S$95.
Prepaid customers can take advantage of S$70 in free talk time and 350MB of data, along with an additional S$30 in free talk time when they trade in a 2G phone.
Postpaid customers on Silver Plan Combo 1 and 2 will receive a 20% discount on their monthly bills.</description></item><item><title>Get double the mobile data for just a small increase with Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Coinciding with the start of IT Show 2016, Singtel is introducing DataX2, a new service that doubles customers&amp;rsquo; monthly mobile data for a fixed price of S$5.90. This new option reflects Singtel&amp;rsquo;s focus on data-driven services, building on the success of last year&amp;rsquo;s SIM Only Plan.
DataX2 lets customers double their data when they sign up for or renew a Combo Mobile Plan (Combo 2 or higher).</description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Singapore polytechnics on initiatives for small and medium enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Singtel is partnering with Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) and Singapore Polytechnic (SP) to equip small and medium enterprises (SMEs) with digital skills, as part of the 99% SME initiative. This partnership aims to help SMEs in the retail and food and beverage industries thrive in the digital world.
The collaboration with NYP&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Institute of Retail Studies (SIRS) will connect SMEs with re-skilled professionals who can guide them in e-commerce, data analysis, and digital marketing strategies.</description></item><item><title>Starting on August 17, Singtel will be accepting pre-orders for the Samsung Galaxy Note7</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:27:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The Galaxy Note7.
Singtel has revealed that registered customers can pre-order Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Galaxy Note7 starting August 17th. Pre-orders will be delivered or available for pickup on August 19th, preceding the official launch.
The large-screen Galaxy Note7 and its S Pen boast IP68 certification, making them water and dust resistant. The Note7 features cutting-edge iris recognition technology for enhanced security, complementing the defense-grade Samsung Knox security platform for an unparalleled level of protection and user-friendliness.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new XO Plus plans powered by 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-xo-plus-plans-powered-by-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-xo-plus-plans-powered-by-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Singtel&amp;rsquo;s new XO Plus plans come with 5G access, large data packages, and a free three-month subscription to both AR educational materials and live VR music experiences.
Singtel is introducing a new generation of XO plans, bringing customers into the 5G era. These XO Plus plans offer an enhanced mobile experience, featuring the newest 5G phones, data plans up to 150 GB, 5G connectivity, and complimentary three-month subscriptions to Bookful, an augmented reality (AR) educational content platform, and MelodyVR, which provides virtual reality (VR) live music experiences.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV set top boxes will now include the Netflix app for seamless integration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</guid><description>Singtel is integrating the Netflix app into their TV set-top boxes. This means customers can easily access Netflix content directly on their TVs.
Subscribers with set-top boxes connected to Singtel Fibre Broadband can find Netflix on Channel 404 or by using the Quick Access Button on their remote. This feature will be rolled out gradually and should be available to all customers by the end of April.
Through an exclusive partnership, Singtel is offering customers up to nine free months of Netflix when they re-contract or sign up for eligible mobile, fiber broadband, and Singtel TV plans.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new LVL UP plan tailored for young people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The LVL UP plan is targeted at youths.
Singtel introduced a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;LVL UP&amp;rdquo; for young adults, coinciding with the start of The PC Show 2017. The name, inspired by the gaming term &amp;ldquo;level up,&amp;rdquo; signifies advancement to higher levels of difficulty in games. This plan provides free upgrades for Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Youth Combo plans and additional data.
This plan, available to students and full-time National Servicemen aged 26 and under, offers close to S$600 in savings over two years.</description></item><item><title>Obtain a prepaid virtual Visa account through Singtel Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one mobile payments app, Dash, now features Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first virtual Visa account. All Dash users, new and existing, will automatically receive a Dash Visa Virtual Account. This account can be used for mobile payments at over 50,000 merchant locations in Singapore.
To use the mobile payment feature, customers sign in to the Dash app, add funds to their Dash Visa accounts, and make purchases at Dash merchants and participating e-commerce websites like Qoo10, Zalora, and HungryGoWhere.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with the addition of HBO</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</guid><description>Singtel is adding HBO programming to its television offerings. The deal means Singtel TV and its Singtel TV GO app users will have access to HBO Asia’s six channels. To mark the occasion, Singtel is offering a free preview of all six channels until February 28, 2019.
Beginning March 15, subscribers can access HBO GO, HBO Asia’s streaming service, through CAST, Singtel’s video app for mobile and smart TV.
Yuen Kuan Moon, CEO, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, said the company is “thrilled” to welcome HBO to its roster.</description></item><item><title>Singtel celebrates National Day with Olympics film honoring Singapore's resilient spirit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 21:42:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</guid><description>Singtel has chosen an Olympics theme for its annual National Day (August 8) tribute.
Source: Singtel. Sprinter Shanti Pereira is featured in Leading Through Uncertainty, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s National Day tribute for 2021.
This year&amp;rsquo;s film, Leading Through Uncertainty, spotlights several of the nation&amp;rsquo;s top athletes who represented Singapore at the 2020 Olympics in Tokyo. It chronicles the athletes&amp;rsquo; journey to the Games amidst the uncertainty of the COVID-19 pandemic and its impact on the 2020 Games.</description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds.</description></item><item><title>The Nathan Hartono concert is brought to you by Singtel Music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:45:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Singtel Music presents Hartono concert.
At the beginning of 2017, music enthusiasts will have the opportunity to connect with Singaporean singing star Nathan Hartono. Singtel Music is showcasing its support for local musical talent by holding an exclusive event, Up-Close with Nathan Hartono, on January 21, 2017.
Singtel states that fans can experience Hartono&amp;rsquo;s performance and interact with him during the event. Hartono, backed by a full band, will perform a selection of songs in both English and Chinese, including new original pieces from his EP scheduled for release in early 2017.</description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Airtel to launch hi!India plans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:05:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</guid><description>Singtel and Airtel have partnered to provide Singtel prepaid mobile customers with access to high-quality calls to India through the Airtel Talk app. This service was previously only available to credit card holders.
Now, Singtel prepaid customers can utilize Airtel Talk by purchasing hi!India plans using their prepaid credits. Calls made through Airtel Talk are transmitted via standard IDD lines, resulting in enhanced call clarity.
Hi!India plans start at S$5 for 100 minutes (S$0.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides eSIMs for the Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</guid><description>Source: Samsung website. This Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch functions on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE network.
Singtel has launched the Samsung Gear S3 frontier (LTE) on its 4G LTE network. Equipped with an eSIM, this smartwatch offers independent 4G LTE connectivity. This allows users to make and receive calls, send text messages, and browse the internet without needing their smartphones.
Singtel customers will also experience 4G ClearVoice, also known as VoLTE.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces Malaysia's tonton to its CAST app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</guid><description>Singtel has added Media Prima&amp;rsquo;s tonton, a popular Malaysian streaming platform, to its CAST video streaming app. This partnership, along with existing offerings on Singtel TV, makes Singtel a leading provider of Malay entertainment content in Singapore.
This is the first time tonton is available outside of Malaysia. Through CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus pack, subscribers will have access to over 23,000 hours of Malay entertainment, including content from TV3, TV9, and tonton originals.</description></item><item><title>Singtel hosts launch event for iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:08:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Singtel began offering the iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus to customers this morning. Eager customers with confirmed appointments started lining up as early as 4:45 am, hoping to be among the first in Singapore to get their hands on the new devices.
Over 40,000 customers expressed interest in the new iPhones, and all 12,000 launch appointment slots were booked. The iPhone 6s Plus and the rose gold models were particularly popular, selling out in less than three minutes.</description></item><item><title>Fans in Singapore of Song Seung Heon may have the opportunity to meet him</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for Saimdang featuring Song.
To kick off the new year, Singtel is bringing South Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon to Singapore on January 7, 2017. Song&amp;rsquo;s visit will promote the drama Saimdang (师任堂), which premieres on Singtel TV&amp;rsquo;s Oh!K channel (channel 525/611) on January 25, 2017, at 9 pm.
Singtel TV subscribers can enter to win 20 pairs of tickets to a meet-and-greet and autograph session with Song.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill.</description></item><item><title>The Aneka Plus pack on Singtel CAST now features Tribe from Astro</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The show &amp;ldquo;Qadr&amp;rdquo; from Tribe is now available through CAST.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CAST platform now includes Tribe, a regional video service by Astro. Showcasing content from Astro&amp;rsquo;s Malay channels, like Astro Ria and Astro Prima, Tribe will be part of CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus package.
For the first time in Singapore, viewers can access Astro&amp;rsquo;s premium on-demand Malay programs anywhere. Tribe offers complete seasons of drama series, variety shows, movies, and award shows.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>Singtel will provide ZoneAlarm Mobile Security protection from Check Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:16:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</guid><description>Singtel has partnered with Check Point Software Technologies to launch ZoneAlarm Mobile Security. This mobile security app offers extensive protection against digital threats like malware, hacking attempts, and Wi-Fi attacks.
ZoneAlarm, available for both iOS and Android devices, conducts thorough risk evaluations. It scans installed applications, identifies unsafe Wi-Fi networks, and suggests the safest Wi-Fi hotspot choices. Additionally, it alerts users of any questionable processes running on their phones and safeguards their operating systems from attacks.</description></item><item><title>Singtel announces pricing for iPhone SE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Singtel has revealed its plans to offer Apple&amp;rsquo;s 4-inch iPhone SE starting March 31, 2016. Customers can pre-order the device now. A 16 GB model with the most affordable plan, costing S$27.90 per month for two years, is priced at S$350.
The telecom provider recently conducted a crowdsourced study, highlighting its superior 4G network speed and coverage in Singapore. The study, based on data from IDA&amp;rsquo;s MyConnection SG crowdsourced survey and 4G Mobile Service Coverage results, positioned Singtel as a frontrunner.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is encouraging subscribers to use their phones for payment at the supermarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</guid><description>A picture of a Dash payment reader at a FairPrice checkout.
Starting November 17th, shoppers can use Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash mobile payment app at over 200 NTUC FairPrice locations, including their supermarkets, Xtra hypermarkets, and standalone Cheers stores.
Gan Siok Hoon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of mCommerce, Consumer Singapore, stated that as a major fintech provider, they were excited to partner with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer, FairPrice, to offer this fast and secure payment option to their over half a million daily shoppers.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel Cyber Security Institute aims to enhance the skills of individuals and businesses in the field of cyber security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</guid><description>Singapore Telecommunications established the Singtel Cyber Security Institute (CSI) to bolster the cyber security skills of businesses and governments in the Asia Pacific region. The CSI is the first organization of its kind in the region, merging an advanced cyber range with an educational institute to provide companies with realistic training to handle complex cyber threats.
Bill Chang, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Group Enterprise CEO, highlighted the lack of preparedness among companies, with over 85% lacking robust cyber response plans or realistic training opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Singtel customers enjoy the top roaming experience in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Opensignal. 4G download speed experience in Mbps for Singapore roamers in Malaysia compared to the experience for Malaysian mobile users.
A 2019 Opensignal study on Singaporean 4G users roaming in Malaysia revealed that Singtel subscribers had the best download speeds, upload speeds, and latency.
M1 and StarHub users experienced comparable download and upload speeds while in Malaysia. However, StarHub users enjoyed better latency compared to M1. Although both StarHub and M1 users faced significantly slower latency than Malaysian domestic users, indicating a poorer experience, Singtel users only lagged behind domestic Maxis users by 2.</description></item><item><title>Singtel Music is excited to announce the addition of TIDAL to its portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</guid><description>Singtel Music now offers its customers access to the global music and entertainment platform, TIDAL.
TIDAL differentiates itself as the sole music app providing high-fidelity, lossless audio quality and exclusive content from top global artists. Singtel Music users can enjoy both TIDAL Premium and TIDAL HIFI without impacting their data plans.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its music streaming options. Following the addition of Saavn in October, TIDAL further solidifies Singtel Music&amp;rsquo;s goal of providing the best music streaming experience with diverse content, attractive pricing, and no data charges.</description></item><item><title>Tickets for the Nathan Hartono showcase are now available through Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tickets-for-the-nathan-hartono-showcase-are-now-available-through-singtel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 23:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tickets-for-the-nathan-hartono-showcase-are-now-available-through-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Nathan Hartono recently held a live performance on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page.
Nathan Hartono&amp;rsquo;s performance video, broadcasted on Singtel’s Facebook page last week, has garnered over 99,000 views and is still climbing. This event is a continuation of Singtel’s Christmas tradition of giving back to the community and supporting the Singtel Touching Lives Fund.
During the event, organized by Singtel to celebrate the festive season and spread generosity, fans could interact with Hartono and request song dedications for their loved ones.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash is running a flash campaign offering mystery cashback for purchases made on Lazada.SG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment app, Dash, is holding a short promotional campaign with online store Lazada.SG. From October 2nd to 9th, 2015, shoppers can receive a surprise cashback reward of 15% to 50%*.
Each day of the campaign features a &amp;ldquo;Dash Happy Hour.&amp;rdquo; During this limited time frame, which lasts up to two hours, customers using Dash to pay for purchases on Lazada.SG can earn cashback. The specific cashback amount won&amp;rsquo;t be disclosed until the end of each day and will be added to customer accounts within three business days.</description></item><item><title>The 5-Min Video Challenge has been introduced by the Singtel Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</guid><description>Source: The 5-Min Video Challenge website. Invitation to enter the local rounds.
Singtel Group launched The 5-Min Video Challenge to promote creative content across its global markets. The competition is a collaborative effort among Singtel&amp;rsquo;s associates, including Optus, AIS, Airtel, Globe, and Telkomsel. Winning videos will be shared with over 600 million customers within the Singtel Group.
Content creation is a key element of the Group&amp;rsquo;s strategy for customer engagement in a world where mobile devices are everywhere and demand for online video entertainment is high.</description></item><item><title>The video-on-demand service HOOQ has been launched in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 06:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: HOOQ. Bithos.
HOOQ, a leading premium video-on-demand service targeting the Asian market, has officially launched in Singapore. This expansion follows successful launches in the Philippines, Thailand, India, and Indonesia, bringing their reach to a potential audience exceeding 1.6 billion people.
Established in Singapore in 2015, HOOQ is a joint venture between Singtel, Sony Pictures Television, and Warner Brothers. This partnership represents a significant collaboration between major media companies to revolutionize entertainment consumption in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Singtel now offers budget-friendly roaming options for Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
Singtel is introducing a new &amp;ldquo;Roam Like Home&amp;rdquo; DataRoam Saver plan for customers traveling to Australia. The DataRoam Saver Australia (Monthly) 1 GB plan is currently offered at a promotional price of S$10 for the first gigabyte of data. After exceeding this limit, users will be charged S$0.10 per megabyte.
Singtel claims this plan is the most budget-friendly option available and builds upon the success of the DataRoam Saver Malaysia (Monthly) 1 GB plan launched last October.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has launched new mobile plans that include HBO content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</guid><description>Singtel has launched three innovative &amp;ldquo;XO&amp;rdquo; postpaid mobile plans, the first to offer premium entertainment as part of the package.
These new XO plans are designed to provide both generous data allowances and significant handset discounts, offering customers the best of both worlds. Additionally, XO plans include an HBO GO subscription, giving customers access to top-tier video entertainment.
The XO 78 Plan provides customers with 30 GB of data, 300 minutes of talk time, 300 SMS messages, and a 24-month HBO GO subscription for S$78 per month.</description></item><item><title>Singtel releases National Day video and shows support for SEA Games 2017 athletes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-releases-national-day-video-and-shows-support-for-sea-games-2017-athletes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 04:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-releases-national-day-video-and-shows-support-for-sea-games-2017-athletes/</guid><description>Singtel has launched its first significant National Day video celebrating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s independence. Released after August 9th, the company aims to motivate Singaporeans to maintain the spirit of &amp;ldquo;Majulah,&amp;rdquo; meaning &amp;ldquo;onward&amp;rdquo; in Malay, even after the National Day festivities.
Lian Pek, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP for Group Strategic Communications and Brand, explained that the slightly delayed release is intentional. Singtel wants to extend the enthusiasm from the National Day celebrations and inspire ongoing national pride and a desire to contribute to Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Newsstand service is launched by Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/newsstand-service-is-launched-by-singtel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/newsstand-service-is-launched-by-singtel/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singtel Newsstand, a service providing discounted digital subscriptions to major international and local newspapers and magazines. Subscribers can save up to 20% off standard rates.
Singtel postpaid mobile subscribers can access global news, business, and lifestyle content, including podcasts and videos, without using their local mobile data.
Initially, Singtel Newsstand will feature The Straits Times and international publications like The Wall Street Journal, TIME Magazine, and Fortune Magazine.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing a football package that includes both Copa America and UEFA Euro 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Singtel will broadcast the Copa America Centenario USA 2016. This competition is the oldest international tournament for nations in the Americas and features top players like Alexis Sanchez, Lionel Messi, and Luis Suárez. This year, for the first time, the tournament will be hosted outside of South America.
Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director, Home, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, stated that combining Copa America 2016 and UEFA Euro 2016 broadcasts allows Singtel to provide fans with two of the most exciting football events globally.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is dedicated to improving its services and is now providing Better Thursdays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 03:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. The new logo at Singtel headquarters in Singapore.
Singtel recently introduced a refreshed brand identity, the first update in 16 years, with the tagline &amp;ldquo;Let’s make everyday better&amp;rdquo;. This signifies a new chapter in Singtel’s evolution beyond traditional telecommunications, expanding into multimedia and ICT services.
Chua Sock Koong, Singtel Group CEO, stated: “Singtel is a familiar name for many generations in Singapore. We are seen as a dependable and trusted brand at the forefront of technology.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils new flagship store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-new-flagship-store/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 07:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-new-flagship-store/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. From left: Anna Yip, Deputy CEO, Singtel Singapore; Yuen Kuan Moon, Group CEO, Singtel; Ng Tian Chong, CEO, Singtel Singapore; and Lionel Chng, MD, Customer Success, Singtel Singapore.
Singtel just launched its latest flagship store, Singtel Shop 313@Somerset, in the middle of Orchard Road. This 4,900 square foot space showcases cutting-edge retail technology to create an enhanced customer experience for shopping, creating, and entertainment. This new store represents Singtel Singapore&amp;rsquo;s renewed dedication to improving the customer experience.</description></item><item><title>Customers who are retrenched will have their bills waived by Singtel Bill Protect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-are-retrenched-will-have-their-bills-waived-by-singtel-bill-protect/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-are-retrenched-will-have-their-bills-waived-by-singtel-bill-protect/</guid><description>Singtel and Etiqa Insurance Singapore have teamed up to introduce Singtel Bill Protect, a free insurance plan designed to help Singaporeans navigate tough economic times and maintain their connectivity even if they encounter financial difficulties. This launch comes as retrenchments in Singapore have increased for three consecutive quarters, according to the Ministry of Manpower&amp;rsquo;s latest labor market reports.
In response to growing economic uncertainty and job insecurity, the Bill Protect plan aims to support Singtel customers experiencing financial strain due to job loss by providing waivers on their upcoming Singtel mobile and fixed broadband bills.</description></item><item><title>Insurance is now available through Singtel's Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash app is launching Dash EasyEarn, a new financial product offering a 2% annual return. This insurance savings plan is available exclusively through the Dash app and is backed by Etiqa Insurance.
Source: Singtel. Dash EasyEarn is a fully digital insurance product, allowing users to manage their plans entirely through the Singtel Dash app.
This innovative addition to the Dash app, which already provides various services like payments and mobile top-ups, aims to make saving simple and accessible.</description></item><item><title>Customers of Singtel and AIA Singapore will enjoy the advantages of digital wellness initiatives offered in collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 05:51:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</guid><description>Singtel and AIA Singapore are joining forces to encourage healthier lifestyles in Singapore. This partnership between leaders in communications technology and life insurance is the first of its kind in the country.
The collaboration aims to digitally reach their combined customer base of over 5 million, motivating them to be active and healthy. They also intend to develop innovative insurance products tailored to the evolving digital habits of their customers.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and Riot Games Southeast Asia introduce the world's first gaming bundles for League of Legends: Wild Rift that are zero-rated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-riot-games-southeast-asia-introduce-the-world-s-first-gaming-bundles-for-league-of-legends-wild-rift-that-are-zero-rated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-riot-games-southeast-asia-introduce-the-world-s-first-gaming-bundles-for-league-of-legends-wild-rift-that-are-zero-rated/</guid><description>Singtel has teamed up with Riot Games Southeast Asia to launch the first-ever zero-rated gaming bundles for League of Legends: Wild Rift. Zero-rating means data used for a specific activity won&amp;rsquo;t count towards a user&amp;rsquo;s data limit and won&amp;rsquo;t incur extra charges.
League of Legends: Wild Rift, a five-versus-five mobile multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA), brings the popular PC game League of Legends to mobile devices.
These new RiotGO and RiotGO+ bundles, available exclusively for Singtel postpaid mobile customers, offer unlimited data-free gameplay and up to S$40 worth of in-game content for Wild Rift.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singtel's Chinese New Year short film is on building connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Stills from the festive video emphasizing the importance of positive connections.
Singtel released its yearly short film for the Lunar New Year season. This year&amp;rsquo;s film uses humor to highlight the importance of connecting with others and nurturing relationships. The lighthearted short, His Grandfather’s Road, portrays a heated encounter between two families during the holiday rush. However, their road rage takes an unexpected turn when they discover shared ground and end their confrontation amicably.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is showcasing career opportunities in the field of cyber security to the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 23:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</guid><description>Singtel launched the Singtel Cyber Security Experience (CSX), an interactive online platform, to bolster Singapore&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity workforce. This portal aims to attract students and career changers to the field.
CSX showcases cybersecurity career paths through profiles of professionals from Singtel, Trustwave (its US-based subsidiary), and the Cyber Security Agency of Singapore (CSA). The platform features interactive simulations that mimic real-world scenarios, illustrating the skills needed for various roles.
Visitors can test their knowledge through challenges focused on fundamental cybersecurity concepts.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing complimentary content and data to commemorate Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 51st birthday on August 9th, Singtel is offering customers complimentary mobile data, alongside free access to Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO.
Postpaid mobile users will enjoy free data from 12:01 am to 11:59 pm on August 9th, allowing them to connect with family and friends on social media, stream music, and watch videos.
From August 5th to 9th, Singtel TV subscribers will have free access to over 140 channels, including popular options like Disney Channel, National Geographic Channel HD, FOX Movie Premium HD, KBS World HD, Astro Ria, and Sun TV.</description></item><item><title>Dash has increased its services in response to the COVID-19 outbreak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 05:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</guid><description>Dash, a mobile wallet by Singtel, is introducing new features to assist customers and partners during the COVID-19 pandemic. These features offer more convenient options for sending money, shopping online, and connecting businesses with customers while social distancing measures are in place.
Dash is providing free mobile remittance services to help employers and foreign workers in Singapore affected by stay-at-home guidelines and travel restrictions. This service allows for secure digital money transfers to seven countries: Bangladesh, China, India, Indonesia, Malaysia, Myanmar, and the Philippines.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel NumberShare service is compatible with the Apple Watch Series 3, which comes with built-in cellular capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</guid><description>Singtel is the first in Singapore to offer Apple Watch Series 3 (GPS + Cellular), allowing users to stay connected without their iPhones. The watch has been available in Singapore since September 2017 and works with compatible plans.
Apple Watch Series 3 with cellular enables users to stay in touch, make calls, and send and receive texts without needing their iPhones nearby, as long as their carrier provides a compatible plan.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides triple the mobile data for a low price, along with Wi-Fi calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</guid><description>Singtel launched a new mobile data add-on called DataX3 at their iPhone 7 event held at Marina Bay Sands Convention Centre. For S$9.90 per month, DataX3 allows customers to triple their mobile data limit. This add-on is available to Singtel Combo Plan customers (Combo 2 and above). It follows the successful launch of the DataX2 add-on earlier this year.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, highlighted the importance of affordable mobile data for communication, shopping, banking, and entertainment in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>