<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Voice and Data on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voice-and-data/</link><description>Recent content in Voice and Data on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voice-and-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Bandwidth is Cheap Downtown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</guid><description>Want to increase your business internet speed without breaking the bank? Head downtown! The city center offers more competition and cheaper prices than anywhere else. Can&amp;rsquo;t relocate for better bandwidth deals? There&amp;rsquo;s a comparable solution that works for many businesses.
Why is bandwidth cheaper downtown when real estate is so expensive? The answer is density. Imagine real estate as a pie: limited supply and high demand for the best slices drive up prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed IP Networks Enable Voice and Data Convergence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 04:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</guid><description>Businesses have been looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing service, and combining their computer and telephone networks into a single, multi-functional LAN that can connect to the public Internet and phone network seems like a good way to do it. Ideally, this means one network, one connection per desk, and one support team. However, the reality isn&amp;rsquo;t always so simple.
The reason for this is that computers and telephones use networks in very different ways...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dynamically Allocate T1 Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a reliable choice for transmitting voice and data for many years. Traditionally, it was believed that the purpose of the line (voice or data) needed to be determined before installation. For voice communication, a channelized T1 line or ISDN PRI configuration was used, with each of the 23 or 24 channels dedicated to a single phone call. Conversely, a clear channel T1 line was used for point-to-point data transmission or dedicated internet access, allowing for the full 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PRI over Cable Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 01:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</guid><description>Many businesses use ISDN PRI, a technology that bundles multiple phone lines onto a single digital cable, for cost-effective phone service. While initially implemented with T1 lines, offering 23 usable voice channels after reserving one for signaling, ISDN PRI can now be delivered over cable networks.
Modern phone systems, including PBX and key systems, typically support ISDN PRI, allowing businesses to scale their phone lines up to 46, 69, 92, or more...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telephone and Internet for Chain Stores</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</guid><description>Cost-conscious small businesses need reliable communication systems. They can&amp;rsquo;t risk losing customers due to failed credit card transactions or dropped calls. Businesses with multiple locations also need efficient ways to connect their operations. Integrated T1 offers a solution that addresses these needs while staying budget-friendly.
Integrated T1 merges voice and data services onto a single line, combining the reliability of T1 phone lines with the efficiency of T1 internet connections. This approach minimizes costs without sacrificing quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>