<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>10 Gbps on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/10-gbps/</link><description>Recent content in 10 Gbps on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/10-gbps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>