<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computing/</link><description>Recent content in Computing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Service Providers Colocate With Customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</guid><description>A new trend is emerging, and it&amp;rsquo;s not just about companies moving their data to the cloud. Now, cloud service providers are moving into the same facilities as their customers.
Why is this happening? Companies are realizing that running applications on distant servers can&amp;rsquo;t match the speed of having them on-site. While this can be addressed by investing in high-bandwidth, low-latency connections, it&amp;rsquo;s often more cost-effective to simply be in the same location as your provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Benefit From New Cloud Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about cloud computing and might be wondering if it can help your small or medium-sized business (SMB). While it seems like cloud services are designed for large corporations, they offer significant potential for businesses of all sizes.
The cloud can be even more beneficial for SMBs because it levels the playing field. Large companies often have the resources to build their own private clouds, while smaller companies may struggle with the cost and staffing required for such an undertaking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>