<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Apple on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apple/</link><description>Recent content in Apple on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple has revealed that the Apple Watch will be available in additional countries starting on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Apple has announced the availability of the Apple Watch in more countries, including Singapore, South Korea, and Taiwan, starting June 26th. The smartwatch will be sold through Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, and authorized retailers.
Select retailers such as BOONTHESHOP Cheongdam in Seoul and Malmaison by The Hour Glass in Singapore will offer a curated collection of Apple Watch models at launch. In the Asia Pacific region, the Apple Watch is already for sale in Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, and Japan.</description></item><item><title>Now, you have the ability to answer calls directly on your Apple Watch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple Watch 3 includes phone capabilities.
Apple has launched the Apple Watch Series 3, a smartwatch with built-in cellular capabilities. With this new feature, users can make and receive calls and texts, and stay connected even when they don&amp;rsquo;t have their iPhone nearby.
This third-generation Apple Watch is designed for health and fitness, offering smart coaching features, water resistance up to 50 meters, and a new barometric altimeter for measuring elevation changes.</description></item><item><title>Apple reveals special edition iPhone to celebrate 10th anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-reveals-special-edition-iphone-to-celebrate-10th-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:35:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-reveals-special-edition-iphone-to-celebrate-10th-anniversary/</guid><description>Image Source: Apple. The iPhone X is dust- and water-resistant.
Apple has unveiled the iPhone X, its tenth-anniversary smartphone, sporting an all-glass design. Although Samsung phones already offered some of the phone&amp;rsquo;s debut features, the iPhone X introduces facial recognition for unlocking, authentication, and payments, alongside the ability to animate emojis with facial expressions.
The iPhone X boasts a 5.8&amp;quot; Super Retina display, A11 Bionic chip, wireless charging, and an upgraded rear camera with dual optical image stabilization.</description></item><item><title>Guvera introduces support for Apple TV and updates its product</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</guid><description>Source: Guvera.
Guvera, a music streaming service supported by brand funding, has announced significant upgrades to its product and compatibility with Apple TV.
The updated Guvera 3.0 app introduces music channels and a variety of new editorial features. These include artist interviews, news articles, reviews, photo galleries, brand competitions, and product promotions.
Hazel Savage, Head of Marketing and Operations for Guvera Asia, stated that the company recognizes that music is more than just individual tracks; it represents a whole culture and way of life.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Final 3D Printed Part Added</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</guid><description>I have completed the final 3D printed component for my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control system. This piece fits into a 10mm opening on the remote control receiver board, allowing it to be secured using one of the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s screws. The image below shows the part with the screw in place:
Once the remote control board is in place, the original screw can be used to fasten it. The cylindrical portion is designed to prevent the remote board from pressing against the component pins on the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main PCB while ensuring a secure fit.</description></item><item><title>Pre-orders for the Apple Watch will begin on April 10th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-apple-watch-will-begin-on-april-10th/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-apple-watch-will-begin-on-april-10th/</guid><description>Source: Apple website. The Apple Watch Edition can cost up to US$17,000.
Apple has revealed the release dates for the Apple Watch, a device that combines the functions of a timepiece, communication tool, and health and fitness tracker. Starting on April 24th, it will be available in Australia, Canada, mainland China, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, the UK, and the US.
What it does With the Apple Watch, users can send messages, check email, and answer calls received on their iPhone directly from their wrist.</description></item><item><title>Starting today, the Apple iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are now available in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 04:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus will be offered in China starting October 17th through various channels like Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, major carriers, and authorized retailers. These smartphones will also be available in 36 more countries and territories by the end of October, reaching a total of over 115 countries by the year&amp;rsquo;s end.
Source: Apple. The iPhone 6 and
the iPhone 6 Plus.
Both iPhone models support TD-LTE and FDD-LTE, allowing customers to use 4G/LTE networks from China Mobile, China Telecom, and China Unicom throughout mainland China.</description></item><item><title>Can iPhone 3G S Be The Universal Gadget?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-iphone-3g-s-be-the-universal-gadget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 17:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-iphone-3g-s-be-the-universal-gadget/</guid><description>People love electronics but hate carrying a lot of them around. A single, universal gadget would be ideal – one that combines the functions of a cell phone, TV, camera, computer, and more.
Such a device would need to be a phone, TV, DVR, high-quality camera, camcorder, audio recorder, navigation system, gaming console, computer, messaging system, productivity tool, radio, eBook reader, music player, stock trading platform, watch, alarm clock, weather tracker, and shopping service.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has announced that the iPad Pro is now available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-announced-that-the-ipad-pro-is-now-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-announced-that-the-ipad-pro-is-now-available/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Singtel now offers the new iPad Pro with Wi-Fi + Cellular. This tablet boasts a 12.9-inch Retina display, packing 5.6 million pixels for exceptional resolution, and its size rivals some laptops. Customers can also purchase smart cases and silicone covers.
According to a Singtel representative, &amp;ldquo;Singtel will offer iPad Pro with a variety of attractive data plans that will allow customers to connect to its tri-band 4G network.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a 3D Printed Installation Tray</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control upgrade, specifically the receiver board insulation. My previous solution, using plastic foil, wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal aesthetically.
To address this, I designed a plastic tray that safeguards the receiver board from the main circuit board&amp;rsquo;s solder points. The tray is designed to click into place without additional screws.
Here are some photos:
Tray and board before assembly:
The tray features three rectangular cutouts to provide clearance for the solder points.</description></item><item><title>Entry-level Mac receives a new look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entry-level-mac-receives-a-new-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entry-level-mac-receives-a-new-look/</guid><description>Apple has reduced the starting price of the Mac mini, making it their most affordable computer.
The updated Mac mini features a fourth-generation Intel Core processor, improved integrated graphics, 802.11ac Wi-Fi, and Thunderbolt 2 connectivity.
According to Philip Schiller, Apple’s Senior VP of Worldwide Marketing, the Mac mini is a great starting point for new Mac users. He highlights the latest CPU, graphics, faster Wi-Fi, two Thunderbolt 2 ports, OS X Yosemite, and a starting price of just US$499 as key features.</description></item><item><title>StarHub shows appreciation for loyal customers during iPhone launch by offering rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-shows-appreciation-for-loyal-customers-during-iphone-launch-by-offering-rewards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-shows-appreciation-for-loyal-customers-during-iphone-launch-by-offering-rewards/</guid><description>Four loyal StarHub customers were treated to an exclusive experience: becoming the first in Singapore to own and activate the new iPhone. They enjoyed a luxurious supercar ride to StarHub&amp;rsquo;s flagship store in Plaza Singapura for the launch event.
At the store, they were greeted by StarHub executives, including Chief Executive Peter Kaliaropoulos. At precisely 8 am, the four customers activated their new iPhones, marking them as the first users in Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This article details the installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control Module into a Beogram 4002 (Type 5504) turntable. This particular unit was restored for a customer in Australia and also features an internal Beolover RIAA phono pre-amplifier.
The Commander Module, seen here before installation, allows for remote control of the turntable:
The module includes an IR receiver (black wire at the bottom), an adapter board (narrow board on the right), a wiring harness (white wires), and an auto-repeat indicator (red wire at the top).</description></item><item><title>iOS 9 has been released by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple has announced that its latest mobile operating system, iOS 9, will launch on September 16th. This free update for iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch users boasts enhanced search capabilities and improved Siri functionality.
One of the standout features of iOS 9 is its new multitasking capabilities for iPad. Users can now work with two apps concurrently, viewing them side-by-side. A Picture-in-Picture feature also allows for video playback while using other apps.</description></item><item><title>Apple has released new Apple Watch options, including the addition of the Hermès collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The Apple Watch.
Apple has launched new Apple Watch cases and bands, updated its watch operating system, and introduced new gold and rose gold aluminum models for the Apple Watch Sport.
Available as a free update on September 16, the watchOS 2 operating system delivers new features and native third-party apps to Apple Watches. With watchOS 2, apps run faster. Users will also find new watch faces, third-party app information viewable on the watch face, and a &amp;ldquo;Time Travel&amp;rdquo; feature that provides chronological context.</description></item><item><title>Singtel hosts launch event for iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:08:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Singtel began offering the iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus to customers this morning. Eager customers with confirmed appointments started lining up as early as 4:45 am, hoping to be among the first in Singapore to get their hands on the new devices.
Over 40,000 customers expressed interest in the new iPhones, and all 12,000 launch appointment slots were booked. The iPhone 6s Plus and the rose gold models were particularly popular, selling out in less than three minutes.</description></item><item><title>The iPhone SE is introduced by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 06:02:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Apple has launched the iPhone SE, boasting a 4-inch display and impressive processing power in a familiar compact design. This updated model features smooth, angled edges, a color-coordinated stainless steel Apple logo, and a choice of four metallic finishes, including rose gold.
“The iPhone SE is a fresh take on a beloved design — we took a popular, iconic look and completely redesigned its internals.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Installation Video</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 &amp;ldquo;Commander&amp;rdquo; remote control system has recently seen a surge in popularity, with multiple orders coming in over a short time. This could be linked to the Commander&amp;rsquo;s new compatibility with a specific Apple TV remote, allowing it to integrate with Apple devices in the same space. Designed for later models of the 4002 turntable with the keypad connector on the main circuit board (types 551x and 552x), I recently built three receivers over the weekend and shipped them out today, each packaged with a compatible Apple remote:</description></item><item><title>Singtel announces pricing for iPhone SE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Singtel has revealed its plans to offer Apple&amp;rsquo;s 4-inch iPhone SE starting March 31, 2016. Customers can pre-order the device now. A 16 GB model with the most affordable plan, costing S$27.90 per month for two years, is priced at S$350.
The telecom provider recently conducted a crowdsourced study, highlighting its superior 4G network speed and coverage in Singapore. The study, based on data from IDA&amp;rsquo;s MyConnection SG crowdsourced survey and 4G Mobile Service Coverage results, positioned Singtel as a frontrunner.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a Professionally Made PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</guid><description>I recently had a professionally made circuit board manufactured for the remote control receiver in my Beogram 4002 (5513). It was exciting to see the new board arrive and start assembling it.
The biggest changes in this design were simplifying the assembly by placing all the components on the top side and repositioning the ISP port to avoid interference with the aluminum top panel fixture. I also removed the reset button and made more space for the keypad connector.</description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay.</description></item><item><title>The latest Apple watches have the capability to contact someone in case of a fall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</guid><description>Apple has released the Apple Watch Series 4, a redesigned smartwatch focused on connectivity, activity tracking, and health management.
Maintaining its classic look, the fourth iteration boasts a 30% larger screen and a smaller, slimmer casing. This model introduces advanced fitness and communication features with watchOS 5, a new accelerometer and gyroscope for fall detection, and an electrical heart rate sensor that enables electrocardiograms (ECGs) through the new ECG app.</description></item><item><title>The Flickr App for iPad has been optimized for iOS 8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a new Flickr app designed for iPads, allowing users seamless photo management across all devices. Yahoo claims the app is optimized for iOS 8, providing an enhanced experience for capturing, editing, and browsing images.
Source: Yahoo.
Current iPad users can update their existing Flickr app, while new users can download it from the App Store. The app supports multiple languages, including English, French, Indonesian, Korean, Chinese, and Vietnamese.</description></item><item><title>The iPhone 8 and 8 Plus will be released in late September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-8-and-8-plus-will-be-released-in-late-september/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-8-and-8-plus-will-be-released-in-late-september/</guid><description>Apple has unveiled the iPhone 8 and iPhone 8 Plus, featuring a sleek glass and aluminum design available in three colors. The new models boast Retina HD displays, the powerful A11 Bionic chip, and are optimized for augmented reality (AR) experiences.
Source: Apple. The new iPhone 8 and iPhone
8 Plus feature all-glass designs.
The inclusion of single and dual cameras with Portrait Lighting on the iPhone 8 Plus, along with wireless charging capabilities, brings exciting new features to the iPhone lineup.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>The new iPad Air 2 from Apple is thinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-ipad-air-2-from-apple-is-thinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 11:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-ipad-air-2-from-apple-is-thinner/</guid><description>Apple unveiled its slimmest iPad yet, the iPad Air 2, at a highly anticipated event on October 16th.
The updated iPad boasts an enhanced Retina display for improved contrast, a richer color palette, and superior cameras. Available in gold, alongside the classic silver and space gray, both the iPad Air 2 and the new iPad mini 3 feature Touch ID. In the US, these models will also offer Apple Pay, a new payment system.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide.</description></item><item><title>StarHub announces pricing for newest iPhone models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 14:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone 11 Pro and iPhone 11 Pro Max are available in midnight green, space grey, silver, and gold finishes.
StarHub has quickly released pricing for the newly announced iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, and iPhone 11 Pro Max. The iPhone 11 Pro and iPhone 11 Pro Max represent a new generation of iPhones offering high-level performance.
According to Apple, the pro line boasts a new Super Retina XDR display, the brightest ever seen on an iPhone.</description></item><item><title>Fishbat provides commentary on the latest developments in iOS8 and the introduction of Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple, the tech giant, recently launched the first beta version of iOS 8.1. This upgrade comes shortly after the release of iOS 8.0.2, which was itself a fix for a bug found in the recently launched iOS 8.0.1.
This new beta version offers several new features:
A redesigned icon for iBooks. An option to enable dictation within the keyboard settings. Updated application permission settings. Larger application icons specifically designed for the new widgets in the notification center.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Apple Remote Controls All Functions of Turntable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</guid><description>After several weeks of testing, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my latest creation: a remote control receiver designed specifically for the Beogram 4002 (5513 model) turntable. This receiver seamlessly integrates with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s existing keypad connector without affecting its functionality.
The receiver board is compatible with the latest Apple TV remote, chosen for its sleek aluminum design that complements the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic. The remote&amp;rsquo;s minimalist button layout also aligns perfectly with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description></item><item><title>Starting from 26 September, StarHub is excited to welcome buyers of the iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 18:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Source: StarHub. Customers waiting in line inside the newly renovated StarHub Shop in VivoCity, one of 38 StarHub stores serving pre-order customers on September 25th.
On September 25th, pre-orders for Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus became available for pickup at 38 StarHub stores across Singapore. To ensure a smooth pickup process, customers who pre-ordered were given specific locations and time slots when they booked their appointments.
Starting September 26th, customers can visit any StarHub Shop or participating authorized retailers to purchase the phones directly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of Beolover RIAA Preamp and 4002 Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (5523), culminating in the installation of gold-plated RCA plugs. My customer opted to have my recently developed internal BeoloverRIAA preamplifier added, along with the 4002 Commander remote control system, which enables control of all functions via a paired Apple remote.
This marks the first 4002 to feature both the Commander and the RIAA preamp – a true fusion of past and present!
Pictures showcasing the installation process of the BeoloverRIAA board and the 4002 Commander are included.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander MkII: Remote Control for Beogram 4002 Now With Integrated Auto-Repeat Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable and planned to install my 4002 Commander Remote control system. This system is great because it keeps the keypad pristine and allows for operation without touching it. You can find demonstration and installation videos on my blog if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in upgrading your own 4002. The Commander board is compatible with all models equipped with a DC motor.
This restoration project inspired me to create an updated MkII version of the 4002 Commander, featuring an auto-repeat function similar to the Beogram 8000 and 8002 turntables.</description></item><item><title>The Apple Macbook is revolutionizing the laptop industry with its numerous innovative features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apple-macbook-is-revolutionizing-the-laptop-industry-with-its-numerous-innovative-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 02:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apple-macbook-is-revolutionizing-the-laptop-industry-with-its-numerous-innovative-features/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The new MacBook is offered in three aluminum finishes—gold, silver, and space gray. Its thickest point measures 13.1 mm.
Apple has introduced the redesigned MacBook, a new notebook lineup representing the thinnest and lightest Macs to date. Every aspect of the new MacBook has been meticulously redesigned to achieve a remarkably thin and light profile, weighing a mere two pounds and measuring a mere 13.1 mm thick.</description></item><item><title>Apple introduces the iMac featuring the Retina 5K display, the most advanced display resolution to date</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-introduces-the-imac-featuring-the-retina-5k-display-the-most-advanced-display-resolution-to-date/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-introduces-the-imac-featuring-the-retina-5k-display-the-most-advanced-display-resolution-to-date/</guid><description>Forget 4K, Apple has jumped ahead with 5K resolution.
Source: Apple.
Apple introduces the 27-inch iMac with a Retina 5K display, boasting the world’s highest resolution display with 14.7 million pixels. This advancement results in sharper text, more realistic videos, and an unprecedented level of detail in photographs.
“Thirty years after the first Mac revolutionized technology, the new iMac with Retina 5K display and OS X Yosemite is the most impressive Mac we&amp;rsquo;ve created,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s Senior VP of Worldwide Marketing.</description></item><item><title>Apple is recalling Beats speakers and offering refunds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</guid><description>Apple initiated a voluntary recall of Beats Pill XL speakers due to a potential fire safety risk. The company determined that in rare cases, the battery in these speakers may overheat.
This recall only affects the specific Beats Pill XL speaker model shown in the images and no other Beats or Apple products.
Apple prioritizes customer safety and urges all Beats Pill XL users to stop using their devices.
To return their speakers and receive a refund of US$325 (or equivalent in local currency) as Apple Store credit or electronic payment, owners can visit www.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of Beolover Commander MkII Remote and Internal RIAA Pre-Amp Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 09:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</guid><description>The owner of the Beogram 4002 (5513) requested the installation of a 4002 Commander remote control and an internal RIAA pre-amplifier module. The Commander enables complete control of the 4002 using an Apple remote, while the RIAA provides a strong output signal, allowing direct connection to modern amplifiers via CD/DVD/AUX inputs.
The first image displays the RIAA board and its mounting adapter, which elevates it above the output PCB headers.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean banks are getting their customers ready for Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 09:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s website in Singapore now features a dedicated page for Apple Pay, which includes a list of participating banks and retailers. Among the banks listed, DBS and POSB have almost identical images on their websites, and UOB also has a dedicated page. Standard Chartered currently does not have any information available. DBS clarifies that Apple Pay offers a fast and secure payment method compatible with a user&amp;rsquo;s preferred DBS card. Contactless payments are also supported for iPhone and Apple Watch users.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of 4002 Commander MkII Remote Control and Internal RIAA Preamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</guid><description>I recently completed a Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration, and the customer requested two upgrades I developed: the Beolover 4002 Commander MkII remote control receiver and the internal RIAA pre-amplifier. These upgrades are detailed further on my blog, along with installation instructions. Both are available for purchase; feel free to contact me for more information.
This image showcases both boards:
The lower board is the Commander MkII. This version includes a repeat function, indicated by the CD4 light on the keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Mass Production!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 02:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</guid><description>More orders for the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control have been placed. The Commander is now compatible with a designated Apple TV remote, eliminating interference with other Apple devices in the same room. Designed specifically for later models of the 4002 turntable (types 551x and 552x) that feature the keypad connector on the main circuit board, the Commander offers a simple plug-and-play installation process. Today, five new units were assembled.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel NumberShare service is compatible with the Apple Watch Series 3, which comes with built-in cellular capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</guid><description>Singtel is the first in Singapore to offer Apple Watch Series 3 (GPS + Cellular), allowing users to stay connected without their iPhones. The watch has been available in Singapore since September 2017 and works with compatible plans.
Apple Watch Series 3 with cellular enables users to stay in touch, make calls, and send and receive texts without needing their iPhones nearby, as long as their carrier provides a compatible plan.</description></item></channel></rss>