<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Theresa May on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/theresa-may/</link><description>Recent content in Theresa May on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/theresa-may/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the Prime Minister hinting at a potential shift in Brexit stance with his unexpected mention of competition policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</guid><description>Andreas Stephan, Professor of Competition Law &amp;amp; Head of UEA Law School, University of East Anglia*
In a speech delivered on March 2, 2018, Prime Minister Theresa May aimed to clarify the UK&amp;rsquo;s Brexit objectives. She proposed aligning UK State Aid and Competition rules with those of the EU, while allowing UK courts to consider European Court of Justice (ECJ) judgments. However, she emphasized that the ECJ would not have jurisdiction over the UK.</description></item><item><title>Brexit: The Prime Minister chooses the incorrect direction.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-the-prime-minister-chooses-the-incorrect-direction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 17:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-the-prime-minister-chooses-the-incorrect-direction/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Prime Minister Theresa May’s recent speech provided insights into the UK government’s approach to Brexit. While there were some positive takeaways, the speech ultimately presented a flawed vision for the country’s future.
Positive Aspects of the Speech
The speech commendably acknowledges that a successful EU remains in Britain’s best interest, both economically and in terms of security. May’s suggestions for the EU, though unlikely to be well-received, offer some sensible points.</description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals.</description></item></channel></rss>