<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Router on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-router/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Router on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-router/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Services Give Small Companies an Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</guid><description>During the ongoing economic downturn, businesses of all sizes face the challenge of maintaining competitive electronic services with limited budgets. Managed services present a solution, particularly for smaller companies lacking substantial IT departments and hiring capacity.
The concept of managed services is straightforward: you delegate management to an external provider. Consider your phone system. One option is to independently research, purchase, and install a PBX system, along with the necessary hardware and staff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>