<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WordPress on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wordpress/</link><description>Recent content in WordPress on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:33:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WordPress Hosting Made Cheap and Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/</guid><description>A lot of dedicated bloggers and website creators opt for WordPress to power their websites. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable and boasts a large community of developers who create themes and plugins. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to WordPress, you can start with the online version to learn the basics. However, you&amp;rsquo;ll eventually want the control and scalability that comes with hosting WordPress yourself.
Now you need to make a decision: Do you want to host WordPress the easy way or the hard way?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK Domains and Web Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-domains-and-web-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-domains-and-web-hosting/</guid><description>Network Solutions, a leading provider of domain registration and web hosting, offers a wide range of services tailored for users in the United Kingdom. These services extend beyond .co.uk domain names to include web hosting, email hosting for businesses, SSL certificates, and design and marketing solutions, catering to both UK-focused and global businesses.
](http://www.tkqlhce.com/click-1726600-10868378) While .uk is the UK&amp;rsquo;s designated country code top-level domain (ccTLD), registering a .uk domain differs from registering a ...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-domains-and-web-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-domains-and-web-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Web Application Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-web-application-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 01:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-web-application-hosting/</guid><description>You might want to utilize popular web applications for your business, but the technical hurdles of hosting, software updates, and maintenance can feel overwhelming, especially without a dedicated IT team.
There&amp;rsquo;s a solution: managed web applications. This service takes the burden of hardware and software management off your plate, effectively acting as your IT department. Similar to cloud computing, everything is handled externally for a recurring fee.
Myhosting.com specializes in managed web applications, offering standard hosting services along with specialized business solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-web-application-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-web-application-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The free WooCommerce WordPress plugin has reached 4 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 06:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</guid><description>WooThemes, a developer of WordPress themes, plugins, and shopping cart features, announced that its WooCommerce WordPress plugin has been downloaded over 4 million times. WooCommerce is WooThemes&amp;rsquo; free flagship product, officially partnered with companies like Amazon, Mastercard, and PayPal.
Source: WooThemes website.
WooCommerce enables businesses to operate e-commerce sites using WordPress as their content management system.
WooThemes uses a freemium model. The basic plugin and some add-ons are free, while more advanced extensions and themes require payment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Have Reseller Hosting When You Don’t Resell Anything?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:16:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</guid><description>Web hosting companies offer various plans, from shared hosting to dedicated servers and cloud services. One option is &amp;ldquo;reseller hosting,&amp;rdquo; which many website owners use without actually reselling hosting.
Many website owners use reseller hosting to manage multiple websites easily. Basic web hosting, like HostGator&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hatchling&amp;rdquo; plan, is affordable for individuals and small businesses with simple websites. These plans offer shared resources like disk space and bandwidth at a low cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>