<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crime Victims' Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crime-victims-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Crime Victims' Rights on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:46:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crime-victims-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do crime victims now have additional rights under EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
*This analysis is taken from the upcoming 4th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Victims of crime are often disheartened not just by the crime itself but also by the criminal justice system&amp;rsquo;s indifference to their needs. To tackle this issue, the EU introduced a Directive on crime victims’ rights in 2012 that Member States were required to implement by November 16, 2015. This law supersedes an earlier Framework Decision on this matter from 2001...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing Complex Legal Issues from a Legal Standpoint with Partiality and Passion, or The European Union's Approval of the Istanbul Convention: Jurisdiction, Foundations, and Consensus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - @CateBriddick*
On March 11, 2021, Advocate General Hogan of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) presented his legal opinion on the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s inquiry regarding the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) potential membership in the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Istanbul Convention)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's strategy to eliminate human trafficking is all talk and no action.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</guid><description>Dr Matilde Ventrella, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Wolverhampton (UK)
1. Introduction
The European Commission recently released two important documents on October 17th: a progress report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat human trafficking and a report on how a specific directive (Directive 2004/81) is being used to protect victims. This analysis will delve into the key findings of both reports and offer concluding observations.
2. Progress Report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s Fight Against Human Trafficking..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to effectively help in the prohibition of forced labor by the ILO?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although often used lightly, the term &amp;ldquo;wage slaves&amp;rdquo; reflects a harsh reality for millions trapped in forced labor globally, a modern form of slavery. This exploitation represents a significant aspect of human trafficking, alongside sexual exploitation.
Key international entities like the United Nations and the Council of Europe have been at the forefront of combating human trafficking. However, the International Labour Organisation (ILO) brings long-standing expertise, particularly concerning labor exploitation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dillon Judgment, Exemption of Laws, and Article 2 of the Northern Ireland Protocol/Windsor Framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD researcher, Queens University Belfast, and Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Aaronward, via Wikicommons media
In a landmark decision, a UK court has disapplied portions of a UK Act of Parliament for the first time since Brexit due to conflicts with the Withdrawal Agreement, specifically highlighting the ongoing connection between UK and EU legal systems. This unexpected development, though previously argued for, underscores the UK government&amp;rsquo;s consistent underestimation of Article 2&amp;rsquo;s impact on rights-related cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU truly dedicated to addressing violence against women, or is it just empty words?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre of the University of Oxford - @CateBriddick
Background
The European Union (EU) has a core legal commitment to fight discrimination, including sex-based discrimination, and to promote gender equality. However, it has faced ongoing and valid criticism for not upholding these commitments, especially regarding its treatment of female migrants and refugees. Therefore, the Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2016 announcement that the EU would sign and ratify the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women (the Istanbul Convention) was welcomed by activists and academics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Details of the upcoming referendum on Denmark's participation in EU Justice and Home Affairs Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Denmark&amp;rsquo;s involvement in international criminal law, exemplified by the TV show &amp;ldquo;The Bridge,&amp;rdquo; is facing uncertainty due to changing EU regulations. This situation will soon lead Denmark to vote on modifying its current near-total opt-out of EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) laws. While the general implications have been discussed, the specifics of this vote are now clearer.
To recap, Denmark negotiated opt-outs from the euro, defense, and parts of JHA law in 1992...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Number of Human Trafficking Victims in the EU: A Statistical Puzzle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</guid><description>Dr. Vladislava Stoyanova
Postdoctoral Fellow, Faculty of Law, Lund University; Author of Human Trafficking and Slavery Reconsidered. Conceptual Limits and States’ Positive Obligations in Europe (Cambridge University Press, 2017)
In May 2016, the European Commission presented its initial findings on the progress made in combating human trafficking. This report, mandated by the 2011 EU Trafficking Directive, examines advancements in prosecuting traffickers, safeguarding victims, and preventative measures. It highlights trafficking patterns, incorporating statistical data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's groundbreaking Directive 2024/1385 on Violence Against Women is a significant step forward in promoting gender equality.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</guid><description>Dr. Ceren Kasım, Postdoctoral Research and Teaching Fellow, University of Hildesheim, Germany
Photo credit: MesserWoland, via Wikimedia Commons
INTRODUCTION
May 14, 2024, marked a pivotal moment for the European Union (EU) as it unveiled its first legally binding instrument to combat violence against women and domestic violence. This Directive, officially known as Directive 2024/1385, signifies the EU&amp;rsquo;s strong commitment to achieving genuine equality for women.
Gender-based violence is a pervasive issue across the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disappointing ruling by the CJEU on reverse discrimination against rape victims</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 20:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</guid><description>Steve Peers
National criminal justice systems are frequently criticized for overlooking the needs of crime victims. In contrast, the EU has been attentive to this matter since the initial stages of EU criminal law development. Early on, one of the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Framework Decisions&amp;rsquo; addressed victims&amp;rsquo; rights. This measure has since been superseded by a comprehensive Directive on this subject, which Member States are required to implement by October 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>