<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2011/95 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2011/95/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2011/95 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:28:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2011/95/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reconsidering Gender-Based Asylum: Examining the Advocate General's Perspective on Female Refugees Escaping the Taliban</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand (Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law) and Salvo Nicolosi (Senior Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law)
Photo credit: USAIDAfghanistan, via Wikimedia Commons
A central question in international refugee law is whether women can qualify for refugee status based solely on their gender. This debate recently reached the Court of Justice through two connected cases, AH and FN, concerning women seeking asylum. Advocate General Richard de la Tour issued his opinion on these cases on November 9, 2023.</description></item><item><title>Is the non-refoulement principle in the EU's qualification Directive considered invalid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 14:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</guid><description>By Pieter Boeles, visiting professor migration law, VU University Amsterdam, emeritus professor University Leiden
Introduction
The principle of non-refoulement, which forbids returning individuals to unsafe nations, is generally considered absolute. However, ambiguity persists concerning its application within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, which governs the determination of refugee or subsidiary protection status. The Czech Nejvyšší správní soud inquired with the Court of Justice of the European Union on July 14, 2016, about the potential conflict between Article 14(4) of the Qualification Directive and the principle of non-refoulement (Case C-391/16).</description></item><item><title>Is Childhood Coming to an End? The Court of Justice Affirms the Right of Unaccompanied Child Refugees to Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Reaching the age of 18 is a major milestone, signifying a transition to adulthood. While it may not bring immediate changes to family dynamics, it holds significant legal implications.
However, in immigration and asylum law, turning 18 can mean reduced legal rights, especially for vulnerable unaccompanied minors. Given lengthy legal processes, a key question arises: When an applicant starts as a minor but turns 18 before the process concludes, do they keep the protections afforded to children?</description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening and weakening the legal standing of individuals granted subsidiary protection under European Union law – the ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union in the case of Alo and Osso.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</guid><description>Dr. Louise Halleskov Storgaard, Assistant Professor, Aarhus University
Can a country that offers subsidiary protection (a form of protection similar to refugee status) restrict the movement of those beneficiaries within its borders if they receive social security benefits? This is the central question addressed by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Alo and Osso case on March 1, 2015. The CJEU’s answer is notable, innovative, and potentially contentious as it reinforces the influence of the Geneva Convention on subsidiary protection standards but also raises questions about the applicable non-discrimination standard.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice has clarified that foreign fighters' accomplices are not eligible for refugee status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 15:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</guid><description>When can someone be refused asylum for terrorism? Professor Steve Peers
What happens when a person seeking refuge is suspected of terrorism or aiding terrorists? Can they still be considered a refugee? If not, how do we legally define &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; to justify denying their claim? The recent EU Court of Justice judgment in the Lounani case clarifies some aspects of this complex issue but leaves some challenging questions unanswered.
Legal Framework The UN Refugee Convention (Geneva Convention) outlines an &amp;rsquo;exclusion&amp;rsquo; clause in Article 1.</description></item></channel></rss>