<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mediterranean on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mediterranean/</link><description>Recent content in Mediterranean on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mediterranean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EU leaders are avoiding taking significant action to address the migrant crisis.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU leaders convened yesterday and agreed on a policy to handle the escalating migrant death toll in the Mediterranean Sea. This new policy expands on the recently implemented 10-point plan established by ministers. Notably, some significant last-minute revisions to the initial draft highlight the leaders&amp;rsquo; priorities.
Detailed comments
The leaders&amp;rsquo; statement appears to demonstrate more empathy than the prior 10-point plan. It acknowledges the immense loss of life as a tragedy and prioritizes the prevention of further deaths at sea.</description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU's reaction to migrant fatalities focused on safeguarding and stopping them, or is it merely a way to disguise policy laundering?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU foreign and interior ministers recently agreed on a ten-point plan to address the tragic loss of migrant lives in the Mediterranean. While a summit and a new strategy are forthcoming, this initial plan is disappointing. It lacks crucial specifics and prioritizes border control and restrictive measures over aiding migrants facing perilous journeys and seeking safety.
This analysis will examine each of the plan&amp;rsquo;s ten points, followed by a look at the suggested &amp;ldquo;Australian solution&amp;rdquo; and the controversial &amp;ldquo;Christians only&amp;rdquo; approach.</description></item><item><title>The Temporary Protection Directive: A Crucial Element Missing from the European Migration Agenda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-temporary-protection-directive-a-crucial-element-missing-from-the-european-migration-agenda/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-temporary-protection-directive-a-crucial-element-missing-from-the-european-migration-agenda/</guid><description>Meltem Ineli-Ciger, PhD Candidate, University of Bristol Law School[1]
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s Temporary Protection Directive came into effect in 2001, marking the first EU directive on international protection after the Treaty of Amsterdam&amp;rsquo;s implementation in 1999. This directive provides a practical and streamlined structure for managing mass arrivals of displaced individuals, standardizing and harmonizing the protection they receive. Despite this, the directive has never been put into practice. While the Council contemplated activating it in the early 2000s due to increasing asylum seekers from Iraq and Afghanistan, no action was taken (Klug).</description></item><item><title>Etihad provides a wider range of choices for Mediterranean travel destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is increasing the number and capacity of flights to Athens, Greece, and Larnaca, Cyprus.
Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, stated that the new flights to Athens will offer travelers two different departure times to and from Abu Dhabi. The additional flights to Larnaca will provide more options and flexibility, as well as enhanced connectivity through Abu Dhabi.
He added that these additions will support business and leisure travel growth through Abu Dhabi and offer travelers a wider choice of destinations in the Gulf region, Indian Subcontinent, Asia, and Australia.</description></item><item><title>Is Nigel Farage's claim that the EU's asylum policies will allow in half a million terrorists accurate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, the UK Independence Party leader, recently asserted that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s response to the migrant crisis could unintentionally allow a large number of terrorists into the EU. He bases this on the threat by ISIS to use smuggling routes to infiltrate the EU and urges David Cameron to block the EU&amp;rsquo;s plans.
These claims lack merit. The EU&amp;rsquo;s approach essentially maintains the existing situation. The current maritime surveillance efforts, while being expanded, may not become full-scale rescue missions.</description></item><item><title>How can the EU address migrant fatalities in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>The recent tragedies in the Mediterranean Sea have added to the already significant number of migrant deaths. EU officials are responding to this urgent issue, and this is what their response should include.
First, a large-scale search and rescue operation is needed. The EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Triton&amp;rsquo; operation, which replaced the Italian &amp;lsquo;Mare Nostrum,&amp;rsquo; is insufficient for saving lives. It was incorrectly assumed that ending &amp;lsquo;Mare Nostrum&amp;rsquo; would deter migrants and reduce deaths.</description></item></channel></rss>