<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Network Connection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-network-connection/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Network Connection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:07:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-network-connection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High Fiber Diet for Business Not Expensive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</guid><description>With business picking up, many companies are hitting a wall – their internet connections can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the increased data flow. The solution? A high-fiber diet for their network.
Fiber optic cables are incredibly efficient. A single strand can handle massive amounts of voice, data, and video simultaneously, far exceeding the needs of most businesses. This capacity can be further multiplied by splitting the light into different wavelengths, each carrying gigabits per second...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is HPBX Your Next PBX?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</guid><description>Businesses across the country are ditching their in-house phone systems and returning to outside phone service providers, mirroring a past era. However, modern telephony has evolved significantly. While maintaining in-house phone systems seemed cost-effective initially, companies are realizing that it comes with unexpected expenses and complexities.
Larger businesses often require numerous phone lines, leading to challenges in internal communication. Having individual lines for each phone necessitates long-distance charges for calls outside the company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>