<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Celebrity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/celebrity/</link><description>Recent content in Celebrity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/celebrity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has welcomed three new celebrity chefs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. From left: Costa, Joinie-Maurin, Kurdahl, Semblat and Silva.
The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has added three new chefs to its roster of acclaimed restaurants, aiming to elevate the dining experience for their guests.
Jose Silva, CEO of Jumeirah Group, stated that the addition of these culinary experts to their flagship Dubai hotel signifies the beginning of a more diverse and innovative culinary program. He emphasized their dedication to guest experiences as a crucial aspect of luxury hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Song Seung Heon is in Singapore to promote Saimdang</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon spent time with fans and Singtel TV subscribers during a Singapore trip sponsored by Singtel and Oh!K.
Two hundred Singtel TV subscribers in Singapore enjoyed an exclusive meeting with Korean actor Song Seung Heon, hosted by Singtel and Oh!K.
Song&amp;rsquo;s visit was to promote his K-drama Saimdang (师任堂). Before a large public event at The Cathay, Singtel TV subscribers could take pictures with Song and chat with him...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/song-seung-heon-is-in-singapore-to-promote-saimdang/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Nathan Hartono concert is brought to you by Singtel Music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:45:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Singtel Music presents Hartono concert.
At the beginning of 2017, music enthusiasts will have the opportunity to connect with Singaporean singing star Nathan Hartono. Singtel Music is showcasing its support for local musical talent by holding an exclusive event, Up-Close with Nathan Hartono, on January 21, 2017.
Singtel states that fans can experience Hartono&amp;rsquo;s performance and interact with him during the event. Hartono, backed by a full band, will perform a selection of songs in both English and Chinese, including new original pieces from his EP scheduled for release in early 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fans in Singapore of Song Seung Heon may have the opportunity to meet him</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for Saimdang featuring Song.
To kick off the new year, Singtel is bringing South Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon to Singapore on January 7, 2017. Song&amp;rsquo;s visit will promote the drama Saimdang (师任堂), which premieres on Singtel TV&amp;rsquo;s Oh!K channel (channel 525/611) on January 25, 2017, at 9 pm.
Singtel TV subscribers can enter to win 20 pairs of tickets to a meet-and-greet and autograph session with Song...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Twitter has revealed its inaugural collaboration with Singaporean musician @Sezairi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:22:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</guid><description>● #SezairiQA and live songs on Twitter and Periscope @ 6:30pm on August 31, 2016 ● #SezairiLive debut show at Twitter APAC HQ in Singapore @ 7:30pm on September 2, 2016 ● Winners of @Sezairi photo caption contest get free tickets to #SezairiLive event
Singaporean singer Sezairi (@Sezairi) will be performing live (#SezairiLive) on Twitter, Periscope, and at Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters. The performances follow a pre-listening party (#SezairiPreLP) on Twitter held the previous week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>