<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sri Lanka on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sri-lanka/</link><description>Recent content in Sri Lanka on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sri-lanka/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir will be operating SIA flights SQ466 and SQ467 to Colombo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 18:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</guid><description>Starting April 8, 2017, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines (SIA), will begin flights to Colombo, the commercial hub of Sri Lanka and a diverse city home to a large population.
SilkAir will take over flights SQ466/SQ467, offering three weekly flights to Colombo. SIA will maintain its daily nighttime service, operating flights SQ468 and SQ469. Adding SilkAir to the Singapore-Colombo route allows the SIA Group to optimize resource allocation and better match capacity with demand.</description></item><item><title>This year, Teardrop Hotels is introducing three new tea plantation experiences in Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Teardrop Hotels is expanding its portfolio in 2018 with the addition of three renovated tea planters&amp;rsquo; houses: Goatfell, Nine Skies, and Pekoe House. These vintage managers&amp;rsquo; bungalows, located along the tea country route, will offer a modern take on traditional tea plantation accommodations.
Opening in April 2018, Goatfell is a former superintendent’s residence situated on a working tea estate above Nuwara Eliya. This four-bedroom main house, with two additional standalone chalets, boasts living and dining rooms and a swimming pool.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is adding another daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates has launched an additional daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka. Starting August 1, 2016, the airline will offer five daily flights between the two cities, except on Wednesdays, when four flights will be available. This new flight will provide an extra 2,520 seats and boost cargo capacity by 161 tonnes weekly in both directions, increasing the total weekly services on this route to 34.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir expands its network to include Colombo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-network-to-include-colombo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 05:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-network-to-include-colombo/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, has introduced flights to Colombo, Sri Lanka, becoming the second airline in its group to operate on this route. With the addition of three weekly flights to Colombo, SilkAir now reaches 53 destinations in 15 countries.
These flights will operate on Wednesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, using Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both Business and Economy Class seating. Passengers will enjoy a full range of services, including meals, in-flight entertainment on SilkAir Studio, and baggage allowances of 40kg for Business Class and 30kg for Economy Class.</description></item></channel></rss>