<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Packet Loss on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/packet-loss/</link><description>Recent content in Packet Loss on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/packet-loss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies.</description></item><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic.</description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Symmetric Internet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you unhappy with how the internet performs for your business? Do you think it&amp;rsquo;s more for entertainment and casual use than for getting work done quickly and efficiently? You need the internet to function, though. Your customers and suppliers, along with important information, are online. Even your software and communication tools might be cloud-based. What you likely need is a business-grade broadband connection with better performance.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>The Value of Low Latency Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-value-of-low-latency-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 20:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-value-of-low-latency-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow network speeds, particularly when connecting to the internet or other company sites, could point to a latency problem. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how businesses and organizations can achieve faster network connections:
For businesses that rely on high-speed network performance, like high-frequency financial trading, minimizing latency is crucial. Some companies even choose to be in the same building as stock exchanges to be just feet away from servers.
While most applications aren&amp;rsquo;t that demanding, factors like bandwidth, latency, packet loss, and jitter still matter.</description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards.</description></item></channel></rss>