<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fake on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fake/</link><description>Recent content in Fake on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The US has published the 2016 Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</guid><description>The Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR) has released its annual Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets report. The 2016 review calls attention to online and physical marketplaces around the world that reportedly engage in or facilitate significant copyright infringement and trademark counterfeiting.
USTR Michael Froman emphasized the problem of piracy and counterfeiting in online markets, saying that governments need to address these issues throughout the supply chain to protect consumers from unsafe products.</description></item><item><title>The inexpensive cellphone you recently purchased may be counterfeit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 02:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</guid><description>The global black market for counterfeit and substandard cell phones is a significant issue, costing the industry an estimated US$6 billion each year, as reported in a recent study by the Mobile Manufacturers Forum (MMF). This comprehensive analysis, &amp;ldquo;Counterfeit/Substandard Mobile Phones - A Resource Guide for Governments&amp;rdquo;, examines the prevalence of these phones across all major brands.
According to MMF Secretary General Michael Milligan, research suggests approximately 148 million counterfeit or substandard cell phones were sold in 2013 alone, primarily through established retail channels.</description></item></channel></rss>