<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Finance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/finance/</link><description>Recent content in Finance on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:47:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fitch Learning has teamed up with Golden Education to provide a certificate in quantitative finance in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:47:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</guid><description>Fitch Learning has partnered with Golden Education, a financial education company in China, to provide the Certificate in Quantitative Finance (CQF) program to professionals throughout the country. The CQF is gaining recognition in China, as demonstrated by a 55% increase in enrollment by Chinese participants from 2018 to 2019.
The CQF program includes six modules, two elective advanced modules, three exams, and a final project. Quantitative finance utilizes mathematical modeling to examine financial markets and securities.</description></item><item><title>Value Added Tax (VAT) has been implemented in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>In anticipation of the January 1, 2018 Value Added Tax (VAT) launch, the KSA General Authority for Zakat and Tax introduced a mobile app on December 30, 2017. This app provides key information about VAT and helps consumers verify VAT registration status of businesses.
The app&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;check&amp;rdquo; function allows consumers to scan the barcode on a VAT registration certificate or enter the business&amp;rsquo; Commercial Registration Number or 15-digit VAT identification number from an invoice to confirm registration.</description></item><item><title>According to the Brand Finance Global 500 2016 report, Disney is recognized as the most influential brand in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</guid><description>· Out of the top 10 fastest growing brands, four are Chinese.
· Disney is the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential brand due to the immense success of Star Wars.
· Despite experiencing a decline in sales, Apple&amp;rsquo;s brand value increased by 14% to US$145.9 billion, making it the most valuable brand globally.
· Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s brand value experienced a decline of US$12 billion as a consequence of the emissions controversy.
· Leading brands are outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500 average in terms of share performance.</description></item><item><title>IndianMoney.com is creating additional financial education content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</guid><description>IndianMoney.com, a leading financial education company in India, partnered with Kannada news channel Suddi TV to create Money Maathu (Money Talk), an educational series about personal finance. The series features short episodes, typically eight to ten minutes long, that cover a wide range of financial topics. With 35 episodes already released, the goal is to empower viewers with the knowledge to make informed financial choices.
CS Sudheer, founder and CEO of IndianMoney.</description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa.</description></item><item><title>Singapore businesses can access cybersecurity and financing services from Acronis and Minterest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyberprotection company, has partnered with Minterest, a Singaporean online financial services provider, to offer financing to Singaporean businesses. This collaboration, called Acronis #CyberFit Financing, Powered by Minterest, aims to help businesses in Singapore stay resilient and #CyberFit during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Acronis and Minterest want to empower businesses by providing easily accessible, customized financing solutions. This will help businesses navigate challenging times while also strengthening their cybersecurity defenses.</description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>New OCBC Securities app and Android OCBC app now offer fingerprint security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 08:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</guid><description>Source: OCBC. The iOCBC TradeMobile app allows users to perform in-depth technical analyses of stocks using standard indicators.
OCBC Securities has introduced a new mobile app called iOCBC TradeMobile for iPhone users. Existing OCBC Securities customers can now conveniently monitor their stock portfolios and access real-time market data for their stocks using Apple&amp;rsquo;s Touch ID technology. This fingerprint authentication feature, known as OneTouch, offers both OCBC Bank and OCBC Securities customers a secure and convenient way to access their banking and brokerage accounts.</description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC places a strong emphasis on ensuring compliance and transparency in all business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 11:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</guid><description>Following the release of the Panama Papers, the Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC) has reaffirmed its commitment to facilitating cross-border trade and investment, especially within the ASEAN region. The organization emphasizes its dedication to maintaining strict transparency and regulatory standards for all business activities conducted within the centre.
In a statement, the organization highlighted its continuous efforts to strengthen its regulatory framework and supervisory system. These efforts aim to meet international standards and practices related to transparency and regulatory compliance.</description></item><item><title>Term deposits from ICBC are available through Alipay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</guid><description>ICBC, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest bank by assets, now offers three-year term deposit services through Alipay, a popular digital lifestyle platform.
This collaboration between Alipay and ICBC began in 2005 with online payment services. In January 2020, ICBC introduced a one-year term deposit service on Alipay, allowing customers to make deposits directly through the platform. This service has seen a sevenfold increase in size since May.
The new three-year term deposit option, called Anxin Cun (Secure Deposits), offers a 3.</description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge.</description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM.</description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right).</description></item><item><title>Harmoney proudly displays impressive first-year results</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</guid><description>The remarkable first-year performance of Harmoney, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s sole peer-to-peer (P2P) lending platform, highlights a substantial unmet need for crowdfunded microloans.
Established on September 10, 2014, with NZ$100 million in committed capital from prominent institutions like Blue Elephant Capital Management and Heartland Bank, Harmoney has facilitated NZ$100 million in personal loans within its inaugural year. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid expansion has resulted in the creation of 65 new jobs across New Zealand, Australia, and Fiji, with plans underway for an Australian launch.</description></item><item><title>The IMF emphasizes the importance of AML/CFT for maintaining stability in the financial sector of the Kyrgyz Republic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</guid><description>Despite external pressures decreasing and some positive economic signs, the recovery has been modest. Economic growth sped up towards the end of 2016, hitting 3.8% with 0.5% deflation, partly due to a currency appreciation of about 9%. The 2016 deficit was kept to 4.5% of GDP due to controlled spending on less critical items and the rescheduling of some investment projects, even though tax revenue fell short of expectations. Efforts to consolidate the budget should continue to achieve the 2017 fiscal deficit target of 3% of GDP.</description></item><item><title>Global Payout expands MoneyTrac assistance to the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 12:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</guid><description>Global Payout, a company that offers business-to-business electronic payment solutions, has expanded its proprietary MoneyTrac consolidated payment gateway (CPG) platform to the Philippines.
MoneyTrac allows users to make secure payments to employees and business partners. Users can configure virtual accounts to meet specific payment needs, sending funds to bank accounts in supported countries, debit cards, credit cards, or even other users on the system.
Bill Rochfort, President and VP of Sales, highlighted the significant opportunity in providing financial services to the Philippines&amp;rsquo; large population, including millions of Filipinos working abroad (OFWs).</description></item></channel></rss>