<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Switched Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/switched-ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Switched Ethernet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/switched-ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?</description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH.</description></item></channel></rss>