<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Black on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/black/</link><description>Recent content in Black on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:44:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/black/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dawn Black Badge provides luxurious open-top driving in a striking black color</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</guid><description>Source: Rolls-Royce Motor Cars. The Rolls-Royce Dawn Black Badge.
Rolls-Royce Motor Cars has introduced the Dawn Black Badge, a new addition to their lineup.
This model joins the Wraith Black Badge and Ghost Black Badge, offering a luxurious and bold take on open-top driving with a darker and more sensual aesthetic. The Dawn Black Badge was revealed in a strikingly deep black shade, achieved through a meticulous painting and polishing process that is the most extensive ever employed by Rolls-Royce for a solid paint color...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy introduced black bean mooncakes to their selection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy.
At the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, this Mooncake Festival, indulge in a modern take on classic handmade mooncakes created by Head Chef Lester Wang.
With over 20 flavors, Chef Wang&amp;rsquo;s baked and snowskin mooncakes offer a delightful blend of traditional and contemporary tastes. Popular choices include Jia Wei Durian, Signature Italian Dark Coffee, and Raspberry with Dark Chocolate mooncakes.
This year&amp;rsquo;s selection introduces two new flavors: traditional baked mooncakes with black bean paste and the ‘Ying Yang’ snowskin mooncake, featuring a harmonious blend of white lotus and black bean fillings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>