<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Staff on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/staff/</link><description>Recent content in Staff on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/staff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Workers value recognition more than money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</guid><description>Source: ACCA report. Tone at the top influences corporate behaviour the most, according to 61% of respondents.
A recent report by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) titled &amp;ldquo;Culture and channelling corporate behaviour: ACCA member survey&amp;rdquo; found that workplace recognition is the most significant motivator for employees across all ages, industries, and locations. Notably, this recognition even outweighs monetary rewards.
The survey, conducted with support from the Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC), gathered insights from nearly 2,000 ACCA finance professionals globally.</description></item><item><title>CIMB introduces a program to enhance the skills of non-executive employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</guid><description>CIMB Group, the second-largest financial services provider in Malaysia, has initiated a program to enhance the skills, productivity, career advancement prospects, and earning potential of its non-executive employees. This program, known as the CIMB Accelerated Career Enhancement Programme (CIMB ACE), was officially launched by Dato’ Sri Richard Riot Anak Jaem, the Minister of Human Resources.
The CIMB ACE program aligns with PR1ME (Program Majudiri 1Malaysia), a national initiative launched by the Prime Minister of Malaysia in November 2013.</description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued.</description></item></channel></rss>