<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MasterCard on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mastercard/</link><description>Recent content in MasterCard on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mastercard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Female entrepreneurs need more than just determination to succeed, according to Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</guid><description>The first Mastercard Index of Women Entrepreneurs reveals that strong support systems, such as easy access to financial services and a business-friendly environment, are crucial for women-owned businesses to succeed. These enabling factors are essential in overcoming the two biggest hurdles women face in entrepreneurship: cultural bias and limited opportunities for advancement.
Developed economies lead the index, with New Zealand (74.4), Canada (72.4), and the US (69.9) claiming the top spots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australian consumers are pleased to use contactless cards for payment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard survey highlights the increasing popularity of digital payment methods among Australians. Over 80% of Australians use contactless payments, also known as &amp;ldquo;tap and go,&amp;rdquo; weekly. This preference is so strong that a significant number of consumers get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer this option, with some even choosing to shop elsewhere.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and petrol stations are the most common places where Australians use contactless cards. Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, Garry Duursma, emphasizes that Australians view tap and go as a faster and more convenient payment method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangkok is the top tourist destination in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Mastercard. Report cover.
Although Bangkok, Thailand remains the top spot for visitors in the Asia Pacific, the latest Mastercard Asia Pacific Destinations Index 2017* shows that Singapore outpaces the Thai capital in total tourist spending.
Singapore experienced an 18% increase in visitor spending between 2015 and 2016. As one of just five destinations in the top 20 for overall expenditure to hit a minimum daily spend of US$200, Singapore drew in the biggest spenders at US$254 per day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>