<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fixed-mobile-convergence/</link><description>Recent content in Fixed Mobile Convergence on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fixed-mobile-convergence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Business Needs Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There was a time when the only way to communicate electronically was with that clunky black phone on your desk. While that phone might still be there, modern technology has made it lighter and brought a wealth of new communication methods. Email, text messages, mobile phone calls, and video chats are now commonplace across various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, smartphones, and even watches.
A significant challenge, particularly in business, is that these platforms and applications don&amp;rsquo;t always work well together...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Communications Advantages Explained</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</guid><description>Many businesses are unsure if switching their communications to the cloud is a good idea. XO Communications, a large networking and telecom provider, explains why this change is beneficial. Their short video illustrates why this might be the right choice for your business.
XO&amp;rsquo;s Enterprise Cloud Communications provides large businesses with services similar to what hosted PBX systems offer smaller companies. Essentially, it transitions a company from managing its own phone system to simply using a sophisticated service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Comes To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s professionals juggle multiple devices like smartphones, tablets, and laptops in addition to their office setups, which often include desktop computers, LAN connections, and speakerphones. This begs the question: how can we unify these devices for a seamless workflow?
This multifaceted connectivity issue has plagued corporate IT departments for years as communication devices multiply faster than solutions for integrating them. Often, the simplest answer is printing business cards with separate numbers for each device...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone Offers Awareness In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The traditional office phone, once a large and stationary fixture on every desk, is becoming a relic of the past. Modern business communication has evolved into a dynamic and multifaceted process, incorporating instant messaging, online collaboration tools, file sharing, and web-based applications alongside traditional voice calls and conferencing. This evolution begs the question: are conventional PBX systems still equipped to handle the demands of today&amp;rsquo;s business environment?
As outdated phone systems increasingly hinder productivity, many companies are turning to cloud-based solutions for a more modern approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Visual Guide To Enterprise VoIP Justification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</guid><description>Thank you to MegaPath Broadband Service Providers for this interesting infographic.
Is your company missing out on the advantages of enterprise VoIP technology, which can potentially reduce costs and increase productivity? A variety of on-site and hosted options are available to accommodate businesses of all sizes. Explore business VoIP solutions and pricing from MegaPath and other providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>