<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Housing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/housing/</link><description>Recent content in Housing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/housing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU upholds the right of asylum seekers to family housing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:41:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This piece examines the housing obligations of EU Member States toward asylum-seeking families. The European Court of Justice (CJEU) recently clarified the minimum standards required of Member States in its ruling on the Saciri case. The judgment is a positive development, confirming that regardless of the challenges Member States face in providing reception services for asylum-seekers, families cannot be left homeless or in extremely poor living conditions by denying them financial aid for housing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Restoration of the Carriage Position Sensor - Development of a New Beolover Part</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) being restored had a broken carriage position sensor photo resistor housing with damaged mounting tabs. After removing the housing and extracting the photo resistor, a replacement housing was designed and 3D printed.
The new housing consists of two parts. The photo resistor is placed on the insert part after straightening its leads. The main housing is then slid over the insert, sandwiching the photo resistor. This assembly is then inserted into the existing mounting cutouts and soldered to the PCB.</description></item></channel></rss>