<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>New on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/new/</link><description>Recent content in New on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:50:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/new/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starbucks in Asia is offering merchandise for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>To commemorate the 2016 Lunar Year of the Monkey, Starbucks has introduced a special collection of limited-edition items available in Asian markets. This merchandise includes:
[Image of Starbucks Monkey Mug]
Lunar New Year Monkey Mug
This red ceramic mug features a three-dimensional white monkey. Its body wraps around the side, its tail forms the handle, and its playful expression peeks out from the mug&amp;rsquo;s surface. The design is enhanced with a glossy red glaze, a contrasting yellow interior, and gold-colored vines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The amount of money given as gifts for Chinese New Year in 2017 was calculated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</guid><description>Source: Gift Something blog post. Survey results for monetary gifts during Chinese New Year in Hong Kong. Values are in Hong Kong dollars.
Gift Something, a Hong Kong-based online retailer specializing in premium gifts, conducted a survey to understand the practice of giving red envelopes (known as angpow or red packets in Singapore, and lai see or red pockets in Hong Kong) during Chinese New Year. Traditionally, married couples give these envelopes to unmarried individuals during the first 15 days of the Lunar New Year to bring luck...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick reference guide for Chinese New Year in the Year of the Water Tiger</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:44:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</guid><description>In 2022, the ox replaces the rat as the third animal in the 12-year Chinese zodiac cycle, bringing hope for positive change. Chinese New Year commences on February 1st, ushering in a period of customary greetings and well wishes.
A wish for plentiful business opportunities.
生意兴隆.
Common greetings include &amp;ldquo;Happy New Year&amp;rdquo; (新年快乐, xin nian kuai le) and &amp;ldquo;Congratulations on receiving riches and prosperity&amp;rdquo; (恭喜发财, gong xi fa cai). Prosperity holds significant value in Chinese culture, particularly during Chinese New Year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick guide for Chinese New Year in the year of the rat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</guid><description>The rat is associated with a new 12-year cycle in the Chinese zodiac. Legend has it that a race among all the animals determined which twelve would be featured in the zodiac. The animals finished in the following order: rat, ox, tiger, rabbit, dragon, snake, horse, goat, monkey, rooster, dog, and pig. This sequence dictates the order of the animals in the zodiac.
The rat is generally agreed to be very clever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consider pricing and marketing strategies for successful product launches in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Almost 75% of new products launched in the Asia-Pacific region fail. This rate surpasses other global regions, according to a study by strategy consultants Simon Kucher &amp;amp; Partners. The study, Global Pricing Study 2014, was conducted in partnership with the Professional Pricing Society (PPS).
[Image of watches for sale in a shopping district]
Globally, the ability to implement price increases is declining. While companies in 2012 could successfully implement 50% of planned price increases, that number has fallen to about 33% in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawksford has released the latest data on new business formations in Singapore for the fourth quarter of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 09:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</guid><description>Source: Hawksford report. Data represents the shareholder&amp;rsquo;s country of origin. Although the final quarter of 2015 saw a decrease in new Singaporean company formations compared to the previous quarter and the same period last year, international investors continue to set up companies and subsidiaries in Singapore, according to Hawksford, a provider of corporate, private client, and fund administration services.
Hawksford notes this decline is typical for the fourth quarter. Private limited companies made up the largest portion of new formations at 48...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 'Save' feature is a new addition to Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-save-feature-is-a-new-addition-to-facebook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-save-feature-is-a-new-addition-to-facebook/</guid><description>Facebook has launched a new feature allowing users to save items they find on the platform for later viewing. According to a July 21st blog post, savable content includes links, locations, movies, TV shows, and music.
This &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo; feature will be rolled out globally across iOS, Android, and web platforms in the coming days.
Source: Facebook blog.
Facebook Software Engineer Daniel Giambalvo, the author of the blog post, emphasizes that saved items remain private unless a user chooses to share them with friends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-save-feature-is-a-new-addition-to-facebook/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-save-feature-is-a-new-addition-to-facebook/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick guide to Chinese New Year for the Year of the Pig</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</guid><description>The Lunar New Year period is a time when Chinese communities are filled with a palpable sense of celebration. Vibrant red decorations, believed to bring good luck, are prominently displayed, and the atmosphere is alive with the melodies of traditional festive music. The Chinese New Year, which falls on February 5th in 2019, is a time when well-wishes are exchanged, particularly during the first fifteen days of the lunar year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify celebrates the year of the rooster with a fresh playlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Welcoming the lunar new year.
To celebrate the Lunar New Year on January 28th, Spotify has launched a special playlist. This playlist features popular songs by artists born in the Year of the Rooster.
Interested?
Check out Spotify&amp;rsquo;s 恭賀新年 (welcoming the new year) playlist..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CulinaryOn Singapore is offering Lunar New Year dinner experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Culinaryon Singapore. Yusheng with salmon sashimi.
For this Lunar New Year, CulinaryOn Singapore is offering special dinners starting on December 26th, 2017. These dinners feature premium six-to-eight course meals and include a taste of their cooking classes with a noodle-making activity. Guests can also choose to create their own desserts.
The eight-course premium menu features dishes such as yusheng with salmon sashimi, shiitake mushrooms with broccoli, crayfish braised longevity noodles, golden shrimp with honeydew mayo, and mango ice cream with pomelo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kaspersky Lab is providing security tips in preparation for the Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown is prominently featuring dog decorations in celebration of the new year.
As shoppers navigate the excitement and rush of Chinese New Year shopping, Kaspersky Lab cautions that they are more susceptible to making simple errors that could jeopardize their personal information.
Sylvia Ng, General Manager of Kaspersky Lab Southeast Asia, acknowledges that holiday shopping is a top priority for consumers. However, she emphasizes that it&amp;rsquo;s also an opportune time for cybercriminals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant is launching a fresh new menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant, found within the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, has introduced a new menu to coincide with the arrival of their new head chef, Victor. The dishes are meant to complement the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s modern Eastern aesthetic and embody the Chinese principle of &amp;ldquo;家味,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;flavors of home.&amp;rdquo;
The menu features popular Eastern dishes like Chef&amp;rsquo;s superior fish maw served with seafood soup, and fresh prawns accompanied by two special sauces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>