<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upgrade on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/upgrade/</link><description>Recent content in Upgrade on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/upgrade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LG G3s will be the first to receive the Lollipop upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</guid><description>LG Electronics claims to be the first worldwide smartphone maker to launch the Lollipop update in 2014. According to LG, the updated Android operating system, Android 5.0 or &amp;ldquo;Lollipop,&amp;rdquo; will be available for its G3 smartphones starting in Poland the week of November 10, with other major markets following shortly after.
Source: LG.
This newest Android OS offers a variety of enhancements, including enhanced depth, shadows, and animations. With a fresh design and color scheme, notifications have been enhanced and will be visible on the new lock screen.</description></item><item><title>Issue with upgrading Project Accounting and Purchase Order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 03:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</guid><description>A recent upgrade from GP9 to GP10 resulted in an unexpected issue: purchase order line items were missing account numbers. This was perplexing because previous upgrades, even those involving project accounting, had gone smoothly.
The problem became evident when a user discovered that upon receiving purchase orders, no Cost of Goods Sold account defaulted. This was because the purchase order line items lacked account numbers. Database examination confirmed that the INVINDX field, which stores account indexes for purchase order lines in the POP10110 table, was empty for all 7500 lines.</description></item><item><title>Starting on July 29, upgrades to Windows 10 will be available for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</guid><description>Source: Windows blog.
Microsoft has revealed that Windows 10 will launch on July 29th in 190 countries. The company states that Windows 10 will enhance productivity and offer a more personalized and intuitive user experience across devices. Windows 7 and 8.1 users can upgrade to Windows 10 for free, making it accessible to a majority of current Windows users.
&amp;ldquo;Windows 10 empowers users to achieve remarkable things,&amp;rdquo; says Terry Myerson, Executive VP at Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>Data-driven alerts are introduced in Tableau 10.3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</guid><description>Tableau Software, a leading provider of visual analytics solutions, has launched Tableau 10.3. This latest release empowers businesses to derive data-driven insights swiftly.
Francois Ajenstat, Chief Product Officer at Tableau, stated that companies are seeking to maximize the value of their data, aiming not just for basic analysis but for the capability to effortlessly and efficiently unlock insights from all their data. Features like smart recommendations enable customers to find the right data quickly, bypassing the need to search for suitable tables and joins.</description></item></channel></rss>