<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Remote Backup on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remote-backup/</link><description>Recent content in Remote Backup on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remote-backup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Store Your Files For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</guid><description>With the current state of the economy, you&amp;rsquo;d expect the best price for file storage to be free – and you&amp;rsquo;d be right! Anything more would be asking too much.
Of course, this applies to storing digital files, not physical ones. Don&amp;rsquo;t show up at a self-storage facility with boxes of papers expecting free storage – they won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to show you the door!
Instead, try storing your computer files for free with Mozy (http://www.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own Private Cloud Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</guid><description>Lots of small and midsize businesses are using cloud storage, particularly for disaster recovery. However, local storage is still necessary. While Storage Attached Networks (SANs) are a common solution, they&amp;rsquo;re expensive and complex. A simpler option exists.
Introducing Drobo, an advanced hard disk storage solution that&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to use. It works with standard 3.5&amp;quot; SATA drives of any capacity, resembling a straightforward multi-bay drive enclosure. Adding or removing drives, even swapping a 1 TB for a 2 TB, is always possible.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth For Remote Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</guid><description>Businesses need to have a solid plan to safeguard their important data. While basic backups on disks or tapes can help with minor issues like a crashed computer, they are inadequate for major events like natural disasters. Offsite backup is crucial in these situations.
The key is choosing a location geographically distant from your primary site to avoid shared risks. Backing up data across regional offices, separated by significant distances, enhances data protection.</description></item></channel></rss>