<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nutrition on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nutrition/</link><description>Recent content in Nutrition on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:50:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nutrition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor has discovered that India and China have lower-than-average per capita calorie purchases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</guid><description>A new study by Euromonitor International reveals how many nutrients people consume daily from packaged foods and beverages. This data, found in their Passport: Nutrition database, tracks the consumption of calories, fats, saturated fats, carbohydrates, sugars, salt, protein, and fiber across 54 countries.
Globally, we buy enough packaged food and soft drinks to consume 1.5 trillion calories per day, averaging 765 calories per person. While a healthy daily intake is around 2,000 calories, North America and Western Europe exceed 1,500 calories, contrasting with India&amp;rsquo;s 150 and China&amp;rsquo;s 510.</description></item><item><title>Making small changes to your lifestyle can lead to a healthier you in the long run, according to Herbalife</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</guid><description>People in Asia are interested in expanding their fitness routines beyond traditional practices like yoga and tai chi. However, Samantha Clayton, Director of Worldwide Fitness Education at Herbalife, notes that they face unique challenges, such as extreme weather and demanding work schedules, and need to adapt their fitness routines accordingly.
She emphasizes the importance of integrating fitness into everyday life, especially when environmental factors like air quality, heat, and humidity can be obstacles.</description></item></channel></rss>