<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AZEW877H9NFU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/azew877h9nfu/</link><description>Recent content in AZEW877H9NFU on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/azew877h9nfu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs T1 in Under 3 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Ethernet bandwidth services are generating a lot of interest, but are they truly superior to traditional T1 lines? Is switching from copper to fiber a wise decision financially? This brief comparison of Ethernet and T1 services will provide clarity.
Interested in determining which connectivity and hosted services best meet your business needs? Get instant pricing and availability for Ethernet, T1, and other connectivity options.</description></item></channel></rss>