<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Two-Factor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/two-factor/</link><description>Recent content in Two-Factor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/two-factor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA.</description></item><item><title>ESET advocates for the use of two-factor authentication to enhance security for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, cautions that small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) are frequently targeted by cybercriminals due to the vulnerability of their data. Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research&amp;rsquo;s study reveals that stolen personal data fuels a multi-billion dollar industry.
Lukas Raska, COO of ESET Asia, emphasizes the evolution of cybercrime from viruses to the current threat of identity theft, highlighting its potential to cripple businesses and compromise customer trust.
Parvinder Walia, Director at ESET APAC, explains that SMBs are attractive targets because they often lack the robust cybersecurity budgets and dedicated personnel of larger companies.</description></item></channel></rss>