<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Geneva Convention on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/geneva-convention/</link><description>Recent content in Geneva Convention on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/geneva-convention/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Opinion of AG de la Tour in C-621/21: Is it a helpful clarification or an unnecessary hindrance to women seeking international protection from gender-based violence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Grundler, a Lecturer in Law at the Department of Law and Criminology, Royal Holloway, University of London, examines a recent legal opinion concerning refugee and subsidiary protection eligibility for women at risk of violence within their families.
Advocate General (AG) de la Tour&amp;rsquo;s Opinion in case C-621/21 tackles the scope of the refugee definition within Article 2(d) of the Qualification Directive and the definition of subsidiary protection beneficiaries in Article 2(g) concerning women facing potential violence within a family setting.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft EU/Turkey agreement on migration and refugees legally sound?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent legal debates have arisen concerning the proposed EU/Turkey agreement on refugees. While general points were discussed last month, a leaked draft of the final deal necessitates a closer examination before the finalizing summit.
The agreement, framed as an EU-Turkey statement, builds upon the March 7, 2016, statement with added elements. It is crucial to note that as a statement, it won&amp;rsquo;t be legally binding, requiring no formal EU or national approval beyond the summit&amp;rsquo;s endorsement.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening and weakening the legal standing of individuals granted subsidiary protection under European Union law – the ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union in the case of Alo and Osso.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</guid><description>Dr. Louise Halleskov Storgaard, Assistant Professor, Aarhus University
Can a country that offers subsidiary protection (a form of protection similar to refugee status) restrict the movement of those beneficiaries within its borders if they receive social security benefits? This is the central question addressed by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Alo and Osso case on March 1, 2015. The CJEU’s answer is notable, innovative, and potentially contentious as it reinforces the influence of the Geneva Convention on subsidiary protection standards but also raises questions about the applicable non-discrimination standard.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the Legal Implications of the EU/Turkey Refugee Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</guid><description>Steve Peers analyzes the legal and political implications of the recent EU-Turkey agreement on refugees. The agreement, while legally controversial, aims to address the refugee crisis and restore order.
A key point of contention is the return of migrants arriving in Greece to Turkey. While the agreement states this will be done in accordance with international law, returning all migrants without considering individual circumstances raises concerns about collective expulsion, a violation of EU and international law.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice has clarified that foreign fighters' accomplices are not eligible for refugee status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 15:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</guid><description>When can someone be refused asylum for terrorism? Professor Steve Peers
What happens when a person seeking refuge is suspected of terrorism or aiding terrorists? Can they still be considered a refugee? If not, how do we legally define &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; to justify denying their claim? The recent EU Court of Justice judgment in the Lounani case clarifies some aspects of this complex issue but leaves some challenging questions unanswered.
Legal Framework The UN Refugee Convention (Geneva Convention) outlines an &amp;rsquo;exclusion&amp;rsquo; clause in Article 1.</description></item></channel></rss>