<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>So on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/so/</link><description>Recent content in So on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/so/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sofitel SO Bangkok announces the chef lineup for So Amazing Chefs 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel SO Bangkok. The Sofitel SO Bangkok has announced that 12 world-renowned chefs will be in Thailand for the 4th So Amazing Chefs event, happening from October 6th to 11th, 2015.
Yves Mudry, General Manager of Sofitel SO Bangkok shared, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s food festival is our most prestigious yet, featuring an incredible lineup of chefs with a combined seven Michelin stars. This event highlights Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a culinary destination and fosters the exchange of culinary ideas and inspiration.</description></item><item><title>Experience a unique twist on French-inspired dining this holiday season at Sofitel So Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel So Singapore. Paulo.
At Sofitel So Singapore, Xperience restaurant&amp;rsquo;s head chef, Trevor Paulo, is celebrating his first Christmas season at the hotel with a special four-course Christmas Eve dinner.
The dinner starts with a small bite of blinis topped with dill yogurt and herring roe. The first course is a visually appealing dish of house-cured Salmon Gravlax arranged to look like a miniature garden with edible truffle &amp;ldquo;soil&amp;rdquo; and pickled shallots.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Sub-Chassis and the Platter, and RPM Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 04:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</guid><description>Today was dedicated to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis on a Beogram 4002 (5513) that I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I aimed to align the platter&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface with the surrounding panels, center the sub-chassis within the transport locks&amp;rsquo; limits, and ensure the arms were parallel to the aluminum surfaces. It&amp;rsquo;s intricate work involving aligning numerous components. After gaining experience with this process, I achieved a satisfactory result, aligning the Beogram to specifications.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Broken SO ('Shut Off') Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 05:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about a malfunctioning &amp;ldquo;Shut Off&amp;rdquo; (SO) switch, which was missing a crucial plastic part, causing issues with the deck&amp;rsquo;s shutdown process. To address this, a 3D printed replacement part was designed and created. The &amp;ldquo;End Switch&amp;rdquo; (ES), still equipped with its plastic component, is pictured alongside the SO switch, highlighting the missing element.
Creating a functional replacement part was challenging due to its small size and the limitations of the 3D printer.</description></item></channel></rss>