<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Year End on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/year-end/</link><description>Recent content in Year End on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:09:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/year-end/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Please don't end my year...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s debunk some common misconceptions about year-end closing in Dynamics GP:
Myth #1: All adjusting entries must be finalized before closing the General Ledger.
This is false. Dynamics GP allows posting to the most recent historical year. After closing 2009, for instance, adjustments can still be made to it, just not to 2008. This requires enabling &amp;ldquo;allow posting to history&amp;rdquo; in GL setup and ensuring the fiscal period is open in Fiscal Period Setup.</description></item><item><title>Should you report on a 1099 form or not?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-report-on-a-1099-form-or-not/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-report-on-a-1099-form-or-not/</guid><description>Recent Dynamics GP versions offer significant enhancements to 1099 tracking. The ability to track 1099 amounts by type and box at the transaction level enables more detailed tracking, eliminating the assumption that all vendor payments fall under the same 1099 type and box number.
Despite these advancements, comprehensive reporting features for reviewing this information by type and box are limited. While inquiries can be made easily (Inquiry&amp;ndash;Purchasing&amp;ndash;Vendor 1099 Details, Cards&amp;ndash;Purchasing&amp;ndash;1099 Details), these methods have limitations.</description></item><item><title>Remember to bring your keys (and report your taxable wages)!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 08:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, there have been some recurring support cases related to taxable wages on the manual payroll checks window, particularly when starting with initial balances. Here are a few common issues:
Federal taxes are accurate, but Federal wages are incorrect. FICA/S and/or FICA/M are accurate, but the corresponding wages are incorrect. Federal wages don&amp;rsquo;t match FICA/M or FICA/S wages, and the reason is unclear. Let&amp;rsquo;s break down how these issues occur:</description></item><item><title>Enjoy the Payroll FICA Fun!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 01:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sharing Michael Lupro&amp;rsquo;s recent blog post about the changes to FICA rates. The post highlights the different rates for employees and employers, which may require manual adjustments in Great Plains until a system update is available to address this discrepancy.
http://btosteam.blogspot.com/2011/01/manual-employer-fica-tax-calculations.html</description></item><item><title>SmartList and Year End: A love affair.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-and-year-end-a-love-affair/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 22:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-and-year-end-a-love-affair/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of SmartList, especially with the added power of SmartList Builder. While we save that for later, let&amp;rsquo;s focus on basic SmartList uses for year-end tasks. I&amp;rsquo;m preparing a presentation on this and want to share some of my top SmartLists.
Here they are, in no specific order:
1099 Transaction Audit: Verify 1099 amounts against transaction details.
Use &amp;ldquo;Payables Transactions.&amp;rdquo; Add &amp;ldquo;Document Amount,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;1099 Amount,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;1099 Type&amp;rdquo; columns.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions About Year-End Payroll</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 23:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</guid><description>This information comes from a Microsoft and Terry Heley webinar and addresses common questions about FICA rate changes:
Q: I already applied the 2011 tax tables before creating the year-end wage file. What should I do? A: Change the FICA/Social Security tax rate back to 6.2% in the Payroll Tax setup. Then, create the year-end wage file and reset the rate to the 2011 value of 4.2%.
Q: Can I rebuild the year-end wage file using the above method if I already processed 2011 payrolls?</description></item><item><title>Tips and Tricks for the End of 2008</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-the-end-of-2008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 11:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-the-end-of-2008/</guid><description>The process of upgrading to GP 10 Service Pack 3 and applying the year-end update can be done from any computer, but it might be faster on the server. As a precaution, back up your reports.dic file before installing the GP 10 SP3/year-end update. After installation, rebuild the reports dictionary. After closing the year 2008, ensure your Dynamics GP user date is set in the new year to perform a check run.</description></item></channel></rss>