<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Lines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet.</description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points.</description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements.</description></item><item><title>LMDS Fills the Fiber Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</guid><description>Although fiber optic bandwidth is widely available across the country, connecting businesses to this network over the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; is a different story. It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to realize that less than 20% of commercial buildings are equipped for fiber optic telecommunications services.
This is primarily due to the high cost of installing fiber optic cables, a process that&amp;rsquo;s difficult to justify when businesses already have access to telephone and data services through existing copper lines.</description></item><item><title>FastE Is The New DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than their T1 lines can provide have usually upgraded to DS3. However, a faster and more affordable option, Fast Ethernet (FastE), is now available.
While you might not know Fast Ethernet as a Metro or Carrier bandwidth service, the term is likely familiar. Fast Ethernet refers to 100 Mbps Ethernet, one of the standard LAN speeds alongside 10 Mbps and 1,000 Mbps Ethernet (Gigabit Ethernet or GigE).</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Service Access For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</guid><description>Having internet access is essential for businesses today, whether they operate primarily online or from a physical location. It&amp;rsquo;s how businesses connect with customers, suppliers, remote employees, and even their own offices. But is the internet service used by businesses the same as what individuals use at home?
There are actually different options for internet service, each with unique features: dedicated or shared bandwidth, symmetrical or asymmetrical speeds, wired or wireless connection, copper or fiber optic cables, and varying levels of bandwidth and cost.</description></item></channel></rss>