<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Best of the Best on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/best-of-the-best/</link><description>Recent content in Best of the Best on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 20:52:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/best-of-the-best/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Eye Ring scanner transforms printed text into audio and Braille</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eye-ring-scanner-transforms-printed-text-into-audio-and-braille/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 20:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eye-ring-scanner-transforms-printed-text-into-audio-and-braille/</guid><description>Source: Red Dot Design website
Struggling to read? There&amp;rsquo;s a ring that could help. The Eye Ring, honored with a Best of the Best Red Dot Design Award in 2013, is a page scanner designed to be worn as a ring when not actively being used.
To use, the top of the ring is placed face-down on the text, initiating optical character recognition to transform the text into audio or Braille.</description></item><item><title>Adobe aims to achieve the highest level of performance in order to increase repeat visits and online sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</guid><description>Source: Adobe.
Recent Adobe research indicates that marketers in the Asia Pacific region who use best practices are significantly outperforming their competitors.
The Adobe Digital Index Best of the Best Benchmark for Asia Pacific analyzed websites across six regions: Australia and New Zealand, Southeast Asia, India, South Korea, Hong Kong, and China, comparing the average website performance with the top 20% based on six key performance indicators: mobile and tablet traffic, stick rate, visits per visitor, time spent, and conversion rate.</description></item></channel></rss>