<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Case Study on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/case-study/</link><description>Recent content in Case Study on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors.</description></item><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item></channel></rss>