<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intel/</link><description>Recent content in Intel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:50:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intel Security is turning to the cloud to enhance consumer security protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-is-turning-to-the-cloud-to-enhance-consumer-security-protection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-is-turning-to-the-cloud-to-enhance-consumer-security-protection/</guid><description>Intel Security has released its 2017 consumer security product line, aiming to provide better protection for everyday devices. The main feature is a new anti-malware engine that increases efficiency and effectiveness by performing analysis in the cloud. Enhancements for multiple devices are also included in McAfee AntiVirus Plus, McAfee Internet Security, McAfee Total Protection, and McAfee LiveSafe.
The McAfee Labs Threats Report: June 2016 revealed a 120% rise in new ransomware since Q1 2015 and over 4.</description></item><item><title>Intel has introduced solid state drives designed for use in business environments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 23:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</guid><description>Source: Intel website.
Intel has introduced the Intel SSD Pro 2500 Series, a new business-class addition to their Solid-State Drive (SSD) Professional family.
The Intel SSD Pro 2500 Series provides robust security features and capabilities designed for businesses of all sizes, giving them peace of mind. These drives offer hardware-based encryption, remote management capabilities, and a lower annual failure rate than traditional hard disk drives (HDDs), reducing the need for on-site IT support.</description></item><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology.</description></item><item><title>Technology usage in 2015 could be vastly different</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</guid><description>Source: Intel infographic. Learn more here.
Our current world relies on multiple connected devices, and this trend will only intensify. Intel believes that while we currently utilize various devices like wearables, smartphones, tablets, and PCs, the future holds even more significant changes.
Hermann Eul, VP and GM, Mobile and Communications Group at Intel, points out that users constantly demand better device performance. He highlights that in 2015, devices will need to meet the need for improved imaging, extended battery life without sacrificing performance, integrated experiences, and enhanced responsiveness.</description></item><item><title>Are your passwords secure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-passwords-secure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-passwords-secure/</guid><description>Intel Security commemorated World Password Day by providing helpful advice on enhancing online security through diverse authentication methods.
Steer Clear of Predictable Logins
Short and seemingly clever passwords are easily guessed. Cybercriminals often begin their attacks by testing common password combinations. Simple keyboard patterns like &amp;ldquo;qwerty&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;12345678&amp;rdquo; are just as insecure as passwords like &amp;ldquo;welcome&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;login.&amp;rdquo;
Craft Strong, Complex Passwords
Longer passwords are always more secure. Incorporate a mix of numbers, lowercase and uppercase letters, and symbols.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time.</description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing.</description></item><item><title>A new version of McAfee Mobile Security has been launched by Intel Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</guid><description>Intel Security has released the newest version of McAfee Mobile Security (MMS) for Android devices. This updated software offers enhanced security and improved device performance.
As people increasingly rely on their mobile devices for personal and sensitive tasks, MMS provides protection and addresses the need for faster speeds, longer battery life, and secure browsing on Android phones and tablets.
This new version of MMS allows users to maximize their Android device performance with features that optimize speed and battery life.</description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware.</description></item></channel></rss>