<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Criminal Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/criminal-law/</link><description>Recent content in Criminal Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/criminal-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's Returns Directive beneficial or detrimental to the well-being of undocumented migrants?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at the EU Returns Directive: Five Years On Many EU citizens are worried about the impact of immigration, especially when it comes to unauthorized migrants without legal status. Others, however, prioritize humane treatment for these individuals. To manage this challenge, the EU created the &amp;ldquo;Returns Directive&amp;rdquo; in 2008, outlining procedures for returning unauthorized migrants, including detention rules and procedural rights.
Upon its introduction, the Directive faced criticism from NGOs and academics who felt it was overly harsh...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Has the European Court of Justice shifted from being an offender to a protector of human rights in the context of the European Arrest Warrant?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Since its rushed creation after the 9/11 attacks, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) has become a cornerstone of EU criminal law. It replaces traditional extradition with a streamlined system lacking most of the usual limitations. This has worried critics concerned about potential miscarriages of justice but pleased supporters who appreciate the faster return of more fugitives to face justice.
Despite concerns from some EU countries&amp;rsquo; constitutional courts, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) has long dismissed human rights criticisms of the EAW...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unexpected turn of events? Case C-128/18 Dorobantu: the conditions of detention and the ECHR's relevance in the EU legal system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</guid><description>Ágoston Mohay, University of Pécs Faculty of Law
Introduction
The EU legal system is often viewed as a distinct entity, separate from both international and national law. Within this system, safeguarding fundamental rights is paramount. Article 6 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) establishes a three-pronged approach to fundamental rights protection: 1) the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union, 2) the EU&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and 3) general principles of EU law derived from the ECHR and shared constitutional values of member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advocating for children? The Directive on procedural safeguards for children suspected or accused in criminal proceedings.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</guid><description>Protecting Young Suspects in the EU: A Look at the New Directive If we don&amp;rsquo;t stand up for children, then we don&amp;rsquo;t stand for much.
Marian Wright Edelman
Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
Ensuring fair treatment within the criminal justice system is crucial, and this fairness necessitates different safeguards based on individual circumstances. Children, being particularly vulnerable, require special protective measures, as recognized by international standards such as the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child and the Council of Europe Guidelines on child-friendly justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Evolution of EU Criminal Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 06:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2014 was significant for the European Union, marked by events such as European Parliament elections, the establishment of a new European Commission, and notable legislative and case-law developments. This post, the first in a series, reviews key developments in specific EU law areas.
The most substantial change in EU criminal law occurred on December 1st, ending the five-year transition period for EU criminal law measures enacted before the Lisbon Treaty came into effect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pilate cleanses his hands. The CJEU's stance on pre-trial detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</guid><description>By Adriano Martufi (Assistant Professor, Leiden University) and Christina Peristeridou (Assistant Professor, Maastricht University)
Introduction
The recent judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of DK (C-653/19 PPU, 28 November 2019) has validated two concerning observations about the state of European criminal law. Firstly, Directive 2016/343 on the presumption of innocence has limited practical application, particularly regarding pre-trial detention. Secondly, pre-trial detention is a contentious subject, with both the CJEU and the EU legislator hesitant to establish common standards despite their absence negatively impacting mutual trust between Member States&amp;rsquo; judicial systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union rejects benefit tourism by EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant ruling in the case of Dano, which dealt with the ability of EU citizens to access social welfare benefits when they relocate to another Member State. The Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the laws in this case (and other rulings earlier this year involving EU citizens with criminal histories) suggests a stricter approach, possibly reflecting the ongoing political discussions regarding the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Restrictions on extradition to countries outside the EU due to EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) is a well-known EU law that streamlined extradition between member states, EU law generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern extradition to non-EU nations. Exceptions exist in cases of pre-existing treaties, like those with the USA and Norway/Iceland, or regarding asylum seekers. The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum laws restrict extraditing asylum-seekers before determining if the requesting country intends to persecute them.
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Petruhhin case has changed this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU guarantees the fundamental democratic and judicial oversight of the EU's foreign policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirmed in its recent decision in European Parliament v Council that the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) is subject to a minimum standard of democratic and judicial oversight.
The case involved a challenge by the European Parliament (EP) to the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign and ratify a treaty between the EU and Mauritius. This treaty pertained to the EU&amp;rsquo;s military operations against pirates operating in the Indian Ocean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Impact on UK's Participation in EU Policing and Criminal Law: EU Referendum Brief 5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
This piece examines the relationship between EU membership and UK policing and criminal law, exploring potential impacts of Brexit.
Summary
The UK held veto power over EU laws in this domain before the Treaty of Lisbon (enacted December 1, 2009). Subsequently, the UK secured two opt-out mechanisms: the ability to opt into (or out of) any new EU law in this area post-Treaty, and the option to retroactively opt out of pre-existing EU laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU bolsters criminal law protection of the EU's finances in The Italian Job.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Contrary to popular belief, fraud against the EU budget is not typically committed by corrupt EU officials. As per EU reports, the usual culprits are individuals or companies exploiting EU funds managed by Member States. These violations also extend beyond spending to include EU income reduction, such as evading customs duties on imports.
Establishing and upholding EU-wide regulations for such misconduct has been challenging. However, the Court of Justice (CJEU) significantly strengthened the law in this area with its recent Taricco judgment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Poor drivers and European Union legislation: The Court of Justice of the European Union takes the wrong approach.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</guid><description>Steve Peers
There&amp;rsquo;s a humorous anecdote about national stereotypes, where an American, a Canadian, a Brit, and a Frenchman are asked to write about elephants. The punchline highlights their different perspectives: the Frenchman focuses on the elephant&amp;rsquo;s mating habits, the Brit on its colonial significance, the American on its military uses, and the Canadian on whether the elephant falls under federal or provincial jurisdiction. This humorous scenario underscores how jurisdictional issues are central to Canadian identity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dear Colleague, Do You Possess Sufficient Independence? The Impact of Systemic Deficiencies in a Member State's Justice System on the Principle of Mutual Trust</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah*
*Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund For Scientific Research (F.R.S.-FNRS). The author wishes to thank Pr. S. Van Drooghenbroeck. The usual disclaimer applies.
Advocate General Tanchev recently presented his opinion on case C-216/18 PPU. This case involves multiple European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) issued by Polish authorities against an individual, LM, suspected of drug trafficking. The case, brought before the European Court of Justice (ECJ) by the Irish High Court, questions whether an EAW is enforceable if the issuing Member State&amp;rsquo;s conditions contradict the fundamental right to a fair trial due to systemic rule of law issues within its justice system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Arrest Warrants and the autonomy of public prosecutors as ruled by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Julia Burchett, PhD candidate at the Université libre de Bruxelles and the University of Grenoble
Introduction
Widely recognized as a cornerstone of EU criminal law, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as one of the most, if not the most, utilized tools for judicial cooperation in criminal matters among EU member states. This streamlined cross-border surrender procedure, designed for prosecution or execution of custodial sentences and detention orders, has replaced traditional systems relying on political involvement from individual member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Imprisoning bankers: the latest EU Directive on enforcing criminal penalties for market abuse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU politicians likely feel a sense of relief as they&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a group even less popular than themselves: bankers. This unpopularity has only intensified as the global financial crisis and resulting austerity measures continue to impact ordinary citizens across numerous Member States. Politicians understand that targeting disliked groups rarely hurts them in the polls, leading EU institutions to enact legislation that could imprison bankers for specific wrongdoings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The decision in Celaj by the CJEU: Implications of criminal penalties, entry bans, and the Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</guid><description>By Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a decision on October 1, 2015, in the case of Skerdjan Celaj (C-290/14) that once again addressed the relationship between immigration and criminal law. Specifically, the court examined whether national criminal penalties for unlawful migration align with the EU Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU foreign policy sanctions: utilizing EU criminal law powers to extend and enforce them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 02:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post draws upon research for the forthcoming 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law (OUP, 2023)
The EU Council recently decided to expand its criminal law authority to encompass breaches of EU foreign policy sanctions. Following this, the EU Commission presented a proposal for a Directive that aims to utilize this expanded authority to harmonize the criminal laws of Member States on this subject...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmonisation of criminal law and foreign policy sanctions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post builds on and updates research for the 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law(OUP, 2023)
In late 2023, EU Member States and the European Parliament reached an agreement on a Directive designed to standardize criminal law related to violations of EU foreign policy sanctions. (Update: The Directive was formally adopted in April 2024 and subsequently published in the EU Official Journal)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the CJEU judgment in LM a new era for mutual trust and independence of the judiciary, or just business as usual?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</guid><description>Dr. Agnieszka Frąckowiak-Adamska, Faculty of Law, University of Wroclaw
In the case of C-216/18 PPU LM, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was asked by an Irish court to consider a significant legal issue facing the EU: how restrictions on judicial independence in one member state impact other EU member states. A series of laws enacted in Poland from 2015 to 2018 has been widely criticized by numerous institutions, both within and outside Poland, for enabling legislative and executive branches to significantly interfere with the judicial process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's groundbreaking Directive 2024/1385 on Violence Against Women is a significant step forward in promoting gender equality.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</guid><description>Dr. Ceren Kasım, Postdoctoral Research and Teaching Fellow, University of Hildesheim, Germany
Photo credit: MesserWoland, via Wikimedia Commons
INTRODUCTION
May 14, 2024, marked a pivotal moment for the European Union (EU) as it unveiled its first legally binding instrument to combat violence against women and domestic violence. This Directive, officially known as Directive 2024/1385, signifies the EU&amp;rsquo;s strong commitment to achieving genuine equality for women.
Gender-based violence is a pervasive issue across the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Negotiating the future relationship between the UK and EU: the EU's mandate for negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Thanks to Georgina Wright, of the Institute for Government, for a &amp;rsquo;track changes&amp;rsquo; version of the negotiation mandate. The usual disclaimer applies.
This week, the UK-EU future relationship negotiation process progressed. The EU Council approved the negotiation mandate, differing from the initial proposal. This post provides an updated analysis, comparing the final mandate to the political declaration, highlighting differences between the EU and UK&amp;rsquo;s positions that are expected to make negotiations difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice has clarified that foreign fighters' accomplices are not eligible for refugee status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 15:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</guid><description>When can someone be refused asylum for terrorism? Professor Steve Peers
What happens when a person seeking refuge is suspected of terrorism or aiding terrorists? Can they still be considered a refugee? If not, how do we legally define &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; to justify denying their claim? The recent EU Court of Justice judgment in the Lounani case clarifies some aspects of this complex issue but leaves some challenging questions unanswered.
Legal Framework The UN Refugee Convention (Geneva Convention) outlines an &amp;rsquo;exclusion&amp;rsquo; clause in Article 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Inquiries for potential Commissioners of Home Affairs and Justice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 01:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Emilio de Capitani, and Henri Labayle present a series of questions for Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to pose to the candidates for Commissioners of Immigration and Home Affairs and Justice. These questions aim to understand the candidates&amp;rsquo; plans and secure commitments on crucial matters.
Immigration and Asylum
Given the Commission&amp;rsquo;s stance on framing migration policy with the non-binding Global Approach to Migration and Mobility Partnerships, would the candidate propose a legally binding basis for agreements with relevant nations, based on Articles 77, 78, and 79 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cracking down on online terrorism - a threat to freedom of speech? The EU Regulation on online terrorist content under scrutiny.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
On September 12th, 2018, the European Commission presented a proposal for a regulation aimed at combating terrorist content online. This regulation would mandate that EU Member States require internet platforms to proactively remove such content and ensure that authorities possess the capabilities to address this illegal material. This proposal builds upon existing voluntary partnerships like the EU Internet Forum and previous non-binding recommendations from the Commission on tackling illegal content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What's all the fuss about the draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</guid><description>Cian C. Murphy, The Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London
The transnational public sphere continues to be gradually suppressed. The European Union&amp;rsquo;s initial legislative response to recent killings by Islamic State militants in Europe and elsewhere is a draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism, which was published last month. The Directive, which seeks to expand the scope of EU law in national criminal law regarding terrorism, will replace the Framework Decision on Combating Terrorism, which was initially approved in 2002 and revised in 2008...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK is now part of the Schengen Information System, bringing the Panopticon Home.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The idea of a &amp;ldquo;Panopticon,&amp;rdquo; a prison where guards could potentially see any inmate at any point, was conceived over two centuries ago by British philosopher Jeremy Bentham. He believed that the constant threat of observation would motivate prisoners to act appropriately. This concept is now often used to illustrate contemporary patterns in widespread monitoring and societal control.
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) initial move in this direction was the establishment of the Schengen Information System (SIS) during the 1990s...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>