<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Constitutional Courts on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/constitutional-courts/</link><description>Recent content in Constitutional Courts on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/constitutional-courts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Close partners: The highest courts of member states and the enforcement of EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Two high courts in France and Spain recently issued significant rulings concerning how lawyers and domestic courts should apply EU law. Although dealing with distinct issues, both decisions are important for properly implementing EU law. As noted a few weeks prior, national high courts are becoming crucial in EU law, a trend the Court of Justice should encourage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Arrest Warrant and the German Constitutional Court: A new development in the legal conversation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The German Constitutional Court (GCC) has issued another impactful ruling, this time concerning fundamental rights. In an order published yesterday, the GCC exercised its authority to review the implementation of a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) from Italy to Germany. The subject, a US citizen convicted in Italy in absentia, argued that his conviction lacked due process and that Italian law provided no recourse for appeal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Constitutional Conflict in the European Union: A Jurisprudential Analysis (OUP 2022)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</guid><description>Ana Bobić, Law Clerk at the Court of Justice of the European Union
Photo credit: Antoine Montulé, via Wikicommons
It has been almost 60 years since the Court of Justice established that EU law takes precedence. However, this principle still sparks discussions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s constitutional system. Initially, the integration of EU law into national legal frameworks caused tension between the Court of Justice and national constitutional courts. The Court of Justice believes strongly in the importance of EU law&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness and expects all national courts to share this view...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>