<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2030 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2030/</link><description>Recent content in 2030 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:38:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2030/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dell: This is the perspective of Singaporean business leaders on the future of human-machine interaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/</guid><description>A significant shift towards human-machine partnerships is underway, but business leaders in the Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) region hold differing views on its implications, according to a global study by Dell Technologies. While 80% of APJ business leaders anticipate humans and machines functioning as integrated teams within five years, their outlook on this future is divided.
While a majority (58%) of Singaporean business leaders believe automation will increase their free time, opinions are split on the broader societal effects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2030 Food: Sustainable, Healthier, Personalized</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</guid><description>- Businesses for Good: In the future, successful companies will be those committed to improving the well-being of both the planet and its people.
- Personalized Nutrition: Technological advancements will allow consumers to create highly customized approaches to enhance their physical and mental health.
Source: Mintel.
- Tech-Driven Food Solutions: Consumer confidence in food science and technology will grow as these become essential for securing the food supply. Mintel, a market research firm focused on consumer insights, has identified three significant trends expected to shape the global food, drink, and food service industries in the coming decade:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>