<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wellness on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wellness/</link><description>Recent content in Wellness on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wellness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Activpass provides discounted rates for wellness activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</guid><description>Source: Activpass. Activpass is a mobile-based marketplace for booking lifestyle activities.
The team behind Activpass, a platform designed for businesses and professionals in fitness, wellness, and beauty, believes in living life to the fullest. Their mobile platform gives users access to over 1,000 services like yoga, training sessions, golf, massages, and beauty treatments, all without requiring a long-term commitment.
Users can easily book and pay for services on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globetrekker Challenge creates a wellness portal for Garmin in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Globetrekker Challenge, a Singapore-based corporate wellness software company, will provide their corporate wellness platform to Garmin for distribution across Asia and the Pacific. This collaboration leverages each company&amp;rsquo;s strengths, allowing them to focus on their core offerings.
Globetrekker&amp;rsquo;s platform offers customizable wellness programs, real-time analytics reporting, and health risk profiling for employers. Through this partnership, Garmin&amp;rsquo;s clients can access these features and integrate them with Garmin&amp;rsquo;s wearable devices, creating a comprehensive employee health improvement solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anantara's Al Baleed Resort Salalah introduces new wellness program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</guid><description>Source: Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara. The Balance Wellness by Anantara program includes custom-designed vegan cuisine.
The luxurious, private pool villa resort Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara has introduced a new wellness program with an a la carte approach.
Situated between a private beach and a freshwater lagoon in Salalah, Oman, Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara provides a serene setting for guests to focus on their wellness goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Employers in Singapore are struggling with stress and mental health concerns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:23:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</guid><description>A large majority (72%) of Singaporean employers view stress and mental health as factors that negatively impact productivity, according to the APAC Benefits Strategy Study 2017 conducted by global professional services firm Aon.
The International Labour Organization has labeled stress a &amp;ldquo;global epidemic&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;silent killer,&amp;rdquo; particularly within many Asian countries experiencing rapid economic growth and adopting Western lifestyles, including Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and mainland China.
Early physical symptoms of stress can manifest as chronic back pain, fatigue, and headaches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Making small changes to your lifestyle can lead to a healthier you in the long run, according to Herbalife</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</guid><description>People in Asia are interested in expanding their fitness routines beyond traditional practices like yoga and tai chi. However, Samantha Clayton, Director of Worldwide Fitness Education at Herbalife, notes that they face unique challenges, such as extreme weather and demanding work schedules, and need to adapt their fitness routines accordingly.
She emphasizes the importance of integrating fitness into everyday life, especially when environmental factors like air quality, heat, and humidity can be obstacles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BDMS Connect Center in Bangkok now offers a wider range of MICE options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</guid><description>Source: Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok. BDMS Connect Center.
The BDMS Wellness Campus is proud to introduce its latest addition, the BDMS Connect Center. This cutting-edge facility, spanning over 3,400 square meters in the heart of Bangkok, is set to redefine the standards of meeting and event spaces.
Dan Smith, General Manager of Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok, expressed his enthusiasm for the new facility, stating that the BDMS Connect Center is a one-of-a-kind space, emphasizing both functionality and a commitment to wellness and sustainability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers of Singtel and AIA Singapore will enjoy the advantages of digital wellness initiatives offered in collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 05:51:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</guid><description>Singtel and AIA Singapore are joining forces to encourage healthier lifestyles in Singapore. This partnership between leaders in communications technology and life insurance is the first of its kind in the country.
The collaboration aims to digitally reach their combined customer base of over 5 million, motivating them to be active and healthy. They also intend to develop innovative insurance products tailored to the evolving digital habits of their customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>