<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lebanon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lebanon/</link><description>Recent content in Lebanon on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lebanon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The bank in Beirut provides live video conferencing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</guid><description>Bank Audi has established a new flagship branch called &amp;ldquo;Novo&amp;rdquo; in Beirut Central District&amp;rsquo;s Palladium Building. This branch is open every day of the year from 10 am to 10 pm and provides customers with interactive banking services.
In addition to smart ATMs offering services like cash withdrawals, cash and check deposits, and credit card payments, the branch introduces a first-of-its-kind feature in Lebanon: Interactive Teller Machines (ITMs). These ITMs enable customers to connect with personal tellers through live video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coral Beirut Al Hamra now offers two additional Ambassador Suites as part of its room options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</guid><description>The Coral Beirut Al Hamra Hotel recently introduced a new suite category featuring expansive rooftop terraces with outdoor seating areas. Situated on the 11th floor, the 87 square meter Ambassador Suites offer fully equipped kitchens, large living rooms, and luxurious bathrooms, complete with high-end amenities.
Hartmut Grauel, General Manager of the hotel, stated that these new suites cater to the preferences of discerning travelers. He noted a consistent demand for spacious accommodations akin to full-size apartments, complete with kitchens and living rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>