<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Cable on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-cable/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Cable on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:59:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-cable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Copper Thrives In The 21st Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</guid><description>For over a century, copper wire has been the backbone of telecommunications, connecting homes and businesses. While fiber optic technology has advanced, copper remains dominant, even in the 21st century.
Despite the rise of fiber optics, copper persists due to its widespread availability and established infrastructure. Connecting to existing copper is often more cost-effective than installing new fiber optic lines.
While copper-based systems were designed for analog signals, they can still handle today’s high-speed digital demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speeds Come to Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</guid><description>Cablevision Systems Corp. is pushing the boundaries of broadband speed by offering internet speeds exceeding 100 Mbps over its existing cable TV infrastructure. This new high-speed internet service, launching on May 11th, provides download speeds up to 101 Mbps and upload speeds up to 15 Mbps for approximately $100 per month.
One might wonder how cable TV lines, which traditionally use coaxial cables, can achieve such high speeds, usually associated with fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Cable Gets Limber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 05:38:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</guid><description>Fiber optic and copper cable are competing to be the main wiring used in communication setups, whether for renovations, improvements, or brand new projects. However, fiber is already recognized as the superior long-term option. Copper persists due to its widespread implementation and compatibility with existing switches and routers.
A significant installation obstacle has hindered the widespread adoption of fiber optic cabling: limited fiber bending flexibility. Exceeding this limit not only risks snapping the delicate strands but also creates functional issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>