<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sized on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sized/</link><description>Recent content in Sized on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>