<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cyber Monday on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cyber-monday/</link><description>Recent content in Cyber Monday on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cyber-monday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday Cell Phone Deals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</guid><description>The best deals on cell phones can be found online, especially during sales like Cyber Monday. These limited-time offers on free and discounted phones are valid until midnight today, Monday.
For a limited time, get a free BlackBerry Bold 9700 for AT&amp;amp;T after an instant online discount. This offer includes a bonus of free activation for up to five lines, making it perfect for family plans.
Prefer a different BlackBerry? The BlackBerry Curve in Titanium or silver is also available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Picking On Cyber Monday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</guid><description>Similar to how Black Friday has become a tradition for in-person shopping, Cyber Monday is now the time for finding exceptional online deals. With that in mind, let&amp;rsquo;s explore a standout product line this year: BlackBerry devices from Research in Motion.
Business users have long favored BlackBerry for mobile communication. RIM has prioritized supporting corporate IT with the performance and security needed for serious business use on the go. But how affordable are these popular BlackBerry models?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cash In Old Gadgets To Buy New Gadgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 03:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</guid><description>The holiday shopping season is here, and with it comes the temptation of new electronics and gadgets. However, it&amp;rsquo;s also a time to be mindful of spending. One smart solution is to turn your old electronics into cash to fund those new purchases.
It&amp;rsquo;s common to have unused electronics lying around. We hesitate to discard them because they still hold value. This unused tech represents a potential savings account that can help you afford those tempting new gadgets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath’s Black Friday Strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</guid><description>Black Friday, the day following Thanksgiving, is the traditional kickoff for Christmas shopping. Its success is crucial for retailers, as it can significantly impact their yearly profitability.
The term &amp;ldquo;Black Friday&amp;rdquo; is believed to originate from the accounting practice of using red ink for losses and black ink for profits. Many retailers struggle throughout the year, making the holiday shopping season, especially Black Friday, vital for their financial stability.
Black Friday, along with its online counterpart Cyber Monday (the Monday after Thanksgiving), initiates the busiest and most demanding sales period for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>