<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IPad on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ipad/</link><description>Recent content in IPad on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ipad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud On The Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</guid><description>Big corporations are shifting their data centers to the cloud for financial and logistical benefits, enabling work from anywhere. But what about smaller businesses? Can they enjoy similar advantages?
One cloud solution often overlooked due to its existence before the cloud trend is GoToMyPC. Although not typically associated with the cloud, it embodies the concept.
GoToMyPC enables remote login to your computer. But isn&amp;rsquo;t accessing your desktop from a restaurant, running office applications, conceptually similar to using a private cloud?</description></item><item><title>What To Do With Old Cell Phones and Electronics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</guid><description>So, you&amp;rsquo;ve finally upgraded to the latest smartphone but now you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with your old one. It&amp;rsquo;s useless without a service plan but you hesitate to get rid of it.
Years pass and you stumble upon it again, completely forgotten. It&amp;rsquo;s just an outdated piece of technology now, the battery long depleted. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe it was once worth hundreds of dollars, leaving you wondering if you could have sold it.</description></item><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars.</description></item><item><title>Bosign is broadening its range of technology products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosign-is-broadening-its-range-of-technology-products/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosign-is-broadening-its-range-of-technology-products/</guid><description>Bosign, a privately held Swedish company known for designing, patenting, and producing reasonably priced, top-notch Scandinavian lifestyle products, has introduced a new line of tech accessories for mobile device users.
A standout feature of the new iPad Carrying Sleeve is its discreet leather fold-out handles, offering a convenient alternative for carrying the iPad. Measuring 28cm wide, 21cm high, and 1.2cm deep, the iPad Carrying Sleeve is crafted from felt to shield iPads from scratches and dust.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has announced that the iPad Pro is now available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-announced-that-the-ipad-pro-is-now-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-announced-that-the-ipad-pro-is-now-available/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Singtel now offers the new iPad Pro with Wi-Fi + Cellular. This tablet boasts a 12.9-inch Retina display, packing 5.6 million pixels for exceptional resolution, and its size rivals some laptops. Customers can also purchase smart cases and silicone covers.
According to a Singtel representative, &amp;ldquo;Singtel will offer iPad Pro with a variety of attractive data plans that will allow customers to connect to its tri-band 4G network.</description></item><item><title>The Flickr App for iPad has been optimized for iOS 8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a new Flickr app designed for iPads, allowing users seamless photo management across all devices. Yahoo claims the app is optimized for iOS 8, providing an enhanced experience for capturing, editing, and browsing images.
Source: Yahoo.
Current iPad users can update their existing Flickr app, while new users can download it from the App Store. The app supports multiple languages, including English, French, Indonesian, Korean, Chinese, and Vietnamese.</description></item><item><title>The new iPad Air 2 from Apple is thinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-ipad-air-2-from-apple-is-thinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 11:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-ipad-air-2-from-apple-is-thinner/</guid><description>Apple unveiled its slimmest iPad yet, the iPad Air 2, at a highly anticipated event on October 16th.
The updated iPad boasts an enhanced Retina display for improved contrast, a richer color palette, and superior cameras. Available in gold, alongside the classic silver and space gray, both the iPad Air 2 and the new iPad mini 3 feature Touch ID. In the US, these models will also offer Apple Pay, a new payment system.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has observed that 20% of its users access the website via iPads, prompting the airline to develop an iPad app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 10:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</guid><description>Emirates airline has introduced the Emirates App for iPad, available globally through the App Store. This app allows users to easily explore destinations and manage their Emirates travel experiences.
With a simple tap, users can discover information on over 130 Emirates destinations across six continents and learn about the airline&amp;rsquo;s renowned services.
The Emirates App for iPad simplifies travel management for Emirates customers, whether they&amp;rsquo;re on the move, in flight, or at home.</description></item><item><title>Evernote introduces a new and improved app with a redesigned interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</guid><description>Evernote has announced three updates: a brand new app, a significantly enhanced feature, and a major app redesign.
As detailed in a recent blog post, the company will introduce &amp;ldquo;Scannable,&amp;rdquo; a mobile scanning app. Scannable can transform physical items like business cards and receipts into digital content that can be easily shared and acted upon. It also integrates with the ScanSnap Evernote Edition desktop scanner, enabling shared scanning across a user&amp;rsquo;s network and essentially turning it into a shared office resource.</description></item><item><title>ItSeez3D has released an updated version of its 3D scanner app for iPad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</guid><description>Source: itSeez3D page on the App Store.
itSeez3D, a company that develops 3D scanning software, has released an updated version of their mobile scanning app, also named itSeez3D. This app, designed for use with the Occipital Structure Sensor 3D device, now allows iPads to generate lifelike, full-body 3D models.
This updated app serves as a valuable tool for 3D printing, enabling the scanning of a full-color figurine in under two minutes.</description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing.</description></item></channel></rss>