<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content Management on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-management/</link><description>Recent content in Content Management on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:33:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WordPress Hosting Made Cheap and Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/</guid><description>A lot of dedicated bloggers and website creators opt for WordPress to power their websites. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable and boasts a large community of developers who create themes and plugins. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to WordPress, you can start with the online version to learn the basics. However, you&amp;rsquo;ll eventually want the control and scalability that comes with hosting WordPress yourself.
Now you need to make a decision: Do you want to host WordPress the easy way or the hard way?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wordpress-hosting-made-cheap-and-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Uncovering the untapped potential of business cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uncovering-the-untapped-potential-of-business-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uncovering-the-untapped-potential-of-business-cards/</guid><description>Although 62% of surveyed individuals believe business cards remain important, their full potential often goes unrealized.
On average, respondents accumulated 864 business cards throughout their careers.
Despite the rise of digital tools, 90% of those surveyed haven&amp;rsquo;t digitized all their collected business cards.
Inaccurate data entry poses a significant concern, with 70% citing it as a challenge when digitizing cards.
Individuals who shared contacts within their company saw over double the referral business compared to those who didn&amp;rsquo;t...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uncovering-the-untapped-potential-of-business-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uncovering-the-untapped-potential-of-business-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>