<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guide on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guide/</link><description>Recent content in Guide on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:48:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2015 Singapore Christmas Gift Guide: The Joyful Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</guid><description>The holiday season is here, and with it comes the need for corporate gift ideas. Fortunately, there are many options to choose from this year.
Source: Kaizer Leather website.
Kaizer Leather offers a variety of leather business gifts, ranging from handcrafted luggage to smaller leather accessories. One notable option is the Cavalry Business Bag (shown above), crafted from high-quality Italian calf leather and featuring a detachable, adjustable shoulder strap.
~ o ~..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Hong Kong offers a plethora of high-end gift options. Make a lasting impression with these distinctive incentive or corporate gift suggestions:
For the Fashionable
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjTOBGQGtqMhlt_i0m3XHwBn1QjO906znU9xMy97VBPqWBHVy80nBxjOKm1Lgg1I_v5sIp6sxy7HGCTZRC2xSpXTAGFdVOIKDSwZQes3MFguk5NpzGOVFh1lp4vHGEYKbE_CzRPC6l2PblW/s1600/chandelier+earrings.JPG)
Source: The 5th C. My 5-Ways chandelier earrings.
The 5th C, a Hong Kong-based diamond consultancy and jewelry brand, presents My 5-Ways, a completely customizable pair of diamond earrings. At their core, My 5-Ways are elegant stud earrings. However, with a few simple adjustments, they transform into studs with drops, elegant dangle earrings, or eye-catching chandelier earrings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2020 Christmas Gift Guide: Must-Have Gadgets for the Holiday Season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:34:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>As the year ends, it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to treat yourself. Check out these gadgets for relaxation and maybe even work:
OPPO Find X2 Pro smartphone
The OPPO Find X2 Pro blends technology and elegant design. Marketed as &amp;ldquo;a cinema in your hand,&amp;rdquo; it boasts a 120 Hz QHD+ Ultra Vision screen with exceptional resolution, color, refresh rate, and brightness. Enjoy immersive audio and video with its powerful dual speakers and Dolby Atmos...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sydney's Christmas programme has been officially launched by the City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</guid><description>Source: City of Sydney. Lord Mayor Clover Moore launched the Sydney Christmas program at Martin Place.
Sydney has officially begun its Christmas celebrations, featuring an array of decorations, carols, light displays, concerts, Christmas trees, and special retail events.
Lord Mayor Clover Moore expressed her enthusiasm for the festivities, stating, &amp;ldquo;Each year, we warmly welcome thousands of people from all over Sydney to the city center for our Christmas celebrations. With live concerts, vibrant light projections, excellent shopping opportunities, and the chance for kids to meet Santa, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone - visitors, shoppers, and locals alike...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Shizuoka guide provides exclusive tips for exploring the city</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 09:27:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</guid><description>Source: Shizuoka City Tourism &amp;amp; City Relations Division.
The Shizuoka City Tourism &amp;amp; City Relations Division in Japan has created the &amp;ldquo;SHIZUOKA GUIDE,&amp;rdquo; a 52-page guidebook containing coupons. The guide helps inbound tourists enjoy local food and shopping at affordable prices.
Information was collected from locals who typically share recommendations through word-of-mouth. The guide features:
Lists of popular restaurants ranked by popularity. Locations offering local products like green tea and Mount Fuji souvenirs at reasonable prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New report on Expatriate Services launched by Alliott Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 13:49:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/</guid><description>The Alliott Group has released a new &amp;ldquo;Expatriate Services&amp;rdquo; report to assist businesses in relocating employees internationally. Alliott Group&amp;rsquo;s global member firms help companies optimize their mobility process, evaluate compensation packages, and manage cross-border employment structures and expenses.
The report, produced by a renowned international alliance of professional services firms, spans 29 countries, including Turkey, Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, New Zealand, and Singapore. It serves as a resource for navigating the complex web of tax, immigration, and employment laws impacting globally mobile workforces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>