<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Launch on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/launch/</link><description>Recent content in Launch on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/launch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the ability to hail a cab using Hailo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</guid><description>Hailo, a highly-rated taxi app boasting more five-star reviews than any other similar service, launched in Singapore on October 29th. With a global network of over 60,000 drivers and a strong user base exceeding 1.4 million, Hailo reports a ride request every two seconds somewhere in the world.
Source: Hailo. From left: Benny Lim, Managing Director, SMRT Road Holdings; Ron Zeghibe, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Executive Chairman, Hailo Global, and Yu Hsiang Wong, General Manager, Hailo Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Evernote is unveiling new additions to the Pfeiffer Collection of desktop accessories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</guid><description>Evernote has expanded its Pfeiffer Collection, a line of modern desktop accessories designed in collaboration with Eric Pfeiffer.
The latest additions are bent plywood platforms crafted to securely elevate laptops, tablets, and monitors on desks, while also providing extra storage space.
Source: Evernote blog.
The new products include:
Laptop platform: This stand, made of walnut bent ply, supports 13” or 15” laptops. A curved front trough can hold small items, and cables can be routed through the back.</description></item><item><title>Where could my Integration Manager be hiding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-could-my-integration-manager-be-hiding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-could-my-integration-manager-be-hiding/</guid><description>A user encountering an issue in Microsoft Dynamics GP where the &amp;ldquo;Integration Manager&amp;rdquo; option under Tools &amp;gt; Integrate appears unresponsive, despite having proper security permissions and the application launching correctly from the Start menu, can resolve this problem with a simple fix.
The solution involves navigating to the Microsoft Dynamics GP program directory (typically located at C:\Program Files\Microsoft Dynamics\GP) and locating the &amp;ldquo;Dex.ini&amp;rdquo; file within the Data folder.
Open this file using Notepad and verify that the file paths specified for &amp;ldquo;IntegrationManagerExePath&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;IMWizard&amp;rdquo; are accurate, making any necessary corrections.</description></item><item><title>Dell introduces an improved range of PCs for both consumer and commercial markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</guid><description>Dell debuted groundbreaking personal computing innovations at the annual Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in the US. They also updated their XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware consumer lines. Their OptiPlex, Latitude, and Precision commercial products received upgrades to 7th Gen Intel Core processors, USB-C with Thunderbolt 3 connectivity, and new professional graphics from NVIDIA and AMD. Dell&amp;rsquo;s monitor lineup also saw a refresh. The new Dell PC portfolio is equipped with Windows 10 and 7th Gen Intel Core processors, designed to maximize user productivity and creativity.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has seen the launch of four new BMW models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</guid><description>BMW Group Asia is launching four new car models simultaneously for the first time in Singapore.
The First-Ever BMW i8 Roadster The BMW i8 Roadster features upward-opening doors.
This groundbreaking convertible plug-in hybrid, dubbed a &amp;ldquo;gentleman&amp;rsquo;s racer,&amp;rdquo; can accelerate from 0 to 100 km/h in 4.6 seconds. CS Liew, a director at an agricultural science company, owns the first edition in Singapore, which is already on the road. Initially preferring hardtop convertibles, Liew was captivated by the i8 Roadster&amp;rsquo;s design.</description></item><item><title>Dell updates tablets, unveils new 5K monitor and smart desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 20:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</guid><description>Dell has improved its PC selection to boost productivity with new tablet functionalities, a 5K Ultra HD monitor, and a futuristic &amp;ldquo;smart desk&amp;rdquo; workspace.
Jeff Clarke, Dell&amp;rsquo;s Vice Chairman of Operations and President of Client Solutions, highlighted Dell&amp;rsquo;s focus on improving productivity and business outcomes at the recent Dell World Executive Summit.
The Dell UltraSharp 27 Monitor, available in December for US$2,499, offers Ultra HD 5K resolution (5,120 x 2,880), seven times sharper than Full HD.</description></item><item><title>Starting from 26 September, StarHub is excited to welcome buyers of the iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 18:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Source: StarHub. Customers waiting in line inside the newly renovated StarHub Shop in VivoCity, one of 38 StarHub stores serving pre-order customers on September 25th.
On September 25th, pre-orders for Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus became available for pickup at 38 StarHub stores across Singapore. To ensure a smooth pickup process, customers who pre-ordered were given specific locations and time slots when they booked their appointments.
Starting September 26th, customers can visit any StarHub Shop or participating authorized retailers to purchase the phones directly.</description></item><item><title>The launch of Windows 10 in Singapore is met with great excitement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-windows-10-in-singapore-is-met-with-great-excitement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-windows-10-in-singapore-is-met-with-great-excitement/</guid><description>The Windows 10 launch event in Singapore was a resounding success, drawing a large crowd.
Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows 10 is now widely accessible, offered as a free upgrade for a limited time or with new computer systems and tablets in 190 countries. This latest version introduces features like Windows Hello, Cortana, an Xbox app, and the Microsoft Edge browser, aiming to deliver a familiar yet enhanced user experience.
Jessica Tan, Managing Director of Microsoft Singapore, highlighted that Windows 10 empowers individuals and groups to achieve remarkable things.</description></item></channel></rss>