<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microsoft on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microsoft/</link><description>Recent content in Microsoft on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adobe and Microsoft software will now collaborate more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</guid><description>Adobe has enhanced Adobe Document Cloud as part of their partnership with Microsoft. Both companies want to provide excellent digital document experiences to their many shared customers.
Adobe Sign is now more integrated with Microsoft Dynamics 365. This provides real-time access to customer information from LinkedIn Sales Navigator and allows for more automated sales processes. New PDF integrations will enable all Office 365 users who subscribe to Adobe Acrobat DC for teams or enterprises to create, edit, and view secure, high-quality PDFs.</description></item><item><title>What qualities define exceptional training?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:35:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading training sessions, including a Dynamics GP Distribution Partner Academy and a customized Forecaster training. These distinct classes got me thinking about the elements of exceptional training and what makes it truly valuable. I&amp;rsquo;d love to share my thoughts and hear yours!
Relevant Content: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for training content to align with student needs. While this can be challenging with pre-determined classes, instructors can bridge the gap by connecting content to real-world scenarios.</description></item><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors.</description></item><item><title>Bank Mandiri is seeking submissions for the Young Entrepreneur award 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</guid><description>Bank Mandiri, a prominent bank in Indonesia, launched its yearly competition called Mandiri Young Entrepreneur (WMM) in 2015.
Kartika Wirjoatmodjo, the Director of Finance &amp;amp; Strategy at Bank Mandiri, stated that this competition aims to discover young individuals with entrepreneurial potential who can contribute to Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s growth. Kartika added that the competition also intends to inspire a passion for entrepreneurship and innovation among students and graduates, encouraging more young entrepreneurs to emerge.</description></item><item><title>The Australian government, in collaboration with Microsoft and MassChallenge, aims to enhance the local startup ecosystem</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</guid><description>The Australian government is investing A$280,000 to bring MassChallenge, a leading global startup accelerator, to Australia. The goal is to support the growth of local startups.
MassChallenge, in partnership with Microsoft Australia and the Australian government, will offer resources such as idea-pitching competitions, boot camps, and mentoring to strengthen the Australian startup ecosystem. As a non-profit, equity-free accelerator, MassChallenge provides promising startups with the opportunity to compete for millions of dollars in cash awards.</description></item><item><title>Trend Micro advises Windows users to update their operating system to safeguard against the Winshock bug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</guid><description>A recently discovered flaw in Microsoft Windows has Trend Micro urging all Windows users to immediately update their systems. The issue exists in Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s data transfer platform, which is designed for secure communication. Trend Micro warns that users who don&amp;rsquo;t update are highly vulnerable to attacks, potentially allowing hackers to take control of their systems without any user interaction.
This bug, nicknamed &amp;ldquo;Winshock,&amp;rdquo; received a severity score of 9.3 out of 10 from the Common Vulnerability Scoring System.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans will receive increased support for SkillsFuture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</guid><description>Source: SkillsFuture Singapore. Minister Puthucheary watches on as Ng (left) and Kevin Wo, Country GM, Microsoft Singapore (right) sign the MoU.
To better equip Singapore&amp;rsquo;s workforce and businesses for a digital-centric economy, SkillsFuture Singapore (SSG) has launched new initiatives. These include a partnership with Microsoft and enhancements to the national SkillsFuture for Digital Workplace program.
Dr. Janil Puthucheary, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Transport and Ministry of Communications and Information, announced these developments at the first SkillsFuture Festival X Smart Nation (SFFXSmart Nation) event.</description></item><item><title>Get inspired anywhere with a Microsoft Surface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-inspired-anywhere-with-a-microsoft-surface/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-inspired-anywhere-with-a-microsoft-surface/</guid><description>Mindflyer utilizes the Surface, with his design for the angpows displayed on the screen. The artwork features his interpretation of Nian, a mythical creature symbolizing the arrival of spring.
The Microsoft Surface series presents an excellent option for creative professionals. Singaporean artist Michael Ng, known professionally as Mindflyer, was commissioned to design red packets for Microsoft in 2019. Ng shared that the Surface platform is well-suited for his commissioned work, which he creates entirely on a Surface tablet.</description></item><item><title>You can now pre-order the new Microsoft Surface 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</guid><description>At an event in Singapore in April, bloggers were given the opportunity to test out the Surface 3, as well as the Lumia 640 and 640 XL.
The Surface Pro was a hit, but some users desired more. Ian Tan, the Surface Lead for Consumer at Microsoft Singapore, revealed during a media event that certain customers requested a lighter, more budget-friendly device, a request to which Microsoft paid attention.</description></item><item><title>Dropbox and Microsoft collaborating more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Dropbox and Microsoft are joining forces to make it easier for their users to work together. This collaboration will allow users to seamlessly work with Dropbox and Microsoft Office on their phones, tablets, and computers. Given that over 1.2 billion people use Microsoft Office and 35 billion Office files are stored in Dropbox, this partnership has the potential to benefit a lot of users.
This integration will enable users to edit their Dropbox documents directly in the relevant Office application.</description></item><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server.</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Troublesome Window and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mystery-of-the-troublesome-window-and-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mystery-of-the-troublesome-window-and-security/</guid><description>It can be frustrating when setting up security in GP 10.0 (or GP 2010). Take limiting access to payroll data, for instance. You disable the Payroll Clerk role, thinking that&amp;rsquo;s enough, but then you test it and find various Payroll windows still accessible.
While the Payroll Clerk role manages transactions and cards, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t cover setup, utilities, routines, reports, Smartlists, or inquiries. Even after removing relevant tasks and roles, like those within the Accounting Manager role, some windows remain stubbornly visible.</description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself for the Windows 10 experience on all your devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-windows-10-experience-on-all-your-devices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-windows-10-experience-on-all-your-devices/</guid><description>Microsoft introduced a new, more personalized version of Windows designed to provide a consistent experience across a variety of devices, from Xbox and PCs to phones, tablets, and more.
Windows 10 aims to adapt to different devices and user activities, creating a unified and user-friendly experience. CEO Satya Nadella emphasized the goal of making Windows 10 beloved by current users and attracting billions more.
The company prioritizes a seamless experience across devices, supporting natural interactions like voice, gestures, and gaze.</description></item><item><title>The most effective productivity hacks for Microsoft Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</guid><description>Microsoft Office 2013 offers several improvements over previous versions, but long-time users may not be aware of these useful additions. At the Singapore launch of Office 365 Personal, Elsie Chong, Marketing Manager for Microsoft Singapore, highlighted her favorite new features:
PDF Reflow in Word 2013 allows users to open PDF files as editable Word documents, retaining the original formatting as much as possible. The modified document can be saved as a PDF or a Word file.</description></item><item><title>Eliminating uncertainty in analytics with BeyondCore Apps for Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</guid><description>Source: BeyondCore website.
BeyondCore has introduced BeyondCore Apps for Office, a solution that provides automated analysis for the Microsoft Office suite with a single click. The company recognized the need for accessible and efficient analytics tools for business users who require data-driven insights to make informed decisions and improve their operations.
Arijit Sengupta, CEO and Founder of BeyondCore, highlighted the challenges of traditional analytics, describing it as a manual and time-consuming process.</description></item><item><title>Protect your Office 365 emails with the latest Dropsuite cloud solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</guid><description>Smaller businesses can access Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s email backup and archiving tool for Microsoft Office 365 through intermediary companies like Ozhosting in Australia and ICONZ-Webvisions in Singapore.
Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Charif Elansari, emphasized their commitment to developing user-friendly solutions that are easy for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to buy and use.
Ozhosting CEO, Doug Endersbee, expressed satisfaction in offering Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive email archiving service, which meets legal requirements for retaining records, to their customers.</description></item><item><title>A new budget-friendly Lumia is about to be released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The Lumia 430.
Microsoft has released the Lumia 430 Dual SIM, its most budget-friendly Lumia smartphone that can be upgraded to Windows 10*. Priced at approximately S$119, the Lumia 430 joins Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s affordable smartphone lineup alongside the Lumia 435, which features Lumia Camera.
Equipped with Windows Phone 8.1, a Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a 1.2GHz dual-core CPU, and pre-installed Microsoft Office, Skype, and OneDrive, the Lumia 430 Dual SIM enables users to be productive at work, enjoy entertainment, and stay connected while on the move.</description></item><item><title>Today is International Women's Day: can you help create the future? #MakeWhatsNext</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft blog. Ada Lovelace was the world&amp;rsquo;s first computer programmer.
In honor of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day, a global celebration of the achievements of women, Microsoft is encouraging girls around the world to pursue careers in STEM fields with their #MakeWhatsNext campaign.
According to the World Economic Forum, the gender gap won&amp;rsquo;t close until 2133. This gap is especially prominent in computer science and STEM fields. Dr. Daiana Beitler, Microsoft Philanthropies Lead for Asia, notes in a blog post that the Asian Development Bank found women in the region are 70% less likely to be employed than men.</description></item><item><title>The market welcomes four new Surfaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</guid><description>Microsoft has introduced four new Surface products designed for the modern world.
Source: Microsoft website. The Surface Pro 6.
&amp;ldquo;Today, people need devices and technology that move with them and are ready whenever and wherever inspiration strikes,&amp;rdquo; stated Microsoft Chief Product Officer, Panos Panay, in a blog post.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the power of Surface, Windows, and Office working together through the cloud to provide the perfect tool. We designed these products together, optimizing every detail to empower your productivity and creativity.</description></item><item><title>Balancing work and play on your smartphone: Four helpful tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. View the full infographic.
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming harder to separate our work and personal lives with smartphones being used for both. For instance, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Lumia 640 and 640 XL come with an Office 365 subscription.
Dr. Mark Batey, an Organizational Psychologist at Manchester Business School in the UK, collaborated with Microsoft to offer advice on finding a good balance:
1. Capture inspiration immediately.
He says, &amp;ldquo;Make use of note-taking apps on your phone to jot down brilliant ideas as they come, anytime and anywhere.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai government is collaborating with Microsoft to develop a new font named "Dubai."</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-government-is-collaborating-with-microsoft-to-develop-a-new-font-named-dubai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-government-is-collaborating-with-microsoft-to-develop-a-new-font-named-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Government Media Office.
The Dubai Crown Prince and Chairman of the Dubai Executive Council, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid, has instructed the General Secretariat of the Dubai Executive Council to create a new font called &amp;ldquo;Dubai.&amp;rdquo; The initial phase will concentrate on developing unique Arabic and English fonts with advanced typographic capabilities.
Sheikh Hamdan emphasized that this initiative will reinforce Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing in information technology, aligning with the government&amp;rsquo;s strategy for leadership and innovation.</description></item><item><title>Your Windows device will soon enhance your creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The possibilities of Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, sketched on a Microsoft Surface by Michael Mindflyer.
Microsoft has launched the latest version of its operating system, the Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, offering it as a free upgrade to current Windows 10 users globally. This update, the fourth major one for Windows 10, prioritizes creativity. It aims to make mixed reality and 3D design accessible to Windows users, leading to improvements in gaming, audiovisual content, and mixed reality experiences.</description></item><item><title>Local computer vendor in Singapore raided by police, counterfeit Microsoft software discovered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-computer-vendor-in-singapore-raided-by-police-counterfeit-microsoft-software-discovered/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-computer-vendor-in-singapore-raided-by-police-counterfeit-microsoft-software-discovered/</guid><description>Microsoft is urging consumers and small businesses to be cautious when buying software, warning them about the risks of accidentally purchasing and using counterfeit products. This advisory comes after a recent raid on a computer vendor in Kembangan Plaza by the Intellectual Property Rights Branch (IPRB) of the Singapore Police Force.
The shop in question had been advertising unauthorized &amp;ldquo;Microsoft license keys&amp;rdquo; as genuine and offering computers bundled with counterfeit software at heavily discounted prices through their online store.</description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing.</description></item><item><title>Coding is an essential skill for future careers for the following four reasons</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coding-is-an-essential-skill-for-future-careers-for-the-following-four-reasons/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coding-is-an-essential-skill-for-future-careers-for-the-following-four-reasons/</guid><description>September 12th, the 256th day of the year, is a significant date for programmers because the number 256 represents all the values possible within an eight-bit byte. This day is celebrated as International Programmer’s Day.
Dr. Daiana Beitler, Philanthropies Lead at Microsoft Asia, emphasizes how much we rely on the work of programmers. Our ability to connect with loved ones and shop online is thanks to their efforts.
Microsoft highlights the importance of coding for several key reasons:</description></item><item><title>SMBs can access Office 365 through GoDaddy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a technology company that supports small businesses, has partnered with Microsoft to offer Microsoft Office 365 to small businesses in Asian markets. This collaboration is part of GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s ongoing effort to provide top-tier business management solutions worldwide.
By offering Office 365, GoDaddy allows its customers to easily access professional email linked to a domain name, secure cloud storage, and a wide range of productivity and collaboration tools.
&amp;ldquo;GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s understanding of small businesses combined with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s email and productivity suite gives small business owners in Asia the tools they need to simplify their operations,&amp;rdquo; said Roger Chen, Vice President of Asia, GoDaddy.</description></item><item><title>Practicing and Opinions on Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</guid><description>I recently co-trained a new course in Atlanta called &amp;ldquo;Project Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementations with Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step&amp;rdquo; (Course 80053A). This course was paired with a one-day class, &amp;ldquo;Project Management Skills Essentials for Microsoft Dynamics,&amp;rdquo; developed by Kristi Honey and Scott Mertes.
The first day concentrated on the essential soft skills needed for each stage of an implementation. We had many engaging discussions throughout the day. It was a fantastic opportunity to gain insights from different perspectives on Dynamics implementation project management.</description></item><item><title>Starting on July 29, upgrades to Windows 10 will be available for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</guid><description>Source: Windows blog.
Microsoft has revealed that Windows 10 will launch on July 29th in 190 countries. The company states that Windows 10 will enhance productivity and offer a more personalized and intuitive user experience across devices. Windows 7 and 8.1 users can upgrade to Windows 10 for free, making it accessible to a majority of current Windows users.
&amp;ldquo;Windows 10 empowers users to achieve remarkable things,&amp;rdquo; says Terry Myerson, Executive VP at Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring social media shows the sentiments towards Formula One in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>In July, Microsoft launched Microsoft Social Listening in eight Asia Pacific markets. This service is designed to help professionals in sales, marketing, and customer care understand and engage with customers on social media more effectively. Microsoft Social Listening provides tools for analyzing market intelligence from social conversations, including sentiment analysis across multiple platforms. It also allows users to monitor products, brands, competitors, and campaigns globally in real time to gain a comprehensive understanding of their customers and their business in the social media landscape.</description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network.</description></item><item><title>Asia is included in global ransomware attacks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 20:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</guid><description>WannaCrypt, also referred to as WannaCry or WCry, holds data files hostage and demands a $300 USD ransom in Bitcoin. The ransom message warns that the payment will double after three days. If payment isn&amp;rsquo;t received within seven days, the encrypted files are permanently deleted.
A key feature of WannaCrypt is its ability to self-propagate within company networks without any user intervention. This is achieved by exploiting a known weakness in the Microsoft Windows operating system.</description></item><item><title>The initial significant update is now accessible for Windows 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Microsoft has released its first significant update for Windows 10, available for both PCs and tablets. This update brings enhancements across the platform, improving user experience according to the company&amp;rsquo;s official announcement. The rollout of Windows 10 has also begun for Xbox One and is expected to reach selected mobile phones shortly.
Terry Myerson, Executive VP of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows and Devices Group, expressed confidence in the update, stating that it marks a level of platform maturity suitable for organization-wide deployment.</description></item><item><title>The launch of Windows 10 in Singapore is met with great excitement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-windows-10-in-singapore-is-met-with-great-excitement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-windows-10-in-singapore-is-met-with-great-excitement/</guid><description>The Windows 10 launch event in Singapore was a resounding success, drawing a large crowd.
Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows 10 is now widely accessible, offered as a free upgrade for a limited time or with new computer systems and tablets in 190 countries. This latest version introduces features like Windows Hello, Cortana, an Xbox app, and the Microsoft Edge browser, aiming to deliver a familiar yet enhanced user experience.
Jessica Tan, Managing Director of Microsoft Singapore, highlighted that Windows 10 empowers individuals and groups to achieve remarkable things.</description></item><item><title>Many Singaporeans are aware of human trafficking but underestimate its prevalence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</guid><description>The International Organization for Migration’s X Campaign (IOM X), in collaboration with USAID, the US Embassy in Singapore, and Microsoft, recently released findings from their pilot outreach program, IOM X Connect Singapore. This initiative sought to increase awareness about human trafficking in Singapore.
During the project, students from the National University of Singapore (NUS) and Singapore Management University (SMU) utilized the newly developed IOM X Learn, Act and Share App. They tested the knowledge of 100 Singaporean residents on the topic of human trafficking.</description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:</description></item></channel></rss>