<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Same-Sex Marriage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/same-sex-marriage/</link><description>Recent content in Same-Sex Marriage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:35:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/same-sex-marriage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jonathan Sumption's perspective on human rights is not coherent when considering the historical context of gay rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</guid><description>In his Reith Lecture, “Human Rights and Wrongs,” Jonathan Sumption argues that the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) has overstepped its boundaries. He believes the court continuously expands its interpretation of the European Convention on Human Rights, creating new rights and encroaching on areas that should be determined by elected officials.
Sumption has raised similar concerns previously, stating in 2016 that the ECtHR is at the forefront of creating fundamental law that goes beyond the original text of the Convention.</description></item><item><title>Anticipating the ECJ Decision in Coman: Progressing Towards EU-wide Recognition of Same-Sex Marriages across Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Photo: Mr Adrian Coman (right) with his spouse, Mr Claibourn Robert Hamilton (left)
(picture from PinkNews http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/29/romania-goes-to-court-over-whether-to-recognise-gay-couples-marriage/)
Introduction
The question of legal recognition for same-sex relationships has become a major topic in recent decades, sparking intense discussions globally in legislative bodies, courts, and the media, with strong opinions on both sides. This complex and delicate issue intersects with human rights, religious beliefs, moral perspectives, traditions, and constitutional principles like equality, personal freedom, and inherent human worth.</description></item><item><title>Dr. David L. Parris v. Trinity College Dublin and Others represents yet another missed chance to effectively protect LGB rights under EU law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>By Dr. Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Introduction
The recent ruling in the Parris case represents a missed chance for the European Court of Justice (ECJ) to provide meaningful protection to LGB individuals and same-sex couples under EU law. While recent cases like Asociaţia Accept and Hay suggested a shift towards stronger protection of LGB rights, the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s judgment in Parris, similar to the Léger case preceding it, reveals a hesitancy to address matters considered sensitive by Member States.</description></item><item><title>The case of V.M.A. v Stolichna obshtina, rayon 'Pancharevo' and the rights of rainbow families to freedom of movement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 06:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Linguist agent at the European Commission and honorary fellow European Union law at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Introduction
Advocate General Juliane Kokott, in her opinion, highlights the unfair burden placed on children of same-sex couples due to differing societal values among EU member states.</description></item><item><title>Ensuring the right to a nationality for children of same-sex couples in the EU - A crucial matter in the case of V.M.A. v Stolichna Obsthina (C-490/20) before the CJEU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-right-to-a-nationality-for-children-of-same-sex-couples-in-the-eu-a-crucial-matter-in-the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obsthina-c-490-20-before-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-right-to-a-nationality-for-children-of-same-sex-couples-in-the-eu-a-crucial-matter-in-the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obsthina-c-490-20-before-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Patrícia Cabral, Legal Policy Officer, European Network on Statelessness*
The recognition of LGBTQ* rights, including same-sex partnerships or marriages and legal parentage for same-sex couples, varies significantly across Europe. This inconsistent landscape presents challenges for rainbow families (families with at least one LGBTQ* parent), particularly regarding the legal recognition of their civil status, birth registration processes, and access to birth certificates. Consequently, some children in these families face statelessness or a heightened risk of it.</description></item></channel></rss>