<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smartlist Builder on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smartlist-builder/</link><description>Recent content in Smartlist Builder on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:14:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smartlist-builder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summary of Payroll Audit SmartList POW!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/</guid><description>Last week, I was asked to create a report that summarized payroll amounts and hours by pay code. This report would be used as a final check before printing paychecks, ensuring accuracy after payroll calculation.
Using SmartList Builder, we created the report in minutes! Here&amp;rsquo;s how:
Navigate to the SmartList Builder: Microsoft Dynamics GP &amp;raquo; Tools &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder. Input a SmartList ID, Name, and Item Name. Select Product: Microsoft Dynamics GP, Series: Payroll...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-payroll-audit-smartlist-pow/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GP Multi-Company SmartLists - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:19:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-2/</guid><description>In the first part of this series, we discussed a scenario where a centralized accounting team could benefit from SmartLists that query data from multiple Dynamics GP company databases. We then covered the fundamentals of creating multi-company views as the foundation for these SmartLists.
Before continuing, let&amp;rsquo;s address the Bonus Quiz from Part 1. The missing step to enable adding a custom view to a new SmartList in SmartList Builder involves SQL Server database security settings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GP Multi-Company SmartLists - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 08:26:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-1/</guid><description>Part 1: Creating Multi-Company SmartLists in Microsoft Dynamics GP 1. Introduction This series will guide you through creating SmartLists that combine data from multiple Dynamics GP companies. We&amp;rsquo;ll leverage SmartList Builder, custom SQL scripts, and address security considerations. This solution is particularly beneficial for organizations with numerous GP company databases managed centrally, such as Consolidated Property Corporation in our example.
While this solution involves SQL queries and Visual Basic scripting, each step will be broken down to make it manageable for those without extensive programming experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-1/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>