<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bonding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonding/</link><description>Recent content in Bonding on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flight Experience Singapore and McGallen &amp; Bolden offer unique leadership workshops that stand out from the rest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</guid><description>Source: McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden.
Flight Experience Singapore, the first flight simulator open to the public in Asia, has partnered with the consulting firm McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden to offer leadership workshops.
Their program, Leadership Secrets at 30,000 Feet, is designed for business leaders and executives. It uses a realistic cockpit setting to teach leadership skills. The customized, four-hour workshop draws on decades of experience from Captain Michael Caston, a pilot with experience flying Boeing 747 and 737 jets for British Airways and Singapore Airlines.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature.</description></item><item><title>3 Mbps to 6 Mbps Bonded Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</guid><description>Reliable and fast business internet access is crucial for customer interaction and order processing. While you aim for a stable connection with sufficient bandwidth, you also need a budget-friendly option. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to incrementally boost your internet speed in line with your business requirements.
](http://www.T1Rex.com/)
Dedicated internet access used to be limited to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line or a 45 Mbps T3 line (DS3 bandwidth). Shared bandwidth services offer more choices, but their performance and availability can fluctuate.</description></item><item><title>Twice the T1 Line Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your internet connection feeling a little slow? That T1 line that used to be more than enough might be struggling to keep up with your current needs. You&amp;rsquo;re not the only one experiencing this. While T1 bandwidth was sufficient for even large companies a decade ago, today, even small and medium-sized businesses are finding themselves needing more. The shift towards online applications and connectivity, while beneficial for productivity, has led to a significant increase in bandwidth demands.</description></item><item><title>Copper While Waiting For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</guid><description>Fiber optic connections are the optimal choice for high bandwidth, offering speeds from 10 Mbps to 10 Gbps using either SONET or Carrier Ethernet protocols. However, accessing these options requires &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber service, which can take several months or more due to potential construction delays. So, how do you maintain connectivity in the meantime?
While waiting for fiber activation was once the only option, many carriers now offer a two-stage solution for businesses needing immediate bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>CruCycle brings a fresh perspective to the fitness scene in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</guid><description>Krewfit recently introduced CruCycle, a new spin studio concept in Singapore, to fitness and fun enthusiasts. The studio&amp;rsquo;s classes operate on the principle of &amp;ldquo;Riding with the Pack,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing group workouts, teamwork, and camaraderie. This makes CruCycle&amp;rsquo;s workouts perfect for corporate team-building events.
Source: Crucycle.
The Ding siblings – Valerie, Calvin, and Beatrice – founded, own, and operate CruCycle. The inspiration for the studio came from their upbringing in Los Angeles, California.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent.</description></item></channel></rss>