<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Carrier on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-carrier/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Carrier on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-carrier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DS3 Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Mid-sized and larger businesses that have outgrown the capacity of T1 lines have turned to DS3 Internet Service as the next step in their telecommunications services. Currently, there are more choices for businesses, both small businesses with high bandwidth demands and larger companies seeking this service level.
DS3, short for Digital Signal level 3, is a well-established telecommunications standard for transmitting digital data. It provides a reliable 45 Mbps bandwidth suitable for dedicated point-to-point connections, PBX telephone systems, or internet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet VPLS Extends Your LAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</guid><description>Traditional methods of connecting multiple business locations, such as Frame Relay, VSAT satellite terminals, internet-based VPNs, and dedicated T1 lines, have been around for a while. However, a new technology called Ethernet VPLS offers superior performance and cost advantages, making it a compelling option for businesses with multiple locations, including branch offices, retail franchises, and medical clinics.
Ethernet VPLS, which stands for Virtual Private LAN service, essentially functions as a carrier-managed local area network that can span across cities, states, or even the entire country.</description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises.</description></item></channel></rss>