<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WFH on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wfh/</link><description>Recent content in WFH on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wfh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Workers are open to making concessions in return for flexible schedules and locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-are-open-to-making-concessions-in-return-for-flexible-schedules-and-locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-are-open-to-making-concessions-in-return-for-flexible-schedules-and-locations/</guid><description>According to the ADP Research Institute&amp;rsquo;s People at Work 2022: A Global Workforce View report, employees desire flexible work arrangements and are willing to negotiate to achieve them.
The global survey of nearly 33,000 individuals across 17 countries indicates that half of the respondents would accept lower pay for schedule flexibility, even without altering total work hours. In Singapore, over 72% desire schedule flexibility with consistent hours, while 38% would consider a pay reduction for location flexibility.</description></item><item><title>Part 12: 2023's Work Trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</guid><description>Source: Deel playbook. 12 work
trends for 2023.
Deel, a provider of payroll and compliance solutions for global teams, has identified twelve emerging workplace trends for 2023:
Overemployed
Deel found that remote workers are increasingly taking on multiple jobs simultaneously, leveraging flexible schedules and asynchronous communication tools.
The Chief Remote Officer (CRO)
The role of CRO is gaining traction, with companies seeking individuals to oversee all aspects of remote work, including in-person events, time-zone management, compensation, and communication tools.</description></item><item><title>A survey on employee productivity has discovered that productivity is higher in the early part of the day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-survey-on-employee-productivity-has-discovered-that-productivity-is-higher-in-the-early-part-of-the-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-survey-on-employee-productivity-has-discovered-that-productivity-is-higher-in-the-early-part-of-the-day/</guid><description>A recent study by Milieu Insight, a consumer data and analytics firm, revealed that employees are typically most productive for five to six hours daily, especially in the morning. This conclusion comes from surveying 500 full-time employees in Thailand, Singapore, Indonesia, the Philippines, and Vietnam.
The study found that 45% of respondents felt most productive for five to six hours daily. A significant 72% identified the period between 8 am and 12:59 pm as their most productive.</description></item></channel></rss>