<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extradition on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/extradition/</link><description>Recent content in Extradition on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/extradition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New developments in EU case law regarding extradition to non-EU countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A recent European Court of Justice (ECJ) decision in the Pisciotti case concerning the extradition of citizens from one EU Member State to a non-EU country (in this instance, the USA) provides further legal precedent in this domain and carries potential implications for Brexit. This ruling expands on the September 2016 Petruhhin judgment, which dealt with extraditing citizens from one EU Member State to Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Restrictions on extradition to countries outside the EU due to EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) is a well-known EU law that streamlined extradition between member states, EU law generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern extradition to non-EU nations. Exceptions exist in cases of pre-existing treaties, like those with the USA and Norway/Iceland, or regarding asylum seekers. The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum laws restrict extraditing asylum-seekers before determining if the requesting country intends to persecute them.
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Petruhhin case has changed this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenges to Judicial Independence in the European Arrest Warrant System and Potential Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</guid><description>Dr Leandro Mancano, Senior Lecturer in EU Law, Edinburgh Law School
This blog post builds upon Leandro Mancano&amp;rsquo;s work, ‘You’ll never work alone: A systemic assessment of the European Arrest Warrant and judicial independence’, published in Common Market Law Review, Volume 58, Issue 3 (2021) pp. 683 – 718
Introduction
The European Arrest Warrant Framework Decision (EAW FD) has significantly altered cooperation between EU states on criminal justice matters (for its effects beyond the EU, see the Court of Justice’s judgments in Petruhhin – discussed here – and IN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>