<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PBX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx/</link><description>Recent content in PBX on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore.</description></item><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>Buy Convergence By The Byte</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</guid><description>XO Communications is revolutionizing telecommunications by offering IP Network services priced by bandwidth usage instead of traditional lines or channels. This shift to an IP-based network and the use of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for telephone trunking are rendering traditional telephony services obsolete. By utilizing a packet-switched network and transmitting everything in packet protocol, voice, and data traffic can easily share a single circuit.
The concept of convergence, using one network for voice, video, and data, has gained traction with IT departments aiming to simplify network management and executives seeking cost reductions.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Duet Combines Voice and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses need both phone and internet services. Their phone systems often start small and expand over time, adding lines as needed. Similarly, internet service might begin with dial-up, transition to DSL, and eventually upgrade to dedicated connections for better reliability.
This piecemeal approach often leads to businesses overspending on telecommunications. Optimizing these systems could potentially cut costs by up to 50%.
The key to saving money is bundling services.</description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Solutions Include New Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</guid><description>Cloud services are changing how we think about technology. Just like server racks are moving to the cloud, so are office phone systems. Traditional PBX systems are being replaced by cloud-hosted solutions. But this transition begs the question: what happens to the physical phone lines?
Similar to connecting data servers off-site, a connection called a SIP Trunk links your on-premise network to the hosted PBX. While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to use existing analog phones with adapters, this approach misses out on the advanced features of Voice over IP (VoIP).</description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses.</description></item><item><title>T1 PRI is More Than Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</guid><description>T1 lines are the most common way to link PBX phone systems to the telephone network. T1 PRI service is often the preferred choice because it can transmit Caller ID information to business phones or call centers. However, there are additional ways that T1 PRI can offer the most budget-friendly phone line trunking.
T1 PRI is a highly specialized telecom service. T1 lines have been in use for over half a century to carry phone calls, and more recently, for point-to-point data, dedicated internet service, and connections to private networks.</description></item><item><title>TalkSwitch Supports both VoIP and Legacy PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</guid><description>Choosing between a traditional phone system (analog or digital TDM PBX) and a newer VoIP system can be tough. TalkSwitch offers a solution by supporting both technologies.
For example, the TalkSwitch 244vs desktop PBX handles 2 incoming lines, 4 extensions for analog phones, and features like voicemail and music on hold. It also supports 10 remote extensions, allowing cell phones, home phones, and phones on other systems to connect by dialing a 3-digit extension.</description></item><item><title>Velox Networks claims that it can offer B2B phone services at a 95% lower cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/velox-networks-claims-that-it-can-offer-b2b-phone-services-at-a-95-lower-cost/</guid><description>Velox Networks, a new telecommunications company in Singapore, offers a voice over internet protocol (VoIP) and cloud-based private branch exchange (PBX) communications platform. They claim their service could save businesses up to 95% compared to traditional major telcos.
Currently, Singaporean businesses primarily use traditional PBXs for business-to-business communication. Velox aims to change this with its affordable, cloud-based PBX solution that surpasses the quality of free VoIP services, which often rely on less dependable consumer-grade technology.</description></item><item><title>Contact Center Telecom Service Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</guid><description>Contact centers manage various communication methods like phone calls, faxes, emails, and mail for businesses and organizations. These centers often use a lot of telecommunications technology, making them a significant expense for the company. A typical center might have analog phone lines, digital phone lines (T1 or DS3), SIP trunking for VoIP, dedicated internet, and private lines for specific needs.
Contact center managers need voice and data services that reduce costs without sacrificing performance or reliability.</description></item><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Communications Services To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>A significant shift from traditional phone systems to cloud-based communication is happening right now. XO Communications, a leader in this field, predicts 60% of companies will move almost a third of their voice communications to the cloud in the coming years.
For a free consultation and quotes tailored to your company&amp;rsquo;s communication needs, our partners at Telarus offer fast and reliable service from expert product specialists. Contact them at http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/.</description></item><item><title>High Quality Call Termination With SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Prioritizing voice packets on a network ensures high-quality VoIP calls within an organization. However, connecting to the outside world poses a challenge due to the incompatibility between modern packet-switched networks and the traditional circuit-switched phone system. To bridge this gap, organizations can either manage the conversion internally or outsource it to a third-party provider through SIP trunking.
SIP trunking offers a potentially cost-effective solution by consolidating multiple phone lines into a single &amp;ldquo;trunk&amp;rdquo; line and utilizing the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for call switching.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines might be leaving money on the table if they haven&amp;rsquo;t explored T-1 digital phone lines. Even businesses already using T1 service might be unaware of potential savings from newer options.
Digital telephony emerged in the 1950s as phone companies sought efficient ways to handle large call volumes. Analog phone lines carried a single conversation per wire pair. While analog multiplexing (carrier telephony) allowed multiple calls on a single wire pair, it suffered from quality issues over long distances.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Phone Lines For PBX Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 16:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</guid><description>Many modern business phone systems utilize T-1 lines to link their buildings to the local telephone company. This is because merging multiple individual lines into one or two T-1 lines is more cost-efficient. This holds true whether your internal phone system is analog or digital, as even most VoIP systems rely on T-1 lines for external calls.
Smaller setups like basic one or two-line phones or key systems with 4-6 lines typically use analog lines.</description></item><item><title>Managed Voice over MPLS For High Quality Enterprise Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations are realizing the financial and operational benefits of MPLS networks. MPLS VPNs are emerging as the go-to solution for connecting multiple sites nationally and globally. But what about voice services?
Traditionally, voice and data are kept separate. Telephone systems rely on a proven infrastructure of switched circuit analog and digital trunking. Most PBX systems are designed to connect to standard copper-pair analog business lines or ISDN PRI digital trunks, which act as gateways to the global PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) connecting every phone on Earth.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>End of the Premises Contact Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business telephone systems have evolved significantly. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from single-line phones to switchboards, automated systems, and sophisticated call center PBXs. However, one thing remained constant: these systems were all located on-site.
What’s Wrong With Premises Equipment?
Keeping everything in-house seems appealing because it gives you control over functionality, access, and services. You might even believe that in-house systems are more reliable than off-site solutions.
On-premises systems offer visibility and control.</description></item><item><title>PRI Lines For Domestic Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are turning to domestic call centers, whether they are in-house or independent contractors. All call centers rely on telephone service, and PRI lines are the preferred choice. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, belongs to the Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) standard. ISDN aimed to transition all telephone lines from analog to digital. The basic offering, BRI (Basic Rate Interface), provides two phone lines or one phone line with either a 64 Kbps or 128 Kbps data service.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line as an On Ramp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</guid><description>You might know about T1 lines as dedicated connections for digital data or PBX phone lines, but they also serve as excellent access points for various other services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Most businesses maintain a Local Area Network (LAN) and a Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect with the wider world. Your WAN connection often acts as an entry point to larger public or private networks.
A prime example is &amp;ldquo;T1 dedicated Internet.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system.</description></item><item><title>Who Says You Can't Sell T1 Lines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</guid><description>While your business thrives by selling business phone systems or computer networking services, you might be missing out on providing clients a complete package. This missing piece? PBX trunk lines or WAN network connections. You&amp;rsquo;d definitely want a share of this profitable market.
You might assume this area belongs solely to phone companies. They prefer you think that way. When businesses see an available &amp;ldquo;T1&amp;rdquo; jack, they often contact their local phone provider directly.</description></item><item><title>The VoSKY is the Limit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</guid><description>Skype, known for free international calls, has become a major player with over 300 million users and a growing presence in the corporate world.
While some might think Skype is just for techies, it has evolved significantly since eBay acquired it in 2005. Beyond basic computer-to-computer calls, a range of hardware now complements Skype, resembling traditional phone setups.
VoSKY, a California-based company, exemplifies this trend, catering to both home users and large companies.</description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs.</description></item><item><title>TDM vs VoIP - Why Not Both?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</guid><description>Feeling stuck between choosing a traditional phone system or a modern one? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses hesitate between sticking with their reliable but potentially outdated PBX system and switching to a VoIP system, unsure of the financial implications. The good news is that you have more choices than you might realize. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit to one system completely. You can have a mix of analog, digital, or IP phones at each desk, and you can choose between TDM or VoIP for outside calls.</description></item><item><title>PRI over Cable Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 01:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</guid><description>Many businesses use ISDN PRI, a technology that bundles multiple phone lines onto a single digital cable, for cost-effective phone service. While initially implemented with T1 lines, offering 23 usable voice channels after reserving one for signaling, ISDN PRI can now be delivered over cable networks.
Modern phone systems, including PBX and key systems, typically support ISDN PRI, allowing businesses to scale their phone lines up to 46, 69, 92, or more.</description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Buying Ernest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations often struggle to manage their telecommunications across the board. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t a single, national provider that understands local needs be ideal? While that might seem contradictory, Ernest Communications offers precisely that solution.
Ernest specializes in serving businesses with widespread locations, such as chain stores, hotels, and restaurants, by providing phone lines, data connections, and wireless services. Essentially, any company with franchises, branches, or service centers across various regions fits their model.</description></item><item><title>XO Launches SIP for Multi-Location Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</guid><description>XO Communications, a large telecommunications company, has introduced a new solution that allows businesses with numerous locations to take advantage of enterprise VoIP technology.
Connecting business locations to a phone service provider through SIP trunking is a well-established method for improving network performance and saving money. XO is building on this concept with a multi-site SIP trunking solution. Instead of requiring each location to connect to a remote service provider separately, branch offices, warehouses, and other locations can now use their existing Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect SIP phones back to a central IP-PBX system at the main office.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Telecommunications from Packet8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</guid><description>If your company is outgrowing its current phone system but a full-blown PBX system seems like overkill, there&amp;rsquo;s a middle ground: hosted telecommunications.
Instead of housing your own PBX equipment, hosted solutions put that functionality in the cloud, similar to website hosting. You get all the features of an in-house system without the bulky hardware. Your office phones connect to the provider&amp;rsquo;s equipment through your broadband connection.
Packet8 is a leading provider of hosted telecom for small to medium businesses.</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>What is ISDN and Why Do I Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</guid><description>You might have encountered the term ISDN in the context of phone services. What does it mean and how can it benefit you?
ISDN stands for Integrated Services Digital Network, a technical term for a digital phone service that adheres to specific standards.
The concept of ISDN emerged when dial-up modems using analog phone lines were the norm for internet access. ISDN aimed to combine phone and internet services on a single line with three channels.</description></item><item><title>Private Branch Exchange Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</guid><description>PBX telephone systems are the preferred business phone technology for medium and large businesses, though recent advancements have made them affordable for smaller companies as well, replacing outdated hardwired or key systems. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a new PBX system, reaching out to VAR Network can provide insights into pricing and available options.
Beyond hardware, PBX systems require connectivity, with various options offering different cost and performance benefits. The most basic connection is an FXO, or analog phone line, connecting to a central office.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points.</description></item><item><title>ISDN's Primary Rate Interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</guid><description>The Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) is a digital telephone standard that provided widespread voice and data services before Enterprise VoIP and MPLS networks. Notably, ISDN&amp;rsquo;s Primary Rate Interface remains in high demand due to its seamless integration with existing telephone trunk lines, which are nearly ubiquitous.
The development of ISDN was driven by the increasing use of modems on analog telephone lines for long-distance data transmission. Analog telephone networks, designed for limited voice bandwidth, only allowed for data speeds up to 56 Kbps.</description></item><item><title>PRI vs POTS Telephone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 11:04:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</guid><description>Business telephone systems come in various sizes, from single-line setups to large enterprise systems with thousands of phones. This article aims to help you determine the right system size for your business needs.
The most basic phone service is known as POTS, or Plain Old Telephone Service, although it&amp;rsquo;s often marketed as a business line or dial-tone service. This service provides an analog connection to the nearest telephone company&amp;rsquo;s Central Office (CO).</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach.</description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Installers Business Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</guid><description>For businesses selling or installing business telephone systems, there&amp;rsquo;s a valuable networking service to know about. It can provide you with more warm leads and expand your product offerings without any extra cost.
This service is the VAR Partner Network, an online platform run by Telarus, Inc. Telarus is a master agency that works with many different voice and data carriers. But it offers much more than that. Through its VAR Network, Telarus actively connects with businesses seeking not just communication services, but also equipment sales and installation.</description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual.</description></item><item><title>Types of Business Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Over time, business phone lines have evolved from a single analog option to a variety of choices. While you can still get traditional analog lines, various digital options offer potential cost and performance benefits.
The standard business phone line remains largely unchanged from its origins over a century ago, using a single twisted pair of copper wires to carry signals. This analog line, also called POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is the basis for multi-line phones connecting to multiple POTS lines, commonly seen in small office phone systems with one to four lines.</description></item><item><title>What is Cloud Computing For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is gaining popularity, but what does it mean for businesses beyond giants like Amazon and Google? Essentially, the cloud isn&amp;rsquo;t a new invention. It&amp;rsquo;s a way of structuring technology, similar to the public telephone system, where a central provider manages the complex infrastructure (&amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo;), and users access services through simple devices (&amp;ldquo;thin clients&amp;rdquo;).
This centralized system, known as multi-tenancy, allows numerous users to access resources seemingly simultaneously while remaining isolated.</description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item><item><title>Fonality Call Center in a Box</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</guid><description>Thinking about starting a call center but worried about the initial expenses and complex setup? While a large-scale call center requires significant investment, there are solutions for businesses looking to add call center capabilities or start small and gradually expand. Fonality offers a &amp;ldquo;call center in a box&amp;rdquo; solution, providing a simplified yet robust system.
This solution utilizes an off-the-shelf PC tower functioning as a Linux server, with the option to upgrade to a rack-mount server for increased capacity.</description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Can Improve Telephone Reliability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</guid><description>Many businesses, even large ones, hold onto their own phone systems believing it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to guarantee reliable communication. But is this true, or is it time to reconsider this assumption?
The phone service industry has experienced a significant shift with the emergence of hosted PBX (HPBX), also called hosted VoIP or cloud communications. Like other cloud-based technologies, this is a game-changer. In the future, we&amp;rsquo;ll wonder why we didn&amp;rsquo;t switch sooner.</description></item><item><title>T1 Voice Options for Call Quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 19:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</guid><description>For businesses reliant on phone communication, exceptional call quality is non-negotiable. This means clear, natural-sounding voices with minimal disruptions like dropped calls, echoes, or choppy audio. If this resonates, T1 voice service might be your solution.
T1 lines are a natural fit for business phone systems as they were intentionally designed for this purpose. T-Carrier technology, including T1 (1.5 Mbps) and T3 (45 Mbps), was initially developed for use by phone companies.</description></item></channel></rss>