<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Samsung on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/samsung/</link><description>Recent content in Samsung on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:35:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/samsung/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Incredible variety, suitable for all</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incredible-variety-suitable-for-all/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incredible-variety-suitable-for-all/</guid><description>This document provides an overview of the Samsung Galaxy A72&amp;rsquo;s features.
Samsung Electronics has launched the Samsung Galaxy A52, A52 5G, and A72 smartphones. These devices prioritize desirable features like an impressive camera, high-quality display, and long battery life, embodying the idea that &amp;ldquo;awesome is for everyone.&amp;rdquo; Additionally, the Galaxy A series integrates seamlessly with the broader Galaxy ecosystem, which encompasses devices such as Galaxy Buds Pro, Galaxy SmartTag, and Galaxy Tab...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incredible-variety-suitable-for-all/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incredible-variety-suitable-for-all/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HALCYON VR murder mystery from Syfy will soon be accessible on the Samsung Gear VR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</guid><description>Source: Syfy. HALCYON investigates a VR murder.
Syfy, known for its imaginative entertainment, will debut its unique hybrid virtual reality (VR) series, HALCYON, on September 22nd at 10 pm. The series is a creation of Secret Location, a multi-award-winning content studio specializing in cutting-edge platforms.
Set in 2040, HALCYON centers on Julie Dover, a detective in the Virtual Reality Crimes Unit. She tackles the first-ever murder within virtual reality, a seemingly impossible crime, and unravels the hidden conspiracy behind it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Presenting the Samsung Galaxy S20</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/presenting-the-samsung-galaxy-s20/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/presenting-the-samsung-galaxy-s20/</guid><description>Samsung Electronics has launched the Samsung Galaxy S20, its newest flagship device series, featuring a redesigned camera system.
“As we begin this decade, 5G will revolutionize how we communicate and experience the world,” said Dr. TM Roh, President and Head of Mobile Communications Business, Samsung Electronics.
“With all three Galaxy S20 variants offering 5G connectivity, Samsung provides a next-generation device that will change people’s lives. Its incredible, AI-powered camera lets you capture moments instantly and connect more smoothly with loved ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/presenting-the-samsung-galaxy-s20/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/presenting-the-samsung-galaxy-s20/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Impressive Samsung Impression Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</guid><description>Get ready to be amazed by a groundbreaking cell phone display technology called AMOLED, short for Active Matrix Organic Light Emitting Diode. This technology delivers a sharper, more vibrant display that is also slimmer, lighter, and more energy-efficient. While it will soon be widely used in various mobile devices, you can currently experience AMOLED technology in the Samsung Impression A877 Blue cell phone.
As cell phones continue to replace laptops, the demand for larger screens has increased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting on August 17, Singtel will be accepting pre-orders for the Samsung Galaxy Note7</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:27:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The Galaxy Note7.
Singtel has revealed that registered customers can pre-order Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Galaxy Note7 starting August 17th. Pre-orders will be delivered or available for pickup on August 19th, preceding the official launch.
The large-screen Galaxy Note7 and its S Pen boast IP68 certification, making them water and dust resistant. The Note7 features cutting-edge iris recognition technology for enhanced security, complementing the defense-grade Samsung Knox security platform for an unparalleled level of protection and user-friendliness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides eSIMs for the Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</guid><description>Source: Samsung website. This Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch functions on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE network.
Singtel has launched the Samsung Gear S3 frontier (LTE) on its 4G LTE network. Equipped with an eSIM, this smartwatch offers independent 4G LTE connectivity. This allows users to make and receive calls, send text messages, and browse the internet without needing their smartphones.
Singtel customers will also experience 4G ClearVoice, also known as VoLTE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exciting news: Samsung unveils the Galaxy A54 and Galaxy A34</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-news-samsung-unveils-the-galaxy-a54-and-galaxy-a34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 16:38:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-news-samsung-unveils-the-galaxy-a54-and-galaxy-a34/</guid><description>Source: Samsung. The Galaxy A54 5G phone in Awesome Lime.
Samsung Electronics has introduced the Galaxy A54 and Galaxy A34, two smartphones that enhance Samsung Galaxy&amp;rsquo;s dedication to delivering exceptional mobile experiences. These latest additions to the well-received Galaxy A series empower users to capture smooth and sharp videos, view content clearly even in bright environments, and enjoy extended battery life.
&amp;ldquo;Providing a top-tier experience is becoming increasingly crucial for our consumers&amp;rsquo; daily lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-news-samsung-unveils-the-galaxy-a54-and-galaxy-a34/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-news-samsung-unveils-the-galaxy-a54-and-galaxy-a34/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Omnia Smartphone for Smart People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Omnia&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; in Latin, a fitting name for a high-tech wireless device designed for mobile professionals.
The Samsung Omnia is a cutting-edge smartphone using the Windows Mobile 6.1 Pro operating system. It boasts a complete HTML web browser, Opera Mobile, on a 3.2-inch LCD touchscreen enhanced with Samsung TouchWiz technology. This technology provides tactile feedback through slight vibrations, while an accelerometer automatically adjusts the display based on the phone&amp;rsquo;s orientation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Galaxy A53 5G and Galaxy A33 5G are both awesome options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</guid><description>Source: Samsung. The new Galaxy A series handsets.
Samsung Electronics has released the Galaxy A53 5G and Galaxy A33 5G, incorporating the latest technology to provide a comprehensive mobile experience at an affordable price. These new Galaxy A series phones boast 5G connectivity, robust security features, and a sleek, eco-conscious design. They&amp;rsquo;re powered by a new processor, include Samsung&amp;rsquo;s AI camera, a large, responsive display, and a long-lasting battery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customized Samsung Galaxy choices arrive in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 07:38:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</guid><description>Samsung is enhancing the customization options for its Galaxy devices in Singapore.
Customers shopping on the Samsung Online Store can now personalize their Galaxy Z Flip4 5G with the Bespoke Edition. This edition offers 75 combinations of glass colors and frame options, including Black, Silver, or Gold frames, and front and back colors like Yellow, White, Navy, Khaki, or Red. Priced at S$1,548, the custom designs are available for the 256 GB variant only, with delivery taking up to four weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>