<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sustainability on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sustainability/</link><description>Recent content in Sustainability on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visa Eco Benefits promote sustainability in every transaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</guid><description>Visa, a digital payment company, has introduced Visa Eco Benefits in the Asia Pacific region. This suite of sustainability solutions aims to help Visa cardholders understand the environmental effects of their everyday spending. They can track their carbon footprint from Visa transactions and explore options for offsetting their impact through carbon offsets or charitable donations via their bank&amp;rsquo;s app or website.
Banks in the Asia Pacific region that adopt Eco Benefits can offer these solutions to their Visa cardholders, addressing the increasing demand for environmentally conscious financial services.</description></item><item><title>IHG will no longer provide mini toiletries as bathroom amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</guid><description>Source: IHG. A shower with sink showing miniatures as amenities.
The InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) is transitioning from small, individual toiletry bottles to larger, bulk amenity dispensers in all 843,000 rooms across its portfolio of hotels. This change, to be fully implemented by 2021, is part of a larger sustainability initiative and establishes IHG as the first global hotel company to entirely eliminate miniature bathroom products in favor of bulk-sized options.</description></item><item><title>The Commonwealth has adopted the Living Lands Charter and has launched the Blue Charter project incubator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</guid><description>Commonwealth leaders have formally agreed to the Living Lands Charter: A Commonwealth Call to action on Living Lands (CALL). This charter represents a commitment from all 54 member countries to protect global land resources and collaborate on climate change, biodiversity loss, and sustainable land management.
This non-binding agreement, announced at the close of the 2022 Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in Kigali, Rwanda, is the result of almost two years of discussions and negotiations with member countries, United Nations Rio Conventions, and other involved parties.</description></item><item><title>New sculptures have been added to the Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi Coralarium</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</guid><description>The Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi resort has added new sculptures to its Coralarium, an underwater art installation that doubles as the Maldives&amp;rsquo; first and only coral regeneration project. This structure, now teeming with marine life, serves as an artificial reef.
The abstract sculptures, conceived by environmentalist and eco-artist Jason deCaires Taylor, draw inspiration from the natural beauty of coral reefs and are designed to resemble coral colonies. These ten partially submerged plinths, reaching heights of up to 5 meters, aim to raise awareness about endangered ecosystems, educate visitors about marine life, and help rehabilitate the reef.</description></item><item><title>The 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards are now accepting submissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</guid><description>Source: GCSA organizers. GCSA winners for 2019 at the GCSF in 2019.
If your company demonstrates a strong dedication to sustainability, we encourage you to apply for the 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards (GCSA).
The Alliance for Sustainable Development Goals (A•SDGs) is hosting the 2020 GCSA in collaboration with the Taiwan Academy of Corporate Sustainability (TACS), the Taiwan Institute for Sustainable Energy (TAISE), and the Center for Corporate Sustainability (CCS).</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Canopy Power is making Southeast Asia more environmentally friendly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</guid><description>Source: Canopy Power. This image shows solar panels installed on the roof of a beachfront pavilion at Batu Batu resort. This installation was part of a larger project by Canopy Power.
Despite the economic downturn of 2020, Canopy Power has announced several accomplishments within the Asia Pacific region.
One such accomplishment was the completion of a renewable energy microgrid in the third quarter of 2020. This microgrid, located on Batu Batu, a sustainable island resort 16 km from Mersing, Malaysia, will allow the 22-villa resort to decrease its reliance on diesel and lower carbon emissions.</description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras.</description></item><item><title>Bee'ah and Chinook Sciences have announced the first waste-to-hydrogen project in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bee-ah-and-chinook-sciences-have-announced-the-first-waste-to-hydrogen-project-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 12:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bee-ah-and-chinook-sciences-have-announced-the-first-waste-to-hydrogen-project-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Dedicated to zero-waste cities and clean energy, Bee&amp;rsquo;ah, a leader in sustainability, revealed its plan for the UAE&amp;rsquo;s first waste-to-hydrogen project.
Source: PRNewsfoto/Chinook Sciences, Bee’ah. The decision to move forward with the waste-to-hydrogen project was reached during a signing ceremony attended by Chinook Sciences Chairman and CEO, Dr Rifat Chalabi (front left), HE Salim Al Owais (front right), Chairman of Bee&amp;rsquo;ah, and representatives from both organizations.
This project, a collaboration with UK-based industrial renewable fuel and environmental technology firm Chinook Sciences, encompasses a green hydrogen production facility and a hydrogen vehicle refueling station.</description></item><item><title>Get a ride and offset your carbon emissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 21:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</guid><description>Grab users will soon have the option to lessen the environmental impact of their trips by utilizing a new carbon offset feature integrated into the Grab app.
Source: Grab.
Explaining the carbon
offset feature.
A recent study across six Southeast Asian countries revealed that 82% of Grab users are concerned about climate change and are taking steps to minimize their environmental impact. However, 44% of those concerned but not actively addressing it cited a lack of knowledge on how to act, while 31% found it too challenging.</description></item><item><title>Travellers now prioritize sustainable travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 20:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</guid><description>Trip.com Group, a leading travel service company, recently published its first-ever Sustainable Travel Consumer Report to coincide with World Tourism Day. The report highlights the growing popularity of sustainable travel and its significant effects on the travel industry and the world at large.
Sustainable travel is increasingly becoming a top priority for travelers worldwide, with over 68% in Singapore and 90% in Thailand recognizing its importance.
Source: Trip.com. Despite regional variations, there is a clear upward trend of individuals adopting sustainable travel habits.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Green Building Week has officially begun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 01:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</guid><description>The DVUCA city management system dashboard uses data from Singapore and other cities to quickly compare water and power consumption. It can even provide granular insights, such as indicating if someone is at their desk.
Singapore Green Building Week has commenced, featuring Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, a Southeast Asian trade show for the region&amp;rsquo;s green building market, and Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional exhibition for HVAC-R*, water, and energy solutions.</description></item><item><title>The Building and Construction Authority of Singapore advocates for the development of super low energy buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-building-and-construction-authority-of-singapore-advocates-for-the-development-of-super-low-energy-buildings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-building-and-construction-authority-of-singapore-advocates-for-the-development-of-super-low-energy-buildings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Building and Construction Authority (BCA) initiated the Super Low Energy (SLE) Programme to advance environmental sustainability within the country. The program includes initiatives like the SLE Buildings Technology Roadmap and the SLE Challenge to promote the development and adoption of cost-effective SLE buildings.
Lawrence Wong, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for National Development and Second Minister for Finance, announced the program at the opening of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW) 2018.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s green building journey commenced in 2005 with the introduction of the BCA Green Mark and three Green Building Masterplans.</description></item><item><title>Singapore SMEs are being advised to view sustainability as a key to achieving growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 01:51:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</guid><description>Ang explains why sustainability is important for Singapore SMEs.
Embracing sustainability provides a competitive edge for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). It aligns them with the practices of larger corporations, potentially opening doors to becoming their suppliers.
Wilson Ang, Executive Director of Global Compact Network Singapore (GCNS), highlighted this during Fuji Xerox DocuWorld in Singapore. He emphasized that sustainability attracts a more discerning investor base, prompting SMEs to adapt to remain competitive.</description></item><item><title>Is the trend for 2020 sustainable red packets?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 19:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Orange/bottle carrier (left) with sustainable
hongbaos middle and right.
For the year 2020, Singtel chose to prioritize sustainability with their red envelope (hongbao) design. Instead of traditional paper, they opted for a material derived from sugarcane stalks after juice extraction.
Two designs were created. The first displays the character 欣, signifying &amp;ldquo;happiness and prosperity&amp;rdquo;. The second features a Chinese couplet, 竞发无极添新彩, 欣荣丰盛增辉煌, translating to &amp;ldquo;delight, happiness, progress with superior competitive advantage, bursting with exciting changes and new opportunities&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>The beauty industry is increasingly prioritizing sustainability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</guid><description>The beauty industry needs a complete overhaul in its approach to sustainability and zero waste, focusing on every part of the process, according to market intelligence agency Mintel. The company highlights &amp;ldquo;Sub-Zero Waste&amp;rdquo; as a major trend that will shape the global beauty and personal care markets in the years to come.
The zero-waste movement is picking up speed as consumers become increasingly affected by environmental problems like natural disasters and water scarcity.</description></item><item><title>Submit your entries for the Zayed Sustainability Prize now!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 17:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</guid><description>The Zayed Sustainability Prize, a prominent global sustainability award based in the UAE, is calling for submissions for its 13th annual edition. Winners in each category will receive US$600,000 to further develop their sustainability solutions and create global impact.
Dr. Sultan Ahmed Al Jaber, UAE Minister of State and Director General of the Zayed Sustainability Prize, expressed confidence that the Prize will continue to draw in top innovators worldwide, tackling pressing global sustainability issues.</description></item><item><title>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental Hong Kong has become more environmentally friendly than ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</guid><description>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong is implementing environmentally friendly practices to offer guests sustainable luxury, including producing its own eco-friendly water and starting a rooftop garden.
The hotel is the first in Hong Kong to work with Nordaq FRESH, a Swedish company, to provide filtered and purified water in reusable glass bottles. This system reduces plastic waste and carbon emissions associated with traditional bottled water. Guests can also refill BPA-free bottles at the hotel.</description></item><item><title>The award ceremony for the Zayed Sustainability Prize 2019 took place</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 02:25:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</guid><description>Source: PRNewsfoto/Zayed Sustainability Prize. The 2019 Zayed Sustainability Prize ceremony took place during Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week (ADSW). His Highness Sheikh Mohamed presented awards to 10 winners across categories such as Health, Food, Energy, Water, and Global High Schools. The ceremony was attended by prominent figures including HH Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of Abu Dhabi Executive Council; HH Lt General Sheikh Saif bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of the Interior; HH Sheikh Mansour bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy PM and Minister of Presidential Affairs; HH Sheikh Hamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Chief of the Abu Dhabi Crown Prince&amp;rsquo;s Court; and HH Sheikh Omar bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of the Board of Trustees of Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan Charitable and Humanitarian Foundation; Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan, Minister of Tolerance; and other high-ranking ministers and officials.</description></item></channel></rss>