<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ultra on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ultra/</link><description>Recent content in Ultra on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ultra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dell introduces new laptops and monitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</guid><description>Dell Singapore has launched new laptops and a monitor for consumers.
The XPS 12 is the first 2-in-1 laptop with a 4K Ultra HD display. The Inspiron 11 3000 series offers an affordable and portable laptop option available in three colors. Dell also released their first 4K consumer monitor, the Dell 28 Ultra HD 4K Monitor.
&amp;ldquo;Consumers have increasingly diverse needs. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a student or a professional, size, power, design, and price all matter.</description></item><item><title>The ASUS EeeBook X205 is now available for purchase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</guid><description>ASUS has introduced the EeeBook X205 to the Indian market. This 11.6-inch ultraportable laptop is designed to offer a user experience similar to a smartphone and is well-suited for young professionals.
The EeeBook X205 features &amp;ldquo;connected standby technology,&amp;rdquo; allowing for near-instantaneous wake-up from sleep mode and continuous social connectivity, even in standby. Equipped with a quad-core Intel Atom processor, the laptop comes with Windows 8.1 with Bing and is offered in four colors: dark blue, white, gold, and red.</description></item><item><title>The Ultra-HD 4K L9450 Pro Theatre TVs from Toshiba are suitable for both living rooms and boardrooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultra-hd-4k-l9450-pro-theatre-tvs-from-toshiba-are-suitable-for-both-living-rooms-and-boardrooms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultra-hd-4k-l9450-pro-theatre-tvs-from-toshiba-are-suitable-for-both-living-rooms-and-boardrooms/</guid><description>Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s new Ultra-HD 4K L9450 series, featuring Android Pro Theatre TVs, blends exceptional picture quality with a wide array of downloadable Android apps from Google Play.
These TVs double as computer monitors, making them ideal for business conference rooms. With the convenience of Android apps, presentations can be downloaded directly to the TV&amp;rsquo;s memory and displayed on screen, eliminating the need for separate presentation equipment. Additionally, wireless mice, keyboards, and gamepads can be used for control, supplementing the standard remote*.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a concentrated ultra high net worth population in Abu Dhabi and Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-concentrated-ultra-high-net-worth-population-in-abu-dhabi-and-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-concentrated-ultra-high-net-worth-population-in-abu-dhabi-and-dubai/</guid><description>The UAE is home to 1,275 ultra wealthy individuals, comprising 20% of the ultra wealthy population in the Middle East, according to Wealth-X. These individuals hold a combined wealth of US$255 billion.
The study also found that 57% of the UAE&amp;rsquo;s ultra high net worth (UHNW*) population built their wealth through entrepreneurship. Inheritance was a less significant factor, with only 8% inheriting their entire fortune and 35% partially inheriting and subsequently growing their wealth.</description></item></channel></rss>