<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hygiene on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hygiene/</link><description>Recent content in Hygiene on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:55:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hygiene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When size is important</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/</guid><description>The market offers a wide variety of feminine hygiene products, each with its own set of claims. While some brands highlight product length as a selling point, ranging from 35cm to 42cm, others leave it unspecified, making comparisons difficult.
Although some brands provide charts illustrating relative product lengths, the lack of specific measurements makes it challenging to determine actual size differences and whether those differences significantly impact usability.
To provide some clarity, here are approximate lengths of various products measured end-to-end:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>