<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Optical Carrier on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/optical-carrier/</link><description>Recent content in Optical Carrier on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/optical-carrier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Same Budget, More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Is Slow Network Speed Affecting Your Business?
Are you experiencing frustrating network issues like slow downloads, choppy calls, interrupted streaming, and sluggish website loading?
Do You Need More Bandwidth?
There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance your internet connection needs more bandwidth. While your internal network might be fast enough, your external connection (WAN) might not be able to handle your current needs.
Signs You Need More Bandwidth
If your internet service hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years but your business relies more on multimedia and online tools, you probably need more bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>