<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extraterritoriality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/extraterritoriality/</link><description>Recent content in Extraterritoriality on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/extraterritoriality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Restrictions on extradition to countries outside the EU due to EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) is a well-known EU law that streamlined extradition between member states, EU law generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern extradition to non-EU nations. Exceptions exist in cases of pre-existing treaties, like those with the USA and Norway/Iceland, or regarding asylum seekers. The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum laws restrict extraditing asylum-seekers before determining if the requesting country intends to persecute them.
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Petruhhin case has changed this.</description></item><item><title>EU Animal Welfare Rules' Extraterritorial Reach</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</guid><description>By Jessica Lawrence, PhD student, VU University Amsterdam
In the Zuchtvieh-Transport case, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that Regulation 1/2005, concerning the protection of animals during transport, applies beyond EU borders. This means that even when transport starts within the EU and ends outside its borders, the regulation still governs the journey. This decision is significant as it promotes animal welfare but also reflects the CJEU’s expanding interpretation of EU jurisdiction, stretching conventional international law principles on &amp;rsquo;territorial jurisdiction'.</description></item></channel></rss>