<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wearable on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wearable/</link><description>Recent content in Wearable on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wearable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Now, you have the ability to answer calls directly on your Apple Watch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple Watch 3 includes phone capabilities.
Apple has launched the Apple Watch Series 3, a smartwatch with built-in cellular capabilities. With this new feature, users can make and receive calls and texts, and stay connected even when they don&amp;rsquo;t have their iPhone nearby.
This third-generation Apple Watch is designed for health and fitness, offering smart coaching features, water resistance up to 50 meters, and a new barometric altimeter for measuring elevation changes.</description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces a new fitness tracker that can measure body composition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-a-new-fitness-tracker-that-can-measure-body-composition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:06:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-a-new-fitness-tracker-that-can-measure-body-composition/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. The TomTom Touch.
The TomTom company has introduced a new fitness tracker in Singapore. This device is the first of its kind to track body composition, steps, sleep, and heart rate all day right from the user&amp;rsquo;s wrist.
Monitoring body composition helps users understand their fitness levels and how those levels change. Before the TomTom Touch, this metric could only be measured using special scales or expensive devices.</description></item><item><title>Pre-orders for the Apple Watch will begin on April 10th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-apple-watch-will-begin-on-april-10th/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-apple-watch-will-begin-on-april-10th/</guid><description>Source: Apple website. The Apple Watch Edition can cost up to US$17,000.
Apple has revealed the release dates for the Apple Watch, a device that combines the functions of a timepiece, communication tool, and health and fitness tracker. Starting on April 24th, it will be available in Australia, Canada, mainland China, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, the UK, and the US.
What it does With the Apple Watch, users can send messages, check email, and answer calls received on their iPhone directly from their wrist.</description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces three new fēnix 5 multisport GPS wearables</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-three-new-f-nix-5-multisport-gps-wearables/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-three-new-f-nix-5-multisport-gps-wearables/</guid><description>Source: Garmin. The fēnix 5 family of multisport GPS watches.
Garmin International has released the fēnix 5, fēnix 5S, and fēnix 5X multisport GPS watches. These wearables are designed for adventurers of all sizes.
Each fēnix 5 model offers 24/7 wearability, extended battery life, daily activity tracking*, Garmin Elevate wrist heart rate technology, and various connected features**. At 47mm, the fēnix 5 is more compact than past models like the fēnix 3HR, while still providing extensive multisport features.</description></item><item><title>L’Oréal introduces a flexible skin sensor that tracks sun exposure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</guid><description>Source: L’Oréal. Model wearing a My UV patch.
L’Oréal recently introduced My UV Patch at the Consumer Electronics Show. It is the first flexible skin sensor designed to track UV exposure and promote sun-safety awareness among consumers. This innovation arrives as sun exposure has become a significant health concern, with 90% of non-melanoma skin cancers linked to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from the sun, in addition to skin pigmentation and premature aging.</description></item><item><title>The potential marketing opportunities presented by a customizable wearable device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</guid><description>Source: Broadcast Wear website. Control the shirt&amp;rsquo;s display with an app.
Broadcast Wear, an innovative company from Hyderabad, has introduced a programmable t-shirt with touch-sensitive technology, opening up exciting possibilities for marketing.
Their invention incorporates a flexible, washable LED screen directly into the fabric. Users can pair the shirt with the Broadcast Wear smartphone app to instantly show any text or image. A simple tap turns the screen on and another tap switches it off.</description></item><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology.</description></item><item><title>Apple has released new Apple Watch options, including the addition of the Hermès collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The Apple Watch.
Apple has launched new Apple Watch cases and bands, updated its watch operating system, and introduced new gold and rose gold aluminum models for the Apple Watch Sport.
Available as a free update on September 16, the watchOS 2 operating system delivers new features and native third-party apps to Apple Watches. With watchOS 2, apps run faster. Users will also find new watch faces, third-party app information viewable on the watch face, and a &amp;ldquo;Time Travel&amp;rdquo; feature that provides chronological context.</description></item><item><title>The TomTom Golfer 2 GPS Watch is created to assist golfers in enhancing their game</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</guid><description>TomTom has introduced the TomTom Golfer 2, a slim GPS watch designed for golfers. The watch uses automatic shot detection to provide detailed analysis after a round, aiming to improve users&amp;rsquo; games.
The TomTom Golfer 2 eliminates uncertainty on the course by measuring distances to greens and hazards. This automatic shot detection helps golfers understand their distance potential by displaying distances for drives and approach shots at a glance. After the game, golfers can analyze their strokes in detail using TomTom MySports.</description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time.</description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach.</description></item><item><title>TomTom's latest Spark GPS fitness watches also have the capability to play music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. TomTom has introduced the Spark GPS fitness watch line. These new watches include a 3GB music player, making it simpler for fitness enthusiasts to enhance their workouts by listening to music directly from their wrist.
The TomTom Spark GPS fitness watch can stream music to a variety of Bluetooth headphones. It also includes a preloaded thirty-minute Running Trax curated by Ministry of Sound. Users can easily download playlists to the TomTom Spark from iTunes or Windows Media Player.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces the latest Moverio smart glasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the third generation of its Moverio smart glasses, designed for augmented reality applications. The Moverio BT-300 utilizes Epson&amp;rsquo;s innovative silicon-based OLED display technology, providing a truly transparent mobile augmented reality (AR) experience for both businesses and consumers.
Epson highlights the Moverio BT-300 as the lightest binocular see-through smart glasses available, boasting a weight reduction of over 20% compared to its predecessor, the Moverio BT-200. These glasses are powered by a quad-core Intel Atom X5 processor and run on Android 5.</description></item></channel></rss>