<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hosted PBX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-pbx/</link><description>Recent content in Hosted PBX on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:13:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-pbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VoIP Phone Service Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes might be considering upgrading their phone systems but are unsure of the best approach. Should they stick with their existing Key Telephone or PBX system and upgrade it, or is it time to transition to VoIP? What many businesses may not realize is the wide range of options that VoIP solutions offer.
The key difference between VoIP and traditional phone systems lies in its network-based approach. While even a single-line phone or cell phone operates on a network, known as the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), this network has limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Such a Stampede to The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is everywhere you turn. This raises the question: are businesses truly shifting from traditional data centers to cloud-based solutions? And if so, what motivates this transition and what are their objectives?
Unveiling the Hidden Potential of Cloud Technology
Cloud storage receives significant attention, but the vast server capacity offered by the cloud is equally compelling. One often overlooked application is Hosted PBX or Hosted VoIP, which replaces traditional phone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Here’s Why Companies Actually Want BYOD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The concept of &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) can be a real headache for IT managers. While employees may enjoy the convenience, it poses a significant risk to a company&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data. When personal devices connect to the company network, carefully constructed security protocols are often bypassed. So, what can be done?
Many companies address this issue by drawing a hard line. Recognizing the challenges of managing diverse personal devices, they prohibit their use for business purposes altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted PBX Adds Video Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems, also known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, are gaining popularity with businesses of all sizes. This technology offers advanced features without requiring a large upfront investment. Now, these systems are evolving to incorporate video services as well.
MegaPath, a leading network and cloud service provider, is enhancing its hosted PBX offerings by including cloud-based unified communications video services.
A new generation of business phones makes voice and video integration possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SMB Phone System Needs Only Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</guid><description>The simplicity of traditional phone systems, where plugging in a phone provided immediate dial tone, is making a comeback with cloud-based communication systems.
This modern approach, known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, shifts the responsibility of complex switching equipment to a service provider. This means the provider manages updates, maintenance, and scalability, leaving you with only the phones to handle.
These aren&amp;rsquo;t your typical phones; they are IP phones designed for computer networks, using different electrical signals and connectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SIP Trunking Supplant ISDN PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses that require multiple phone lines can benefit from digital trunks. While previously only large companies with numerous lines saw advantages with digital trunks, advancements in technology now make them a viable option for businesses with just a few lines and internet access.
What exactly constitutes a telephone trunk? Essentially, it is a collection of phone lines bundled together. Unlike individual analog lines, which consist of a twisted pair of copper wires, a trunk combines multiple lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E911 For Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>The transition from traditional phone lines to internet-based calling has brought about some unexpected issues, particularly with emergency services. We often take 911 for granted, assuming help will always be on the way. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case with internet-based phone systems.
Imagine a scenario where a fire breaks out in your office. You dial 911, report the emergency, and evacuate. However, the fire department ends up at your company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters instead of your current location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free International Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</guid><description>During tough economic times, everyone appreciates a good deal, especially free offers. Phone Power is offering free international calls through 2008 to promote its competitive business and residential VoIP services. This is a great opportunity for anyone who makes a lot of international calls. Even after the promotion ends, Phone Power&amp;rsquo;s rates remain very affordable.
This holiday season, you can call landlines in the following countries for free: United Kingdom (44), Spain (34), Ireland (353), Israel (972), Germany (49), Singapore (65), France (33), Denmark (45), Greece (30), Italy (39), and China (86)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best VoIP Providers For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</guid><description>Thinking about switching from traditional phone lines to VoIP, but unsure about its effectiveness? This guide provides insights and advice for a smooth transition.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, is also known as “network voice” because it operates on computer networks, unlike traditional phone systems. Essentially, voice becomes another service on your network, alongside data, video, and audio streaming. Each service transmits packets routed through the network.
This setup offers significant cost savings for larger businesses by consolidating telephone and data networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Communications Advantages Explained</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</guid><description>Many businesses are unsure if switching their communications to the cloud is a good idea. XO Communications, a large networking and telecom provider, explains why this change is beneficial. Their short video illustrates why this might be the right choice for your business.
XO&amp;rsquo;s Enterprise Cloud Communications provides large businesses with services similar to what hosted PBX systems offer smaller companies. Essentially, it transitions a company from managing its own phone system to simply using a sophisticated service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phone Power... To The People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:43:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</guid><description>VoIP and broadband phone services for businesses and residential customers are steadily replacing the century-old traditional phone industry. The reason? Price!
Traditional phone service relies on tariffs that charge for every little thing. You pay for the line, local service, long distance, and extra features like Caller ID. They even charge a monthly fee for maintaining the wiring in your home! It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that phone bills can be shockingly high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadview Networks OfficeSuite Brings The Cloud To SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</guid><description>Smaller companies often want to adopt money-saving technologies like VoIP, private networks, and cloud services, but the initial investment can be daunting. While internet-based options seem appealing, their quality and reliability are often a concern. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for businesses of all sizes to access these advanced tools without breaking the bank.
Broadview Networks&amp;rsquo; OfficeSuite offers a comprehensive solution, effectively serving as a company&amp;rsquo;s central office across multiple locations. This enterprise-grade PBX system provides the functionality of a traditional system with the convenience of easy administration through a web browser...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Services Give Small Companies an Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</guid><description>During the ongoing economic downturn, businesses of all sizes face the challenge of maintaining competitive electronic services with limited budgets. Managed services present a solution, particularly for smaller companies lacking substantial IT departments and hiring capacity.
The concept of managed services is straightforward: you delegate management to an external provider. Consider your phone system. One option is to independently research, purchase, and install a PBX system, along with the necessary hardware and staff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Concentric Cloud Solutions Virtualizes Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been bombarded with information about virtualization, unsure if it can help control unpredictable business expenses. You might feel overwhelmed about the process of deploying virtualization. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry, Concentric can guide you through it.
Initially confined to local data centers, virtualization has migrated to the cloud. The fundamental concept is maximizing hardware performance. This is achieved by making a single server function as multiple servers, or transforming a cluster of smaller servers into a powerful computing unit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Comes To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s professionals juggle multiple devices like smartphones, tablets, and laptops in addition to their office setups, which often include desktop computers, LAN connections, and speakerphones. This begs the question: how can we unify these devices for a seamless workflow?
This multifaceted connectivity issue has plagued corporate IT departments for years as communication devices multiply faster than solutions for integrating them. Often, the simplest answer is printing business cards with separate numbers for each device...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Does Cloud Computing Work In Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is frequently used today. But what exactly is it, and how can it benefit your business by improving efficiency, speed, and affordability? Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into it.
In business, the term &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; often carries a negative connotation, implying uncertainty and unpredictability. Naturally, clarity and predictability are preferred, especially from a financial standpoint. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable why people might be skeptical when advised to transition their business to the cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should You Buy VoIP as a Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</guid><description>Cloud-based services, including Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), have been around for a while. What&amp;rsquo;s becoming more popular now is the trend of large businesses connecting their different locations using SIP Trunks and all sizes of businesses choosing to outsource their PBX functionality. This can be considered VoIP as a Service.
Many home and small business users adopted cloud-based VoIP early on to cut costs. They did this by replacing their traditional phone lines and using their broadband internet connection for both high-speed internet and phone service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SMB Cloud Computing Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</guid><description>While large companies have widely adopted cloud computing, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) may wonder about its relevance for them. Broadview Networks offers a range of cloud services ideal for such businesses. Already a prominent communications provider in the Northeastern and Mid-Atlantic US, Broadview provides various connectivity options, including T1 lines, Ethernet, fiber optic connections, and traditional phone lines.
What distinguishes Broadview is its ability to provide both cloud services and the reliable connectivity these services require, unlike many cloud providers that only offer the infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Earth to Cloud Network Security Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 18:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</guid><description>Information technology specialists understand the need for secure corporate networks, including enterprise-level security for cloud computing services in remote data centers. However, maintaining security across the entire network, especially when extending the LAN remotely, poses a significant challenge.
Level 3 Communications offers a solution with its “Earth to Cloud” comprehensive global security suite. This multi-layered protection strategy aims to secure every aspect of the network from potential threats.
A key factor in this approach is having a single provider for both connectivity and network security, a role Level 3 is well-equipped to fill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Networking Services Extend Business Footprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 20:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</guid><description>For businesses with a single office in one city, cloud computing or hosted PBX might suffice, as their communication needs are primarily about connecting to a provider&amp;rsquo;s cloud. However, companies with multiple locations require cloud networking services to link these sites seamlessly.
Cloud networking utilizes public or private networks to connect geographically dispersed locations in various configurations. Examples include the internet, privately managed MPLS networks, and even custom-built networks using leased lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center On Demand in the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The sophistication of cloud communications services is constantly increasing, representing a logical progression in the cloud computing revolution. With data servers already transitioned to the cloud, numerous businesses are questioning the necessity of maintaining costly and aging PBX phone systems.
Transitioning business phone systems to the cloud is becoming increasingly practical. Beginning with Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, this shift eliminates the need for substantial hardware and traditional phone lines. Instead, handsets connect to the company network and a high-bandwidth WAN connection links to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vocal IP Networx Offers Free SNMP Monitoring</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with the challenges of managing T1 lines and bandwidth, especially keeping track of service availability across different vendors and equipment. While large companies have dedicated IT teams, smaller businesses often handle this responsibility as issues arise.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be beneficial to have affordable network monitoring support? Vocal IP Networx, a leading IP telephony provider, offers a solution: free, continuous SNMP monitoring for all circuits and customer premises equipment (CPE) they provide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will 2013 Be Your Year of the Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing was a major trend in 2012, with numerous vendors offering a wide range of solutions. Cloud services are no longer limited to powerful supercomputers; they&amp;rsquo;ve become accessible and practical for everyday resources, often surpassing the benefits of in-house solutions. This raises the question: will 2013 be the year you transition to the cloud?
For many businesses, the answer is a clear &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Cost-effectiveness, support, and accessibility are key drivers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Puts Your Complete Office In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:47:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>You might be interested in cloud services, but the process of ordering and integrating them can be overwhelming. Now, a new solution offers a comprehensive bundle of IT services tailored for small businesses at an affordable price.
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
Small businesses often don&amp;rsquo;t need or can&amp;rsquo;t afford large-scale IT infrastructure. Expensive VoIP phone systems and on-site data centers are impractical for companies with limited staff and resources. While cost savings were previously linked to scale, hosted solutions have revolutionized this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>