<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Muscat on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/muscat/</link><description>Recent content in Muscat on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:19:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/muscat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terhal by Bank Muscat provides financing for travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</guid><description>To celebrate the summer holidays (from Q2 to Q3) and the upcoming Eid al Fitr, Bank Muscat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Terhal,&amp;rdquo; a new set of travel services combined with banking features. This initiative reflects the bank&amp;rsquo;s motto, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s do more,&amp;rdquo; and aims to offer a unique banking experience for customers who enjoy traveling.
Terhal provides customers with access to financing up to RO10,000 at a 3.5% interest rate, repayable over a year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>