<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stuck on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stuck/</link><description>Recent content in Stuck on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:33:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stuck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival on Beolover's Bench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</guid><description>During the holiday season, I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable for repair. My initial assessment showed that it was packaged very well, with some innovative methods used to protect it during shipping.
The dust cover was secured using soft foam blocks to hold the sub-platter and the RPM panel in place.
The MMC20E cartridge was also protected by foam and arrived in good condition.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the cartridge after unpacking:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A Second Beogram 4002 (5523) Arrived for some TLC - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) in need of restoration arrived with its MMC4000 cartridge still attached and transport locks disengaged, causing initial concern about potential damage. The foam meant to support the tonearm had deteriorated, leaving it to swing freely.
Fortunately, the cartridge appeared undamaged, likely due to the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s light weight and protective tape. Testing on a restored Beogram 4000 confirmed its functionality.
The hood was in good condition, showing only minor scratches and signs of polishing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of a Seized Solenoid to Tonearm Linkage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:07:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I got from the UK had a seized linkage connecting the solenoid mechanism and tonearm. To lubricate this linkage, I had to disassemble the sensor arm assembly and remove it. Further inspection showed that the linkage&amp;rsquo;s rotating pin was stuck and had detached from its press-fit socket within the sensor arm base. I&amp;rsquo;ve created a video illustrating the problem and the repair process:</description></item></channel></rss>