<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Networking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-networking/</link><description>Recent content in Business Networking on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 01:27:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Poken Pulse Business Networking Gadget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</guid><description>Traditional business networking relies heavily on exchanging physical business cards, a practice that persists despite the rise of smartphones and online networking. Poken offers a modern alternative by digitizing the process.
The Poken device, a small gadget shaped like a four-fingered hand, allows users to exchange contact information wirelessly. When two Poken devices touch, they transfer unique codes linked to the users&amp;rsquo; online profiles.
Unlike traditional business cards, Poken stores contact data in an online portal, making it easier to manage and search...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telephone Installers Business Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</guid><description>For businesses selling or installing business telephone systems, there&amp;rsquo;s a valuable networking service to know about. It can provide you with more warm leads and expand your product offerings without any extra cost.
This service is the VAR Partner Network, an online platform run by Telarus, Inc. Telarus is a master agency that works with many different voice and data carriers. But it offers much more than that. Through its VAR Network, Telarus actively connects with businesses seeking not just communication services, but also equipment sales and installation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Point of Presence Locator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting more bandwidth for your money, and finding an Ethernet Point of Presence (POP) Locator can help. But what is a POP and how can it save you money?
Essentially, a POP is a carrier&amp;rsquo;s service location, such as a central office with termination equipment for their fiber optic network. Think of it as a station for accessing high-speed data and voice services. POPs aren&amp;rsquo;t always in carrier offices; they can be in colocation centers, shared facilities housing servers and offering resources like bandwidth, security, and backup power...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>