<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Suzhou on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/suzhou/</link><description>Recent content in Suzhou on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/suzhou/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is the inaugural Hyatt hotel in the Jiangsu province</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</guid><description>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou has officially opened in Suzhou, a city renowned for its historic canals, stone bridges, and UNESCO-recognized classical gardens.
Source: Hyatt. The hotel boasts a 29-floor atrium, the tallest in Suzhou.
&amp;ldquo;The launch of Hyatt Regency Suzhou is a significant move for Hyatt as we expand our brand presence in China,&amp;rdquo; stated Christopher Koehler, Vice President of Operations for Hyatt in China. &amp;ldquo;We aim to create valuable connections among global business and leisure travelers.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the successful first year of Hyatt Regency Suzhou with our Anniversary Meeting Package</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Suzhou.
The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is commemorating its first anniversary with various special offers as a thank you to its loyal and valued guests for their support throughout the year.
Having opened its doors on August 24, 2014, in the Suzhou Industrial Park (SIP), the conveniently located Hyatt Regency Suzhou boasts 355 rooms and suites. Amenities include a Regency Club, five dining options, and over 15,000 square feet of space for events.</description></item><item><title>Suzhou is gaining more recognition in the MICE industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</guid><description>The Suzhou Culture and Expo Centre Company (SCECC), which manages the Suzhou Culture and Arts Centre and the Suzhou International Expo Centre, claims that Suzhou is arguably the top Meetings, Incentives, Conferences and Exhibitions (MICE) destination in China.
SCECC highlights Suzhou&amp;rsquo;s success in hosting significant events, such as the 53rd World Table Tennis Championships earlier this year and Armani&amp;rsquo;s selection of the city&amp;rsquo;s Humble Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Garden as the venue for the global debut of its Pivoine Suzhou perfume.</description></item></channel></rss>