<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2023 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2023/</link><description>Recent content in 2023 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:41:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore is taking steps to enhance its resilience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-taking-steps-to-enhance-its-resilience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-taking-steps-to-enhance-its-resilience/</guid><description>Concept classroom by dream by WOMBO.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2023 centers around navigating global economic uncertainties by enhancing the country&amp;rsquo;s productivity and competitiveness.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Deputy PM and Finance Minister, Lawrence Wong, highlighted the US ban on advanced chip technology transfer to China and its ripple effects. He stated, &amp;ldquo;We are seeing a fierce competition for dominance in critical technologies, likely to intensify, leading to a concerning trend toward increased economic nationalism and protectionism worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Think about the possibility of working in the Middle East to increase your savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</guid><description>A new study by Business Name Generator (BNG) reveals salary trends in 28 cities worldwide, focusing on four sectors: marketing, HR, creative, and tech.
Tech
Doha takes the lead as the highest-paying city for tech professionals, boasting an average annual salary of £127,888. Data scientists emerge as top earners, commanding an average yearly salary of £361,877. After factoring in the annual cost of living (£26,382), Doha still provides the highest disposable income for tech workers, reaching £101,506 annually.</description></item><item><title>The Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens promotion is now available at the Grand Hyatt Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Hong Kong. Poster for the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens 2023.
To celebrate the return of the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens from March 31st to April 2nd, 2023, Grand Hyatt Hong Kong, an official supplier and package provider, is offering special deals for a complete Sevens experience.
Exclusive packages combining accommodation and Sevens tickets are available starting from HK$3,900. Options include one- or three-night stays, paired with a choice of Friday, weekend, or three-day event tickets to suit every fan.</description></item><item><title>Criteo unveils a retail sales guide for Chinese New Year in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:48:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</guid><description>Criteo, a commerce media company, has unveiled insights from the 2022 Chinese New Year (CNY) to help retailers anticipate consumer demand and leverage similar trends in 2023.
Starting in January 2022, retail sales surpassed typical levels (based on the average between December 18th and 31st, 2021) until a week prior to CNY 2022 (February 1st), indicating a strong consumer appetite for purchasing. In Southeast Asia (SEA), retail sales hit a peak of 27% on January 25th, a week before CNY.</description></item><item><title>THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023 begins in Bangkok on May 23rd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</guid><description>The upcoming THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023, a premier food and beverage industry event, will take place from May 23-27, 2023 at IMPACT Muang Thong Thani in Bangkok, Thailand. This year&amp;rsquo;s event features 11 signature trade shows, six special shows, and a focus on innovation, bold concepts, and advanced solutions. With approximately 3,000 exhibitors from 43 countries and over 60,000 trade visitors from more than 120 countries anticipated, organizers aim for a total transaction value of 70,000 million baht, including over 1.</description></item><item><title>Bioactive ingredients will drive growth in the personal care industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</guid><description>A global shift from synthetic to natural active ingredients in personal care products is driving significant investments in the market, according to research firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. This trend is fueled by a growing consumer belief that natural ingredients are safer for human health and the environment.
Source: Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. Generic personal care dispensers.
Currently, natural active ingredients represent 25% to 30% of the total market share. However, this is predicted to double by 2023, leading to increased innovation in addressing the challenges of incorporating these often delicate ingredients.</description></item><item><title>DBS/POSB introduces Chinese New Year service offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</guid><description>To celebrate the Year of the Rabbit, DBS/POSB is expanding its blended digital and physical (&amp;ldquo;phygital&amp;rdquo;) Chinese New Year (CNY) gifting and rewards programs.
This CNY, customers can take advantage of the following:
Conveniently order DBS QR Gift cards (QR AngBaos) through the bank&amp;rsquo;s chatbot, digibot, and have them delivered before CNY.
A chance to win a Tesla Model 3 and other rewards, including cash rebates, by switching to QR Gift and other DBS/POSB digital transactions.</description></item><item><title>Avanade has been recognized as one of the top employers in Malaysia and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</guid><description>Avanade, a company specializing in Microsoft solutions, has received the 2023 Top Employer award in Malaysia and Singapore from the Top Employers Institute.
Source: Avanade. Kapoor.
The Top Employers Institute Programme grants certifications to companies based on their answers and performance on a survey evaluating their Human Resources (HR) practices. Avanade earned recognition for its exceptional practices in all areas reviewed, including People Strategy, Work Environment, Talent Acquisition, Learning, Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion, Wellbeing, and others.</description></item><item><title>The 18th edition of All That Matters will take place from September 11th to 13th, 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</guid><description>All That Matters, a key event for professionals in Asia&amp;rsquo;s music, sports, gaming, digital, marketing, Web3, and entertainment sectors, is back for its 18th year. It will be held from September 11th to 13th at the Hilton Singapore Orchard.
Source: All That Matters organisers. Event poster.
The event combines a daytime conference with a nightly music festival. It offers attendees, including representatives from major labels, sports organizations, distributors, and publishers, a chance to connect with global brands.</description></item><item><title>Part 12: 2023's Work Trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</guid><description>Source: Deel playbook. 12 work
trends for 2023.
Deel, a provider of payroll and compliance solutions for global teams, has identified twelve emerging workplace trends for 2023:
Overemployed
Deel found that remote workers are increasingly taking on multiple jobs simultaneously, leveraging flexible schedules and asynchronous communication tools.
The Chief Remote Officer (CRO)
The role of CRO is gaining traction, with companies seeking individuals to oversee all aspects of remote work, including in-person events, time-zone management, compensation, and communication tools.</description></item><item><title>The UAE GDP forecasts have been released by the Dubai Chamber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-gdp-forecasts-have-been-released-by-the-dubai-chamber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:57:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-gdp-forecasts-have-been-released-by-the-dubai-chamber/</guid><description>The United Arab Emirates&amp;rsquo; (UAE) real GDP is predicted to grow by an average of 3.8% between 2019 and 2023. This growth will be driven by increased investment and private consumption, according to an analysis by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.
The Dubai Chamber UAE Macroeconomic Model forecasts a resurgence in private spending and sales of consumer goods, particularly in categories like vehicles, furniture, appliances, and medical devices. This growth will be supported by robust investment bolstered by government fiscal measures.</description></item><item><title>Ipsos: More than half of Singaporeans are feeling positive about 2022, but have mixed emotions about 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</guid><description>A recent worldwide survey conducted by Ipsos explored global citizens&amp;rsquo; opinions on the past year and their outlook for the future. The survey revealed that 73% of respondents believe their country had a challenging year, marking a slight improvement compared to the previous year (2021).
The Ipsos Global Predictions for 2023 report, which included data from 36 countries, indicated that over half (56%) of respondents globally considered 2022 a difficult year personally.</description></item><item><title>Deliveroo predicts future food trends in Asia with "Snack to the Future"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 17:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</guid><description>Deliveroo, a food delivery platform, has released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Snack To The Future Report&amp;rdquo; predicting how technology and evolving consumer habits will shape food consumption patterns in the region by 2040.
The report, developed by Deliveroo in collaboration with Singaporean food specialists Yip Hon Mun and Luke Tay, along with other global experts, identifies emerging food trends driven by technological advancements and changing consumer behaviors. Key predictions include personalized dietary recommendations based on breath analysis (&amp;ldquo;Breath-prints&amp;rdquo;), AI-powered customized diets (&amp;ldquo;Me-ganism&amp;rdquo;), and immersive dining experiences using augmented reality (&amp;ldquo;FOODGASMS&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>According to LinkedIn, 65% of employees in Singapore are planning to change jobs in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</guid><description>Although hiring in Singapore experienced a significant drop of 34% in December 2022 compared to the previous year, and despite economic uncertainties, professionals are adopting a forward-thinking approach to their careers. They are investing in skill development and actively pursuing opportunities for advancement. LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s research indicates that a considerable 65% of professionals are contemplating job changes in 2023.
The desire for enhanced financial stability amidst rising living costs is a primary driver behind this job search trend.</description></item><item><title>Players from Manchester United and FC Barcelona will be participating in the GET Riyadh 2023 football competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 10:31:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</guid><description>The Global Esports Tour (GET), a professional esports series by the Global Esports Federation, will commence its third season on August 26-27, 2023. This season&amp;rsquo;s launch event will take place at Boulevard Riyadh City, as a featured part of the Gamers8 festival.
Source: Global Esports Federation. Poster for GET Riyadh 2023.
KONAMI’s eFootball 2023 will be the primary game featured, with a prize pool totaling US$50,000. Professional football players, Lotfi Derradji and Kilyan Katou Judex Faucheux of Manchester United, alongside Alejandro Alguacil Seguira and Saul Adrian Chavez Saucedo of FC Barcelona, will participate alongside esports players.</description></item></channel></rss>