<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Venue on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/venue/</link><description>Recent content in Venue on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/venue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Vines Resort &amp; Country Club introduces a new garden venue for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</guid><description>Source: The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club. The Pavilion.
The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club, located near Perth, Australia, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Pavilion.&amp;rdquo; This new event space is a specially designed garden structure situated at the front of the resort, offering scenic views of the golf course and surrounding gardens. It&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for events such as conference gatherings or product launches.
The open-air venue, capable of hosting 100 guests, has three sides open to the elements.</description></item><item><title>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park in Bangkok provides a versatile indoor-outdoor option for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</guid><description>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park, Bangkok – Marriott Executive Apartments is a unique venue for gatherings in the Sukhumvit area. Combining indoor and outdoor elements, it offers a versatile space for 30 to 160 guests. High ceilings and comfortable furniture create a welcoming atmosphere.
This lounge seamlessly blends several design concepts, creating a space that is both modern and traditional, as well as casual and elegant. Featuring lawn and garden views, the Lounge covers over 400 square meters and can host a variety of events from meetings to cocktail receptions.</description></item><item><title>The Palawan @ Sentosa provides eight lifestyle entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 02:42:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Shangri-La Group has introduced its first lifestyle and entertainment hub, spanning 183,000 square feet on Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Sentosa Island. This complex boasts eight unique experiences, including dining options.
Chan Kong Leong, Regional CEO for the Shangri-La Group in Southeast Asia &amp;amp; Australasia, Hong Kong, Japan and Middle East, Europe, Indian Ocean &amp;amp; The Americas, emphasized the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing enjoyable experiences and Asian hospitality. He stated that this venture aims to create excitement and bring more enjoyment to guests beyond their traditional hotel settings, allowing them to create their own memorable moments through diverse leisure and dining experiences.</description></item><item><title>Elite Havens is proud to announce the addition of three new properties in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: Elite Havens. Caption: Elite Havens expands its Bali Collection with three new villas.
Elite Havens, a high-end villa rental and management company in Asia, has expanded its Bali offerings with three new properties:
Sol Y Mar - Uluwatu, Bali, Indonesia
Situated on Nunggalan Beach, Sol y Mar is a four-bedroom villa featuring a private pool.
Villa Dhanika - Badung, Bali, Indonesia
Nestled amidst Balinese rice paddies, Villa Dhanika is a five-bedroom retreat with an Olympic-sized swimming pool and an outdoor jacuzzi.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Sports Hub has successfully adapted during the pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Sports Hub. Plans for 2021.
The Singapore Sports Hub has adjusted its focus in 2021 to deliver impactful experiences, building on the lessons learned from 2020. This includes their earlier efforts, from providing safe housing for migrant workers during the peak of COVID-19 to creating new event formats for local audiences.
Despite the global pandemic impacting the Hub&amp;rsquo;s ability to host its typical lineup of large-scale sporting and entertainment events, it shifted gears to become a source of support for the community.</description></item><item><title>TCEB commemorates achievements in Thailand's MICE Venue Standard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</guid><description>Forty-two venues in Thailand have now received the Thailand MICE Venue Standard award from the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB). The announcement was made at the Thailand MICE Venue Standard Certification Ceremony held last month.
This standard is a key element of a robust plan to accelerate the growth of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s MICE industry. Emphasizing Thailand&amp;rsquo;s prominent role in the region, TCEB underscored the need to utilize the expertise of MICE operators.</description></item></channel></rss>