<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VMware on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vmware/</link><description>Recent content in VMware on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vmware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singaporean companies are prioritizing cloud technology to gain a competitive edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</guid><description>Source: VMware infographic.
VMware, a leading company in virtualization and cloud infrastructure, recently shared the results of their vForum Singapore Business Survey. The survey shows a positive attitude toward hybrid cloud solutions, which combine public cloud services with internal cloud technology, as a method of driving growth, efficiency, and innovation. Almost every business surveyed (90%) believes that the cloud can facilitate innovation, and nearly half (44%) prefer a hybrid cloud model for their IT infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs Dedicated Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</guid><description>There are many ways to host your emails, websites, and software applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the pros and cons of each option to help you determine the best fit for your business.
You might be tempted to manage your own hosting, which is how many companies started and how some large companies still operate. The basic requirement is a computer that functions as a file server and a bandwidth connection. Internally, this connection can be your Local Area Network (LAN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure Hosting In The Cloud For The US and Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</guid><description>While you&amp;rsquo;re exploring the advantages of cloud computing, cost and security might be concerns. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine what a reliable secure cloud hosting provider, particularly for companies in the US and Europe, should offer.
One provider, with high-security data centers in Phoenix, Dallas, London, and Amsterdam, connects these centers through a private network. They provide access via various Content Delivery Network (CDN) points in major cities across the US, Europe, and Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>