<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DOCSIS 3.0 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/docsis-3.0/</link><description>Recent content in DOCSIS 3.0 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/docsis-3.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comcast’s 100 Gbps Core Network Supports Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</guid><description>Over the past year, major telecom companies have been upgrading their core networks from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. Comcast recently joined this trend by incorporating Ciena&amp;rsquo;s Wave Logic 3 interfaces into their existing Ciena 6500 packet optical platforms. This begs the question: why would a cable company make this change, and how can it benefit your business?
Comcast is widely recognized as a Cable TV provider, or MSO (Multi-System Operator)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cable vs FTTH Bandwidth Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</guid><description>The competition for superior internet speed is underway. Fiber to the Home (FTTH), is perceived as the frontrunner, while Cable Broadband is the contender. It&amp;rsquo;s still uncertain who will come out on top, but one thing is for sure: users with substantial bandwidth requirements will be the ultimate victors.
This clash is unfolding in Washington state, where Comcast, the Cable behemoth, is introducing a 50 Mbps internet service to rival Verizon, the telecommunications giant, and its 50 Mbps FiOS internet service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speeds Come to Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</guid><description>Cablevision Systems Corp. is pushing the boundaries of broadband speed by offering internet speeds exceeding 100 Mbps over its existing cable TV infrastructure. This new high-speed internet service, launching on May 11th, provides download speeds up to 101 Mbps and upload speeds up to 15 Mbps for approximately $100 per month.
One might wonder how cable TV lines, which traditionally use coaxial cables, can achieve such high speeds, usually associated with fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Redundant Business Internet Connection Using Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Large companies have avoided using consumer-grade broadband services due to concerns about their reliability and performance. While it is prudent to use dedicated circuits with service level agreements for critical business operations, there is a cost-effective solution available for backing up telecom services and enhancing internet speed.
Cable broadband has grown rapidly and seen continuous technological advancements, primarily due to its popularity as a consumer internet service. While alternatives like satellite, wireless, dial-up, and fiber optic exist, they often come with limitations in bandwidth, high installation costs, or limited availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.0 Fiberizes Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Cable companies have been envious of Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS fiber optic service because it surpasses the broadband capabilities of coaxial cable. However, a new upgrade to the DOCSIS cable broadband standard might change that. This upgrade boosts digital download speeds to rival those of fiber optic connections, all without needing a fiber optic line to the home.
DOCSIS, which stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification, is the standard for cable modems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>