<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2053DNBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2053dnbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 2053DNBG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:15:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2053dnbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Massachusetts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always wonderful to see a returning customer! Earlier this year, I restored a Beogram 4000 for a client in Massachusetts. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to work on another Beogram 4000 he&amp;rsquo;s sent my way. It seems one can never have too many Beograms!
The Beogram 4000 arrived safely, shipped securely in a Beolover box. It was accompanied by a thoughtful gift for Beolover, for which I am incredibly grateful.
This beautiful reissue of &amp;ldquo;Waltz for Debby&amp;rdquo; by the Bill Evans Trio, a legendary jazz record, is a 180g pressing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with the Bill Evans Trio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable from a Massachusetts customer. The initial evaluation can be found here.
The restoration began by addressing the carriage system. This involved cleaning hardened lubricants from various parts like the arm lowering mechanism, rods, spindle, linkages, and damper, and applying modern synthetic lubricants.
A key aspect of the Beogram 4000 is its solenoid-activated switches, which frequently experience oxidation and require attention. The contact terminals were removed and re-plated with nickel and gold-cobalt alloy for optimal performance and corrosion resistance.</description></item></channel></rss>