<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edward Snowden on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/edward-snowden/</link><description>Recent content in Edward Snowden on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/edward-snowden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is EU data protection law violated by Facebook and the USA? The CJEU hearing in Schrems.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</guid><description>Simon McGarr, a solicitor at McGarr Solicitors, provides an overview of the Schrems v Data Protection Commissioner case heard by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The case revolves around Austrian law student Max Schrems&amp;rsquo; legal challenge concerning the transfer of his personal data from Facebook to the United States. Schrems argues that such transfers violate his data privacy rights due to the risk of mass surveillance under US law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Live. Die. Repeat. Is the 'Privacy Shield' deal stuck in a never-ending cycle of repeating the same mistakes like in the movie 'Groundhog Day'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the USA is globally recognized, some of its customs remain perplexing. Take &amp;ldquo;Groundhog Day,&amp;rdquo; where the presence or absence of a groundhog&amp;rsquo;s shadow on February 2nd supposedly predicts six more weeks of winter. Beyond the USA, it&amp;rsquo;s more famous as a film where Bill Murray relives the same day, striving for perfection and Andie MacDowell&amp;rsquo;s affections. This concept has inspired others: Tom Cruise battling aliens and wooing Emily Blunt in Edge of Tomorrow, and Peter Capaldi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to breach a diamond wall and resurrect Jenna Coleman in Doctor Who&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hell Bent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Europe v Facebook the start of the end for NSA surveillance of EU citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>The &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; Case: Challenging US Data Surveillance in Europe Since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about the NSA&amp;rsquo;s extensive spying activities, concerns have grown about the effectiveness of US data protection, particularly for EU citizens who benefit from stronger protections under the Data Protection Directive. One concern is the NSA&amp;rsquo;s ability to access communications processed by US-based social media companies like Facebook.
The Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s recent decision to refer questions in the &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; case to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) could potentially lead to the end of NSA access to EU citizens&amp;rsquo; data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>